Chapter 310 – Divine Spear Complete

At this time, Lin Ming who was cultivating didn’t know what Mu Qianyu was thinking, nor did he know that his cultivation speed was far too exaggerated for someone who should have a sixth-grade fire origin energy fusion compatibility.

Lin Ming had already entered into the ethereal martial intent state and sealed off his six senses, completely immersed in the happy feelings that came with cultivation.

The ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ was naturally an unbelievably marvelous cultivation method with a thousand benefits. However, it was only a Body Transformation cultivation method. Above Tempering Marrow was the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

This cultivation system couldn’t be used to break through to the Houtian realm or Xiantian realm.

Lin Ming wanted to open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, but he wasn’t planning on giving up on reaching Houtian, Xiantian, and the Revolving Core realms.

So Lin Ming had been missing an essence gathering cultivation system to cultivate his true essence. The ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ just happened to fill in this missing space.

Although this cultivation method had many flaws, because of the presence of the Heretical God Seed, all of the fire attribute fire origin energy around Lin Ming was as docile as sheep, freely allowing Lin Ming to manipulate it in any way he wanted. Because of this, Lin Ming could cultivate the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ with half the effort and twice the results. This was simply a cultivation method that was tailored towards Lin Ming’s strengths!

When Mu Qianyu had first cultivated the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ she had reached Pulse Condensation at 15, Houtian at 17, Xiantian at 22, extreme Xiantian at 26, and now at 27 years of age, she was a half-step into the Revolving Core realm!

Lin Ming’s current cultivation speed of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ was far inferior to Mu Qianyu, someone who possessed a truly terrifying superior seventh-grade fire origin energy fusion compatibility. Even if Lin Ming possessed the Heretical God Speed, that was a speed that he couldn’t hope to reach.

But the greatest advantage of the Heretical God Seed was that it could grow. What would happen once he absorbed another Flame Essence?

If that happened, the Lin Ming’s cultivation speed would constantly increase, and in the future, he might even surpass Mu Qianyu!

Thinking this, Lin Ming was increasingly hungry for the Fire Worm Tribe’s Flame Essence. If the Southern Wilderness wasn’t so far away, he would have probably wouldn’t have waited for the spear and directly paid a visit to the Fire Worm Tribe.

Because of the incomparably rich and pure fire origin energy, the top quality cultivation method ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, in addition to the perfect fit of the Heretical God Seed in assisting him with the cultivation method, Lin Ming’s cultivation speed would be able to progress at 10,000 miles per day. 10 days later, his cultivation had already reached the peak of the early Pulse Condensation period.

Of course, this was also partly due to the amazing merits of the Heaven Opening Pill.

On this day, there was suddenly an extremely loud explosion sound outside of the cave mansion, so forceful that even the protective array formation fiercely trembled. Lin Ming and Mu Qianyu didn’t know what happened, so they hurriedly ran out of the cave mansion, and saw a disheveled and messy Ancestor Chi Yan doing a jiggy dance in joy.

“Haha, I did it, I finally did it!”

Seeing Ancestor Chi Yan like this, Mu Qianyu breathed a sigh of relief. She didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry; for a moment, she even thought that the entire eight trigrams fire array formation had imploded.

“Haha, Nephew Lin, you came at just the right time. What do you think about my great array formation now?” Ancestor Chi Yan waved behind himself. Because he had been continually working night and day for the last 10 days to perfect his array formation, Ancestor Chi Yan was covered in soot and dirt, most of his robe burnt black. He looked like the crazy old hermit he was.

Lin Ming looked at Ancestor Chi Yan’s eyes that shined with an aberrant light, and gulped. He nodded, “It’s um… very good. Perfect.”

“Haha, today – no, tomorrow, I will forge the best spear for you! First, I must rest for the evening and adjust my condition to its best form!”

……………………………….

The next morning –

All the materials were placed atop the stone altar. There was the 10,000 year Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, the 10,000 year Sacred Flame Parasol Tree, a little bit of crystallized fire that was left behind after a Vermillion Bird underwent nirvana, a palm-sized piece of Purple Comet Divine Metal, and about 20 jins of Profound Thunder Stone. These were the main materials to forge the spear.

Every one of these main materials was an absolutely top quality material, any piece enough to make even a Revolving Core powerhouse green with envy. With so many rare materials together, Mu Qianyu was unable to help sighing. This was simply too luxurious, even for her.

Ancestor Chi Yan saw so many top quality materials and his face shined red with joy. With these materials, in addition to the newly evolved eight trigrams fire array formation, he had absolute faith that he would be able to create the best work in his refining career!

With the experience of creating a top-grade weapon, he would also have a better grasp of forging a heaven-step treasure in the future.

Ancestor Chi Yan tied back his crazily scattered hair, and then spat out a cloud of dark green and purple flame. When this cloud of fire appeared, it was like the air had been lit on fire; the surrounding temperature dramatically surged by an alarming degree.

Lin Ming’s pupils constricted. That dark green and purple flame was without a doubt a Flame Essence. It should be Ancestor Chi Yan’s life’s Flame Essence. In terms of how formidable it was, it was probably above the medium-grade earth-step.

Lin Ming had no understanding of how a Flame Essence would be above the medium-grade earth-step, he could only guess.

At this time, Mu Qianyu confirmed Lin Ming’s thoughts. She looked at that the dark green and purple flame and exclaimed in praise, “That is the Silent Nine Emerald Flame, a high-grade earth-step Flame Essence!”

The reason that Ancestor Chi Yan could walk with impunity throughout the entire South Horizon Region was, to a great extent, because of this high-grade earth-step Flame Essence.

The Silent Nine Emerald Flame shot out, fusing into the eight trigrams fire array formation. The flames suddenly turned into a dark green and purple, the temperature rising to an absolutely horrifying degree.

Ancestor Chi Yan first took out the supplementary spear casting materials. This included a massive amount of Aged Gold, Cold Star Iron, and Wrought Gold Heavy Water. These wouldn’t be used to cast the spear, but would only play a catalytic opening role.

The Aged Gold, Cold Star Iron, as well as the Purple Comet Divine Metal were all thrown into the flames. The Aged Gold and Cold Star Iron only took a brief moment before they melted into a muddle of mixed molten metal. Once the Wrought Gold Heavy Water and another batch of supplementary materials were thrown in, it became a boiling cauldron of molten metals.

Then, Ancestor Chi Yan took out the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo and the Sacred Flame Parasol Tree, immersing them into the boiling molten metal so that these two spiritual woods could absorb the metal essence.

Throughout all of this, the Purple Comet was still in the flame, completely motionless.

Ancestor Chi Yan constantly inputted origin energy into the eight trigrams fire array formation. With the addition of fire origin energy from the Primal Chaos Heavens, this massive fire array formation burned for over four hours.

Purple Comet was a material that could just qualify as being worthy to create a heaven-step treasure. After it had stayed in the burning flames for such a long time, it still didn’t show the slightest hint of melting.

Ancestor Chi Yan took a high-grade true essence stone, and began to absorb the true essence stone’s origin energy, while simultaneously taking out a purple pill from his spatial ring and tossing it into the flames. As the purple pill fused into the flames, it immediately turned into a drop of liquid that penetrated into the Purple Comet Divine Metal.

With a ‘chi chi’ sound, the Purple Comet finally began to soften under the effects of the purple pill.

“Huo!”

Ancestor Chi Yan took out a massive crimson hammer from his spatial ring. He flooded this hammer with true essence, and began to repeatedly smash down on the softened Purple Comet Divine Metal, with heavy pounding motions.

Just this large crimson hammer was already a medium-grade earth-step treasure.

Wind whistled, flames twirled.

Ancestor Chi Yan stripped off his robe, revealing a naked upper body that was tightly corded in solid muscle. Just looking at this muscle, there was no way one would think it was the body of an old man.

Clang!

Clang!

Clang!

………………..

The sound of metal clashing against metal reverberated throughout the entire mountain rage. Even Lin Ming, who was standing nearby felt his blood begin to boil and his heart rise with passion as he watched. The beauty and majesty of this absolute power was truly shocking.

Refining Purple Comet and removing the impurities was an arduous and exceedingly difficult process. Ancestor Chi Yan’s entire body was streaming with sweat, and even the Aged Gold anvil under the Purple Comet was smashed apart.

Lin Ming exclaimed in his heart. This Aged Gold anvil was definitely an extraordinary object, and yet it was smashed apart by Ancestor Chi Yan to such a degree. The tenacity of the Purple Comet and its ability to withstand impact could be imagined.

After an entire day and night, after countless hammerings, the originally palm-sized piece of Purple Comet was finally small enough, just the right size to forge a spearhead.

The Purple Comet served as the foundation core of the spearhead, and then the Vermillion Bird crystallized fire was ground into powder and used to permeate the Purple Comet.

The 20 jins of Profound Thunder Stone was refined into its most basic essence by the Silent Nine Emerald Flame, and then also cast into the foundation core.

With a top thunder and fire material integrated into the spearhead, the hammering continued!

The giant hammer smashing into the Purple Comet became increasingly frequent. The wind picked up, and the surrounding fire origin energy actually turned into a massive vortex.

With every hit, sparks would splash out, arcs of bright electricity would shine, and that foundation core was gradually hammered into the shape of a thin spearhead.

Chi chi chi!

Ancestor Chi Yan sunk the spearhead into a giant bath of Glacial Ice Divine Spring. That originally freezing cold Glacial Ice Divine Spring actually started to boil, emitting massive clouds of steam.

This sort of divine water was extremely precious. The Refiner Faction Sovereign had once spent a great price in order to obtain some Glacial Ice Divine Spring, so that his son Huo Yanluo could soak in it, and depend on this to jump realms and absorb a medium-grade human-step Flame Essence.

Now, this great amount of Glacial Ice Divine Spring was actually used by Ancestor Chi Yan as a hardening agent.

After the quenching was complete, up to now, only the spearhead had been finished. A top quality treasure spear had to be thoroughly hammered nine by nine times for a total of 81 times. The first time hammering was the longest. Afterwards, the amount of time would be reduced, but the total time would always amount to around 20 days or so.

During this period, a reigning master would have to continually consume a high degree of strength. Sometimes, they would not only consume their true essence, but their life energy!

In order to refine a top treasure, a refining master needed to put forth his entire effort and soul. After a long period of time, there were some refining masters that would overtax their life to forge a treasure, and finally end up perishing!

Therefore, to request a refining master to forge a spear with all of their ability was very difficult. If it wasn’t for Lin Ming assisting Ancestor Chi Yan in such a great manner, there was no way that he would have helped him forge a top class divine spear.

Time slowly passed, day by day.

Every day, Lin Ming would come over and take a look at Ancestor Chi Yan. But besides this, he spent all of his time cultivating. At this point, his cultivation was slowly reaching the middle Pulse Condensation period.

Finally, on the 20th day, the spearhead and spear shaft integrated into a perfect whole.

The long spear shaft was 10 feet long. It had the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo as the bone, and the surface was twined with the tree silk of the Sacred Flame Parasol Tree. It was both flexible and incomparably difficult to destroy.

With the spear shaft complete, Ancestor Chi Yan started to fully concentrate on drawing the array formation upon the divine spear.

At this moment, in the sky, thunder flashed, and clouds of fire gathered.

The peak of the mountain was the Primal Chaos Heavens. Above the Primal Chaos Heavens, the seven origin energy elements of metal, wood, water, fire, earth, thunder, and wind were in a free state, savage, brutal, and active.

At this moment, the thunder attribute and fire attribute origin energy seemed to be drawn in by some unknown law, gathering together.

Bang!

With a deafening explosion, the Primal Chaos Heavens were ripped apart as if it were the work of some divine hand, and a massive pillar of fire and thunder shot down, bombarding the divine spear!

Ancestor Chi Yan was completely focused on his work, and his physical strength had already been drawn to the limit. He gave a stuffy cough as his entire body was twined with purple lightning and flames, and he tumbled off the stone altar.

“Senior Chi Yan!” Lin Ming was shocked, he quickly ran forwards.

However at this time, Ancestor Chi Yan, whose entire body was burnt black, began to maniacally laugh, the pearly white teeth of his wide smile contrasting against his blackened appearance. “The heavens help me! The heavens help me! A divine weapon is born, bringing forth twin fire and thunder tribulation from the heavens! This is this old man’s best work by far!”

Chapter 312 – Fire Worm Church Leader

“Benefactor, the Fire Worm Shaman’s cultivation is at least at the middle Houtian realm, he might even be at the late Houtian realm!” Na Yi tried to keep her calm, but her voice was still trembling. She knew how astonishing Lin Ming’s talent was, but she found it hard to imagine that Lin Ming’s strength would have progressed so much in just a few months.

Now, she didn’t have accurate information on just how strong the Fire Worm Shaman was. Much less how strong he was, the Fire Worm Shaman would undoubtedly be surrounded by countless masters. If Lin Ming wished to kill the Fire Worm Shaman in such a situation, he would have to have at least the strength of a peak Houtian master in order to dare to do such a thing.

Seeing that Lin Ming’s current cultivation was at most in the Pulse Condensation period, would his true strength actually manage to jump past almost two whole realms?

Na Yi found this unbelievable. Even if it was the Southern Wilderness’ Feather Emperor that was recorded down in the Faith of the Sorcerer’s ancient texts, his strength wouldn’t be so exaggerated at such a young age. In Na Yi’s heart, the Feather Emperor of the Southern Wilderness was only inferior to the Faith of the Sorcerer. This peerless master had once created his own empire in the Southern Wilderness that was equal to a third-grade sect. His power was difficult to estimate, unfathomable.

“Benefactor, let me search around a bit more so I can learn just how strong the Fire Worm Shaman is.”

Lin Ming said, “That doesn’t matter. Even if his strength is at the peak Houtian realm, I have enough hidden abilities to kill him, or I can even freely retreat if I wish. The reason I came today was to inform you that I will complete my promise to you, not to find out information from you.”

Na Yi was speechless. Really, if Lin Ming had come to the Southern Wilderness to kill the Fire Worm Shaman, he would have already had some sort of plan. There was no need for him to come ask her for information on how to kill the Fire Worm Shaman. In any case, the information she had was limited, and she wouldn’t be able to give any valuable advice anyways.

“I understand.” Na Yi nodded. In her mind, Lin Ming was a paradox that managed to complete incredible miracles that others couldn’t. She didn’t think that Lin Ming was crazy or hotheaded, she just found it unbelievable.

“When I go to kill the Fire Worm Shaman, whether I succeed or not, you need to take your little sister far away, as far away from the Fire Worm Tribe as you can. This place is too close, it won’t be safe.” As Lin Ming said this, he took a foot long square box out of his spatial ring, and then gave it to Na Yi, saying, “This is for you sisters. In the future, whether or not you want to live an ordinary prosperous life or try to turn your fate and rebuild your tribe, all will be decided by you.”

Lin Ming placed the box on the table. The sisters had given him a very great fortuitous opportunity. This was the kindness he returned to them to consider all of their debts fully repaid.

“Big Brother Mo Lin… you… ” As Na Shui saw that Lin Ming was about to leave, she pursed her lips, her eyes trembling and shining wet. She didn’t know what to say.

Lin Ming faintly smiled, gently rubbing Na Shui’s head and said, “Cultivate well. Perhaps, in the future, we will meet again.”

As Lin Ming said this, he left the house, activated his movement technique and instantly vanished into the horizon.

Na Yi saw her little sister’s longing look as if she was reluctantly willing to part ways, and then sighed, shaking her head.

In the future, Lin Ming would most likely become an existence similar to the Feather Emperor. He would become a figure that dominated a land of several hundreds of thousands of miles. The disparity between them was simply a ravine that they couldn’t cross.

How could he still be her Big Brother Mo Lin?

As Na Yi was deep in thought, she casually opened the box that Lin Ming left behind. As she looked at the contents inside, she was stunned silly.

The box was packed full of golden banknotes, each one worth 1000 gold taels. These packs of banknotes looked solid, and looking at the thickness, there had to be at least one or two hundred. This meant that this was a few hundred thousand gold taels. An average person could spend lavishly their entire life and never spend it all. Even if they used this to purchase cultivation materials for martial artists, they still wouldn’t spend it all. It was enough for the two sisters to not have to worry about money ever again.

Near the stack of golden banknotes, there was a jade slip. And near the jade slip, there were a few bottles of pills. After opening the pill bottles, a light fragrance wafted out. These were absolutely top-grade pills!

As Na Yi held the jade slip in her hand, she let out a light breath. It was a medium-grade human-step cultivation method. In addition to these pills and golden banknotes, the worth of this box was no less than a million gold taels.

Although Na Yi had been a witch of the great Na Tribe and had been accustomed to wealth, the Southern Wilderness was poorer than the mainland. A great tribe with half a million people would find it difficult to put out so much money.

But Lin Ming had actually casually gifted this, just what degree of influence did he have?

Na Yi suddenly felt that, relative to this great world, the tribes of the south were insignificant ants…

……………….

Fire Worm City was 900 miles west of Fog Valley Tribe. It was the center of command for the Fire Worm Tribe, and also the origin of the Fire Worm Church.

Most tribes of the Southern Wilderness had a theocracy that dominated the secular leader. The Fire Worm Tribe was no exception. The Fire Worm Shaman Chi Yue had a higher degree of influence than the Tribal Chief.

Within the very center of Fire Worm City, there were seven great spirals towers. These spiral towers were all above 200 feet, with the largest one in the center at over 300 feet.

The giant complex that these seven spiral towers revolved around was the Fire Worm Church.

The curtain of night slowly fell upon the land. The noisy streets of the day quieted, and the lamplights of 10,000 families in Fire Worm City shined out, shining out against the endless starry sky. This was a rare scene in the entire Southern Wilderness. These past years, the Fire Worm Tribe had constantly been at war, plundering other tribes and taking slaves. Now, the total population of the Fire Worm Tribe reached several million. Fire Worm City also became one of the largest cities in the Southern Wilderness.

Within the highest room of the central spire, there were several people sitting around a round table. The man in the seat of honor was a bald man. He was dressed in a dark black robe, and on his head was tattooed in strange patterns. His face was calm and indifferent.

Besides him was a long and thick staff. This staff was shaped like a spindle, and there was a circle of white skulls hanging from it.

This man was the Fire Worm Shaman, Chi Yue.

At Chi Yue’s right hand seat, there was a fat middle-aged man. He was hugging a delicate looking maid, and his pudgy stumpy hands were delving into the clothes of a slave girl, recklessly rubbing against her. The female slave bit her lips until they hurt, her whole body trembling but not daring to speak or react.

Although these fat man’s actions were disgusting and lewd and his eyes smiled in a lascivious grin, his eyes actually revealed a hint of murderous intent. “Shaman Chi Yue, the soldiers and horses are already ready, we are just waiting for some masters of the Church to join. As long as Shaman Chi Yue calculates an auspicious day, we shall push forward, and we shall flatten the Agu Tribe in a single sweep! We will plunder their cultivation resources, give them to the Church, kill their heathens, and sell off the slaves to supply the treasure. The rest of the slaves will be used to serve us.”

As the fat man spoke, his smile grew wider, and the strength of his hand increased. The slave girl paled in pain, and sweat began to form on her forehead.

But, she clenched her teeth, not daring to utter a single sound. This man who was groping her was the Chief of the Fire Worm Tribe, and he had extremely cruel and brutal methods for dealing with those he disliked. He was even more vicious than Fire Worm Church Founder. These past years, there were countless slave girls who were humiliated or killed by him. If she couldn’t bear the pain and interrupted the conference of these three people, her fate would be truly pitiful. She had a sister who couldn’t bear the pain and coughed, and then she was thrown into the army camp as a prostitute slave for anyone’s use. Now, it was unknown whether she was dead or alive.

Chi Yue sat in the seat of honor, his right hand flipped up, his palm up, and his thumbs tapped his other four fingers. He seemed to be calculating something. A moment later, Chi Yue slowly said, “Three months later, when the Wolf Star intersects with the Sky Star, that is when you may dispatch the army.”

“Three months? Does it have to be that long?” The Fat Chief frowned. He didn’t want to wait, and he wasn’t satisfied with this time.

With the current strength of the Fire Worm Tribe, demolishing the Agu Tribe was easy. The only problem was how many losses there would be. Chi Yue’s words represented the entire Fire Worm Church. Even if the Fat Chief was the Chief, he could not argue against him.

As the Fat Chief looked at the Fire Worm Great General on his right side, he nodded and said, “Then we shall go in three months. At that time, we shall be depending on the Church of the Shamans to help us at that time.”

“Of course!” Chi Yue said without a break in composure.

As the Fat Chief saw Chi Yue’s expression, he was somewhat unhappy. Every time, this Fat Chief would have to beg the Fire Worm Church to send out masters. Once the cultivation resources were plundered, they were all handed over to the Fire Worm Church. If things continued like this, when would the army ever train a master that would be equal to the masters of the Fire Worm Church? Would they always be reliant on the Fire Worm Church?

Since the Fat Chief wasn’t happy, he groped even more forcefully. Now, the slave girl could no longer bear the pain and uttered a groan.

“Mm!?” The Fat Chief frowned.

As the slave girl heard this sound, her entire body instantly went ice cold.

Her body began to tremble, and now she only had thought in her mind, she was finished. Her fate would be worse than death.

As slaves, they didn’t even have the qualifications to commit suicide. According to the laws of the Fire Worm Tribe, the slaves that killed themselves would be used to feed vicious beasts. And, according to the spiritual beliefs of the Southern Wilderness, if the dead were eaten by vicious beasts or humans, they would not be able to enter into the cycle of samsara, and they would never be reincarnated.

Therefore, while many slaves wished that they could die, none of them dared to kill themselves.

The Fat Chief’s face darkened as he smiled. He was thinking on how he would punish this slave girl tonight to vent his heart’s depression. But, at this moment, an icy voice fell from the sky, covering the entire spiral tower.

“I apologize! I’m afraid that you will not have the opportunity to wait another three months!”

This voice was full of a chilling murderous intent, enough that anyone who heard it would feel their heart race in fear from the hostile aura. The Fat Chief was immediately shocked. He stood up, frightened, and look above his head. He only saw the dark ceiling.

“Who is it!?”

The Fat Chief shoved the slave girl in his hands away, looking startled and alarmed. But, thinking that the Fire Worm Shaman was right near him along with many other masters, he felt a bit more at ease. These fellows would eat people and not spit out their bones, they were truly strong. Otherwise, there was no way that the Fire Worm Tribe would have been able to sweep across the northern Southern Boundary as they had these past years.

Chi Yue’s complexion also changed. This person was actually able to hide from his senses, and even sneak into his tightly defended Fire Worm Tower.

“Who is it? Come out and show yourself! Don’t hide in the shadows!” Chi Yue kept his calm, and he had the ability and capital to remain calm. His cultivation had already reached the late Houtian realm, and with the help of the Eternal Flame Flame Essence, it would be hard for any other martial artist in the Houtian realm to rival him.

Within the entire Southern Wilderness, he wouldn’t say that he was the strongest, but his strength definitely ranked in the top five. Especially since he was in his own domain, he had help from many of his men. There was just no need to be afraid of anyone or anything.

Chapter 313 – Exterminating Chi Yue

On the highest floor of the spiral tower, the candle flames flickered in the night wind, and the shadows of those within disappeared, becoming small and miniscule.

Shaman Leader Chi Yue had an indifferent expression, his hand slowly tracing the side of his staff. His staff jittered, and the skulls hanging from the top began to rattle against each other.

The newly assigned Fire Worm Great General took out the heavy sword from his back, his face calm. He was a man who had struggled and killed his way up the ranks of the army on his own merits and strength, a truly vicious military man. He had been through countless slaughters and battlefields, and had also experienced the bitter taste of attempted assassinations multiple times. Now, facing this unexpected visitor, it was impossible for his heart to feel even the slightest arousal of fear.

The night wind howled, and a black shadow appeared like a desolate ghost on the ledge of the stone window. He held a purple spear in his hand, his eyes cold, and his body overflowing with murderous intent.

“Mm? Early Pulse Condensation period?” The Fire Worm Great General smirked. An early Pulse Condensation boy actually dared to come to their Fire Worm Clan’s Holy Land? This boy didn’t know how to spell the word ‘death’!

“Haha, I was wondering just who it could be, but it turns out it’s merely a foolish idiot. An early Pulse Condensation boy actually dares to come here just to kill himself!” The Fat Chief wickedly grinned, his eyes looking behind Lin Ming. “If you have help, then call them out! Don’t go skulking in the shadows like some rat. I’ll send you both off together!”

As the Fat Chief spoke, a small fire ignited in his palm; this was a sound transmitting talisman. He was using this sound transmitting talisman to pass on a warning. The Fat Chief didn’t think that Lin Ming was really an idiot. If Lin Ming dared to intrude here, that meant there was most likely a master waiting outside for an opportunity to strike.

Although there was only a small danger, the Fat Chief was unwilling to risk his own life.

In the Grand Hall, the Fire Worm Shaman was silent. He froze for a moment as he saw Lin Ming, then instantly recalled just where he had seen him. Several months ago, this youth had killed Chi Guda. Afterwards, the Fire Worm Shaman had sent his own Flame Essence Avatar to chase down Lin Ming through Blackwater Swamp. If his Avatar hadn’t encountered the Vermillion Bird and feared being eaten, then it would have killed Lin Ming long ago.

This youth’s body held countless secrets!

He remembered that when Lin Ming just had a mere peak Bone Forging cultivation, he was already able to fly, and his strength was a level above everyone else. The Fire Worm Shaman was able to determine that Lin Ming had a unfathomable wealthy background and he also had a rare treasure that enabled him to fly. Such a treasure was absolutely priceless. If he could obtain it, then his own power would leap ahead.

Chi Yue flicked his fingers and a wisp of flame ran out from his hands, roaring forth and jumping out the window, making a circle around the spiral tower before it flew back into Chi Yue’s hand.

Then Chi Yue laughed, revealing a vicious grin. His curved lips revealed sharp teeth that were just like a vampire bat, incomparably fierce.

“So it’s really just you… a few months have passed and you broke through from the peak Bone Forging stage to the early Pulse Condensation period. But after the mere advancement of a small realm, you actually think you can kill me within the lair of the Fire Worm Clan? You really think you are the Feather Emperor of the Southern Wilderness reborn!? Hehe, you don’t know what it means to die!”

Chi Yue stretched out his long crimson tongue, licking his lips. To him, Lin Ming was merely a bag of treasures waiting to be opened. Such a young and ignorant young boy like Lin Ming wouldn’t know what true power was. Lin Ming probably assumed that he was some normal Houtian martial artist.

When Lin Ming had killed Chi Guda, his cultivation had been at the peak of Bone Forging. Chi Guda was a half-step into the Houtian realm. Lin Ming hadn’t been able to easily kill him; he had to use many hidden cards, including the Heretical God Force and even Thunderfire Annihilation.

At that point, Lin Ming’s strength was able to compare to the weakest of all Houtian realm martial artists.

Now, in just three and a half months, Lin Ming’s cultivation had only risen by a small degree. Chi Yue simply didn’t even think that Lin Ming had any ability to threaten him. Even if he were the god-like Feather Emperor that was worshipped in the Southern Wilderness, he still wouldn’t have this ability in the Pulse Condensation period!

Suddenly, the door to the meeting room burst open, and a group of heavily armed guards rushed in. The Fat Chief took this opportunity to scurry behind the bodyguards. These were his deathsworn, special guards that the Fat Chief had handpicked from the army, each and every one willing to die for him. They had fought in many battles, killing countless civilians and masters.

With these deathsworn with him – and also countless other masters in the spiral tower – the Fat Chief was much more calm. Although he was a cruel and ruthless individual, he was actually very afraid of death. To him, his life was worth more than gold. He ruled a large swathe of land, he had many women to play with; there was endless wealth of power waiting for him.

“You all protect me! Shaman Chi Yue will deal with this intruder!” The Fat Chief issued out orders via a true essence sound transmission. He could also be considered half a martial artist, but the reason he cultivated was mainly for physical fitness and to violate women.

“I do not care who you are, but since you have come, do not think that you will walk away!” The Fire Worm Great General gave a loud shout, rushing towards Lin Ming, the heavy sword in his hand cutting down!

Lin Ming calmly held the Purple Comet Spear in his hands. He watched, motionless as the Fire Worm Great General rushed towards him, slicing the heavy sword at him. But then, a chilling light suddenly flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes, and he icily spit out a single word.

“Die!”

It was as if this cold voice was the grim whispers of a death god that emanated from an endless, silent abyss. As soon as the Fire Worm Great General heard this voice, his body instantly shook, and both of his eyes lost focus.

Plop!

It was as if the Great General had his soul sucked out of him. His massive body fell to its knees, and then he keeled over. It was unknown whether or not he was still alive.

“Mm!?” The Fire Worm Shaman’s complexion changed.

Soul attack?

A soul attack wasn’t too surprising, but Lin Ming only had a cultivation at the early Pulse Condensation period. Yet, he was able to use this soul attack to kill a peak Pulse Condensation master in a split-second. How was this possible?

The Fat Chief suddenly panicked. He didn’t know that Lin Ming had used a soul attack; he only knew that with a single word, he had managed to directly kill a peak Pulse Condensation Great General. Was this boy a reincarnated demon?

Even those deathsworn near him who had been numbed to the horrors of death and destruction were agitated, unconsciously clenching their fists. They didn’t fear death, but even if they didn’t fear death, they were people of the Southern Wilderness who had deeply ingrained beliefs. What they feared were the demons, and the current Lin Ming seemed like a demon that they heard from folk tales.

“So… it seems that you have mastered a soul attack secret skill. It’s no wonder that you dare to kill me. However, such a secret skill is useless against me!” Chi Yue’s expression finally became grim.

At this time, Chi Yue was only slightly serious. As a martial artist with a late Houtian realm cultivation and also the master of a Flame Essence, the strength of a peak Pulse Condensation Great General was nothing in his eyes. Killing him in a split-second simply didn’t mean anything.

His right hand flashed, and a mass of crimson flames jumped forth from his palm, “I’ll turn you to ashes!”

Chi!

A bright red light shot towards Lin Ming, but Lin Ming didn’t evade or dodge. Instead, his entire body was covered with a shimmering azure light, and he lifted his right hand, grabbing out at the red light.

Peng!

The bright red light exploded like a firework in Lin Ming’s palm. But Lin Ming’s right hand only glimmered with the faintest golden light; not even a single inch of his body had been burned.

“What!?”

The Fire Worm Shaman who had been trying to maintain a calm and collected appearance finally lost his composure. Although he hadn’t used the Fire Essence to attack, he had still used 60 to 70% of his strength. And yet, his attack was actually blocked by the enemy, and bare-handed? This… this was impossible!

At this time, the Fire Worm Shaman already imagined that Lin Ming might be a Xiantian master in disguise. But if he was a Xiantian master, then why would he mask himself under the  illusion of an early Pulse Condensation youth, and come here to trick him?

He no longer had time to wonder; at this moment, Lin Ming had already lifted his spear!

A spear thrust out, thunder howled, true essence cut the air. The meeting table was shattered into pieces, and the tip of that purple spear pierced towards Chi Yue’s chest!

At this critical moment, Chi Yue fiercely bit down on his tongue, and a young boy wreathed in flames flew from his chest, straight towards Lin Ming’s spear!

“You finally came out?”

Lin Ming wildly grinned, and true essence erupted from his body like a volcano!

Heretical God Force – open!

The Heretical God Seed howled, and the power of thunder and fire surged through the shaft of the Purple Comet Spear, its power multiplying!

The speartip pointed towards the young flame boy’s forehead, between his eyes, azure true essence whistling. This young flame boy was the Fire Worm Shaman’s Flame Essence Avatar. And this one strike was to destroy that flame boy’s soul mark!

“Ahh!!!”

The flame boy wailed like a demented beast, its young face twisting in horror. Its two little hands tightly grabbed onto the tip of the Purple Comet Spear!

Chi chi chi!

The Purple Comet Spear was forged from divine materials of heaven and earth. As the flame boy held onto this spear, its two small hands began to smoke. But no matter how painful it was or how its face contorted in agony, it still did not let go of this spear!

“Go die!”

Behind the flame boy, Chi Yue flourished his staff, true essence erupting from his body. He smashed down at Lin Ming with all of his strength!

Lin Ming sneered, and the Purple Comet Spear turned. A steel needle engraved with a Purple Flood Dragon burst out from his fingertip.

Bang!

Chi Yue’s staff pounded the ground. Rocks exploded, and the entire spiral tower trembled. However, Lin Ming’s figure had already disappeared like smoke.

Meanwhile, the coiling dragon steel needle had already pierced between the flame boy’s eyes!

Pah!

With a barely audible sound, the coiling dragon needle shot through the flame boy’s head, exiting from the other side. The flame boy’s face froze for a moment and then immediately issued forth an inhuman wail, his once innocent and cute face already completely twisted into a monster.

“Ahhhhhhhh!!!!!”

Chi Yue’s hair scattered, his eyes bloodshot, completely red. Blue veins stuck out on his forehead like large earthworms, covering his entirely bald head. “You! You actually destroyed my Avatar!”

“Not only did I destroy your Avatar, but I will also kill you!”

Lin Ming was the judge, jury, and executioner of Chi Yue’s fate. His spear flipped over, and thrust straight towards Chi Yue’s throat. With the Concept of Wind fused into the spear, its speed drew near the extreme. Chi Yue could not dodge this!

“Then let’s die together!”

Chi Yue’s ugly face distorted, and he snapped off the top of his staff, revealing a shining knife!

At this time, crazy Chi Yue had fallen into despair. He completely ignored Lin Ming’s attack, grabbing onto to his spear and using the long knife end to stab towards Lin Ming’s heart. He wanted them both to perish together!

Pah!

The Purple Comet Spear instantly pierced through Chi Yue’s throat, and Chi Yue’s hand suddenly stilled. Both of his eyes lost focus, and the knife in his hand seemed incomparably distant from Lin Ming…

At this time, Chi Yue had already found that Lin Ming had drawn far away. He held a long crimson chain in his hand, and this chain was directly connected to the end of the purple spear…

Chapter 315 – Sect Destruction

A Flame Essence was an amazingly powerful natural force. In normal circumstances, when it was a highly potent medium-grade human-step Flame Essence, one would have to be a late Houtian master from a sect, or a peak Houtian master to absorb it. Not only that, but one would usually need the assistance of some rare treasure like the Glacial Ice Divine Spring.

But Lin Ming was currently relying entirely on his own powerful body and strength to forcibly tame this Flame Essence. His advantage was that his meridians were incomparably tough, but the burning pain still felt like he was being roasted from the inside out, spreading through his body like a tide. Lin Ming revolved his azure true essence to protect his meridians. The azure true essence was endless; even after being burned away by the flames, it would quickly regenerate.

With such support, Lin Ming began to stamp out the flames that rampaged through his meridians. Each time, the Flame Essence would weaken, but the Heretical God Seed would grow stronger.

Under this reversal, another quarter hour passed and Lin Ming was finally able to take complete control of the situation. Now, absorbing the Earthcore Crimson Flame was only a matter of time.

Chi chi chi!

The Heretical God Seed’s Flame Essence danced excitedly, greedily devouring all of the power of fire and constantly growing.

To a normal martial artist, a Flame Essence was no different from a weapon. Once a weapon was forged, its grade was already decided. Later, when they became stronger, they would have to replace their weapon just like they replaced a Flame Essence.

But this situation would never occur with the Heretical God Seed. The Flame Essence could absorb other Flame Essences and grow from them.

An hour later, Lin Ming used his soul force to tow a tiny amount of crimson flame through his meridians. These were the final dredges of the power of fire in his meridians, and they had fully integrated within him. With the enhancement of his fusion compatibility, the Earthcore Crimson Flame became increasingly lively.

“The absorption has finally ended.”

Lin Ming let out a light breath, and absorbed all of the leftover flames into the Heretical God Seed. Then a vast power of fire erupted from within, integrating with the fire origin energy he had gathered while cultivating the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’.

There was a slight popping sound, as if something had cracked apart, and Lin Ming was surprised. Then, he was ecstatic. He had finally broken through to the middle Pulse Condensation period!

He had finally made his breakthrough. With the little bit of medicinal strength left over from the Heaven Opening Pill, the absorption of the Flame Essence, and also the month-long high-intensity cultivation within Ancestor Chi Yan’s mountain range, these three factors had come together and enabled him to complete his breakthrough. It had been a long and difficult process.

If he were a normal martial artist, things wouldn’t have been so troublesome. After taking a Heaven Opening Pill, as long as his body didn’t explode from the energy, then he would be able to rush to the late Pulse Condensation period or even the peak Pulse Condensation period in a single go.

This was the price Lin Ming had to pay in order to lay down the most solid of foundations. Every time he made a breakthrough, he would have to pay two times, or even three times the cost of a normal martial artist.

It wasn’t only Lin Ming, but also sect geniuses like Jiang Baoyun, Bai Shuxuan, Qin Wuxin, and others. Before they reached the Xiantian realm, they would have to make a perfect breakthrough at every stage. This was also why they were superior talents that could fight above their ranks, and the reason they were leagues above any common martial artist.

If there was ever a day that their talent was insufficient to carry them to a complete breakthrough, then that would be the signal that they had reached the end of their cultivation road. In the future, it would be exceedingly difficult to reach a higher realm.

After breaking through to the middle Pulse Condensation period, Lin Ming needed to remove all the impurities in his body that he had recently acquired. He readied himself to return to the Seven Profound Valleys so he could calmly cultivate. While he was there, he would also learn the Mirage Faction’s camouflage techniques and explore the mystery of Jiang Baoyun’s spiritual attack.

The Southern Wilderness was quite close to Lin Ming’s hometown. But, he could not visit his hometown on the way back. He was alone, and now with Ouyang Boyan prowling at the edges, he didn’t want to be exposed to the public. Doing so would only invite danger towards his family.

If Lin Ming didn’t kill Ouyang Boyan, his heart would never be at peace.

Lin Ming sighed, and then whistled loudly into the air. The Winged Flood Dragon was called down, and Lin Ming jumped onto its back, flying straight in the direction of the Seven Profound Valleys…

However, sometimes matters never proceeded as one planned; everything was up to the whim of fate. Lin Ming never thought that while he was returning to the sect, there would be a shocking event that would affect Divine Phoenix Island and the 19 third-grade sects, and also an event that would change the climate of the entire South Horizon Region…

………………

Two days later –

Lin Ming sat on the Winged Flood Dragon’s back, flying at full speed towards the Seven Profound Valleys. A strong heavenly wind blew against him, his clothes flapping in the wind, and his black hair wildly dancing in the air.

At this moment, a bright flame suddenly lit in front of Lin Ming. The flame flashed, and was quickly flown past by the Winged Flood Dragon.

Sound transmitting talisman?

Lin Ming was stunned. He was still in the remote lands of the Seven Profound territory. The only one that could use, or would be willing to use a sound transmitting talisman at this time to find him would be Mu Qianyu. Such a super long-distance sound transmitting talisman had an astronomical price; even Mu Qianyu wouldn’t casually use one.

What sort of important matter had happened? She actually used a super long-distance sound transmitting talisman to contact him?

After several breaths, the fuzzy and intermittent voice of Mu Qianyu resounded in Lin Ming’s ear.

“In a single night, the Moon Seizing Sect was destroyed. Over 90% of their sect has perished. The entire region has broken out with vicious beast tides. This is absolutely the work of the South Sea Demon Region’s Beast Control Clan Sovereign. Remember to be careful.”

Mm!?

Lin Ming was stunned. The Moon Seizing Sect was destroyed in a single night!? How did this happen!

The Moon Seizing Sect was one of the 19 third-grade sects under the jurisdiction of Divine Phoenix Island. In terms of strength, they couldn’t compare to the Seven Profound Valleys, but they ultimately were still a third-grade sect, and probably had no less than a hundred Xiantian masters, and most likely even a Revolving Core elder who commanded them. But they had actually been destroyed in a single night!

The South Sea Demon Region was actually the first to make a move!

After Lin Ming overcame his shock, he realized what the intention of the South Sea Demon Region was. It was to destroy the alliance between Divine Phoenix Island and the 19 third-grade sects.

The Moon Seizing Sect was closest to the South Sea Demon Region. As long as five or six Revolving Core masters crossed the sea and snuck into the Moon Seizing Sect, they would be destroyed overnight!

The South Sea Demon Region was temporarily unable to move against Divine Phoenix Island. But, if they wanted to act against these third-grade sects, who could stop the combined power of five to six Revolving Core masters?

If the South Sea Demon Region could exterminate the Moon Seizing Sect, then that meant they could similarly exterminate the Seven Profound Valleys!

Maybe only a top third-grade sect like the Falling Cloud Sect or Peacock Mountain would be able to barely defend themselves. Like this, the alliance of Divine Phoenix Island and the 19 third-grade sects would be in imminent danger. If Divine Phoenix Island couldn’t protect the other third-grade sects, then who wouldn’t be afraid after having the tragic extermination of a fellow third-grade sect placed in front of them?

If Divine Phoenix Island was defeated by the South Sea Demon Region, then the South Sea Demon Region would be the absolute rulers of the entire Divine Phoenix territory. The third-grade sects might be able to maintain a pitiful existence in that situation. But, if they joined hands with Divine Phoenix Island and resisted them, they might not be able to see the next dawn.

Thinking this, Lin Ming couldn’t help but be frightened. The South Sea Demon Region was truly a demonic clan, their actions and conduct were decisively ruthless and brutal. Without any delay – or even having sent a warning – they had directly eliminated an entire sect!

Not only was a sect exterminated, but the Beast Control Clan had also acted, stirring up a massive vicious beast tide. There were countless stories of the terrors and dangers of these vicious beast tides found within the ancient historical texts. For all these tens of thousands of years, there had been countless countries within Sky Spill Continent that had been destroyed by a vicious beast tide. In fact, the reason that the Na Tribe of the Southern Wilderness had been destroyed by the Fire Worm Tribe was because they had been weakened by a vicious beast tide.

Beast tide… Lin Ming’s heart suddenly shook.

This was bad!

His Lin Family was located in Green Mulberry City. South of Green Mulberry City were the Green Mulberry Mountains. And the mountains continued thousands of miles south, reaching into the Southern Wilderness!

The surrounding area of the Green Mulberry Mountains was nothing worth speaking of, but if one went deep in, there were exceedingly formidable vicious beasts. Once a vicious beast tide erupted, then the city that lay at the foot of the mountains would bear the brunt of their rampage.

This was Green Mulberry City!

Thinking this, Lin Ming sucked in a breath of cold air. He had to return home immediately. Green Mulberry City was his hometown, and was no different than his very roots. He could not see his hometown destroyed.

…………………..

As the year ended, and the new year began, the weather started to become warmer with each day, and the fields of snow and ice melted into the ground. The lush world began to regenerate. The trees were thick with vibrant green leaves, and all sorts of little animals began to happily prance through the forests.

This deep valley was like a magical paradise. But, what very few knew was that within this deep valley, there was a relay station that was set up by the Seven Profound Valleys. In truth, this so-called relay station was actually the central transit point of a transmission array. With the background of the Seven Profound Valleys, it was difficult for them to create many long-distance transmission arrays that could span several hundred thousands of miles. So they had to set up transmit points along the way.

These relay stations had masters guarding them all year round. Currently, the deacon stationed there was Liu Yueshan, a master whose cultivation had reached the late Houtian realm.

Beyond the relay station, the land was full of flowers and sun, just like a perfect spring day. But within the relay station, there was an extremely heavy aura. Liu Yueshan frowned. At this moment, his head was lowered, as if he were thinking of something.

Suddenly, a clear roar sounded out from the sky. Liu Yueshan looked up to see the shadow of a winged dragon-shaped creature pass above him, steadily and swiftly soaring down from the sky, shooting past between two mountains and disappearing.

Liu Yueshan didn’t even have time to determine just what had happened, when he saw a black figure jump down from the sky, slowly falling onto the ground.

This just-arrived black-clothed youth seemed to be around 17 or 18 years old, and the sharp contours of his face seemed to hide a sharp energy that made one’s heart race.

Liu Yueshan’s pupils shrank. This person was…

“Liu Yueshan?” Lin Ming shook a little token in his hand. This pure gold token was a Seven Profound Seal that only direct disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys had.

Liu Yueshan was shocked, direct disciple!?

As a deacon of a relay station, his status was inferior to Huoluo Nation’s Seven Profound Martial House Master. As for those lofty characters like the direct disciples that had a status comparable to an elder, that was truly a remote existence.

“Huoluo Nation relay station deacon Liu Yueshan greets Sir.”

At this time, Lin Ming was near desperation; it was like his heart was on fire. So he spared the needlessly complicated rituals and directly asked, “Liu Yueshan, I ask you, has a vicious beast tide erupted within Sky Fortune Kingdom?”

Liu Yueshan was the one who managed this relay station, and this relay station was also used to share news. Also, this place wasn’t too far from Sky Fortune Kingdom. It was very likely that he would be the first to receive any news.

“Reporting to Sir, this subordinate hasn’t received any news. Vicious beast tides have risen up throughout the entire Seven Profound territory. Requests for help are like snowflakes in a winter storm. The Seven Profound Valleys is overwhelmed with requests at this moment.”

The Seven Profound territory was extremely large. In comparison, the Seven Profound Valleys was very small. There were between 100 and 200 Xiantian masters, and over a thousand Houtian masters. If the Pulse Condensation disciples and normal disciples were counted, then there might be just under 20,000 people in total. Where would they have the manpower to quell the problems of the 36 countries and also keep enough people to defend their sect, so that they wouldn’t be destroyed overnight?

Lin Ming let out deep breath. There wasn’t news from Sky Fortune Kingdom, but right now, no news was also good news. He hesitated for a moment, and then said to Liu Yueshan. “Deacon Liu, if I could trouble you to send a message to the Seven Profound Valleys’ Total Faction and ask if they could send some help to Sky Fortune Kingdom. It is fine as long as they are at the Pulse Condensation period!”

Chapter 324 – The Girl in White

Chi! Chi!

The two sword energies shot out from right and left at extremely tricky angles. Although they were only casual strikes, they were still strikes that came from a sect-based Houtian master. If a normal middle Pulse Condensation martial artist was struck by these two sword energies, they would be severely injured.

The yellow-clothed man thought to establish his reputation to avoid future troubles. And the best way to establish that reputation was naturally to slap down Green Mulberry City’s current number one master, Lin Ming.

“You don’t even make sense!”

Lin Ming coldly snorted. He had been dragged into this mess for no reason and this random man had actually attacked him out of the blue. Obviously, there was something wrong with his mind.

Azure light flashed, and Lin Ming punched out twice, meeting these two sword finger energies with his fists.

Bang! Bang!

With the sound of an explosion, the two sword energies were broken apart. Lin Ming hadn’t even been touched, nor had he taken a single step back.

“Oh?” The yellow-clothed youth’s eyebrows slanted up. “A little boy at the Pulse Condensation period can actually block my sword finger attack? You’re quite a character aren‘t you? Hehe, how about if I use 30% of my strength!”

The yellow-clothed character was about to strike out once again, but then he saw that the white-clothed girl was waving her hand at him, interrupting him. “Senior-apprentice Brother, stop it. Don’t try to oppress other people with your power like this.”

The yellow-clothed youth’s cultivation was at the early Houtian realm, but Lin Ming was actually only at the middle Pulse Condensation period. This sort of fight was originally unfair; the yellow-clothed man was simply using his age and cultivation to suppress others. In the opinion of geniuses, even if the yellow-clothed youth won, it still wouldn’t be a victory.

The yellow-clothed was a bit unhappy being stopped by the white-clothed girl, but he still understood the meaning behind her words and went along with her request, “Since Junior-apprentice Sister says so, I’ll forget it. You, boy, today is your lucky day.”

“Oh? I’m lucky?” Lin Ming thought this was hilarious. In that brief tussle a moment ago, that yellow-clothed youth really did only use a small portion of his strength, but Lin Ming had an extremely keen perception, and he was able to feel that the purity of the yellow-clothed youth’s true essence. He thought that this yellow-clothed youth might be a core disciple, but now it seemed more likely that he was the a high ranking inner court disciple.

An inner court disciple was simply nothing. Currently, Qin Xingxuan was already an inner court disciple, and once her talent blossomed in the future, she would most likely become a core disciple.

“What, you aren’t convinced?” The yellow-clothed youth’s eyebrows picked up, “Since my Junior-apprentice Sister has spoken of compassion, today I will not bully the young. If you aren’t convinced, there is a simple solution. When the beast tide attacks tomorrow, you and I will both go out, and we’ll see just who kills the most. How about it?”

Lin Ming hadn’t even spoken when Shi Linkai angrily shouted, “What dog fart nonsense! Like this father needs your help! My Green Mulberry City…”

Shi Linkai had finished, his voice still full of indignant anger, when a loud voice suddenly interrupted him, “Clan Leader Shi, please take note of the current situation and consider the greater good. Green Mulberry City’s decisions will be determined by Green Mulberry City’s people.”

Shi Linkai turned to look, and saw that the person speaking was the garrison army commander, Zhu Ping. He was wearing a military uniform, and seemed to be emitting a little aura of irritation.

Shi Linkai’s heart began to blaze with fury. Only Green Mulberry City’s people can determine Green Mulberry City’s decisions? Were the Salt Clan not people from Green Mulberry City? His brothers had died in order to protect this city, and yet they actually had such a foul reputation?

Shi Linkai’s fury was about to spill over and cause an irreversible scene when at that moment, Lin Ming sent him a true essence sound transmission, “Clan Leader Shi, don’t bother with this trivial matter, stop here for now.”

Before luring out the chess piece that Ouyang Boyan had lain down, Lin Ming didn’t want to stir up a needless fight, thus exposing his own strength.

Lin Ming was a hero that Shi Linkai held a great deal of admiration towards. Shi Linkai had no choice but to back down, icily coughing as he stopped speaking.

Zhu Ping turned a smile on the yellow-clothed youth and said, “I will immediately empty the best mansion in Green Mulberry City, change the bedding and furniture, and have several well trained maids brought over. Two masters, please rest freely.

Zhu Ping bowed as he spoke. Such a welcome that was in agreement with all the specifications seemed like a deliberate attempt to nauseate Lin Ming.

Lin Ming lived in the army compound, ate with the soldiers and lived with the soldiers. Yet Zhu Ping had actually set aside a special residence for these two people.

In this regard, Lin Ming didn’t mind. Some people were like this. If you treated them kindly, that person might not take you seriously. But if you pushed their face into the ground and slapped them around, they would think of you as a true character that couldn’t be offended, and treat you carefully and respectfully.

This kind of person could only be described as shallow and cheap.

Of course, the difference with which Zhu Ping treated Lin Ming and the yellow-clothed youth was also because of hatred and other factors.

Zhu Ping was very glad to see that the yellow-clothed youth and Lin Ming seemed hostile to each other. If these two could fight, and Lin Ming receive a severe injury in the process, killing him would be much easier.

“Hmph, I can tell you’re a sensible one. Hurry up and prepare. Remember to prepare several buckets of spring bath water, and incense to clear the smell. My Junior-sister does not like to live in places like this army compound. Rest assured, once the beast tide comes, I’ll be able to arrive in just a few breaths of time.” As the yellow-clothed youth spoke, he glanced at Lin Ming, an unforgiving expression etched on his face. As for his strike being resisted a moment ago, he naturally wasn’t comfortable with this. It was just that he didn’t want to go against the wishes of the white-clothed girl.

The yellow-clothed youth and his junior-apprentice sister were truly disciples from the Moon Seizing Sect. The Moon Seizing Sect had been destroyed six days go, and over 90% of the disciples had died. Of the Xiantian masters, all of them had perished.

Luckily, the two of them had managed to escape. They had been traveling under the barest conditions, spending most of their time in the jungles of the Southern Wilderness. They lived outdoors, ate wild fruits and dried rations, and didn’t even have the chance to change clothes. For the white-clothed girl who was used to remaining clean, this was very difficult to endure.

The yellow-clothed youth had seized the opportunity to drop the white-clothed girl in this big mortal city, and rest for a few days.

The truth was, he also had his own reason for doing so. This white-clothed girl was actually one of direct disciples of the Moon Seizing Sect. If she was able to escape this time, that meant there must definitely be many treasures on her body. Her own master had died beside her, how could she not have given her disciple everything?

Earth-steps treasures, rare jade slips, and most important of all… Heaven Opening Pills!

The yellow-clothed youth estimated that this white-clothed girl might have five or six Heaven Opening Pills on her!

Although the Moon Seizing Sect was one of the lowest ranked within the 19 third-grade sects, they had still managed to accumulate several dozens of Heaven Opening Pills. Since the white-clothed girl was one of the top ranked direct disciples in the sect, there was a high possibility she would have many Heaven Opening Pills on her!

Besides the Heaven Opening Pill, the yellow-clothed youth was faintly aware that within the Moon Seizing Sect, there also existed a top-ranked extremely valuable medicine. This medicine’s value was far beyond that of a Heaven Opening Pill, and it was said to be related to the former master of the South Sea Demon Region… the master of Silent Demon Emperor City.

Although the Moon Seizing Sect had been on the decline for a long time, it still had a very long and storied sect history, filled with glory and tribulations. 2000 years ago, the Moon Seizing Sect was a top third-grade sect, and its strength surpassed even Peacock Mountain.

At that time, the Moon Seizing Sect had joined forces with the entire South Horizon Region to lay siege to Silent Demon Emperor City. Obtaining such extremely rare and top grade medicine from this siege wouldn’t be unusual.

Silent Demon Emperor City used to be a Holy Land rank sect, and the Netherworld Great Emperor was a top figure of the entire Skill Spill Continent. From an existence like that, whatever came from their hand – even if it were a chamber pot – would be a rare and precious artifact that countless small sects would crazily fight over.

The precious medicine that existed within the Moon Seizing Sect was said to have a very high and impactful effect for Xiantian masters that were trying to break into the Revolving Core realm. As for what it specifically was, the yellow-clothed youth had only ever heard some vague rumors. It had been so many years since then, so it might all be gone.

Of course, the yellow-clothed youth didn’t expect that the white-clothed girl would have such a precious medicine on her body. Even if she did, he wouldn’t be able to swallow a medicine of that level.

His heart’s true desire lay in the Heaven Opening Pills. With his talent, it would not be easy to reach the Xiantian realm. But if he had enough Heaven Opening Pills, it wouldn’t be a problem.

Who didn’t wish to reach the Xiantian realm?

If the white-clothed girl was not an angelic beauty and didn’t have countless life-saving measures, this yellow-clothed youth would have already directly snatched it from her body.

The yellow-clothed youth had originally been an inner court disciple of the Moon Seizing Sect, and the disparity between his status and the white-clothed girl’s status was immense. In normal times, if these two people met, the yellow-clothed youth would have had to be extremely respectful to her. However, in his heart, he had many unnatural and perverted ambitions towards the white-clothed girl. It wasn’t just him, but many of the other male disciples of the Moon Seizing Sect had once dreamed of marrying this white-clothed girl. Once they did, they would be able to obtain extra resources and have the backing of such a beautiful lady. Wouldn’t that simply be perfection?

Of course, the yellow-clothed youth had only ever thought that – it was simply impossible for it to happen.

In particular, just a month ago the white-clothed girl had been chosen as one of the geniuses in the training program carried out by Divine Phoenix Island. She had been one of the 50 human-step talents that were selected.

The Moon Seizing Sect had originally been one of the lowest 19 third-grade sects. When the joint talent training program had first been announced at the Seven Profound Valleys, no one from the Moon Seizing Sect was included in the 20 invited elites. Afterwards, the total joint talent training program had over 100 individuals, and the Moon Seizing Sect merely had a pitiful two disciples chosen.

One was a male disciple, and the other was this white-clothed girl.

Therefore, that male disciple and the white-clothed girl had become the dragon and phoenix pairing of the Moon Seizing Sect. In these circumstances, anyone that had improper thoughts of the white-clothed girl were the same as toads trying to eat swan meat.

The yellow-clothed youth had burned with jealousy. He wished he could kill that lucky fool of a male disciple, take his place, and then obtain the white-clothed girl. He wanted to tear apart her impassionate shell and mercilessly ravage her.

This was probably a common dark and frustrated thought that many of the inner court male disciples in the sect had.

And then, tragedy had befallen the Moon Seizing Sect, and that too-lucky male disciple had actually died. Just this point had caused the yellow-clothed youth to feel immeasurably happy.

The yellow-clothed youth felt as if he were in a dream he didn’t want to wake from. As he was fleeing, he met the white-clothed girl who was riding away on a golden-winged Heavenly Wind Eagle.

This was simply the heavens themselves helping him.

Because the white-clothed girl had lost her master and lost her sect, she must be in immeasurable pain and inner turmoil. For the yellow-clothed youth, this was a golden chance to seize her heart and everything else.

Therefore, for these past days, the yellow-clothed youth had been using all of the experience and knowledge he had of flirting with girls to take advantage of the white-clothed girl’s vulnerable state of mind, and leave a favorable impression and goodwill on her.

If there was any disciple within the Moon Seizing Sect that wanted to thank the South Sea Demon Region even after they destroyed their sect, then it would probably only be this yellow-clothed youth.

Chapter 327 – You Cannot Stop Me

Brutal and manic power of thunder scattered out.

A two inch long simple steel needle. There was a textured image of a Purple Flood Dragon carved onto the surface, twining around the needle a total of nine times.

Because the coiling dragon steel needle was in a completely static state, the power of thunder was fully restrained within it. The old man had plenty of time to observe the energy structure of the steel needle, and his perception wasn’t bounced back either.

As he felt the power of thunder that was compressed to such a terrifying degree, the old man’s lips began to fiercely twitch.

“This… this is…”

The old man had never personally seen a Thunder Soul before, but as a Mirage Faction disciple, he knew that the enemy that was best suited to suppress them were thunder-attribute martial artists. The power of thunder was able to dispel illusions, ghosts, and evil powers. This was something that the old man had learned from reading many ancient texts.

This steel needle in front of him didn’t send out even the slightest bit of power of thunder at the moment. It was endless, and all of the threads of thunder seemed to contain a consciousness; it was alive.

Consciousness… awareness… thunder with life, endless; this was the symbol of a Thunder Soul!

Compared to a Flame Essence, a Thunder Soul was much more rare. Even a low-grade human-step Thunder Soul was an incomparably precious treasure. As for a medium-grade human-step Thunder Soul, that was enough to cause bloodbaths between Xiantian masters…

Seeing the intensity of the terrifying energy within Lin Ming’s hand, this Thunder Soul was absolutely at least a medium-grade human-step Thunder Soul… could it even be a high-grade human-step Thunder Soul!?!?

The old man was unable to imagine that this was a Pulse Condensation period martial artist. Where or how could he have possibly absorbed a high-grade human-step Thunder Soul which only a Xiantian master could absorb?

Even if it were Divine Phoenix Island, they also wouldn’t be able to achieve this. To absorb a Thunder Soul, one could only have limited assistance – the true test all depended on oneself.

Not just that, but the boy had a Thunder Soul and also a Flame Essence!

A medium-grade human-step Flame Essence and a possible high-grade human-step Thunder Soul!

Was this a power that a 16 year old boy could have!?!

The old man was suddenly afraid. He felt that this Lin Ming was too strange, he was just like a demon king hiding within humanity!

In his heart, he couldn’t help but think about retreating. He hadn’t exposed his true identity, and even if Lin Ming hadn’t been bluffing about knowing his identity, he still hadn’t revealed any clues to who he was. If he couldn’t win, then he would flee!

As a Mirage Faction disciple, he was proficient in concealment techniques. As long as he was able to escape Lin Ming’s true essence locking rage, he could easily escape in the night, losing Lin Ming.

In the worst case he would just not return to the Seven Profound Valleys. Although not returning to the Seven Profound Valleys was the same as severing his future hope of becoming a Xiantian master, preserving his life was much more important than some distant Xiantian realm.

The old man treasured his life very much. The reason that he would undertake this mission for Ouyang Boyan was because he wished to break through to the Xiantian realm and live to 180 years old.

The old man turned his palm, and a small thunderclap bead appeared. This was a small Array Faction gadget. Once it was thrown, it would explode and create a massive amount of thick fog. He would be able to use this chance and display his illusion techniques to escape.

However, before he could throw the thunderclap bead, Lin Ming’s Purple Comet Spear began to shine with a dazzling bright purple and a burning crimson red. In the dark night, it was just like a purple and red sun was rising into the sky!

Thunder and fire intertwined!

Lin Ming thrust out his spear. Suddenly, all the sounds of the world vanished, and the surrounding space twisted.

The old man’s face was colored with fear; a dual thunder and fire attack!?

It was too late to run. The old man fiercely clenched his teeth, overdrawing his life essence to forcefully stimulate the true essence in his body to the max.

“72 Swords Absolute Killing Array!!”

This barrage of 72 sword energies was the old man’s strongest move. Once he used it, he would be placed in an incomparably weak position for a short period of time. Because of this, he didn’t dare to use it rashly. But now he had no other choice left to him. That shining red and purple power of thunder and fire on the spear was too terrifying to do otherwise.

Bang!

The spear light and sword energies struck each other. A horrifying true essence current billowed forth, and all the sword energies were completely shattered!

“What!?”

The old man had expected Lin Ming’s strike to be terrifying, but he never imagined that the strongest final blow he had overdrawn his life to use would be destroyed so easily!

….

….

On the outskirts of Green Mulberry City, the beast tide was still coming. The yellow-clothed youth from the Moon Seizing Sect had already killed thousands of vicious beasts, and the blood of countless vicious beasts rained down on the land, dying the earth around him a deep crimson red.

Every sword strike would release dozens of sword energies, and every sword energy was able to take a vicious beast’s life. With a single sword slash, this yellow-clothed youth was able to massacre dozens of vicious beasts. If it wasn’t for the fact that only a few vicious beasts were left around the yellow-clothed youth at the moment, he would have killed even more.

As for third-level vicious beasts, they were nothing but paper in front of the yellow-clothed youth, and equally as fragile. He was able to kill them with a single sword; there wasn’t even a need to stop.

A fourth-level vicious beast would take at most 10 breaths of time to kill. The two Iron-armor Lizards that had attacked the yellow-clothed youth were also equally killed by him!

What kind of abnormal and terrifying strength was this?

Zhuang Fan, Lin Wanshan, and everyone else watching could only sigh in lamentation; martial artists from large sects were just too formidable.

Zhuang Fan and Lin Wanshan who had just stepped into the Pulse Condensation period thought this, and the common mortal soldiers were also stunned. To them, this yellow-clothed youth was just like a war god.

The yellow-clothed youth enjoyed this feeling very much. When he had been at the Moon Seizing Sect, he was only an inner court disciple, and had broken through to the Houtian realm when he was 26 years old. The result could only be considered the most average within the sect. There were just too many geniuses and top-tier talents pressing down on him, making him feel that his existence was weak.

Over the years, the yellow-clothed youth could be considered invisible. But now, he unveiled his power in front of so many people, making him the rising star of this battlefield. This made him extremely happy; even the true essence in his body seemed to be flowing much smoothly than before.

Not just that, but most importantly, he would soon capture the heart of his talented junior-apprentice sister. As long as he was able to obtain her, he would have enough Heaven Opening Pills to attack the Xiantian bottleneck!

He had to thank the South Sea Demon Region. If it wasn’t for them destroying the Moon Seizing Sect, he would never have had this opportunity. Most likely, he would never have had a chance to obtain a Heaven Opening Pill either.

The more the yellow-clothed youth killed, the more vibrant and excited he became. He had originally been hesitant about going to battle, but now he hoped that he could continue fighting for a long time.

But at this moment, he suddenly heard a loud explosion, and the land itself resounded with a deafening thunderclap, He turned his head to a distant spot in the beast tide, his eyes wide with amazement. Purple thunder flashed into the sky, impacting the heavens. Between it, a giant pillar of red flame also ascended upwards. It was as if heavenly tribulation had come down to the world!

‘Mm? What’s going on?’

Although the yellow-clothed youth was extremely far from where it happened, he could still feel the terrifying energy contained in that explosion.

A peak Houtian thunder-attribute martial artist and a peak Houtian fire-attribute martial artist were fighting?

How could that be possible? In this small land, why would two great elders be fighting here?

The yellow-clothed youth hesitated, thinking he would go take a look. But then, those terrifying fluctuations of energy suddenly stopped, interrupted, as if they had been completely sealed off.

‘It’s gone?’

“Senior-apprentice Brother, what was that a moment ago?” The voice of the white-clothed girl’s true essence sound transmission resounded in the yellow-clothed youth’s ears.

The yellow-clothed youth was stunned. He immediately withdrew the shocked expression on his face and replaced it with a casual tone, saying, “Eh, probably some heavenly thunder.”

“Heavenly thunder?”

“Mm.” The yellow-clothed youth calmly analyzed and explained the situation, “If that terrifying power of thunder continued, it would most likely be two great masters fighting. But since it instantly vanished, it was most likely spring thunder that fell down, splitting into heavenly fire. This kind of phenomenon isn’t uncommon.”

“But Senior-apprentice Brother… look at the sky.”

“Mm?”

The yellow-clothed youth suddenly looked up, and then big beads of sweat began to immediately form on his forehead. Above him, the bright moon was shining in the sky like a silver plate, and the entire night was free of clouds, the stars shining brightly.

In this weather, how could there possibly be thunder?

…………………………………

Ten miles away, a black-clothed man was kneeling on the ground, barely propping himself up with his sword. Half of his body was covered in soot and another half of his body’s clothes were burnt away. The flexible armor underneath his clothes was fragmented, and his chest, stomach, arms, and legs dripped with fresh red blood.

This man was Bi Luo. Bi Luo had just fallen from the sky, and his illusion technique had been automatically dispelled, reverting from the appearance of an old man into his true self.

If it wasn’t for him using a self-defensive ice armor bead at the last moment, he would have been severely wounded to the point of losing every bit of combat strength he had left. If that happened, his fate could be imagined.

“Martial House Master Bi, did your sword strike from a moment ago overspend your true essence, thus causing you to be unable to support your illusion, revealing your true self?” Lin Ming asked the severely wounded Bi Luo, a faint smile crossing his face.

Lin Ming didn’t use the full strength of Thunderfire Annihilation, only using one with 40% strength.

This was a technique that Lin Ming had slowly and thoroughly researched, then mastered after spending a month in Ancestor Chi Yan’s mountain range.

The complete and full version of Thunderfire Annihilation was very slow, it had a long activation time. It also consumed a great deal of strength. Not just that, but with Lin Ming’s current cultivation, simultaneously controlling a low-grade earth-step Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder and medium-grade human-step Earthcore Crimson Flame was impossible.

If he rashly used the complete Thunderfire Annihilation, he might not be able to control the power, and would probably kill himself in the explosion he created.

“You…” Bi Luo’s eyes were filled with disbelief as he stared at Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s current strength had completely surpassed the scope of his understanding. This was a strength that was impossible for a 16 year old youth to have.

“Hahahahaha!” Bi Luo suddenly smiled, laughing with unbridled impunity.

“Lin Ming, you think that you can kill me today? I may not be your match, but if I wish to leave, you cannot stop me! You have a high-grade human-step Thunder Soul on your body? If I spread this news, then how many Xiantian masters will take an interest in you?” An evil and vengeful smile curved on Bi Luo’s face.

Lin Ming blankly looked at Bi Luo, not seeming to care for his words.

“Normally, even if someone were interested in you, you could still stay in the sect and no one would dare to touch you. But now… Divine Phoenix Island and the South Sea Demon Region are about to go to war. In such chaos, do you really think you can always be protected?

“Lin Ming, you are too confident in yourself. But then again, geniuses are always so confident, that is why they die so easily! You thought you could lure me out by hiding your strength? You think you can kill me? Since I dared to kill you, then I naturally have ways to save my own life. You… you cannot stop me!”

“You think I can’t stop you?” The corners of Lin Ming’s lips lifted in a faint smile, revealing a thoughtful expression.

Chapter 332 – Brilliance of Thunderfire

“Brothers, while we have two masters in front dealing with the tentacle monster, we will defend against the beast tide! As long as we can last, and the two masters can kill that strange tentacle beast, we will win!” A soldier shouted out from the battlefield.

However, the soldier’s words didn’t have much effect. Anyone could see that the yellow-clothed youth and Lin Ming were in a very disadvantageous position against the Sludge Monster. After the yellow-clothed youth had been injured at the very start, he was forced into danger. As for Lin Ming, he was worse than the yellow-clothed youth, dodging around the sides and not even attacking once.

In this situation, it was already good for the yellow-clothed youth and Lin Ming to not die against the Sludge Monster, let alone kill it.

Even so, none of the soldiers retreated. Behind them was Green Mulberry City, where their parents, wives, children, and everyone they else that they loved lived. If Green Mulberry City fell, everyone within would die.

How could they even think of retreating?

Rumble rumble rumble!

Tentacles lashed out like a flurry of whips. The yellow-clothed youth was desperately dodging all of the attacks; he didn’t even have any strength to launch a full counterattack. Occasionally, he would gasp in exhaustion and slash out with several sword energies towards the dreamland enchantment.

However, the dreamland enchantment wasn’t something the yellow-clothed youth could hope to break through; his sword couldn’t even cause the barrier to shake.

“Boy called Lin, I… I’ve already… caught its attention, quick… hurry up and attack the Sludge Monster! Otherwise we’ll both die here!”

The yellow-clothed youth was thinking of escaping and having Lin Ming attack to draw the attention of the Sludge Monster. However, Lin Ming remained unmoved.

Seeing Lin Ming turn a deaf ear to his pleas and not even help just a bit, the yellow-clothed youth became angry. He rushed over to Lin Ming, intending to drag him down too, but Lin Ming was just too speedy and nimble. There was no way the yellow-clothed youth could catch him.

“Ah!!!”

The yellow-clothed youth suddenly let out a miserable cry. His leg had rubbed against some corrosive mucus, and was immediately covered in blood.

A wound of this level wasn’t enough to disable him, but it made dodging even more difficult.

The yellow-clothed youth gritted his teeth and used this life and death crisis to push his body to its limits. But he knew that he simply wouldn’t be able to keep this up for much longer.

At this time, Lin Ming had already poured a vast majority of the true essence in his body into the Heretical God Seed, constantly compressing it. The power of the Heretical God Seed had already been restored to 95%!

“Just hold on a bit longer.”

Lin Ming looked at the shaking enchantment barriers around him, his mind in complete concentration. Although the Sludge Monster was attacking the yellow-clothed youth, every time it did so, the attack would also splash onto the dreamland enchantment, causing an enormous impact upon it.

The Sludge Monster’s strength was over 100,000 jins. There was no way that the dreamland enchantment would be able to resist this sort of force for much longer.

“It’s almost ready.”

Lin Ming could feel that the total compression of the Heretical God Seed’s power was about to be completed, but the dreamland enchantment wouldn’t be able to last much longer.

The dreamland enchantment had a great practical value for Lin Ming, he didn’t want to lose it like this. Just as the dreamland enchantment reached its limit, at that moment, Lin Ming waved his hand and directly stored the Dreamland Pearl away.

At this time, the Heretical God Force was fully saturated!

Peng!

The yellow-clothed youth was slapped by the Sludge Monster’s tentacle. He flew backwards, spitting blood, no different than a broken ragdoll.

As the yellow-clothed youth flew back, spitting blood, the air whistling in his ears, he didn’t need to look to see that the tentacles were attacking him once again. At this critical moment, the yellow-clothed youth stirred up all of the remaining strength he had, completely willing himself up with his survival instincts, fighting back the intense pain in his organs, and then rushing forwards, barely escaping the fatal blow.

He desperately shouted at Lin Ming, “If… I… if I die, then you’ll die an even worse death! Hurry up and attack its eye… its weakness! Otherwise… we’ll all die!”

In the turbulent wind, the yellow-clothed youth’s voice was barely audible, cut off again and again. In truth, he didn’t know the weakness of the Sludge Monster. Perhaps the Sludge Monster didn’t even have a weakness. The yellow-clothed youth only said this because he wanted to lure Lin Ming in to attack the Sludge Monster’s eye, angering it.

However, the yellow-clothed youth also knew that there was no way a timid and cowardly fellow like Lin Ming would ever attack.

But he didn’t expect to see Lin Ming’s spear and entire body flashing with bright sparks of thunder and flame, incomparably radiant.

Seeing this, the yellow-clothed youth was stunned, and then started chuckling to himself. This boy was finally fooled!

It seemed that the boy called Lin was finally making his move, and not only that, but it looked like his ultimate strike. With that boy as a diversion, the yellow-clothed youth might be able to survive. A moment ago, he had felt the dreamland enchantment finally vanish, or he would have hit the barrier.

As the dream world enchantment vanished, the boy called Lin impulsively rushed towards the Sludge Monster to launch his attack. This attack would inevitably attract the Sludge Monster towards him.

This was the best chance he would have to escape. The yellow-clothed youth could only hope that Lin Ming’s attack was strong enough to provoke the Sludge Monster. He would have thanked Lin Ming in gratitude for giving him this opportunity to escape, but it would have been nothing but a joke. If it wasn’t for Lin Ming, how would he ever have been caught in this dangerous situation? He looked forward to seeing Lin Ming die under the Sludge Monster’s strike.

The yellow-clothed youth withstood the pain and displayed his highest movement technique to escape. This time, the only thing that mattered to him was escaping all of this. What Green Mulberry City? He didn’t care at all about the soldiers’ lives, and even Lan Yi’s life was nothing compared to this.

Wind whistled. Lin Ming opened up the Heretical God Force, the Thunder Soul and Flame Essence in his body intensely trembling.

Although everyone could see that Lin Ming was about to launch his attack, no one besides him knew just how terrifying the power of this strike would be.

True essence crazily flooded into the Heretical God Seed. The compressed power of thunder and fire was at its limits, like a dam that was about to burst open. With the Purple Comet Spear in his hand, the power of thunder and fire was enhanced to the extreme.

Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder!

Earthcore Crimson Flame!

With the Thunder Soul and Flame Essence as its source, this would be the strongest Thunderfire Annihilation. Even if Lin Ming opened up the Heretical God Force, it would be exceedingly difficult to control its power.

The spearpoint faced out. Lin Ming’s entire body was twined with arcs of lightning and wreaths of fire; he directly shot towards the Sludge Monster like a blazing meteor!

Time seemed to slow down. The waving tentacles, the shouts of the soldiers, the roar of the beasts, all of this disappeared, leaving only the terrifying reverberations of thunder and fire echoing in the air.

Peng! Peng!

Two tentacles swiped at Lin Ming. But, they were instantly pierced through by Lin Ming and his spear! The green corrosive mucus was instantly burnt to nothing by the thick power of thunder and fire in the air. Lin Ming rushed towards the Sludge Monster, overwhelming, unstoppable!

Thunderfire Annihilation!

Bang–!

An ultimate power broke forth. In the night sky, it was like a purple sun had dawned. A large fissure appeared in the Sludge Monster, a massive amount of blood and viscous green liquid flowing out.

Lin Ming carried on his slaughter straight through, penetrating the Sludge Monster’s body and rushing out the other side, a shower of green blood appearing in his wake!

“Houu—aa—!”

A gorgeous and shining pillar of flame and thunder pierced into the sky; the Sludge Monster roared in pain.

Flames lit the entire night sky. Countless vicious beasts were charred alive by the fire, there were innumerable casualties as vicious beasts fell to the floor.

Even the nearby yellow-clothed youth almost died. The flames’ shock wave smashed into him, sending him tumbling onto the floor, his hair and clothes burnt.

At this time, he couldn’t care about these things. He could only look at that raging inferno with incredulity, feeling the life-force of the Sludge Monster weakening, his heart shaking.

The Sludge Monster died?

How… what… just what had happened?

The Sludge Monster seemed to be the leader of the second tide of vicious beasts. As its corpse burnt within the fire, all of the vicious beasts stopped as if they had lost all of their courage, and stopped attacking.

Every vicious beast turned towards the Sludge Monster that was wrapped in a cloak of flame. Then, after several breaths of time, they began to retreat like an ebbing tide, running away from Green Mulberry City.

Hualalala…

Soon, all of the vicious beasts on the battlefield retreated, leaving behind only corpses.

The vicious beasts retreated?

All of Green Mulberry City’s soldiers, standing among mounds of flesh and blood, their bodies exhausted and barely able to stand, could hardly believe as they watched the vicious beasts retreat.

That dreadful inferno that pierced through the heavens seemed to cast a warmth on their bodies, heating up their cold spirits.

We won?

No one could believe this as they stared at the giant hill that was the Sludge Monster. That invincible Sludge Monster had actually been killed by Lin Ming in one move.

“We won!”

“The vicious beasts have retreated!”

After a moment of silence, all of the soldiers burst out in thunderous cheers. Many people embraced each other in excitement, hot tears streaking down their faces. The tears ran down faces that were matted with dust and blood, leaving behind clear traces.

These soldiers were different from Lin Ming. After all, they were only mortal. If Green Mulberry City could not be defended, Lin Ming could freely retreat. But as for them, they did not have such a luxury. During this war, the soldiers who came were already prepared to die on this battlefield.

The vicious beast tide seemed endless. They were already at their limits, but then the Sludge Monster had appeared, and the vicious beasts grew increasingly violent, nearly overwhelming their hearts.

However, against everyone’s expectations, the Sludge Monster had been utterly destroyed by Lin Ming in a single strike. After the amazing reversal that followed, they had won!

…………………………

Beside the Sludge Monster, Lin Ming knelt on the floor, propping himself up with his spear. His energy consumption had been massive; this single blow had exhausted a full 60% of his true essence.

With his current strength, even though he had opened the Heretical God Force and also had the increased power of the Purple Comet Spear, he couldn’t use the full strength of Thunderfire Annihilation. He was just barely able to use 70-80% of its strength. Even so, it had still drained him of so much energy.

As Lin Ming looked at the giant pyre of flames, he took a deep breath, and pulled out a pill from his spatial ring, eating it to help restore his true essence. Although it sounded terrifying that he had killed the Sludge Monster in a single blow, this didn’t mean that Lin Ming had strength equal to a sect’s peak Houtian martial artist.

The Sludge Monster had a massive body, and it was also slow. In the end, it couldn’t avoid attacks and became an easy target.

Lin Ming’s most outstanding aspect was his attack power. Once he used Thunderfire Annihilation, its power was truly earth-shattering. But, when facing a top Houtian martial artist like Qin Ziya, he might not have the chance to do so.

Chapter 333 – Lan Yi’s Request

The flames burned brightly. Lin Ming carried the Purple Comet Spear and walked towards the flames. With a wave of his hand, an invisible energy rushed forth, dividing the flames and revealing a passageway.

The Sludge Monster had already stopped struggling. There were only a few tentacles that were still roasting in the fiery heat, curling up as they burnt to ash.

With a single spear, Lin Ming slashed apart the Sludge Monster, walking directly into its body.

Chi chi chi!

Green mucus fell like rain, but it was all burnt away by flames.

A moment later, Lin Ming took out a fist-sized inner core pearl from the Sludge monster, placing it into a spatial ring.

All vicious beasts above the fourth-level had core pearls within them. Whether it was for alchemy or for countering poisons, the Sludge Monster’s core pearl would be an extremely good material. Naturally, Lin Ming wouldn’t leave it.

The Sludge Monster’s sinews were also a good material. But the Sludge Monster had been slashed apart by Lin Ming, and had also been charred black. These sinews no longer had any value.

The flames separated into a path as Lin Ming carried his Purple Comet Spear and walked out from the blazing inferno, his spearpoint leading the way. At this time, his hair was loose, and he was covered in residual arcs of purple lightning and flame. At this moment, he looked like a peerless demon god.

The person closest to Lin Ming was the yellow-clothed youth from the Moon Seizing Sect. The yellow clothed-youth was slumped on the ground, exhausted. As he watched Lin Ming emerge from the fire, his lips twitched, and his eyes were blank like he had lost his soul.

He thought that Lin Ming was inviting death with that spear of his, but he never imagined that a single blow was able to kill the Sludge Monster…

This was a fifth-level vicious beast, whose strength was comparable to a peak Houtian martial artist. As for Lin Ming, his cultivation was only at the mere middle Pulse Condensation period!

Who was he?

The yellow-clothed youth was very clear just how terrifying it was to have this strength at this cultivation, and at such a young age!

It was impossible for him to be unknown.

At this moment, he heard a rallying cry spread through the entire army, as if it were an endless tide.

“Long live Hero Lin!”

“Long live Hero Lin!”

“Long live Hero Lin!”

“Long live Hero Lin!”

To an ordinary soldier, Lin Ming was their benefactor and also their savior. Without Lin Ming, not only would they have died, but all their family that stood behind them would have been turned to bones by the vicious beast tide.

Surname Lin… His surname was Lin…

A 16 year old genius surnamed Lin… a name suddenly popped up in the yellow-clothed youth’s heart, causing him to be completely petrified. He sat on the ground like a statue, watching as Lin Ming walked past him…

The cheers continued. Lin Ming looked in the distance to see that the soldiers were all bloodied, but they were cheering in high spirits, and his mood became complex.

In this battle, the ones that had the greatest impact were the masters. But, if these soldiers hadn’t used their own bodies to create a wall of flesh and blood to block off the beast tide, then no matter how strong Lin Ming was, or how many vicious beast he killed, they would have broken into Green Mulberry City and killed innocents.

In this fight, these ordinary soldiers had paid the greatest cost, but the cheers and accolades they received were the least.

He even saw a soldier who had lost his arm in battle. After a simple wrap to staunch the bleeding, this soldier used all of his weary strength to raise his right arm, saluting Lin Ming.

At this moment, Lin Ming’s heart suddenly felt heavy. This was a war of mortals. In an army that was once 10,000 strong, there were now only a few thousand left. To the soldiers, being able to survive, or knowing that their families were safe, was already the best possible result.

Thinking of the culprit that was behind this entire farce – the South Sea Demon Region, Lin Ming’s mind and heart filled with waves of surging hatred.

To a lofty fifth-grade sect, the lives of mortals were no different than ants.

In order to swallow Divine Phoenix Island and the South Horizon Region, and to warn the 19 third-grade sects, the South Sea Demon Region didn’t hesitate for a second before setting off a terrifying beast tide that embroiled the entire Divine Phoenix Province. Because of their actions, death reigned everywhere, and countless innocent lives were lost.

Lin Ming walked towards the army camp and hadn’t even arrived when he was swarmed by people. They were all being led by high level people of Green Mulberry City such as Lin Wanshan and Zhuang Fan.

That vivid image of Lin Ming killing the Sludge Monster with a single strike of his spear could be described as a miracle. The monster was the size of a hill, but was stabbed to death with a single move. Purple lightning and roaring flames had impacted the heavens; this had left a greatly humbling impact upon everyone watching.

The Salt Clan’s Shi Linkai had a very ruddy complexion, red with excitement. He laughed loudly and said, “Hero Lin, you are truly a war god reincarnate!”

He was ready to let out some more praise, when he found that something didn’t seem right about Lin Ming’s condition.

“Hero Lin, is everything alright?”

Lin Ming waved his hand and said, “I’m good. I just need to rest for a moment.”

Lin Ming had only consumed too much energy; it wasn’t because he was injured by the Sludge Monster. The Sludge Monster had a great deal of corrosive mucus in its body, but most of it was burnt away by the power of thunder and fire. As for the rest, it wasn’t able to melt through Lin Ming’s protective true essence.

At this time, a white-clothed girl came out from the crowd. Her delicate red lips parted, and she carefully called out, “Sir Lin.”

This girl was Lan Yi. She had seen all she needed in that brief moment to confirm that this was Lin Ming. Within all of the talents of the 19 third-grade sects, who could display this level of power besides Lin Ming?

In fact, according to Lan Yi’s impression, Lin Ming should not have had this amount of terrifying combat strength. This was not strength that a Pulse Condensation period martial artist should have. In fact, there were even certain elders within the Moon Seizing Sect that couldn’t match up. The Moon Seizing Sect was a relatively weak and small sect, and some of the outer court elders were only at the peak Houtian realm. Their attack power would never reach this level.

For a 16 year to have attack power that compared favorably to an outer court elder of the Moon Seizing Sect… Lin Ming truly deserved his title as the top talent and young genius within the 19 third-grade sects.

Lan Yi never expected that she would meet Lin Ming in such a remote mortal city. Naturally, she would not miss this rare opportunity.

Lin Ming looked up at Lan Yi, “What’s the matter?”

At this point, Lin Ming was able to confirm that Lan Yi had recognized him. The reason she repeatedly approached him must be because she had some matter to discuss.

“Sir Lin, this is a Blue Lotus Pill, it can help you recover your strength.” As Lan Yi spoke, she took out a small bottle from her spatial ring. A rich aroma emitted from the pill – it was indeed a top-grade pill.

“I don’t need it.” Lin Ming waved, “I already have pills. If Miss Lan has any matters to discuss, please speak frankly.”

“This…”

For a moment, Lan Yi seemed somewhat embarrassed. To brazenly and openly ask others for help was quite difficult.

At this point, Shi Linkai also revealed a mischievous smile, his eyes lighting up with a ‘hehe’ expression. He gave Lin Ming a meaningful glance, silently saying ‘Brother, you are very fierce!’, and quickly excused himself and left.

Obviously, to Shi Linkai, Lan Yi was infatuated with Lin Ming. To him, this was a completely normal matter. After all, beautiful women loved heroes, the two were of a similar age, and Lin Ming had an attractive aura to him.

As Shi Linkai thought that he was being clever, this caused Lan Yi to be even more embarrassed. She coughed and said, “Sir Lin, I would like to request a favor, may I speak with you alone?”

“Alright, let’s go to the army compound.” Lin Ming also wanted to understand how the Moon Seizing Sect was attacked, so he didn’t reject her.

Chapter 334 – Moon Seizing Sect’s Hidden Treasures

Seeing Lin Ming and Lan Yi’s departing forms, Zhuang Fan glanced at Lin Wanshan and said, “Old Lin, Lin Ming is 16 this year isn’t he?

“Mm… it’s about time for engagement.”

According to the traditions of Sky Fortune Kingdom, once a man reached 16 years of age and became an adult, he could be engaged, and once he reached 18 years of age, he could get married.

But a martial artist was fundamentally different. It wasn’t strange for a Xiantian realm martial artist to not be married even at 100 years of age. Lin Wanshan didn’t know what sort of plans Lin Ming had for marriage, or if he even planned to. With a single word from Lin Wanshan, he could decide who a common Lin Family junior would have to marry. If they wanted to marry who they wanted, they would have to leave the family.

But as for something so important as Lin Ming’s marriage, that was something that Lin Wanshan had absolutely no power to influence. It would all be up to Lin Ming’s own choice.

Zhuang Fan sighed, then shook his head. He casually spoke a few words regarding Lin Ming’s age of engagement, but Lin Ming was destined to never marry into their Zhuang Family as a son-in-law. Their Zhuang Family simply couldn’t produce a daughter that was able to match up to Lin Ming. He guessed that every noble family in Sky Fortune City already had their eyes on him. As long as Lin Ming revealed the slightest bit of interest, all of the noble families would probably line up their daughters, waiting in line to deliver them up to Lin Ming, even willing to send them off as concubines.

………….

Lin Ming’s tent was in the center of the army camp. The arrangements inside were very simple, but actually very comfortable. There was a sturdy wooden cot that was covered with clean cotton sheets. Because it was pressed a bit too much, it was a little hard to sit on.

“Sit.” Lin Ming indicated the wooden cot as he spoke to Lan Yi.

“Sir Lin, my name is Zhou Xinyu. The name of Lan Yi was only my childhood nickname…” The reason that Lan Yi hadn’t given her true name was because she wanted to conceal her identity. But now that she was requesting something from Lin Ming, she naturally had to be honest in her intentions.

“Zhou Xinyu…” Lin Ming thought back and remembered that in Divine Phoenix Island’s joint talent training program, there was a girl with this name. She was one of the 50 human-step talents. “Miss Zhou is a disciple of the Moon Seizing Sect?”

Zhou Xinyu hesitated for a moment, then nodded. There was no longer any reason to hide her identity, and this was easily found out.

“I’m sorry, but could Miss Zhou tell me who destroyed the Moon Seizing Sect?” Lin Ming tried to make his tone as gentle as possible as he poured a pot of tea, in order to not aggravate her wounds.

As the topic of her sect’s destruction was brought up, a look of hatred mingled with sorrow in Zhou Xinyu’s eyes. She still vividly recalled that bloody day when her master had died a tragic death.

“They were all Revolving Core masters. Seven of them in total.” Zhou Xinyu spat out between clenched teeth.

Within the entire Moon Seizing Sect, only their Highest Elder had barely managed to break through to the Revolving Core realm. Even with several dozens of Xiantian masters combined together, none of them could block the slaughtering rampage of seven Revolving Core powerhouses – there was even one at the middle Revolving Core stage.

Lin Ming’s heart sank. With this extermination line-up, even the Seven Profound Valleys would face certain doom. Even Peacock Mountain and Falling Cloud Sect would suffer serious losses.

He let out a heavy breath and then continued, “And what matter does Miss Zhou have to discuss with me?”

“Mm… that is, I… I want to join Divine Phoenix Island. I… would like to ask that Sir Lin recommend me, if possible. I would like to have a chance to study Divine Phoenix Island’s core cultivation methods. I would be very grateful.” Zhou Xinyu started out a bit embarrassed, but afterwards just spoke her request in one go. She had originally planned to befriend Lin Ming and then slowly lay down her request, but now that the situation has become like this, there was no point in beating around the bush.

“You want to study the core cultivation methods?” Lin Ming furrowed his eyebrows. If it was simply a recommendation, then Lin Ming would easily be able to help. With Zhou Xinyu’s talent, it wouldn’t be too difficult to join Divine Phoenix Island.

However, if he wanted to recommend her to study the core cultivation methods, then that was something he wouldn’t be able to do.

Divine Phoenix Island had two main core cultivation method manuals, ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ as well as ‘Blue Luan Abstract Phantom Code’. These were the both legacies left behind by the ancient Phoenix Clan, they were incomparably precious.

These two cultivation methods were normally only passed down to core disciples. Ordinary disciples could only study the most superficial knowledge of them. Even Lin Ming, who hadn’t yet officially joined Divine Phoenix Island, was only taught the first layer of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. Not only that, but Lin Ming had also made a pledge on his heart of martial arts that he wouldn’t leak out this cultivation method.

This was because there were too many profound secrets contained within the, ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ as well as ‘Blue Luan Abstract Phantom Code’. As the legacies of the ancient Phoenix Clan, it was said that if one managed to cultivate them to the highest realm, one’s body would be like a phoenix, and they would be able to rebirth in a nirvana of flames, immortal and indestructible.

Such a precious ancient legacy was enough to cause many powerhouses to covet it, even with all the flaws they had.

The ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ and ‘Blue Luan Abstract Phantom Code’ were difficult to cultivate if one didn’t have the bloodline of the Vermillion Bird or Blue Luan. Of course, this didn’t mean that one couldn’t cultivate it entirely. In the history of Divine Phoenix Island, there was once an demonic man who cultivated fire-attribute cultivation methods, and had stolen away the Saintess of Divine Phoenix Island to plunder her Primordial Yin, so that he could double cultivate the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. Like this, a catastrophe was brought down upon Divine Phoenix Island.

But Divine Phoenix Island had learned from this grave mistake. From that point on, they had strictly controlled these secrets.

“I apologize, I cannot help you.” Lin Ming said, directly rejecting Lan Yi. “The core cultivation methods of Divine Phoenix Island are only passed down to the core disciples. If you could become a core disciple, then you don’t need my help to do so.”

Zhou Xinyu was stunned, and then her entire complexion was colored with disappointment. Core disciple… with her talent, the most she could be was an outer court disciple. There was no way she could compete against the inner court disciples, much less a core disciple.

Thinking of the vengeance she needed to take for her master and her sect, Zhou Xinyu absentmindedly asked, “Divine Phoenix Island will not pass on the core cultivation methods to inner court disciples?”

Lin Ming shook his head, “An inner court disciple can only learn the first few layers of the core cultivation methods. Divine Phoenix Island is very strict in the management of their core cultivation methods. Sorry, but I simply cannot help you…”

“Sir Lin… I…” Zhou Xinyu had a begging expression, but the words she wanted to say were caught in her throat. Her original intent was to produce a few Heaven Opening Pills as a reward for Lin Ming’s help.

But now it appeared that Heaven Opening Pills were useless. Lin Ming wasn’t lacking in Heaven Opening Pills. According to what Zhou Xinyu had heard, Lin Ming had already obtained three Heaven Opening Pills. Once Lin Ming stepped into the Houtian realm, there would probably be more.

A core disciple of Divine Phoenix Island probably received similar treatment to Lin Ming. To use a few Heaven Opening Pills in exchange for the treatment of a core disciple was simply too naïve.

Zhou Xinyu was aware that with her own talent, the most she could achieve would be becoming an inner court disciple; there was no way she would ever be able to learn the full core cultivation method manuals and enter into the Revolving Core realm. Divine Phoenix Island was too strong, a core disciple had a high chance of entering the Revolving Core realm, otherwise, this Revolving Core realm would be too worthless.

Did she really have to put out that…

If she gave it to Mu Qianyu, she might be able to trade it for a core disciple position. But… the price was too steep.

After the Moon Seizing Sect was destroyed, the treasure that they left behind was the hope of her master, as well as the hope for the future revival of the Moon Seizing Sect.

Without it, even if she became a core disciple and was able to learn the core cultivation methods, it would be too difficult to step into the Revolving Core realm.

But if she had it, then she wouldn’t be able to reach the Revolving Core realm as she wouldn’t have a high-grade cultivation method. If she didn’t reach the Revolving Core realm, she wouldn’t have the qualifications to avenge her master or rebuild the Moon Seizing Sect.

As Zhou Xinyu thought of this, her mind was torn…

“I’ve disturbed Sir Lin, excuse me.” Zhou Xinyu barely smiled, and then quietly left the tent.

As she left, Lin Ming saw her desolate back, and he suddenly sighed with emotion. He hesitated for a moment, then said, “I will bring this up with Divine Phoenix Island’s Miss Mu. However, what she does will depend on her.

Zhou Xinyu was happy. She hurriedly thanked Lin Ming and said, “Thank you Sir Lin, I will engrave this kindness within my mind.”

After Zhou Xinyu profusely thank him, she finally left. Lin Ming could only shake his head. The road of a martial artist was fraught with hardships and emotions. Talents such as Zhou Xinyu may seem like fairy maidens to a common mortal, but if they truly wished to reach the Revolving Core realm, they had to pay a great cost.

In order for a common martial artist to earn a few resources, they had to venture through lands filled with vicious beasts and risk their lives to hunt for precious materials. These materials were also what young and beautiful girls sought from the Seven Profound Valleys’ Acacia Faction. In order to reach the Pulse Condensation period and extend their lives, they would exchange their own virginity for the longer-lasting youth. These sect talents were the envy of countless others, in order to search for lucky opportunities, they would enter into dangerous lands and possibly die…

The road of martial artists seemed bright and attractive, but once one stepped onto it, it was full of thorns and perils. If one fell off for any reason, there was no more hope for them.

Zhou Xinyu had a wish and obsession to revive her sect and avenge her master. This obsession was truly worthy of Lin Ming’s pity and respect. However, at most, Lin Ming would only be able to mention this subject to Mu Qianyu; he couldn’t help her in any substantial way.

No longer thinking about these things, Lin Ming closed the tent curtains and then took out a spatial ring. This spatial ring was left behind by Bi Luo. After Lin Ming killed Bi Luo, he had only taken the spatial ring because he was in a hurry to return to the battlefield; he hadn’t had time to investigate what was inside.

Bi Luo had a limited status within the Seven Profound Valleys. Lin Ming didn’t have much hope that there would be anything within that was too valuable. He started with the mindset that it would be like looking for meat in a mosquito leg, and he began to remove the objects inside one at a time.

There were several medium-grade human-step treasures, as well as a high-grade human-step treasure sword and flexible armor. There were several bottles of high-grade pills for a Houtian realm martial artist to increase their cultivation, over 1000 true essence stones, and several jade slips.

There was no need to look at treasures like the flexible armor. To Lin Ming, these treasures were things he could just give away. As for the high-grade cultivation pills, those were barely up to standards. They were probably gifted by Ouyang Boyan, so it would be useful to keep them. As for the 1000 true essences tones, they were better than nothing.

Afterwards, Lin Ming picked up the jade slips and began to casually glance through them. Suddenly, he was surprised. Mm? There was a medium-grade earth-step auxiliary secret skill jade slip?

To a sect, core secret skills were the unique legacies of those sects. For instance, Divine Phoenix Island’s ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, and the Acacia Faction’s ‘Divine Acacia Power’ had no grade.

But there were some secret skills that were spread out and thus obtained a grade. A medium-grade earth-step cultivation method jade slip was equal to a top medium-grade earth-step treasure in value.

Initially when Lin Ming had learned the ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’, that had only been an incomplete medium-grade earth-step martial skill. But, the abstract principles found within were extremely profound. Although a medium-grade earth-step auxiliary secret skill was just a bit lower in value, it was more than enough to exchange for two Heaven Opening Pills.

“This Bi Luo, he was actually thinking of trade for two Heaven Opening Pills with this secret skill after he reached peak Houtian, and then breaking through to the Xiantian realm! How ambitious…”

Lin Ming didn’t think that Bi Luo’s treasure trove was so deep that it would have such a precious treasure.

As Lin Ming swept through the contents of the cultivation method, his heart immediately stirred. This was a set of appearance changing and concealment methods!

No wonder Bi Luo’s appearance changing technique and concealment skill had been so superb!

Chapter 338 – Speed of Life and Death

As Huang Zixuan saw Huang Sanping instantly suffer a major injury, his eyes turned red with rage, “Scoundrel! I’ll kill you!”

Now he would naturally kill Lin Ming first. However, just as Huang Zixuan’s eyes lit with a grim light and he was about to use his master stroke, his complexion instantly changed.

Huang Zixuan saw that another spear had appeared in Lin Ming’s hand. As Lin Ming grasped the long spear, his body erupted with true essence, the energy circulating within him to the limit, 20,000 jins of human strength bursting forth.

Sou!

The spear shot out, piercing forth like an arrow towards Huang Sanping. The air trembled, the wind howled, the power of his spear was enough to level a palace!

Huang Zixuan’s eyes were bloodshot, “You scoundrel, I’ll have you remember me!”

Huang Zixuan didn’t have time to deal with Lin Ming right now. He launched his movement technique and had to chase after the spear. Otherwise, if the severely wounded Huang Sanping who had been put into a coma was struck, he would die without a doubt.

“Go!”

Lin Ming sank. He grabbed the stunned Zhou Xinyu and rushed out of the camp.

If Lin Ming wanted to rescue Zhou Xinyu under the gaze of Hang Zixuan, this was the only way. Otherwise, with Lin Ming’s speed, it was impossible to escape from Huang Zixuan while bringing someone else. He could only strike at Huang Sanping and force Huang Zixuan to save him; this was their only chance at survival!

“Where are you going?”

At this time, Lin Ming suddenly heard a shout from above him, and then the howling of sword energy. The man who attacked him was the man who had stood with Huang Zixuan, the middle Houtian realm martial artist.

This middle Houtian martial artist felt that Lin Ming was strong, and only wanted to pin down Lin Ming and prevent him from escaping, letting Huang Zixuan return and kill Lin Ming himself. Thus, he had slashed out with a large amount of sword energy, wanting to force Lin Ming into a sieged position and blocking him from running.

“Out of my way!”

At this time, Lin Ming overflowed with killing intent. Whoever dared to stop him would die! He flicked his finger, the coiling dragon steel needle howled!

Boom boom boom!

The sword energies were completely shattered. The coiling dragon steel needle roared as it shot towards the middle Houtian martial artist, his complexion completely changed, paling. The man linked his hands together, and five true essence shields appeared before him. However, there was only a popping sound as the true essence shields blew up. When the last true essence shield was about to break, the coiling dragon steel needle exploded, purple thunder radiated out, and the man screamed. Half of his body was blown to bits, and he fell down from the sky.

Lin Ming didn’t even glance at him. Both of his feet moved at full speed towards the outside of the barrier array. After the coiling dragon steel needle had nearly killed the middle Houtian martial artist, it whistled as it caught up to Lin Ming, submerging back into his body.

With the Concept of Wind fused into his movements, Lin Ming’s body began to fly up. At that moment, Zhou Xinyu only felt Lin Ming pulling up her hand, the whirring wind in her ears. She looked down to see that her feet were getting farther and farther away from the ground, and she was incredulous as in a brief moment, she was suddenly dozens of feet up in the air. After steadying her mind from the series of electric brilliances that had made her dizzy, she finally realized that an impossible matter had occurred.

“We’re… flying… flying up?”

How was this possible?

Lin Ming could actually fly!?

This was clearly an ability that only a Xiantian master could have!

In the chaos, Zhou Xinyu no longer had any words to voice her thoughts. As she saw a great curtain of light approaching, her complexion changed; the barrier formation was ahead!

Lin Ming’s pupils narrowed. Although he didn’t look back, his perception was already locked onto the black-shrouded man. This fellow had already rescued Huang Sanping, and was now chasing him!

Time was extremely tight! If he stopped to attack the barrier array, even if it only took several breaths of time, the black-shrouded man would catch up!

“Boy, you cannot run away!” As Huang Zixuan chased Lin Ming from behind, he saw with his own eyes as Lin Ming brought Zhou Xinyu flying into the sky, and a inexplicable horror quickly passed over his face. “What sort of rare flying treasure does this boy have? Humph it doesn’t matter. With the barrier array formation supported by Third Brother, it will take him time to break it. I’ll capture this boy alive and take a good look at what secrets he has on his body!”

“Sir Lin, in… in front!”

Seeing Lin Ming not even slow down as he approached the barrier array, Zhou Xinyu’s pretty face drained of all blood. She thought it was impossible that Lin Ming hadn’t discovered the barrier array, but now it seemed that Lin Ming was even helplessly running into it!

His speed was too quick. From the time that Zhou Xinyu had felt that something was strange to the point that she spoke, it was already too late!

“Ahh!”

Zhou Xinyu screamed in panic as she closed both her eyes. At this speed, it was equal to crashing into the ground from thousands of feet high. If they didn’t die, they would at least be severely wounded!

Hu!

At the split second that Lin Ming and Zhou Xinyu dashed into the barrier array, the space in front of them seemed to have a strange distortion. Lin Ming and Zhou Xinyu flew through the barrier array like a swallow through smoke, rushing past, unimpeded!

Close behind Lin Ming in hot pursuit, Huang Zixuan had been counting on the barrier array to stop Lin Ming. But now, his eyes widened as he stared at this scene before him.

How was this possible!?

At this moment, on Lin Ming’s back, Zhou Xinyu had her eyes closed, and her face was pale as she screamed with all her might.

A girl’s scream contained a truly terrifying energy.

She had screamed out for several breaths of times before she found that something was wrong. She opened her eyes and saw the surrounding scenery rapidly blurring. They had apparently already made it outside the army camp.

They passed through the barrier array?

She turned her head to look. The barrier array was truly behind them!

“This… what… how… how did this happen?”

Zhou Xinyu was instantly placed in a confused state of mind… how had they managed to pass through?

At first, Lin Ming had saved her from a nearly impossible situation from under the watchful eyes of Huang Zixuan. Then, they had flown into the sky without help from any tools or treasures, and now they had flown past the barrier array without any hindrance!

As impossible events occurred one after another, Zhou Xinyu was overwhelmed. She could only look in incredulity at Lin Ming’s hand grabbing hers. From her angle, she could only see Lin Ming’s profile.

His face was expressionless. Whether she screamed or was turned silly, he remained unmoved, only rushing forwards. Through that entire series of life and death events that had caused Zhou Xinyu’s heart to stop one after another, Lin Ming had never lost his calm even once. His eyes that looked straight forward seemed to be as deep and profound as the stars in the night sky, giving off a sense of security and a feeling that he was someone she could rely on, as if he were an omnipotent being…

At that moment, turbulent waves began to surge in Zhou Xinyu’s heart…

…………………

“Damn, why was the barrier array malfunctioning at this time? Just what is Third Brother doing!?”

Huang Zixuan was enraged. He quickly attributed everything to a malfunction in the barrier array. His third brother was only the most basic and crude of array masters, but a situation in which there was a glitch in the array formation had never happened before.

As Huang Zixuan cursed his third brother as an incompetent mess, he launched his movement technique and rushed forth, wanting to cross through the barrier array. This sort of shoddy array formation naturally didn’t recognize individuals. If Huang Zixuan wanted to pass, he didn’t need to destroy it, but he still had to put in a decent amount of effort.

But now that the barrier array had failed, there was no need to waste so much time. He could directly rush through and save himself the effort.

Dozens of feet passed in a fleeting second.

Soon, as Huang Zixuan was about to break through the barrier array at full speed, he suddenly felt that something was wrong.

Mm?

He tried to make an emergency stop, but there wasn’t enough time. With a ‘peng’ sound like a piece of pork slapping against a cutting board, Huang Zixuan collided solidly against the barrier array. His head was knocked into confusion, and even his intestines seemed to be scrambled.

Seeing this, Zhou Xinyu’s eyes widened. She watched as Huang Zixuan struck the barrier array like a blind fly, spitting blood and limping down to the floor…

Zhou Xinyu’s mouth widened in surprise. What happened to Huang Zixuan?

Zhou Xinyu wanted to take a good look at just how this unusual and fortunate change of events occurred, but Lin Ming was too fast. In a blink of an eye, Huang Zixuan had disappeared into the endless night, invisible.

………………….

“You idiot!”

Huang Zixuan was furious. He tossed back a bunch of healing pills and screamed out, “Third Brother you idiotic fool! Hurry up and remove the array, we’ll catch up to him together!”

“Ah—a–!”

A high-pitched bird cry sounded out, and the golden-winged Heavenly Wind Eagle shot into the sky. Huang Zixuan, the handler, the severely wounded Huang Sanping, Huang Zixuan’s younger Third Brother, and a Houtian martial artist all leapt onto the golden-winged Heavenly Wind Eagle together, chasing after Lin Ming.

Heard the cry of the eagle, Zhou Xinyu panicked. She had been wondering how Huang Zixuan had found her so quickly, and it seemed as if the truth lay within the golden-winged Heavenly Wind Eagle!

Alas, this golden-winged Heavenly Wind Eagle which was her only means of transportation, as well as the beast that had protected her life, had actually become something that had almost killed her.

“Lin… Sir Lin… they’re riding the Golden Wing…”

As Zhou Xinyu worriedly spoke, she hadn’t even finished when she suddenly shut up. Her eyes widened as she saw a massive dragon-shaped beast with a 60 foot wingspan and a long tail, its entire body covered in shimmering scales, fly up from a deep dark mountain valley.

Its scales were like crimson fire, and its eyes were a deep glazed gold. Its teeth were sharp, and it gave off an aura that made one’s heart race! This was clearly a winged red dragon!

This… this is…

Zhou Xinyu gulped, her expression bitter. With the beast tide freely rampaging area, they had actually encountered such a high-grade vicious beast. This was normal, but for them to encounter such a beast at this time and have to fight it off, that was simply bad luck.

Zhou Xinyu didn’t know what to do. But at this time, Lin Ming yanked her hand, throwing her straight towards the Winged Flood Dragon.

“Roar!”

The bass dragon roar resounded throughout the world; the clouds split in half!

Zhou Xinyu was stunned. Lin Ming stepped onto the back of the Winged Flood Dragon, and then the Winged Flood Dragon spread open its massive wings. It was like a flaming red feathered arrow, directly piercing into the dark blue sky!

Zhou Xinyu was speechless with horror. Now that she stepped onto the solid back of the red dragon beast, she could hear the howling of the wind and the terrifying roars of the beast, like a saber cutting through grass. Just by the wind buffeting against her, one could imagine how fast this red dragon beast was flying!

‘This is… Sir Lin’s mount?’

‘It is… a Winged Flood Dragon?’

In the rush a moment ago, Zhou Xinyu wasn’t able to clearly recall the origins of this vicious beast. But when she calmed down a bit and had time to think, she suddenly remembered that she had read about this Winged Flood Dragon in the ancient texts. Its value was at least 10 times higher than the golden-winged Heavenly Wind Eagle! And after growing up, it would be a vicious beast equal to a Xiantian master!

She opened her mouth several times, but as she saw Lin Ming standing in front of her, a cold and indifferent expression on his face, she didn’t know what to say.

“What do you want to say?” Lin Ming suddenly turned his head, looking at Zhou Xinyu.

Chapter 345 – Reborn

Huang Sanping’s lips trembled, and his voice shook as he asked, “You… you are Lin Ming?”

Lin Ming glanced at Huang Sanping in surprise; he hadn’t expected that the mewling kid in front of him would guess his identity the moment before his own death. But, it wasn’t too difficult to guess. The strength he had just shown belonged to a sect’s absolute top talent, and this was also the territory of the Seven Profound Valleys. His name had been floating around for a while, ever since Divine Phoenix Island had announced him as their sole heaven-step talent.

This time, Lin Ming had no need to hide anything. He indifferently nodded and said, “That’s right.”

“So you were…” Huang Sanping’s frightened face bent up in an awkward smile. As he smiled, his face began to twitch, and it looked somewhere between an extremely ugly laugh and a cry.

As one of the geniuses on Divine Phoenix Island’s joint talent training program, how could he never have heard the name of Lin Ming, the only heaven-step talent that was listed. A heaven-step talent could enjoy treatment equal to a core disciple of Divine Phoenix Island.

How many people envied?

How many people were jealous?

Huang Sanping had always been an extremely jealous man. When he had heard of this, jealousy had flooded his entire body, incapacitating him. He had always kept a thought in the back of his mind that he would take revenge on Lin Ming one day, but he never thought that…

Genius? How ridiculous!

Huang Sanping had been labeled a genius ever since he was a child. Now, that title, in front of this monster, was nothing more than a joke. In front of this monster, he didn’t even have the slightest ability to resist. Huang Sanping always thought that if he could obtain the treasures left behind by the Moon Seizing Sect, then the future world would be his for the taking. He would become the heroic lead of the entire Sky Spill Continent. But now, all his hopes and dreams seemed incomparably comical, a complete farce.

A monster like Lin Ming was able to swallow the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal with a mere Pulse Condensation period cultivation. Against this person, how could he possibly compare to him in any measure?

Lin Ming looked at Zhou Xinyu and said, “Do you want to do it yourself?”

Lin Ming assumed that the resentment and grudges that ran between Huang Sanping and Zhou Xinyu were deep. If she finished this by her own hands, it would be easier for her to clear her thoughts and spirit.

Zhou Xinyu glared at Huang Sanping with hate seething in her eyes. Although Huang Sanping was severely injured, that still didn’t resolve the hostility in her heart. She had almost been captured by him. And if she were, she would have suffered a life of endless torment, being humiliated daily.

Thinking this, Zhou Xinyu shuddered.

Zhou Xinyu grit her teeth, took out a treasure longsword, and stabbed Huang Sanping’s heart.

Blood shot out, and Huang Sanping’s eyes turned lifeless. As Lin Ming saw this, he sighed; yet another genius had fallen from the skies.

On the path of martial artists, a mediocre person may not have a good life, but a genius could die a miserable death at any time.

Of course, to a sect at the level of Divine Phoenix Island, Huang Sanping couldn’t even be considered a genius; he would have been long eliminated before the Xiantian realm.

The Xiantian realm, Revolving Core realm, and even higher realms above, every stage had a vast number of martial artists that were eliminated from advancement. To talents that were even more amazing and extraordinary than Huang Sanping – like Qin Wuxin – they would be stopped after the Xiantian realm. To talents even more outstanding than Qin Wuxin – like Jiang Baoyun – they might be eliminated from advancing after reaching the Revolving Core realm.

As for talents even more exceptional than Jiang Baoyun – like Mu Qianyu – they might be stopped after becoming a Peerless Emperor…

The path of martial arts was infinite and endless. Lin Ming could feel in his soul that if he didn’t seize every chance to enhance his cultivation, then one day, the destiny of being eliminated would fall upon his own head!

After witnessing the inimitable war within the Realm of the Gods, Lin Ming’s scope of vision had already transcended Sky Spill Continent and stood on a higher level. He would never be complacent with any achievements that he attained.

He knew that he was just a frog in the well that had taken a brief scenic trip on the outside before returning. Even when it came to the most basic of Body Transformation’s realms, the Tempering Marrow boundary, he had only traced the very edge of it.

Lin Ming guessed that in order to fully complete Tempering Marrow, he would need thousands upon thousands of Heaven Opening Pills.

Although the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal was strong, a dozen or so of those crystals could not match up to several thousand Heaven Opening Pills. With the help of half a Shattered Demon Heart Crystal, Lin Ming’s Tempering Marrow was only semi-complete. Even with a dozen more Shattered Demon Heart Crystals, it would still be nearly impossible to thoroughly complete Tempering Marrow.

However, in the path of Tempering Marrow, the quality was much more important than quantity. Normally, the first time a pill was eaten would have the greatest effect. Afterwards, the effects would increasingly weaken every time. Although the Heaven Opening Pill was good, after one or two thousand, Lin Ming would reach the limit of its effectiveness; anything more than that wouldn’t help.

The Shattered Demon Heart Crystal was a top-level high quality potently powerful pill in comparison to the Heaven Opening Pill, but what effects would there still be if he ate 10?

Lin Ming wasn’t sure, but even in a bad situation, he should still be able to complete 60-70% of Tempering Marrow. With that success, he might not even need to fear Ouyang Boyan.

He might even kill him instead.

If this idea of Lin Ming’s was known by other martial artists, they might have died from vomiting blood in anger. The incomparably precious Heaven Opening Pill was actually considered being taken in units of 1000; if they weren’t struck to death by thunder, they would be irritated to death.

After tidying all of Huang Zixuan’s followers, Lin Ming returned to Zhou Xinyu and begun to search through the spatial rings.

Lin Ming didn’t have much hope that these people would have anything too interesting; a third-grade genius’ belongings could only be considered change to him now.

After looking through everything, the only objects of notice were several high-grade human-step treasures, the Moon Seizing Sect’s cultivation method jade slips, several thousand low-grade true essence stones, and also some bottles of pills. Through everything, there wasn’t even a single Heaven Opening Pill.

He didn’t know that the reason Huang Sanping had gotten tangled into this mess was because he had given his Heaven Opening Pill to Huang Zixuan to swallow.

The cultivation method jade slips were all given back to Zhou Xinyu. Naturally, he had no need for things like this. He kept the treasures and pills, for future use or if he needed to give them to anyone. As for the true essence stones, they were kept for spending money. As for the rest, Lin Ming didn’t have much hope, and his Lin Family didn’t need it either. He was preparing to throw it away, but at this moment he took another casual glance and found something interesting.

This wasn’t Huang Zixuan’s or Huang Sanping’s, but it belonged to the weakest eagle handler. It was a very ancient jade slip that contained some sort of technique called the Psychic Soul Art.

In summary, it was a secret method to communicate with beasts. This eagle handler was a complete mess when it came to martial talent and cultivation, and at 40 to 50 years of age had only reached an early Pulse Condensation cultivation, and that was also relying on pills to forcefully raise it. His combat strength wasn’t better than a common martial artist; in fact, it was even worse.

However, because he had a talent that was able to communicate with beasts, he was appointed by the Moon Seizing Sect to handle the golden-winged Heavenly Wind Eagle. It seemed that this eagle handler’s talent had a great connection to this jade slip.

Although this jade slip didn’t seem very practical, it looked like a lot of fun. Thus, Lin Ming readily placed it in his spatial ring.

“Let’s go, we’ll look for a cave to rest in. I have to meditate and restore my true essence.” Lin Ming said to Zhou Xinyu.

“Mm.” Zhou Xinyu timidly nodded. The series of events that just occurred was too shocking for her. Lin Ming, with his Pulse Condensation cultivation had swallowed the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal and hadn’t died. Not only that, but afterwards he had revived and killed Huang Zixuan in less than 10 breaths of time!

However, there were things that confused Zhou Xinyu. The Shattered Demon Heart Crystal was supposedly a top quality miracle medicine that needed one to be at least a Xiantian master to take; its medicinal efficacy could be imagined. Since Lin Ming swallowed half of one at only a cultivation of the Pulse Condensation period, his cultivation should have rapidly risen, directly breaking through to the Houtian realm. But how did he only advance by such a small level that he was stuck in the late Pulse Condensation period?

Zhou Xinyu really couldn’t understand this, but she tactfully decided not to ask.

The two quickly found a distantly hidden mountain cave.

At this time, the sun had just risen.

Inside the mountain cave there was a deep pool that came from a steadily flowing mountain stream; it was very cool and light. Lin Ming said, “I’m going to take a bath, you can wait for me at the entrance.”

Lin Ming’s entire body was currently covered in blood and shorn off black and red skin. His entire body was also in rags. Not taking a bath as soon as he could would be a travesty.

“Mm.” Zhou Xinyu nodded, and then politely waited at the entrance.

Lin Ming finished his bath in a quarter of an hour, and then changed into some loose and unlined clothing from his spatial ring. He had also eaten up some strong true essence supplementary pills, and meditated for a short period of time. The true essence in his body was nearly restored, and the Heretical God Force’s compressed true essence reserves were at maximum capacity.

Then, Lin Ming called Zhou Xinyu into the cave.

When Zhou Xinyu saw Lin Ming after he had trade his clothes and washed off all the bloody scabs and torn skin from his body, she was stunned.

After the preliminary Tempering Marrow, Lin Ming’s looks had changed beyond recognition. Underneath the bloody scabs was the tenderest skin, delicate like a newborn babe. His entire body seemed to be brimming with potent vigor, and the slightly bulging and protruding muscles of his body only seemed to accentuate his healthiness and give him an extremely symmetrical and beautiful appearance, just like a graceful cheetah.

His stature had raised some, making him seem even more righteous and tall.

There were even subtly significant changes to his features. Originally, Lin Ming seemed valiant and noble, but in truth that was because there was a sharp aura that came from his forehead. In terms of Lin Ming’s looks, he couldn’t have been considered too outstanding, but now, after Lin Ming had been reborn, his eyebrows were sharp like swords, his eyes shone like the infinite stars in the sky, and his face seemed to be like the most valuable jade that had been carved by a saber. He was simply a jade-like god, yet not losing any of his sharp fortitude and masculine handsomeness.

All with the simple and unlined blue clothes that clung to his tight and compact body, as he stood illuminated against the rising sun of the morning, and the rays of the dawn sprinkled upon his comely appearance. He seemed to have an ethereal sense of beauty.

All of this caused Zhou Xinyu to fall into a silly trance.

After several breaths, Zhou Xinyu finally came to her senses. She then haltingly said, “Sir Lin… I… I’m sorry for what I did. I thought you died, so…”

Zhou Xinyu was naturally referring to when she had stabbed Lin Ming’s chest with her dagger. Now looking back at it, Zhou Xinyu only thought she was an incompetent fool, she simply had no merits to speak of.

“Forget about it. I know that you were well-intentioned in your actions. But actually, about the Moon Seizing Sect’s hidden treasures, I was wondering if Miss Zhou could tell me?” Lin Ming’s gaze swept past Zhou Xinyu. When Zhou Xinyu had stabbed him, the truth was that he could have dodged. But, he still had finished tempering his marrow with the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal. He also didn’t want to prematurely quicken the true essence stored within the Heretical God Seed; that was the last of his strength.

The reason that Lin Ming had let Zhou Xinyu freely stab him was because he had enough confidence in his own body’s defense after the preliminary Tempering Marrow phase.

“The hidden treasure…” As Zhou Xinyu heard Lin Ming mention this, her face was full of a complex color. She didn’t think there would be a day when the treasures that her master had entrusted to her to revive the Moon Seizing Sect would be personally given to an outsider by her.

Chapter 356 – The Birthday Banquet Begins

Divine Phoenix Island was extremely powerful. They did not lack in those that pretended to be humble, nor did they lack in talents. However, nobody knew just how many of these talents were truly loyal to Divine Phoenix Island.

The beautiful woman didn’t fully approve of Lin Ming just because of her words. But, she could affirm in her heart that Lin Ming wasn’t someone who faked appearances.

A truly ungrateful person that forgot grace and held no virtues, well, their promises were useless. As for those righteous individuals that didn’t betray their mortality, there was no need to have them make any promise. Thus, the beautiful woman gave Lin Ming the greatest degree of freedom equal to a secret disciple.

“First you will apprentice under Yu’er. She will also be the one to hand down and teach you the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle. This old woman is called Yuhuang. Later, you will also call this old woman Master Ancestor Yuhuang! If you can blossom in radiance within the year or maybe if you reach the Houtian realm before 17 years of age, then I will personally teach you.”

The beautiful woman spoke her words and then left. Mu Qianyu bowed to see her off, and Lin Ming also deeply bowed like a good disciple.

In a flash, only Lin Ming and Mu Qianyu were left in the hall. The serious expression that Mu Qianyu had quickly faded, and as she looked at Lin Ming, she couldn’t help but laugh.

Lin Ming subconsciously traced his nose, sheepishly saying, “What makes Miss Mu smile?”

“What did you just call me?” Mu Qianyu winked, grinning as she sardonically looked at Li Ming.

“Ah…” Lin Ming was a bit embarrassed, “Master Mu.”

“Who are you calling Master Mu? Just call me Master. I didn’t think that Master would place you under me as my disciple. In fact, you are my very first disciple. Divine Phoenix Island has over 30 core disciples, and around 20 of those were from the Vermillion Bird Faction and another dozen or so from the Blue Lian Faction. All of those disciples have masters that are Revolving Core powerhouses, and I’m the only one whose cultivation is below the Revolving Core realm!” Mu Qianyu sounded a bit excited. The first time being someone else’s master always gave a very unusual feeling.

Lin Ming was utterly speechless. He thought that being Mu Qianyu’s disciple was an outlandish and strange turn of events. In truth, he was hoping to apprentice under an elder. For instance, that old lady Yuhuang.

It looked like the only route he had was to show off his talents as soon as possible and attract the attention of that old woman Yuhuang, so he could apprentice under her and quickly get rid of this crappy status.

Mu Qianyu noticed Lin Ming’s astonished expression and that it was somewhat funny. She continued to say, “Alright, I won’t mess with you. I know your status is only temporary. I’ll be honest with you. You haven’t yet obtained the approval of my master. Although I’ve already spoken of your talent to Master, seeing is better than believing. Whether it is entering the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm or my senior uncle’s 400th birthday banquet, both are opportunities for you to display your talent. The sooner you can enter as a disciple of my master and become a direct disciple, the more advantageous it will be for you.

The 10 direct disciples of Divine Phoenix Island were all taught by top masters like old lady Yuhuang. Although Mu Qianyu was a monstrous genius, in terms of being someone’s master, she simply didn’t have the experience.

Lin Ming said, “I have to attend Tianguang Revered Master’s celebratory birthday banquet?”

“Mm. Since you’re a core disciple, you naturally have to participate in the birthday banquet. It is also a process for my master to approve of you. Remember, although you will be entering the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, there are also good areas and bad areas. One kind is for the ordinary group which can only enter around the periphery of the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm. As for the other, they may enter the main Ancient Phoenix central hall. The difference between the two is astronomical, and there is a limit of 16 individuals that may enter the main hall. 10 of those will be the direct disciples, leaving only 6 spots for the core disciples. If you can’t display a great enough talent, then one of those spots won’t be given to you.”

“So it’s like this…” Lin Ming’s mind stirred. Naturally, he didn’t want to miss out on this Ancient Phoenix central hall.

“Now return. And don’t underestimate everyone else here. They are all talents that are much higher than anyone from the Seven Profound Valleys. Even if Jiang Baoyun was placed here, he wouldn’t be anything special.” As Mu Qianyu spoke, she flipped her hand and two red jade slips appeared in her palm.

“This is the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ jade slip. Take good care of it and definitely don’t lose it somewhere!”

Lin Ming took a deep breath and solemnly took the jade slip. This was the core cultivation of Divine Phoenix Island, its value could be imagined.

Although there was most likely a special mark on this jade slip to track its location, for Mu Qianyu to give this jade slip to him like this was already a reflection of the enormous trust she held in him.

……………..

That night, the moon hung bright in the sky. Lin Ming sat in the garden of his little building, tranquilly meditating over the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’.

Of the two jade slips, one recorded the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, and the other contained insights from when Mu Qianyu had cultivated it. Not only were they the experiences of Mu Qianyu, but also the experiences that many other seniors had left behind, all of them reorganized by Mu Qianyu and completely engraved onto the jade slips. When she had been cultivating, she had also held a jade slip in her hands. Whenever she thought of something useful, she would record it.

Those things that were recorded in the jade slip were all mostly related to the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. There were some supplementary materials, some skills, some analyses on how to make a better breakthrough, and other such experiences. This small jade slip was the accumulated wisdom of generations of wisdom.

“Good stuff!” Lin Ming couldn’t help but exclaim.

Although the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ was a top cultivation method, it was still incomplete. If one didn’t have these supplementary materials, it would be even more difficult to cultivate.

Lin Ming used a full half hour to skim through the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ and then laid down the jade slip, rubbing his forehead. The ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ was shocking; it was even more terrifying than when he had first cultivated the ‘Heretical God Force’.

According to the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, if one filled in the empty spots and restored this cultivation to the full glory of the Ancient Phoenix Clan – and also cultivate it to the highest levels with the pure bloodline of the Ancient Phoenix – one could rebirth themselves in the fires of nirvana.

After nine nirvanas, they could reach Perfection of this cultivation, becoming immortal and indestructible.

Even the two Supreme Elders’ memories that Lin Ming had inherited didn’t dare to boast about any cultivation like this. The senior that left behind the Sorcerer Pagoda also lived for tens of thousands of years, but in the end was unable to escape the samsara of life and death, eventually leaving the mortal coil after failing his closed door seclusion.

However, considering the characteristics of the phoenix itself, this ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ didn’t seem to be like empty talk. Of course, whether or not any of this was true couldn’t be verified. To complete the entire Ancient Phoenix Clan’s secret technique was simply a dream.

As Lin Ming’s conscious was immersed within the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, he also quickly entered into the ethereal martial intent state, sealing off his six senses and letting the flow of time drift past him.

The rich fire origin energy flowed into Lin Ming’s body, forming a vortex of origin energy that swirled around him. This was the rich fire-attribute origin energy of the Parasol Tree Pavilion; if one practiced the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ here, they would have twice the result with half the effort.

After the origin energy entered Lin Ming’s body, it was all absorbed by the Heretical God Seed without even the least bit leaking out. It could be said that Lin Ming’s body was a bottomless pit; whatever went in, wouldn’t come out.

Even Mu Qianyu had been shocked by Lin Ming’s talent at fire-attribute cultivation methods. She had called him the ‘child of flame’.

The Heretical God Seed began to excitedly stir, and the Flame Essence that revolved around the Heretical God Seed began to howl. After some time, an invisible ring of fire rippled outwards from Lin Ming, quickly spreading. This invisible ring of fire was fast like a gust of wind, rustling all of the parasol tree leaves of the forest.

Those that lived near Lin Ming’s little building were mostly Vermillion Bird Faction core disciples, and they were extremely sensitive to fire origin energy fluctuations. As the felt the fire origin energy blowing in the wind, they were surprised.

Just what was that?

Everything had happened too fast; they didn’t have time to investigate just what the source of that fire origin energy was. They released their senses to detect the source, but after being unable to find anything, eventually gave up.

The fire origin energy gradually faded. Lin Ming let out a long breath and opened his eyes. He had finally reached Perfection of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ cultivation method’s first layer!

If it wasn’t for too many pill toxins being left in his meridians, then reaching Perfection of this cultivation method’s first layer would have already been enough to help Lin Ming break through to the peak of Pulse Condensation.

From the Pulse Condensation period to the Houtian realm and Xiantian realm, the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ was no longer applicable to help him advance. However, this ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ seemed as if it were tailor made for his body, perfectly complementing with the Heretical God Force and allowing Lin Ming’s cultivations to increase by leaps and bounds. In addition to Lin Ming’s ethereal martial intent, his martial talent no longer hindered him.

Lin Ming cultivated for the entire night until early the next morning. As the day dawned, the entire Parasol Tree Pavilion was bustling with lively activity; today was Tianguang Revered Master’s 400th birthday banquet.

A Revolving Core martial artist could live up to 500 to 600 years old. As they only had a few century birthdays in their life, naturally they had to make grand arrangements.

The Senior-apprentice Brother Zhang that lived across from Lin Ming knocked on his door in the morning and began to talk to him about the banquet and the rules he needed to follow. His superiors had already informed him that he needed to bring Lin Ming to attend the banquet.

“For this banquet, eight great sects have arrived to attend the celebrations. There are more than 10 Revolving Core masters and 100 Xiantian masters. Nearly everyone else that isn’t a Xiantian master is a core disciple of their sect, and each one has talent comparable to a monstrous genius. Heh, such a great scene, let alone you, even I rarely see this. Don’t make a fuss about everything just because you’re a newbie, otherwise you’ll lose face.”

As Zhang Zhen spoke, he looked over Lin Ming’s clothing to see if there were any faults. Since eight great sects had gathered together, everything had become a matter of the sect’s honor. Naturally, no one could slack off in any aspect.

Lin Ming smiled and nodded. Although this Senior-apprentice Brother Zhang was a bit arrogant and overly stiff, his heart actually wasn’t too bad. These days he had taught Lin Ming many of the rules and customs of Divine Phoenix Island.

“Those that can enter the banquet stage are already famous characters. You’re a bit young and your cultivation is also low, and you’re even a new disciple, so there shouldn’t be anyone that is willing to take the initiative to challenge you. Just have a good time and eat everything you can. This birthday banquet has the best feast with delicacies from everywhere. If you eat a big meal, it will be equivalent to many years of hard earned cultivation for a common martial artist.”

“Also, if someone challenges you and they are a bit older, you don’t have to bother with them. There will be some senior-apprentice brothers that will stand up for you. You can compare skills with someone who’s close to your level though, but don’t go beyond that. Understand?”

“I understand.” Lin Ming didn’t refute Zhang Zhen’s words. The scenario that no one would take initiative to challenge him was only Zhang Zhen’s wishful thinking. As Lin Ming had walked down the road these past days, he could feel the gaze of others on him. There were disciples of Thundercrest Sect, and also disciples of Storm Valley.

Lin Ming didn’t know any of these people. They were probably ordered to bother him at the behest of others after arriving at Divine Phoenix Island.

Zhang Zhen looked at the time and said, “The birthday banquet will begin in half an hour. Let’s go over now.”

Chapter 357 – To See Blood

Among the countless dangerous and magnificent peaks, there was one peak covered with thick green bamboo that was dozens of feet high.

Within this green bamboo forest, there was a lake with clear rippling water. On this lake was a green hall that seemed to be carved from jade. This was the land of the Blue Luan Faction – Blue Luan Palace. Tianguang Revered Master was a Vice Island Master of Divine Phoenix Island, and was also a Great Elder of the Blue Luan Faction. His 400th year birthday banquet would be held here.

As Lin Ming arrived at Blue Luan Palace with Zhang Zhen, less than a third of the seats were filled. Most of them were juniors, and not even the direct disciples of the sects had arrived yet.

“Little Junior-apprentice Sister, that is Lin Ming.”

At a corner of Blue Luan Palace’s square, Zhan Yunjian was pointing at Lin Ming as he spoke to a purple-clothed girl. He wasn’t afraid that Lin Ming would find him looking at him, because it wasn’t anything out of the ordinary.

“16 year old late Pulse Condensation period? Not bad.” The purple-clothed girl stroked her smooth and pointed chin as she gazed at her opponent for this banquet, her words sounding a bit old.

Zhan Yunjian wanted to laugh. He thought to himself, wasn’t this little girl only 17 years old?

“Mm, that’s right. He is a junior of Divine Phoenix Island who is well regarded by Fairy Maiden Qianyu. However, Divine Phoenix Island is a bit lacking in talent these days. Ever since the Saint rank talents Fairy Maiden Qianyu and Fairy Maiden Bingyun appeared, there hasn’t been any outstanding heroic elite in the current young generation. Even the Vermillion Bird Faction chief disciple Mu Dingshan and the Blue Luan Faction chief disciple Mu Xiaoqing aren’t any better than the direct disciples of the seven sects from the Five Element Region.” As Zhan Yunjian spoke, he sighed, “Divine Phoenix Island has really had a great stroke of luck. Even if the next few generations of Divine Phoenix Island are all failures, as long as Mu Qianyu and Mu Bingyun exist, then Divine Phoenix Island will prosper for the next several hundred years.”

In the minds of the many young heroes and elites, a Saint level talent was like an unattainable peak that they could never approach. Even the arrogant Zhan Yunjian had to acknowledge the difference between him and a Saint level talent. This sort of talent would only appear in a fourth-grade sect every hundred years; it was stroke of fate that couldn’t be forced.

After listening to Zhan Yunjian, the purple-clothed girl smiled, extremely bright and happily.

“Mm? Why are you smiling?” Zhan Yunjian asked.

“Hehe, I’m just smiling, it’s nothing.” The purple-clothed girl was clearly hiding something. A 17 year old girl had limited trust, and her mood was written all over her face.

Zhan Yunjian was puzzled; what caused this little girl to be so happy?

Was she implying that the Thundercrest Sect also had a Saint level talent?

As he thought of this, Zhan Yunjian’s expression changed. Then, he thought of it some more and shook his head. ‘It’s unlikely. The seven sects of the Five Element Region all closely monitor each other; even I’m familiar with the direct disciple of the Thundercrest Sect. If they have a Saint level talent then it’s impossible that I wouldn’t have heard a rumor of it.’

As Zhan Yunjian thought to himself, he wasn’t too sure in his heart. If this was true, then the balance between the seven great sects of the Five Element Region would be broken. Once a Saint level talent grew up, it would be hard to find a worthy opponent for them!

After half an hour passed, more and more people began filtering into Blue Luan Palace. Many important figures began arriving one after another. Even in a fourth-grade sect, Revolving Core masters weren’t too common.

Tianguang Revered Master finally arrived. He wore a long green robe, and he had a three foot long white beard. His emitted a very calm and extraordinary temperament.

Behind him followed several disciples, and even Mu Qianyu was among them. As Lin Ming saw Mu Qianyu, he was stunned for a bit.

‘Mm… something feels off?’

As he noticed her blue clothing, Lin Ming suddenly realised that this woman was Mu Qianyu’s younger sister, Mu Bingyun. He had heard that Mu Qianyu and Mu Bingyun were twin sisters, but normally there would be some differences even between twins. However Mu Qianyu and Mu Bingyun seemed almost entirely alike; there wasn’t even a mark on their face to distinguish between them.

There was only a slight difference between their temperaments. It seemed that Mu Bingyun was a bit less noble, a bit icier, and a bit more indifferent.

Throughout the entire time, Mu Bingyun silently followed behind Tianguang Revered Master.

As if it were arranged, right after Tianguang Revered Master arrived, the old Revolving Core masters of the eight sects soon followed. The front door opened wide, and an old man in a red robe walked in with a group of disciples. This old man’s entire face was red all over, and his steps were light. He and his group had a ball of sacred flames embroidered on their chests – these were all disciples from the Sunfire Sect.

“Haha, Mu Tianguang, how have you been? You haven’t changed in such a long time!” The old man smiled. If this old man was able to call Tianguang Revered Master by his full name, then he was naturally a character on the same level as Tianguang Revered Master.

“Haha, I didn’t think the Sunfire Sect Sovereign would personally come. This old man truly has face!” Mu Tianguang cupped his fists together. Obviously, he and the Sunfire Sect Sovereign were old friends.

As the two old men greeted each other and exchanged some small talk, Lin Ming noticed that there was a red-robed girl following behind the Sunfire Sovereign. She looked around 18-19 years old, and her cultivation was at the early Houtian realm. She was the girl known as the Sunfire Princess, Huo Ruyan.

At this point, all eyes had gathered on Huo Ruyan, even more so than the Sunfire Sovereign. After all, the majority of those present were young heroes and elites. A high level figure like the Sunfire Sovereign had no relation to them, so they wouldn’t pay attention to someone like him. But as for another young heroic elite like Huo Ruyan, she was someone that everyone noticed. After all, a bit later from now, they might have to challenge her in a contest.

As the disciples of the Sunfire Sect took their seats, they were soon followed by those from the Thundercrest Sect. What surprised Lin Ming was that even the Thundercrest Sect Sovereign himself had personally come.

It stood to reason that a normal Revolving Core master would come to this birthday banquet, but a Sovereign wouldn’t personally attend. It had to be known that there were around 20 some high-level figures like Tianguang Revered Master in the great sects of the Five Element Region and the South Horizon Region. If the sect Sovereigns were to attend all the century birthday celebrations of these figures, they would have to make a trip every five years. Making such a long and distant journey was an arduous event, and it wasn’t like the various sect Sovereigns didn’t have anything else to do.

After the Thundercrest Sect arrived, those from the Deep Earth Sect, Arctic Ice Palace, and Golden Bell Mountain also arrived. Most of those that came were Sovereigns of their sect, and the worst among them were Vice Sovereigns, this really surprised Lin Ming.

Did Tianguang Revered Master really have such great face? A century birthday celebration actually had so many Sovereigns in attendance?

Finally, the last one to appear was the old lady Yuhuang of Divine Phoenix Island. As an Island Master of Divine Phoenix Island and also the leader of the Vermillion Bird Faction, old lady Yuhuang had a status that was even higher than Tianguang Revered Master. All the Sovereigns cupped their hands together. Of the entire audience present, old lady Yuhuang was the strongest; no one dared to disrespect her.

However, old lady Yuhuang had a very unpleasant expression. She gave a few casual smiles, and then sat in the seat of honor, not speaking as an awkward silence and sullen atmosphere floated around her.

Tianguang Revered Master was a bit embarrassed. He stood up, raised his glass and said, “Everyone who has arrived today has shown me the highest honor. First, I will raise a cup to you all!”

As Tianguang Revered Master spoke, he drank a toast to all the guests and the guests all raised their glasses too, offering a number of birthday congratulations and speeches. Then, the atmosphere of the banquet was revived.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but whisper, “How come High Master Yuhuang is looking at the eight sect Sovereigns with such a dour expression?”

Zhang Zhen, who was sitting near Lin Ming, heard his question. He reluctantly said, “I don’t know why, but I guess it’s because the talks of the alliance didn’t go too well…”

“Alliance?” Lin Ming was stunned, and then immediately understood. “An alliance to go against the South Sea Demon Region?”

“Mm, yes.”

Lin Ming had a flash of insight. No wonder so many Sovereigns and Vice Sovereigns had arrived. They actually came to discuss such an important matter. It seemed that Tianguang Revered Master’s birthday banquet was just a ruse, and the truth was that they came to discuss an alliance to resist the South Sea Demon Region.

A war between superpowers at the rank of Divine Phoenix Island and the South Sea Demon Region wasn’t like the wars between two small countries. Just because they declared war on each other didn’t mean they would immediately begin. Even though these two great powers had decided to engage each other, there were still many considerations and preparations that had to be made. Before, Divine Phoenix Island had drawn in the 19 third-grade sets, and now it seemed they were even trying to draw in the fourth-grade sects from the Five Element Region. The situation had already escalated to this degree. It was probable that the South Sea Demon Region was also looking for their own allies!

Lin Ming said, “If Divine Phoenix Island is defeated, then would the Five Element Region be able to live their future days in peace? Don’t they know about the concept of co-interdependence?”

Zhang Zhen stared at Lin Ming like he was an idiot, obviously looking down on Lin Ming’s shallow experience. “What do you mean co-interdependence? Divine Phoenix Island is millions of miles away from the Five Element Region. Even if it was when Silent Demon Emperor City still existed, the Five Element Region didn’t suffer a disaster. The reason they came here is to see if we could offer conditions to these old fellows’ satisfaction. Now that the talks have broken down, High Master Yuhuang isn’t feeling too happy about the situation.”

“So it’s like this…” Lin Ming was already used to Zhang Zhen looking down on him. But it didn’t matter, he really didn’t know anything about the Five Element Region.

Zhang Zhen said, “High Master Yuhuang has a very ardent and strong personality. If you are good to her then she is friendly to everyone. But, if she doesn’t feel comfortable, then she doesn’t care about giving anyone face. You can see from her expression that she’s not hiding anything at all. It looks like this banquet is going to be a lively one.”

“Mm? Lively?”

“Hehe, do you think that High Master Yuhuang won’t vent her fire here? If matters of the alliance had come to a pleasant agreement, then the atmosphere of the banquet would be enjoyable. But now that things have gone south, it seems that when we compare skills I’ll have to be serious; even blood might spill now.” As Zhang Zhen spoke, he seemed to be filled with excitement.

“Uh… will it come that?” Lin Ming’s expression changed as he craned his neck.

“Heh, just wait and see. High Master Yuhuang is not in a pleasant mood. If anyone causes her to lose anymore face today, they might anger her at their own peril. Just look at Senior-apprentice Brother Mu Dingshan’s appearance.” Zhang Zhen winked with his eyes.

Lin Ming glanced at Mu Dingshan and saw that he really did have an extremely bitter and pained expression.

“Does Senior-apprentice Brother Mu not have confidence in himself?”

“How can he have confidence like this? Senior-apprentice Brother is fierce, and he’s no worse than any of the other direct disciple of the Five Element Region, but now it’s one against eight. Oh, well with the Blue Luan Faction’s Mu Xiaoqing, that makes it two against eight. How can they resist so many of them? Now that High Master Yuhuang is so angry, losing like this will mean a miserable future for them.”

“The direct disciples of the Five Element Region aren’t some random weaklings. Even if Senior-apprentice Brother Mu put forth his full strength, it isn’t necessarily true that he’ll defeat them. Since he’s going to be going all-out, it won’t be strange to see blood spill.”

Chapter 364 – Trap

“You disgusting pig, watch where your eyes are going!” Song Xiaoyue said with a true essence sound transmission. Naturally, she could not say such harsh words out loud.

“Hehe, little lady, what’s wrong with someone looking at your body? Is it off limits? How are you going to stop me? If you were my wife then I’d let you manage me, but you’re not. Divine Phoenix Island has so many beautiful women, it’s such a shame that they are all wasted. How about you marry into our Deep Earth Sect?”

Shi Hanshan’s words caused Song Xiaoyue to explode into an apoplectic rage. Especially the ‘it’s such a shame that they are all wasted’. Just what did he take the female disciples of Divine Phoenix Island for?

“I’ll kill you!”

Song Xiaoyue gave a cold humph and then a longsword appeared in her hands. She thrust straight towards Shi Hanshan!

She immediately used the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, conjuring a shower of flames that looked like gorgeous fireworks, bombarding Shi Hanshan.

Boom boom boom!

Shi Hanshan created a thick brown wall to block all of Song Xiaoyue’s attacks. This brown wall weathered Song Xiaoyue’s barrage of attacks like a leaf swaying in a storm. Every time it seemed as if it would break, but it would always bounce back.

After 20 to 30 moves had passed, Song Xiaoyue hadn’t been able to break through that defensive wall.

“What’s the matter with Xiaoyue? She lost her presence of mind. The Deep Earth Sect disciples are famous for their defensive strength. What they wish for the most is for their opponent to crazily attack to consume their true essence. If Xiaoyue’s like this, the most she can hope for is a tie.” Mu Zhaoxuan anxiously said.

“Junior-apprentice Sister Song is strong, but she lacks combat experience. She has only competed in a few sect Martial Meetings or core disciple contests and assessments. This is the first time that she’s fought with a disciple from another sect.”

Against the Deep Earth Sect, when they created a shield, the best method to deal with this was to just completely ignore it. This sort of earth-attribute safety mask consumed true essence. If one ignored it, then he would naturally not continue. But if someone were to madly attack him, then this was what he would wish for the most.

Divine Phoenix Island’s disciples worried. In such an intense fight, there was no way they could remind Song Xiaoyue about this with a true essence sound transmission.

After over 30 moves had passed, Song Xiaoyue also realized that something was wrong. She had nearly consumed half her true essence, and her opponent’s true essence hadn’t weakened in the least.

She couldn’t help but slow down her offensive barrage. But at this time, Shi Hanshan slyly smiled and punched out, slamming straight towards Song Xiaoyue’s face!

Song Xiaoyue clenched her shining teeth, cutting down on Shi Hanshan’s fist with her sword!

Peng!

The grating sound of metal colliding rang in the air. Shi Hanshan had an earth-step treasure glove on his hand. Most of the disciples of the Deep Earth Sect were fist fighters.

As he blocked Song Xiaoyue’s sword with his fist, he jabbed out at Song Xiaoyue’s stomach with his other fist!

“Sky Splitting Strike!”

Shi Hanshan’s exposed a fierce and barbarous smile. With a punch, the air around him seemed to stir up.

Song Xiaoyue had consumed too much true essence. She was unable to summon the necessary true essence, and was continually forced back by the fist’s true essence.

As she retreated step by step, how could Shi Hanshan give Song Xiaoyue the chance to come back?

As they reached the front of the stage, the hard stone tiles under Shi Hanshan’s feet that were reinforced by an array formation began to crackle.

“Stone King’s Astral Sky Fist!”

Shi Hanshan’s fist was like the wind, dozens of fist shades dancing in the air. The fist potential was like a roiling tide that swept out, completely dissipating all of the flaming true essence that gathered on Song Xiaoyue’s sword.

“Fist Setting Universe!”

Shi Hanshan punched out one last time, the power of this first at the extreme, like landslide, like the shattering of a dam!

Puff!

Song Xiaoyue flew backwards, her face pale, her mouth spilling blood, and several of her ribs broken.

“Xiaoyue!”

“Senior-apprentice Sister!”

Several of the Divine Phoenix Island’s female disciples gathered around her to help her up. “Xiaoyue are you alright?”

“I’m fine.” Song Xiaoyue sat up with some difficulty. She bit her lips in shame and said, “I lost. I was too stupid, I’ve brought disgrace to everyone.”

Song Xiaoyue understood that Shi Hanshan was using words to provoke her, but his stupid and simple expression had caused her to relax her guard. In the end, this could only be faulted on Song Xiaoyue having grown up as a child in Divine Phoenix Island and lacking the necessary real world combat experience. Otherwise, there was no way she would have been stirred up by just a few words and lost in such a manner.

If she could have fought slowly and steadily, then she could at least have obtained a draw. Song Xiaoyue felt apologetic towards everyone that was counting on her. She had requested to go up on her own initiative, and in the end had lost in such a horrible fashion.

Mu Zhaoxuan looked over Song Xiaoyue’s injuries. She had several broken ribs, but to a martial artist, they would be quickly healed with a few pills and some rest. But, it was no longer possible for Song Xiaoyue to continue participating in this competition.

Now, of the 15 Houtian juniors of Divine Phoenix Island, Song Xiaoyue had lost her combat strength, and the fifth listed core disciple Hua Hong had consumed too much of her strength in her battle against Zhang Lin, and would be unable to fight in a short period of time. There were only 13 individuals left over with the ability to fight. But, of the six opposing great sects, the first ranked core disciples still hadn’t even taken action, nor had their direct disciples.

Once several more rounds passed, there might not be anyone left in Divine Phoenix Island that could still fight.

Mu Dingshan had a very troubled expression. He could only watch helplessly as his core disciple juniors fell into such a troubling position. Yet, he was unable to do anything about it.

At these sort of banquet competitions, there was an established and unspoken rule that those entering the stage would do so in order of weakest to strongest. First, the weakest disciples would come onstage, and then the middle core disciples, the upper-middle core disciples, the top core disciples, the direct disciples, and finally the chief disciple would step on stage.

In terms of cultivation, it would be those at the Pulse Condensation period first, then those at the Houtian realm. This event would usually last the entire day, and the true masters would exchange blows last. Otherwise, there would be no opportunity for the common disciples to step onstage.

If Mu Dingshan stepped onstage at this moment, it would ruin this rule. Not only that, but then the Sunfire Princess, Zhang Yunjian, and other similar characters would step on stage. He and Mu Xiaoqing would be two against six; this pressure would be no less than what the core disciples were feeling.

When that time came, they would also fall into the position of not being able to sit down, and having to give arguments like a loss is a loss.

“These Five Element Region fellows really don’t care about face.” Mu Dingshan said with a dour expression.

“Mm. In usual years during these kinds of competitions, there would not be such obvious targeting. The Five Element Region’s seven great sects would challenge each other, and also the South Horizon Region would have Supreme Mystery Temple and Dire Space Sect participating to share the pressure. Every time, our Divine Phoenix Island would be able to shine. But now because of the South Sea Demon Region, everyone is competing against us and going all out each time. The various measures are endless.” The one who answered was Tianguang Revered Master. Now that his 400th birthday celebration had devolved to this point, he could only ruefully smile.

As the two spoke, more people stepped on stage. They were top ranking core disciples from Divine Phoenix Island and Arctic Ice Palace. Fire and ice collided together, and the defensive barrier trembled. After several moves, their strength was about the same. The Five Element Region’s seven great sects had contested with Divine Phoenix Island for a long time, and they each had an approximate understanding of the other’s strength. When two opponents went onstage, their strength would be about the same.

As the two battled for an incense stick of time, both of them were wounded, but they still continued, the match undecided.

“There’s no more meaning to continue fighting, call this a draw!”

An Arctic Ice Palace elder said.

The two disciples were already severely wounded. If this continued, it would become a life and death struggle.

The Divine Phoenix Island disciple stepped down with extreme unwillingness. At this time, the Deep Earth Sect’s Shi Hanshan unexpectedly jumped onstage. The nearly nine foot tall Shi Hanshan stood on the center of the stage, looking no different to an iron tower. He said, “Deep Earth Sect’s Shi Hanshan, I wish to challenge the young heroic elites of Divine Phoenix Island!”

“This bastard, he actually jumped out again!”

According to the unwritten rules of the banquet competition, one could continue fighting if they won, without limit. But if they lost, they could only obediently sit in the audience. Only if others challenged them would they be able to go up. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have the qualifications to step onstage and challenge others. Since Shi Hanshan won, he naturally had the qualifications to fight again.

Shi Hanshan was very excited. This sort of opportunity for the Five Element Region to battle the South Horizon Region was very rare. If he achieved better results, not only would he become more famous and gain more honor, but he would be given additional attention by the sect, and would even have rewards after returning home.

After exhausting Song Xiaoyue and then defeating her, he actually hadn’t consumed much true essence. He had used the time after the match to take some restorative pills and meditate for an incense stick of time, restoring his condition to near perfection.

The reason he stepped onstage was to continue challenging.

“I wonder which heroic elite of Divine Phoenix Island could advise me?”

Shi Hanshan’s voice was like thunder to the ears. Song Xiaoyue grit her teeth, glaring with utter resentment at this duplicitous pig, wishing she could savagely beat him up. The third, fourth, and fifth ranked core disciples of Divine Phoenix Island had already stepped onstage. Now, only the first and second ranked core disciples were left. If they went up to deal with Shi Hanshan, later there would be no one else to deal with the top ranked core disciples of the other sects.

Hua Hong clenched her teeth, preparing to go onstage and meet this pig’s challenge. She had won her match, and thus also had the qualifications to fight again. Although she had consumed a great deal of energy, she had been able to restore the greater portion of it in this last half hour.

“Junior-apprentice Sister Hua, don’t be so rash. This Shi Hanshan is a bad match for you. You haven’t recovered to your top condition yet. Wait for a few more matches and then restore your best condition before going onstage again, otherwise you’ll only let the villain become increasingly arrogant.”

As Mu Zhaoxuan pulled back Hua Hong, she glanced at all the other Houtian core disciples. Besides her and the top ranked core disciple Mu Dianqing, there was no one else that had the capabilities to step on stage. The only ones left over were the direct disciples, who couldn’t act yet.

It seemed that the only path left was for her to step onstage. Mu Zhaoxuan stood up, but at this time, a true essence sound transmission resounded in her ears. “Senior-apprentice Sister, allow me to go up.”

Mu Zhaoxuan turned around, astonishment in her eyes. She saw Lin Ming stand up.

“Junior-apprentice Brother Lin, you will challenge a Houtian realm master?” Mu Zhaoxuan was stunned.

“Yes.”

Lin Ming hadn’t stepped onstage, and had instead observed the first two fights so he could get a grasp of the strength of a fourth-grade sect’s Houtian genius. He had a plan from the start.

He concluded that a top ranked core disciple of a fourth-grade sect like Shi Hanshan or Song Xiaoyue had a strength similar to Huang Zixuan, who had had killed three months ago.

Although Huang Zixuan was a poor talent, he was still a peak Houtian master that came from a small sect. These fourth-grade sect core disciples could compare to a peak Houtian master at the early Houtian realm. When they reached the peak Houtian realm, they might even be able to compare with a Xiantian master.

This strength was also aligned with Lin Ming’s expectations.

Shi Hanshan saw Lin Ming stand up. He was surprised, and that surprise quickly turned to excitement. He raised his sleeves, rubbing his nose, and smiled as he said, “Hehe, how interesting. Come. I’ve already wanted to challenge you.”

Chapter 365 – I’ll Take All Comers

Shi Hanshan wanted to have a match against Lin Ming. However, because their difference in cultivation was too great, he had no way to challenge him.

He didn’t think that Lin Ming would actually offer himself up.

Shi Hanshan didn’t look down on Lin Ming. Rather, it was because of Lin Ming’s overabundance of talent that he had aimed for him. He believed that with Lin Ming’s talent, he would become a lofty character in the future, a powerhouse on the level of Zhan Yunjian. But now, his current ability was far too weak.

Shi Hanshan realized that he wouldn’t be a match for Lin Ming in a few years. So while Lin Ming was still small and weak, he would take this opportunity to savagely crush him underneath his boot. To crush a monstrous genius beneath one’s boot was a very rewarding experience.

Thinking this, the smile on Shi Hanshan’s face became increasingly wide. He was originally a sorry and foul looking figure, but now with such a bright smiling face, it really caused one’s skin to crawl.

“Lin Ming, don’t be so impulsive. Are you sure? If you aren’t then let me go on first. You’ve already taken the title of number one amongst the Pulse Condensation period. Even if you don’t fight anymore, no one will say anything about you. If you lose, you’ll also lose all the honor that you’ve gained.” Mu Zhaoxuan nervously said.

Lin Ming nodded, his words honest, “I have complete confidence.”

Complete confidence?

Mu Zhaoxuan was shocked. She already thought it would be extraordinary if Lin Ming had a 60 or 70% assurance to win. That would leave some room for doubt. But she didn’t expect that Lin Ming would directly say that he had full confidence he would emerge victorious!

If he said this with such belief, then how could she possibly reject him?

Lin Ming had just stepped onstage when Mu Qianyu’s true essence sound transmission resounded in his ears, “Lin Ming, you won’t have a problem this match, right?”

“No problem at all.” Lin Ming turned around and was surprised to see Mu Qianyu looking at him with a fond smile in her eyes. This startled Lin Ming, was there something to be so happy about?

“Mm. I guess that since you walk on stage so decisively, you won’t have a problem.” After Lin Ming continuously defeated Ma Junhui and Zhou Xiaoling, Mu Qianyu suddenly remembered that Lin Ming himself was a monstrous talent of preposterous proportions, and that all her worries had been in vain. At Thundercrash Mountain, he had even absorbed a low-grade earth-step Thunder Soul, so what other matter could be impossible to him? She smiled as she said, “Lin Ming, Honorable Master bids me to tell you that if you can defeat Shi Hanshan, she’ll have a reward for you.”

“Oh?” Lin Ming was immediately happy. This was a great fortune! A reward that a top fourth-grade sect would give out would naturally be some fantastic treasure.

“What sort of reward?” Lin Ming asked with gusto, his spirit stirred up.

“Haha, you really wake up without some rewards, hm? How about you take a guess?” Mu Qianyu said, keeping Lin Ming in suspense. Lin Ming paused – whatever could have Mu Qianyu keep him in suspense would truly be a wonderful treasure.

What could it be?

Heaven Opening Pills?

Medium-grade, or even high-grade true essence stones?

Although these objects were valuable, they were still relatively popular and common, and were equivalent to money. They shouldn’t be able to enter Mu Qianyu’s eyes.

Maybe it was some miracle medicine like the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal that could help a Xiantian master reach the Revolving Core realm?

That was impossible. Old lady Yuhuang had no idea that he was hiding away his Tempering Marrow realm. And the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal was no different from the purest poison to a Pulse Condensation period martial artist. Old lady Yuhuang would not reward him with something unreasonable that wouldn’t help him at this stage.

“Is it some valuable material that can help increase one’s strength?” Lin Ming casually guessed.

“That sort of thing is useless to you. You already have enough Heaven Opening Pills, so you’re probably tired of eating them. And if you eat too many, you’ll build up too much pill toxin. What Honorable Master promised to reward you is the blood of the Vermillion Bird, this is the transplantation of a Saint Beast’s bloodline!

Transplanting a Saint Beast’s bloodline? When Lin Ming had first heard about the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, he had also heard Mu Qianyu mention that the Vermillion Bird bloodline could be transplanted onto another person.

In order to cultivate the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ and the ‘Blue Lian Abstract Phantom Code’ to their core realm, one had to have the bloodline of the Vermillion Bird or Blue Luan. Otherwise, it was impossible to cultivate.

In Divine Phoenix Island, there were very few individuals that were truly born with the Vermillion Bird Bloodline. Most of the disciples that had this bloodline had it transplanted within them during the Houtian realm. This so-called ‘transplant’ was in fact taking the blood of the Vermillion Bird Saint Beast and sealing it into one’s body using a secret technique, forcing the Vermillion Bird blood to penetrate into one’s bone marrow and fuse with their own bloodline.

This sort of bloodline transplant was very modest. It could only increase a disciple’s fire-attribute true essence fusion compatibility and ability to cultivate the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ by a small amount. Its effects were very limited.

Let alone expecting this bloodline transplant to allow one to cultivate the core sections of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ and ‘Blue Lian Abstract Phantom Code’.

But for Mu Qianyu to emphasize this reward so much, this would definitely not be the usual Saint Beast bloodline transplantation.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but ask, “Miss Mu shouldn’t be speaking of the same bloodline that the inner court disciples have, right?”

“Of course not.” Mu Qianyu snapped back. “You really are too greedy, you can’t lose a bit at all. It is the Vermillion Bird’s blood essence transplant. Honored Master has said that the more geniuses you defeat, and the stronger they are, the richer the bloodline that will be bestowed to you. Honorable Master has the capital, and this is an extremely rare opportunity.”

Mu Qianyu laughed as she spoke. Because Lin Ming could have such a grand opportunity, her mood was also very good.

Lin Ming was jubilant, this was actually the Vermilion Bird’s blood essence transplant! Blood essence and blood were to completely different concepts. Whether it was a Saint Beast or martial artist, losing a bit of blood wasn’t anything at all. They could easily recover it in several days. But if one lost blood essence, that would harm their very foundation.

Once one’s blood essence was drained, that was equal to one’s life being damaged, and also losing cultivation. If a martial artist lost their blood essence, that was an absolute death sentence.

Even Lin Ming didn’t dare to risk his own blood essence. The power of his blood vitality used his blood essence as its base.

For a Vermillion Bird to leave behind blood essence, there were only two possibilities. The Vermillion Bird had either been killed, or had died a natural death.

Ultimately, a Vermillion Bird was a Saint Beast. It was not an endless and immortal being like a phoenix. Its so-called bathing in the fires of nirvana was really only used to treat wounds. Even the most grievous of wounds could be treated by undergoing the fires of nirvana. But, undergoing nirvana would not actually lengthen a Vermillion Bird’s lifespan.

At the end of a Vermillion Bird’s life, they would complete their final nirvana, and also die in nirvana.

After a Vermillion Bird died, they would leave behind a small cup of blood essence.

If Lin Ming could obtain enough Vermillion Bird blood essence and transplant it within himself, his bloodline might not be as pure as that of Mu Qianyu or Mu Bingyun, but it was more than enough to cultivate the core section of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’!

This was too important to Lin Ming’s future cultivation of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’.

Prior to this, the reason that Lin Ming had joined Divine Phoenix Island, besides Mu Qianyu, was that he had joint interests with Divine Phoenix Island. Divine Phoenix Island valued Lin Ming’s talent, but Lin Ming also needed the resources that Divine Phoenix Island could provide. In the future, if Lin Ming could reach the Revolving Core realm, he would in turn be able to help lead Divine Phoenix Island to a stronger position, and even help assist them in becoming a fifth-grade sect.

Lin Ming didn’t think that he was taking advantage of Divine Phoenix Island in any way – that was why he didn’t even prostrate himself in front of old lady Yuhuang.

But now, after Lin Ming heard Mu Qianyu mention the Vermillion Bird blood essence, even he found it difficult to keep his beating heart calm. This was Vermillion Bird blood essence! It was an enormous benefit to any Divine Phoenix Island disciple. From the founding of Divine Phoenix Island until now, just how many Vermillion Birds had died? How much Vermillion Bird blood essence could there possibly be? By comparison, after generation after generation of Divine Phoenix Island disciples coming and going, who knew who how many individuals there were.

Since Vermillion Bird blood essence could be preserved this far, it must be precious to the point that even old lady Yuhuang was reluctant to use it. Yet she had taken out something so treasured and was even rewarding it to him. This act of kindness was enough to engrave itself upon Lin Ming’s mind.

But even though old lady Yuhuang had taken out the blood essence as a reward, the ultimate goal was a joining of mutual interests. Lin Ming also firmed his resolve. In his life, he would help Divine Phoenix Island become a fifth-grade sect. Once he became a Revolving Core Supreme Elder, this shouldn’t be too difficult for him.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but glance at old lady Yuhuang. He was surprised to find that she was still sitting in her chair, her expression reticent and cloudy.

Seeing Lin Ming look at her, old lady Yuhuang sent him a true essence sound transmission, “Boy, don’t be happy so early. If you lose then you won’t get anything. At that time, don’t come crying to me.”

Lin Ming grinned, “Hey, I can win!”

“Humph, I believe you can defeat Shi Hanshan. But once you win, there will be even more Houtian masters challenging you. Do you think you can defeat the dozens of Houtian masters from the six great sects?”

As  old lady Yuhuang spoke, a wave of heroic pride and dignity flooded through Lin Ming. He took a deep breath, calmly saying, “Whoever comes will come. I’ll take all comers!”

Old lady Yuhuang was shocked. This boy was really too arrogant. But, the young should be a bit arrogant, and they should also have an indomitable and cavalier attitude with absolute belief in their own abilities. Only then would they be able to bring out their true potential!

“Good. Then let this old woman have a look at just how many you can take!” Old lady Yuhuang was also looking forward to seeing just how far Lin Ming could go.

Old lady Yuhuang had just finished speaking when another voice sounded in Lin Ming’s ear, “Brother Lin, are we going to do this or what?”

Lin Ming turned to see Shi Hanshan grinning at him. He looked like a simple and honest man, but the truth was that it was only a veneer that hid his cunning edge.

Lin Ming discovered that he had been speaking with Mu Qianyu and old lady Yuhuang too long, and was just standing at the edge of the stage, not even having entered yet.

Shi Hanshan naturally assumed that Lin Ming was afraid.

Because he had impulsively stood up, he had walked halfway but suddenly regretted it. With Lin Ming’s age and cultivation, if he decided to change his direction midway, although it was shameful it was also an understandable action.

This was not what Shi Hanshan was hoping to see.

He cupped his hands across his chest and said, “Brother Lin, you’re very strong. Perhaps within the entire Five Element Region, there is no junior in the Pulse Condensation period that can defeat you. Even Thundercrest Sect’s Junior-apprentice Sister Zhou is not your match at all. Although I am at the Houtian realm, my talent is much worse than yours. Against a ‘Lesser Saint’ talent like yourself, I’m not any better. However, Brother Lin is still young. If Brother Lin doesn’t wish to fight, then I naturally will not force the issue. It’s just that I will find it truly regrettable that I won’t be able to experience the top sub-Houtian master of the South Horizon Region.”

Shi Hanshan’s words seemed to be filled with yearning emotion, but that ‘Lesser Saint’ title was intended to deliberately belittle themselves and raise Lin Ming’s proud nature. This truth was that this was another method of provoking that was completely different from the demeaning kind of the idiotic Ma Junhui. Perhaps this method of prodding was even more effective.

Chapter 376 – Pale Youth

With a mere Bone Forging stage cultivation, Lin Ming had been able to absorb the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder that only a middle Xiantian master should have been able to. If there wasn’t any secret within Lin Ming’s body, Mu Yuhuang would never have been able to believe this. But, if Lin Ming’s bloodline was used as the explanation, she could reluctantly come to terms with it.

After all, the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder contained the brutal will of a Flood Dragon. If it was to encounter a more formidable and ancient bloodline, this Flood Dragon bloodline would be awed into submission. With Yu’er’s help, this could also explain how Lin Ming was able to absorb it.

Mu Qianyu nodded, saying, “This is also the first time disciple has seen the phantom behind Lin Ming. When Senior-apprentice Sister Qinghong returned from the Seven profound Valleys, she described to me what she had seen. It was probably a similar scene… disciple believes that this is an ancient noble bloodline similar to my Divine Phoenix Island’s that Lin Ming managed to obtain through some lucky chance.”

As for Lin Ming’s life and background, they had already been clearly researched by Divine Phoenix Island. The common people of Sky Fortune Kingdom had been mortals for generations, it was impossible for Lin Ming to have this kind of bloodline from his family. Thus, the only other reason was that the heavens had gifted him a lucky miracle.

“Ancient noble bloodline?” Mu Yuhuang hesitated. Perhaps matters weren’t so simple. Just what sort of ancient noble bloodline could cause even the Vermillion Bird bloodline within her to shiver in fear?

Could it be a God Beast?

Mu Yuhuang dared not believe this. A God Beast did not exist in the Sky Spill Continent. It was said that above the Sky Spill Continent was the Realm of the Gods. But, even within the Realm of the Gods, a God Beast was an extremely rare existence. Where did Lin Ming find the blood essence of a God Beast to transplant into his bloodline?

Even if he had gotten that far, how could a mere Bone Forging boy have absorbed such a bloodline?

In any case, it was true that Lin Ming had a secret bloodline within him, and that this bloodline had an extraordinary origin.

However, Mu Yuhuang didn’t wish to pry into his secrets. In truth, lucky chances were also a part of one’s destiny. A great lucky chance came with a correspondingly great destiny. Destiny was the essential truth that an unrivaled talent needed to become a Peerless Emperor. Ever since ancient times, the birth of Peerless Emperors usually resulted from the accumulated destiny of a character that stood at the pinnacle.

If one didn’t have such a destiny but still coveted these things, they would instead attract an unexpected catastrophe upon themselves. History had proven this point again and again throughout the annals of time. These so-called unlucky calamitous treasures were often priceless. However, what was strange was that if one obtained it, they would die as if they had been struck by a curse. If one didn’t have a great destiny as if they were the protagonist of the world, they would not be able to gather such treasures to them.

In order to birth a genius that would become a Peerless Emperor, perhaps not even Divine Phoenix Island had such a destiny. Much less, Mu Yuhuang was just an old lady with a few hundred years of life left in her. This sort of calamitous treasure was not something she would be able to afford. Even if she managed to peacefully obtain it without accident, with her age, it was basically useless.

What Mu Yuhuang most wanted to see now was only that her Divine Phoenix Island would be able to enter an age of prosperity.

………………

On the martial arts stage, Lin Ming and Xiao Chi fought once more. Both spears clashed. One side was a spear skill genius of Golden Bell Mountain whose every move contained profound principles. But as for the other side, he had a deep comprehension of spear potential. Although his spear skills were simple and lacking, every spear was like a landslide, every spear was like a tsunami, every spear contained the power of endless mountains and rivers. These two were well matched against each other.

Clang clang clang clang clang!

With every strike, a violently raging true essence shockwave erupted, an azure color mixing with a golden color, causing the ground itself to shake. Because of the intense shockwaves in the air, the audience that witnessed this battle scene seemed to be watching it under the twisted ripples of water.

Every spear that Lin Ming thrust out contained an enormous pressure. Even though Xiao Chi’s spear contained a strange power, it was actually forcefully dissolved by Lin Ming’s strength.

The two youths fought for several dozen moves. Lin Ming had consumed a great deal of true essence, but so had Xiao Chi.

This battle was the longest that Lin Ming had ever fought.

With his strength, he could simply have used the Thunder Soul and won with overwhelming force. But, he did not do this.

He needed this battle to see what degree of skill one’s spear play could reach.

Xiao Chi turned, thrusting out his spear. Although this spear skill looked very slow, in just a split-second the spearpoint would instantly arrive in front of you. This sort of strange and confusing spatial skill was nearly impossible to defend against.

Pah!

Even Lin Ming was unable to completely dodge the spear with such a confusing spatial skill. The spearpoint rubbed against Lin Ming’s bodily true essence, and with a ripping sound, an incomparably sharp golden spear had pierced through Lin Ming’s bodily true essence, taking just a touch of blood.

“Mm?”

Xiao Chi was surprised. What was going on? In that attack, he had felt like his spear had stabbed into iron, it simply hadn’t been able to do much damage.

But at the same time, Lin Ming’s spear came smashing down like an avalanche!

Xiao Chi quickly lifted his spear to block.

Clang!

As soon as this blow smashed down, the golden spear in Xiao Chi’s hand curved into a crescent moon. He staggered back, every step creating a deep imprint in the ground. The tiles of the stage that were supported by an array formation were broken by the pressure of his feet, cracks littering the stage.

After retreated 70 to 80 feet, Xiao Chi finally came to a stop. He felt like his right arm was numb, and even his fingers were shaking.

“What a terrifying strength and spear potential!”

Although he managed to block that last attack, he felt the blood within his body roiling and his meridians in crazy disorder.

In the audience, the Golden Bell Mountain elder gasped. “What a terrifying boy. Chi’er used a special technique to unload the force on his body. Lin Ming’s strength and spear potential that he unleashed poured along Chi’er’s muscles and skeleton, entering the ground through his feet. Even though he had let so much strength pass through him, he was still wounded. The power of this spear potential is simply like having a mountain fall on you.”

“Indeed… this boy is truly a spear genius. But it’s such a pity that he doesn’t have a great master that can teach him spear skills. If all he learns is some Foundation Spear Technique skills, then it is truly wasteful…” Another Golden Bell Mountain elder said with some regret, obviously sad that Lin Ming hadn’t joined his Golden Ball Mountain.

…………

“Haha, what a great fight!” Xiao Chi suddenly put away his spear. His entire forehead was covered with sweat, and his face was flushed red. Blood was surging within his body, and he had obviously consumed a great deal of strength.

“Same here.”

Lin Ming was also panting for breath. After several continuous battles, even with pills to supplement him, he had consumed over 70% of his true essence. Not only that, but within the true essence of his body, there were many complex and strange factors. Lin Ming’s current combat strength was less than half of his optimal condition.

“You’re just a monster. You fought through five straight fierce matches and yet you can still fight to this degree and have energy left over. I admit defeat.” Xiao Chi sighed, lamenting the result. He had been evenly matched with Lin Ming, but it turned out that Lin Ming’s endurance was much greater than his. If they continued, his defeat was simply a matter of time.

“Well fought.” Lin Ming cupped his hands together and bowed. During this match against Xiao Chi, he had learned many things and gained many insights. It seemed that he really needed to look for a spear art manual in order to make up for his deficiencies there.

After Xiao Chi admitted defeat on his own, the entire audience was silent. The strongest direct disciple under the six great chief disciples had actually lost.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Xiao was defeated…”

Even the Five Element Region disciples that were desperately cheering for Xiao Chi were unable to accept this. The truth was, when Lin Ming hadn’t used this power of thunder and fire, yet was still able to fight evenly with Xiao Chi using just his spear play, they had already foreseen the ending that Xiao Chi would lose. It was just that they weren’t willing to accept this truth.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Xiao lost. Above Xiao Chi, there are only the six great direct disciples…”

Although everyone knew that Lin Ming was already spent of all energy, there was no direct disciples that went onstage to challenge him. Lin Ming’s winning streak had left them breathless, and no one had the courage or qualifications to challenge him.

Lin Ming swallowed a pill and propped himself up on the stage using his spear. This time, he did not challenge anyone to battle. He was well aware that if he fought again, it would be against a chief disciple.

Six great chief disciples… it was unknown just how many he could fight.

Lin Ming turned to look at Mu Dingshan and saw that he was preparing. Next would be a contest between chief disciples!

“Dingshan, Xiaoqing, if you fight, try to delay as much as possible so that Lin Ming can have more time to recover.” Mu Dingshan and Mu Xiaoqing simultaneously heard the true essence sound transmission of old lady Yuhuang.

“Yes, Honorable Sect Master.”

……………………

Within the Thundercrest Sect banquet area, the pale youth glanced at Zhou Lie, ordering him to go onstage. “You challenge Lin Ming to draw out Mu Dingshan, I’ll help you take him!”

The pale youth tersely said.

Zhou Lie frowned. He absolutely did not wish to do something so insidious like taking advantage of someone while they were in a vulnerable situation. This was not how a true gentleman acted. With such a large audience present, he couldn’t afford to lose.

“Hehe, what’s the matter? You think you’re taking advantage of someone while they’re down? Alright, we’ll take a break and look for another reason when they lose.”

The pale youth casually spoke, his words carrying an imperious tone that made Zhou Lie feel uneasy.

‘This fellow seems very keen on what he said before, and wants to challenge the direct disciples of Divine Phoenix Island by himself. What does he want from all this?’ Zhou Lie thought, baffled.

At this moment, the pale youth used a true essence sound transmission to communicate with Lei Jingtian. Then, Lei Jingtian stood up and smiled, “High Master Yuhuang, your great island’s Lin Ming is truly a hero that from among the young. However, after he competed against five masters from my Five Element Region, it seems that he has already exhausted himself. How about we have a truce and take a break so that Lin Ming can rest. Afterwards will be the final competition between chief disciples. How about it?”

“Mm? Mu Yuhuang’s willowy eyebrows rose. This fellow, just what did this little weasel want? What was he thinking about? He actually offered to call a momentary truce?

It had to be known that Lin Ming had consumed too much energy. Even if Mu Dingshan and Mu Xiaoqing were able to delay for a few matches so that Lin Ming could rest, he still wouldn’t be able to fully recover in this short time.

After Lei Jingtian spoke, he sat down with a cheerful laugh before waiting for Mu Yuhuang’s answer.

Zhou Lie was confused, just who was this pale youth? It seemed that his master seemed to care about his opinion a great deal.

‘This fellow is shrouded in mystery, he’s just like a frosty snake! Master said that he was a Saint rank talent that he found in the northern domains, but I always felt that this explanation was too farfetched. His martial talent is surprisingly good and he also understands many different cultivation methods. His cultivation is only at the early Houtian realm, yet he can easily defeat me! Not only that, but he seems to know some secrets about Sky Spill Continent, such as the legends of the Saintess…’

There was definitely a problem with this man!

Just who was he?

For some time, Zhou Lie even suspected that the pale fellow was possessed by some ancient monster. Of course, this was something that only existed in fantasy novels; he had no idea if things like possession existed.

As Zhou Lie was daydreaming, Lei Jingtian was exchanging a true essence sound transmission with the pale youth. “We’ll follow everything as you planned. Events should progress smoothly…”

“Mm, very good!”

Chapter 380 – Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder

Lei Mubai’s face had fallen to the point that it was almost dripping water. “Since High Master Yuhuang has spoken, let it be so. Then, I still ask for advice from all the young heroic elites of Divine Phoenix Island. Since High Master seems so self-assured, I would like to ask: if I can defeat all of Divine Phoenix Island’s disciples by myself, what then?”

Lei Mubai’s words were obviously daring her to act. He calculated that Mu Yuhuang had a very tough and unbending personality that wouldn’t accept defeat, so he could only provoke her like this.

“You want to incite me so that I’ll somehow take the matter of Qianyu’s wedding as a gambling stake with you?”

Lei Mubai calmly stared at Mu Yuhuang, this idea clearly in his heart.

Mu Yuhuang bleakly laughed twice. Suddenly, her willowy eyebrows shot up, and the aura of her entire body erupted forth. In the blink of an eye, a visible crimson ring of fire burst forth from around her; this was the terrifying power of fire condensed from fire origin energy.

Huu!

That ring of fire instantly spread throughout the entire banquet audience. It caused no damage, and not even a single dish was broken in half, but everyone present felt a terrifying pressure like a mountain top was crushing down on them. Especially Lei Mubai, who bore the brunt of this ferocious aura; he felt like his organs had been struck by a sledgehammer and was forced several steps back, his feet hitting the floor with a ‘deng deng deng’ sound.

Mu Yuhuang’s voice was chilling, “Give up on this idea in your heart. This old woman has never feared anyone in making a gambling bet. But this old woman will also not take Qianyu’s marriage as a gambling stake. If you wish to bet on anything else, this old woman will accompany you!”

As Mu Yuhuang spoke, Mu Qianyu had slowly moved behind her, looking at Mu Yuhuang’s hair that had long turned silver, and pursed her lips. Mu Qianyu didn’t say anything. She was aware that Mu Yuhuang had never married in her entire life, and also never had children before. She knew that Mu Yuhuang had viewed her as her own flesh and blood daughter.

The scene was tense, as if it could blow up at any moment.

Lei Mubai took deep breaths, slowly suppressing the roiling true essence within his body that was aggravated by Mu Yuhuang’s terrifying aura. “I’m not interesting in betting anything else. Since High Mastert is not interested, then that too is fine. With my status as the Thundercrest Sect’s Limitless Envoy, I challenge all the heroic elites of Divine Phoenix Island!”

Lei Mubai’s words were filled with arrogance and contempt. As the Saint Son of the South Sea Demon Region, and also the top talent of a fifth-grade sect, he naturally looked down on the disciples of Divine Phoenix Island.

‘I had wanted to use this method of marriage to take Mu Qianyu’s virginity and then use this chance to have the Thundercrest Sect betray Divine Phoenix Island. But I have no idea what sort of drugs this old bag Mu Yuhuang took that she immediately labeled me as a lecherous womanizer, and didn’t even consider the matter before rejecting me. Does she want Mu Qianyu to end up like her and never marry in her lifetime?’

‘Could this old woman have found something wrong with my body?’ Lei Mubai thought of this and his heart tightened on the spot. However, he immediately shook his head. ‘No, that’s impossible. With her personality, if she really did recognize me, then she would probably capture me right here. Not just that, but there is no flaw with my body. Could it have just been her intuition that told her I had another scheme in mind and thus flatly refused me?’

Lei Mubai grit his teeth, wishing in his heart that he could tear Mu Yuhuang to pieces. ‘Since I can’t take Mu Qianyu’s virginity, I’ll ruin all the chief disciples of Divine Phoenix Island. Since I have determined to become a Peerless Emperor, I must step over the corpses of a massive number of geniuses to arrive at that peak. I will shatter their confidence and engrave this experience in my heart! Mu Yuhuang, since you dare to act like this to me, I will break the spirit of your disciples so that they’ll find it difficult to ever step into the Revolving Core realm! This is the revenge that I will take for your insults against me today!’

Thinking this, Lei Mubai looked at Mu Xiaoqing, the corners of his mouth curving up in a nefarious grin. First, he would start with this girl! What a pity that the Blue Luan bloodline within her body was too thin, otherwise having a taste of her would be very delicious.

Mu Xiaoqing frowned. She felt that this Lei Mubai in front of her was no different than a cold and dangerous snake, his eyes filled with aggressiveness.

She flourished her longsword, coldly saying, “Take out your weapon!”

“Weapon?” Lei Mubai crossed his arms behind his back, speaking with utter disdain, “To deal with the likes of you, I don’t need my weapon. If you can last against five of my moves, I’ll consider this your win!”

“What!?”

Mu Xiaoqing’s slender eyebrows shot up, anger pulsing in her heart.

It wasn’t just Mu Xiaoqing, but all the disciples of Divine Phoenix Island were angry. This Lei Mubai was simply too arrogant! These words were all said to humiliate the other party! Normally when other martial artists fought, even if one knew their opponent was far inferior, they would still respect their opponent. But, these words were obviously all said to shame the other party and attack their confidence.

“You are too detestable!”

Mu Xiaoqing clenched her teeth, when had she ever been humiliated like this before?

Lin Ming shook his head. Since Lei Mubai had already spoken such words, this battle would continue, and not only that, but continue in the most violent and desperate manner possible. There was no point in trying to persuade Mu Xiaoqing otherwise. If she was humiliated by her opponent like this and chose to retreat, swallowing this fateful shame, the result would even be worse than suffering a crushing defeat.

“Xiaoqing, Lei Mubai is a Saint rank talent. If you do not have the ability to cope with him, admit defeat now.” Mu Yuhuang feared that Mu Xiaoqing would be provoked into doing something completely irrational, so she cautioned her with a true essence sound transmission.

“Saint rank talent?” Mu Xiaoqing gasped. The truth was that she had already expected this. If Lei Mubai had dared to speak ruthless words, how could he not be confident in his strength?

But deep down, she had an unyielding disposition that had no intention of conceding.

‘So what if you’re a Saint rank talent? Even if I’m weaker than you, I will still force you to use your weapon. At least, even if I lose, I won’t let you defeat me within five moves!’

Mu Xiaoqing stimulated the true essence in her body to the extreme, revolving the ‘Blue Luan Abstract Phantom Code’. Although she was angry, she still maintained her calm reasoning, not losing her heart. If she violently attacked him, she would just be defeated faster.

“Hehe, you’re quite smart. But still useless.”

Lei Mubai gathered his hands together, and red arcs of lightning flashed in his hands like a beautiful living spirit. A faint crackling sound lingered in the air. These red arcs of lightning faintly exuded the aura of blood.

“Red lightning?”

This was the first time that Lin Ming had seen lightning of this color.

As the red light began to radiate more brightly, becoming increasingly dazzling, the thunder in Lei Mubai’s hands seemed to become a floating blob of blood.

“Thunder Soul! It’s actually an earth-step Thunder Soul!” A Thundercrest Sect disciple shouted out, stunned.

Even Zhou Lie was stunned. He had a Thunder Soul in his body, but that was a high-grade human-step Thunder Soul. Even so, his Thundercrest Sect had paid a great price in order to assist him in completing its absorption.

Mu Qianyu let out a light breath; this was actually the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder. In the legends, it spoke of many ancient battlefields on which countless powerhouses fell from the sky, creating a dark and ominous land. These battlefields also happened to be places where there was intense thunder. After tens of thousands of years passed, a Thunder Soul would be born from absorbing the blood essence of the countless powerhouses, thus becoming this Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder!

The Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder could swallow an enemy’s blood essence and use it for oneself. This was an extremely evil and diabolical kind of thunder.

Not only that, but it was a low-grade earth-step Thunder Soul. It was on par with Lin Ming’s Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder!

Such a grade was not something that a non-middle Xiantian realm master would be able to absorb.

Even if a large sect used all sorts of supplementary materials and provided all sorts of facilities and assistance, paying a massive price, at most they would be able to assist an early Xiantian master in absorbing this!

But now, it was actually absorbed by this Lei Mubai. Of course, this didn’t mean that Lei Mubai had strength equal to an early Xiantian master, but it meant that in the aspect of thunder talent, it was possible that he was a peerless monstrous genius!

Naturally, this was far worse than Lin Ming, who had absorbed the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder with a cultivation at the peak of Bone Forging; Lei Mubai had absorbed this Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder at the early Houtian realm. This fact was enough to cause the shock in Mu Qianyu’s heart to subside some.

Mu Yuhuang’s voice was heavy, “This Lei Mubai already has the talent to become a Peerless Emperor. As long as he can gather destiny around him, he will become a Peerless Emperor a hundred years from now!”

In order to become a Peerless Emperor, talent and destiny were indispensable. Mu Yuhuang had believed that Lin Ming had a great hope to become a Peerless Emperor, and that was because she saw a great destiny upon his body.

As for this Lei Mubai, he had a sufficient heaven-defying talent, all he lacked was a great enough destiny!

“Honorable Master, if that truly is the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder, then Xiaoqing will be in danger. If something goes wrong, there will be invisible injuries left within her, affecting her future cultivation.

The Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder could swallow a martial artist’s blood essence. But once once lost blood essence, it was very difficult to recover from this loss. With just a bit gone, it would affect one’s future achievements.

Mu Yuhuang’s eyebrows twitched. Against the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder, it was naturally a dangerous situation. But if Mu Xiaoqing retreated without a fight, this would also create an evil spirit within Mu Xiaoqing’s heart; it would be extremely difficult for her to ever overcome this hurdle. Not just that, but Lei Mubai was younger than Mu Xiaoqing, and his cultivation was only at the early Houtian realm, whereas Mu Xiaoqing was at the peak of the early Houtian realm.

Mu Xiaoqing surpassed him in age and cultivation. If she was humiliated and didn’t fight back, this sort of disgrace would become a fatal blow to a martial artist’s hearts of martial arts.

In the square, Lei Mubai’s Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder had twined around his entire body. It was just like a venomous serpent that was wound around a man.

“Take my first move, Blood Thunder Claw!” Lei Mubai suddenly stepped forwards, the red light around his hand condensing into a giant claw!

The red light in his hands rushed out, expanding into a massive bloody claw that grasped at Mu Xiaoqing.

The bloody claw wasn’t even close, but Mu Xiaoqing felt the blood essence within her body experience a traction force, causing turbulence within her true essence.

In this situation, Lei Mubai didn’t dare to flagrantly swallow Mu Xiaoqing’s blood essence. With that old lady Yuhuang behind her shielding her, he had to let this go. Still, he could severely injure her.

The claw flew out, bringing the rolling sound of thunder with it. Mu Xiaoqing bit her lips, and a deep and vibrant blue light burst forth from the blue sword in her hands. The phantom of an ice lotus appeared behind Mu Xiaoqing, the ice lotus flower beginning to blossom.

“Blue Lotus Sword!”

The spinning blue lotus flower collided with Lei Mubai’s crimson bloody claw, and a brilliant light flashed out, extremely gorgeous. Countless blue ice crystals were like flowers scattered in the air by celestial beauties all around, with red arcs of lightning savagely flying throughout.

True essence surged, blood vitality tumbled. A terrifying cold air flew out in all directions, and a layer of ice instantly covered the ground. However, these ice crystals were all coated with a strange blood red, as if they were exquisite red crystals.

In the moment that the true essence shockwave passed over Lin Ming, his heart shook.

‘Mm? It’s this feeling again!’

Lin Ming felt a very familiar soul fluctuation within this true essence shockwave. At the time when Lei Mubai went onstage, he also felt this once. He thought he had sensed wrongly, but now he had felt it once more.

What was causing this?

Lin Ming was anxious, his heart doubtful.

Chapter 383 – Great Desolate Blood Halberd

Forsaken Blood Halberd replica?

Even Lin Ming, who didn’t know much about the top sects of the Sky Spill Continent, had heard the fierce name of this Forsaken Blood Halberd. The Forsaken Blood Halberd’s former name was the Great Desolate Blood Halberd, and it was a heaven-step treasure that was excavated from an ancient ruin. It was 10 feet long, as thick as an arm, and blood red all over.

It was rumored that this halberd was a high-grade heaven-step treasure.

The original master and creator of this Great Desolate Blood Halberd had long been lost in the vast stretches of time. But it was known that this halberd had existed at least 70 or 80 thousand years ago.

Afterwards, the Great Desolate Blood Halberd was spread through the Sky Spill Continent and passed through several owners. Of those who held this weapon in hand, it could be said that any of these characters were masters that could shake the world, among which were many Peerless Emperors!

However, this blood halberd was simply too dangerous and portentous a treasure. According to the ancient records, everyone that had ever possessed the Great Desolate Blood Halberd eventually died a miserable and violent death. Even the so-called Peerless Emperors were no exception to this rule. It could be said that their destiny which was described within the ancient texts wasn’t enough, and they died to the curse of the blood halberd.

For instance, a thousand years ago the Netherworld Great Emperor had managed to obtain the Great Desolate Blood Halberd. Unfortunately, he perished under the hands of several Peerless Emperors.

Afterwards, this blood halberd was said to have been obtained by a Supreme Elder. But according to rumors, this Supreme Elder had gone into an ancient mystic realm and had been missing for hundreds of years. Until now, there still wasn’t anyone that had a hint of where he was. Thus, the Great Desolate Blood Halberd had vanished along with him.

Humans were wonderful and contradictory creatures. The more ominous a treasure was, the more it would arouse the crazed envy of others. This was because many of them assumed that they were fated for great deeds, as if the heavens themselves had mandated that they would succeed. They believed that a great destiny had come to them and that they wouldn’t die from the blood halberd’s curse. The Great Desolate Blood Halberd even became a symbol of being a Peerless Emperor. Thus, replicas of this Great Desolate Blood Halberd had spread everywhere, and it wasn’t unusual for a genius whose ambition was to one day become a Peerless Emperor to have one.

“So you also use a long weapon.” Lin Ming’s expression was calm. Compared to the spear, the halberd head had many crescent blade tips that could be used to slash and kill. Those that wielded the spear could also wield the halberd.

“Hehe, allow me to remind you. With this blood halberd assisting me, my Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder can become 50% stronger!”

“Oh? What a coincidence. With the help of the Purple Comet Spear, my Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder can also display its greatest strength!”

As the two stared each other down, the young heroic elites present held their breaths, their hearts rapidly racing. This battle was far more wonderful than they had assumed. They thought it would be a one-sided match, but it had actually stayed even until now.

Such a fight was what these people desired to see the most. They opened their eyes wide,  fearing that they would miss any of the exciting moments.

Lei Mubai swept out his blood halberd, and his aura suddenly erupted. The true essence within his body revolved to the limit and a thick bloody energy surged forth from his body.

Chi!

The Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder flowed into the Great Desolate Blood Halberd, the entire halberd shaft growing increasingly bright red as if it were dripping blood. The savage halberd blade began to issue out a keening cry!

“Blood War Throughout the World!”

Kacha!

The tiles under Lei Mubai’s feet suddenly shattered, cracks spreading throughout like a spiderweb. Lei Mubai waved his halberd, and a bloody storm twisted into existence, sucking in all the surrounding stone, tearing it to pieces!

Facing such a powerful attack, Lin Ming gripped the Purple Comet Spear. The spearpoint drew a crescent moon on the ground and began to howl. The coiling dragon steel needle had fused into the Purple Comet Spear. Spear and thunder became one, thunder flashed, arcs of lightning danced in the air.

Lin Ming thrust out his spear, the phantom of an Azure Dragon appearing behind him once again. With this strike, it carried a primal azure true essence as well as a massive snake of thunder that was as thick as a tree trunk. With a cry from the audience, this spear contained an unstoppable momentum as it thrust towards the bloody storm.

Bang bang bang!

A series of explosions sounded in the air. The bloody light mixed with the smashed tiles and the purple electric radiance. All of the stones within were smashed into dust. As the dust mixed into the bloody storm, it transformed into red sand!

The protective array formation that the Revolving Core master had laid down began to vibrate. Cracks appeared out of thin air, and with a light ‘chi chi chi’ sound, the protective curtain of light was punctured. A savage beam of true essence pierced through!

“Be careful!”

Everyone was shocked. Several Revolving Core Elders hurried to lay down a new enchantment. However, because it was too quick, the new enchantment wasn’t able to be instantly laid down. The electric light and true essence explosion shockwave flooded out, overturning the banquet tables and smashing apart the jade dishes!

All the heroic elites of the sects began to revolve true essence around their body to protect themselves. The ones with high cultivation protected those with low cultivation. As the true essence shockwave collided against their true essence, it created a rainbow of colors that dazzled everyone present.

“Who are these two!? The true essence shockwave from their battle can break open the protective array formation and also force our disciples to resist with all their strength!”

“This is too terrifying. Look over there. Even the Deep Earth Sect’s Houtian disciples who excel at defense find this difficult to resist. Can a Houtian master truly have strength of this level!?”

“What Houtian master? That Lin Ming is clearly at the Pulse Condensation period!” With these words, everyone felt as if they were living a waking dream.

That’s right! Lin Ming wasn’t at the Houtian realm! He was even a step away from reaching the peak of Pulse Condensation!

Because of Lin Ming’s strong and dominating performance, everyone had faintly forgotten the fact that Lin Ming wasn’t a Houtian master. Just what was wrong with this world!

The ones most shocked were the Xiantian masters. As the backbone of their fourth-grade sects, they were above 30 years old, and there were even some around 40 or 50 years old.

“Such a strong attack power, is this really the strength of the younger generation? When I was at the peak Houtian realm, even I didn’t have such abnormal attack power!” Those that were able to attend this banquet celebration weren’t average martial artists. When they were at the Houtian realm, they were also outstanding martial artists that surpassed others.

“If this continues, they won’t need much time to compare to a true Xiantian master! An early Houtian realm youth can actually compare to a Xiantian master; just how strong will they be in the future? They might even become Peerless Emperors!”

The difference between the Houtian realm and the Xiantian realm was like a moat that separated the two. As one stepped from the Houtian realm into the Xiantian realm, a martial artist would be reborn as they eliminated the foul Houtian air within themselves and experienced a qualitative change to their true essence that greatly increased the intensity and thickness of it. The Xiantian realm was also considered a massive bottleneck. Every normal Houtian martial artist that had an unstable foundation would be stuck there forever; the only ones left that had a chance of ascending were the most outstanding of individuals. Even Qin Ziya, who was considered a top-class Houtian master, would only be the lowest of Xiantian powerhouses. This showed just how strong a Xiantian realm martial artist truly was.

Therefore it was especially difficult for a Houtian powerhouse to be able to jump realms and fight against a Xiantian master. Within a small sect like the Seven Profound Valleys, it was already good if there existed two or three people that could accomplish this. Not only that, but these two or three people would often be at the peak Houtian realm or even a half-step into the Xiantian realm.

On the stage, Lin Ming and Lei Mubai had already separated from each other. All of the tiles within a 100 foot radius of them had been completely demolished, and the spot where the two youths had collided had been turned into fine sand. After this sand was stained red by the blood essence within the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder, it had turned the center of the stage into a crimson desert.

Lei Mubai hadn’t expected that Lin Ming would be powerful to such a degree. When he was Lin Ming’s age, he didn’t possess this strength – did that mean that Lin Ming’s talent exceeded him?

Lei Mubai’s heart had always been heavy with pride. How could he tolerate a fourth-grade sect genius ever surpassing him!

“I really underestimated you. But, my strength is far more than that! For you to be able to force me to use my true strength, that alone is enough for you to be proud of!”

The true essence within Lei Mubai’s body began to rapidly revolve. Within his meridians, the bloody energy became increasingly thick and concentrated. His entire skeleton began to crackle, and his aura exploded along with it, frightening everyone who sensed it!

Ancient devil arts!

Huu!

The space around Lei Mubai seemed to become its own separate space; his aura increased several times over!

What he was using was the power of the ancient Devil Tome that his master had found within far off ruins!

He didn’t fear using this cultivation method. This wasn’t a cultivation method of Silent Demon Emperor City, but rather a recently unearthed ancient cultivation method manual. Regardless of whether it was Mu Yuhuang of Mu Fengxian, neither of them would be able to recognize it.

Although this wasn’t an orthodox strength, the South Horizon Region sects had never distinguished between good or evil. Everything was based only on the respect for the strong. So, there was nothing wrong with using this ancient devil art technique.

Even if there was something wrong with using this, he no longer cared. If he didn’t defeat Lin Ming here, then he would only frustrate his own spirit!

“Mm? This cultivation method!” Mu Yuhuang’s eyes shined. With the breadth of her knowledge, she was able to instantly recognize the uncommon and extraordinary nature of this cultivation method. This was obviously not the cultivation method of the Thundercrest Sect, and even if it was, it would be recently obtained by the Thundercrest Sect. There was even a high chance that it was this Lei Mubai who had found it!

“Master Ancestor, do you recognize this cultivation method?” Mu Yuhuang asked Mu Fengxian with a true essence sound transmission.

Mu Fengxian squinted her eyes as she looked at Lei Mubai, thoughtfully deliberating for a moment. Then, she hesitated and shook her head, “This cultivation method should have recently appeared in the world, this boy’s lucky fortunes are very great!”

Mu Yuhuang let out a light breath and turned to glance at Lei Jingtian. She saw that his own eyes were shining with acclaim. Suddenly, Mu Yuhuang’s heart went cold – there was an absolute chance that this cultivation method was found by Lei Mubai!

With such a great lucky opportunity falling upon him, she feared that Lei Mubai really might become an almighty Peerless Emperor!

Lei Mubai’s ancient devil arts were truly amazing. But Lin Ming was indifferent. Among everyone present, there was no one who was more experienced in the highest level cultivation methods that him.

In the fragmented memories of the Realm of the Gods’ Supreme Elders, there were countless incomplete cultivation methods, most of them being sporadic and fragmented worthless bits. But Lin Ming still looked over these one at a time. As he compared them to Lei Mubai’s ancient devil arts, he came to the conclusion that these ancient devil arts were probably created by a Peerless Emperor that originated from the Sky Spill Continent.

Perhaps this Peerless Emperor died of old age or perhaps he soared up into the Realm of the Gods. Regardless of what happened, this cultivation method that he left behind as his legacy could only be considered the lowest third-rate cultivation method within the Realm of the Gods.

Under the shadow of the crimson light, Lei Mubai gripped the Great Desolate Blood Halberd, his clothes fluttering in the wind and his jet black hair recklessly flying. With the bloody lightning that twined around his entire body, he was like an ancient demon god that descended into the world.

Lei Mubai stood there, his aura filled with utter disdain for the world. All the young heroic elites felt that Lei Mubai was no different than a giant mountain that stood before him, an unattainable and distant existence. As for the young female disciples of the Five Element Region, their beautiful faces blushed and their hearts wildly beat. As for Zhou Xiaoling, her eyes never left Lei Mubai for a second.

Zhou Lie saw the entranced expression on his younger sister’s face and sighed. He didn’t say anything further. Whether it was Lei Mubai or Lin Ming, they were both characters that had already surpassed the realm of his comprehension.

“Lin Ming! Do you still think you can defeat me!?”

Lei Mubai slowly said, his every word dripping with overbearing arrogance!

His strength had grown two-fold. If he used Blood War Throughout the World again, the power of that move would also be doubled!

Chapter 384 – Tempering Marrow VS Devil Arts

Facing the blazoning might of the ancient devil arts and the crazy Lei Mubai whose hair was bathed in a blood red light, Lin Ming was finally able to completely confirm that Lei Mubai was from the South Sea Demon Region.

‘The ancient devil arts can multiply one’s own strength?’ Lin Ming’s lips curved up in a smile, ‘If I hadn’t completed 20% of Tempering Marrow then I would absolutely have lost this battle. But now, Lei Mubai is able to have me fight to the limits of my strength! With 20% Tempering Marrow added together with the opening of the Heretical God Force, just what would the result be?’

Lin Ming gripped the Purple Comet Spear horizontally and stood tall on the stage, his body exuding a virtuous light. Suddenly, his aura began to thicken, becoming increasingly swift and fierce, and a spear intent that could sweep away all surged forth. At this moment, Lin Ming was like a unrivalled treasure spear, immeasurably keen. With a single thought, he could pierce through the world!

“Mm? Lin Ming’s aura is also intensifying!”

“It’s not only his aura that is intensifying, but the true essence in his body is becoming increasingly thick! Heavens! How can a Pulse Condensation period martial artist have such thick true essence within their body!?”

In this instant, everyone was able to clearly feel the vast aura emitting from Lin Ming’s body like an endless ocean. His true essence was like the wild waves of a storm, boundless and infinite!

With just Lin Ming’s meridians and acupoints, he was naturally unable to release such terrifying true essence. A great deal of Lin Ming’s true essence had been hidden within his marrow, and now all of that hidden true essence had spewed out; the power of 20% of Tempering Marrow completely broke free!

On the banquet’s seat of honor, Mu Fengxian’s sleepy eyes suddenly popped open, an expression of disbelief coloring them. She quietly watched Lin Ming for several breaths of times, took a deep breath, and then said to herself, “This child is a dragon within a deep pool. If my Divine Phoenix Island has a great enough destiny and we are able to survive the incoming cataclysm to wait until the day that this dragon soars into the sky, my Divine Phoenix Island will also be a phoenix that rebirths through nirvana, soaring along with it…”

As Lin Ming’s aura increased, all of the juniors beneath the stage stared with wide eyes. Their mouths were dry, and they watched with utter astonishment.

Lei Mubai couldn’t bear it. As this aura rose, he was no longer willing to wait.

The Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder erupted. Lei Mubai cried out, “Blood Dyes the World!”

The blood halberd swept out. After this move broke forth, the aura of the stage suddenly changed, as if tumultuous and violent waves of blood were crashing around. Lei Mubai tread forwards, and his body was like a phantom as he instantly flashed in front of Lin Ming, his spear sweeping towards his waist.

This halberd strike carried a heavy, roaring potential. Even a small mountain peak would be crushed by this sweeping blow!

In the halberd, Lin Ming could feel all the blood of his body being pulled by an invisible force, rushing to the surface and boiling in his veins as if it would break out of his body!

‘This is the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder’s effect on blood essence? Lei Mubai has no intention of staying his hand at all. If a normal martial artist were to be swept by this halberd, their blood would flow backwards and they would have already died from shock!’

Lin Ming’s mind raced. The coiling dragon steel needle had fused into the Purple Comet Spear, and now the spear seemed to contain its own indelible will. A spear swept out, and because of the instant acceleration, the Purple Comet Spear slightly bent like a whip as he crashed into the blood halberd.

Kacha!

As soon as the blood halberd collided with the Purple Comet Spear, the blood halberd was suppressed. It was like a blood red massive shark that was abruptly pressed down in the water!

The Purple Comet Spear pressed down on the Great Desolate Blood Halberd! The compressed blood vitality of the halberd broke free, creating crashing waves of vibrant blood!

The two young masters struggled, their spear and halberd clashing with each other as red and purple thunder sizzled the air.

The impact of the intense purple and red true essence formed a howling tornado. The tornado picked up the countless crushed stones on the ground, and sent them shooting towards the protective light array enchantment.

Ping ping ping!

The reinforced light screen severely trembled once more.

The complexions of all the heroic elites changed, especially the Xiantian realm martial artists’. They were all frightened, unable to comprehend what was happening. With two juniors fighting, their auras were actually filled with the power of crushing avalanches and tsunamis. Was this really battle between two of the younger generation?

Lei Mubai clenched his teeth, all of the muscles of his body bulging, his blue veins popping up. He had no choice but to admit that Lin Ming had the qualifications to fight him on equal standing!

‘This boy, his true essence is as thick as my own even after I used the ancient devil arts; how is this possible!? A frontal attack is not possible, I have to avoid his Purple Comet Spear and only attack his body.’

As Lei Mubai thought this, he suddenly rapidly dashed around, his footwork accelerating. As he stepped back, his form began erratic, drifting from place to place. The blood halberd in his hand also became a series of blood shades!

“You want to compare speed?” Lin Ming’s smirked. Lei Mubai was not a martial artist who specialized in speed like Jiang Baoyun. If he wanted to have a battle of speed, then he was not afraid. Not to mention that his comprehension of the Concept of Wind deepened with every day, and his Golden Roc Shattering the Void also drew closer to the second layer with every passing day. Soon, it would break through to the next level!

Ca!

Lei Mubai appeared like a ghost behind Lin Ming, his halberd cutting down. However, this halberd directly cut through Lin Ming’s waist, but passed straight through. At this moment, Lin Ming had vanished, leaving nothing behind by an afterimage!

It was just an instant, but Lin Ming had already moved dozens of feet away. “You are fast, but your weapon is a halberd. A halberd is not suited for speed!”

Lei Mubai’s pale face darkened. In terms of speed, a halberd was naturally inferior to a sword. This was common knowledge. But now, since he couldn’t directly confront Lin Ming, he could only compare his speed. “I don’t need you to teach me anything!”

Lin Ming sneered, and suddenly a invisible cyclone of wind formed around his body, propping him up. After he had exposed his ability to fly, he had no more need to conceal the secret of Golden Roc Shattering the Void. “How skillful. In terms of speed, I too am confident in myself!”

On the stage, forceful gales rampaged through the air. Lin Ming stepped forwards with Golden Roc Shattering the Void, and his body became a series of phantom images. With the Concept of Wind fused into the Purple Comet Spear, every spear strike contained a whistling wind origin energy.

In that moment, Lin Ming’s spear shade turned into wind, and the wind became the spear shade. It could not be dispersed, it could not be avoided!

Hu!

Hu!

Suddenly, all of the red and purple lightning on the stage was swept up into a massive vortex, Lin Ming and Lei Mubai disappearing together.

“Where are they?”

“There’s only the afterimage left, I can’t see them!”

Those whose cultivation was below the Houtian realm had already lost track of Lin Ming and Lei Mubai’s shadows. Even the Houtian realm disciples found it hard to see just where they were.

Zhan Yunjian took a deep breath, sighing as emotion filled his heart. So this power was that of the Kings of the younger generation? Perhaps in his entire life he would never be able to surpass them!

“Their strength can actually compare to a Xiantian master!”

Within the banquet area of Golden Bell Mountain, an early Xiantian master shook his head, overwhelmed by the scene in front of him.

“Before, I had thought that their strength was slightly better than when I was at the Houtian realm, but it seems that now, even I don’t dare to say that I could defeat them!”

………………..

“Blood Scattering Endless Sky!”

Lei Mubai gripped the Great Desolate Blood Halberd and smashed down. With an explosion, a massive hole dozens of feet deep was created within the stage. However, Lin Ming had already dodged early, avoiding this attack. Even so, the blood within his body still violently tumbled within him.

“This fellow is too strong!” Lin Ming forcefully suppressed his surging blood. He still had his two final cards: the Heretical God Force and Thunderfire Annihilation. However, these two moves could only be used once, and he had to do so wisely. Otherwise, if he missed or failed, he would instantly be defeated!

Lei Mubai grinned. “You’ve forced me to this point. Now that the battle has reached this stage, even if I have to sacrifice my strength I will still cut you underneath my halberd!”

As Lei Mubai spoke, the skin all over his body began to crack open with a ‘ka ka’ sound. Clouds of bloody fog ruptured forth from these cracks.

“Blood Shadow Avatar!”

As Lei Mubai cried out, the blood fog actually turned into a red human’s shadow that took Lei Mubai’s form. This shadow had no weapon. Instead, there was a long devil claw that was its hand.

Lin Ming was surprised but he didn’t panic. He had already seen a similar attack method at the Seven Profound Valleys’ Total Faction Martial Meeting.

“Go! Suck dry his blood essence!”

The crimson Blood Shadow Avatar uttered a shrill scream, and then reached out its giant claw towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming appeared calm. His moved with Golden Roc Shattering the Void and his figure instantly drew back. At the same time, the Purple Comet Spear in his hand flashed with thunder. The power of thunder was the most effective counter to demons and ghost. He didn’t believe that this Blood Shadow Avatar would be able to block the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder.

“Your opponent is me!”

Lei Mubai’s cold words resounded within Lin Ming’s ears. At the same time, the Great Desolate Blood Halberd slashed down!

Pincer attack?

Lin Ming frowned. The Purple Comet Spear in his hand thrust forth to meet the Great Desolate Blood Halberd!

Dang!

As the spear and halberd collided, the blood essence within Lin Ming’s body roiled and his true essence went into disorder. As for Lei Mubai, his organs were violently shaken by the azure true essence and his face turned ashen.

“Ahh!”

At this moment, the Blood Shadow Avatar cried and extended its claw. The claw grasped at Lin Ming’s throat!

But at this time, Lin Ming’s Purple Comet Spear was already thrust out. He would not be able to pull it back in time and then thrust out again!

At this crucial moment, Lin Ming’s right hand released the Purple Comet Spear. A deep azure light formed on his fist, carrying the power of thunder. This fist punched towards the Blood Shadow Avatar’s blood claw!

“Humph, you are seeking death!” Lei Mubai grinned like a demon. The Blood Shadow Avatar’s claw was as hard as a divine weapon; its toughness was comparable to a low-grade earth-step treasure. To use a flesh and blood fist to meet this claw was no different than courting death!

“Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist!”

In that moment, Lin Ming’s true essence revolved to the limit. 10,000 vibrating true essence filaments roared forth, carrying the integrated power of the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder as well as the power of the 20% completed Tempering Marrow. This strike contained his full strength!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s fist smashed into the Blood Shadow Avatar’s claw. The power of vibration and the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder erupted. There was a loud ‘chi chi chi’ sound as the blood claw was ignited by the thunder before it suddenly exploded into a bloody fog!

“What!?”

Lei Mubai’s mind shook and then he spat out a mouthful of blood. The Blood Shadow Avatar was connected to his body – if it took damage, so would he!

As Lei Mubai spat blood, he kneeled on the floor, a looked of incredible disbelief in his eyes as he stared at Lin Ming. How was this possible? A bare human fist had shattered the Blood Shadow Avatar’s demon claw!?

“Lei Mubai is injured!”

“Heavens! This is too fearful. Lei Mubai’s strength is already so terrifying, but he was actually severely wounded by Lin Ming!?”

All of the young heroic elites present sucked in a deep breath.

Everyone believed that Lei Mubai had been hiding his strength, but no one imagined that he would be so strong.

However, what was even more unbelievable was that this amazingly strong Lei Mubai was actually severely wounded by Lin Ming!

Chapter 386 – Action First, Consequences Later

The Thundercrest Sovereign Sect Lei Jingtian was shaking in disbelief. No one understood more than him just how terrifying Lei Mubai’s strength was. But now, this Lin Ming had actually jumped realms and defeated him! The mental impact that this brought was too great, he simply couldn’t believe it!

As for the young disciples of the Five Element Region, all of them were still in a daze. Whether it was Lei Mubai or Lin Ming, the power of these two had already surpassed the scope of their understanding. And now, Lin Ming’s victory made them feel like they were living a lucid dream.

This was the first time they ever realized that a late Pulse Condensation martial artist and an early Houtian martial artist could achieve such a degree of power.

This shock was too intense, none of them were able to open their mouths to speak. Even a Saint rank talent wasn’t insufficient to describe Lin Ming. In their view, he was like a character that had only existed in ancient legends. For instance, the Netherworld Great Emperor, who had once taken the heads of all the sect leaders of the Five Element Region…

Within the Sunfire Sect banquet area, the Sunfire Princess stared at Lin Ming, her heart pounding and her face flushed red, sighing. She had been feeling a bit resentful because the spotlight had been stolen from her, but after bearing witness to the glorious battle between Lin Ming and Lei Mubai, she instead felt that she was very lucky. With her strength, if she went onstage it would be nothing more than a good laugh.

“How deplorable. I once thought that I was a top talent, but now, it seems I was just a frog in a well.”

It wasn’t just the Sunfire Princess, but even the proud Zhou Lie, the clear Zhan Yunjian, and the indifferent Bai Aoxuan, all of them had the same idea. Ever since they were children, they had grown up under the aurora of being top geniuses, and they had no peers that were able to compete on their level. This inevitably gave birth to thoughts that they would become the future heroes of the world. But now, if they compared themselves with Lin Ming, they feared that they would never catch up to him in their lifetimes.

Mu Fengxian withdrew her gaze, her eyes slowly closing. Lin Ming was a genius that had exceeded the ability of Divine Phoenix Island to raise. Such an existence should have appeared in a fifth-grade sect, or even a Holy Land.

Only a great power that had thousands or even tens of thousands of years of accumulated destiny would be able to raise a genius like Lin Ming so that he could one day become a Peerless Emperor. He would one day ascend to the skies, eventually leaving behind an indelible legacy in his people, being known as an unrivalled Peerless Great Emperor.

Within the entire square, no one spoke for several breaths of time; the audience was starkly silent. The Revolving Core Elders were sighing in their hearts, and the young heroic elites were etching the details of this battle between young Kings in their mind. This battle had simply left too great an impression on their minds, and had completely subverted the way in which they view the world. Before, many of them had dreams of being a chosen of heaven that would ascend to the heavens, but now, it was as if they had been rudely awakened from this dream. Perhaps, to them, this wasn’t a bad thing at all.

In the silence of the square, as the audience was still disoriented, Lin Ming recovered the Purple Comet Spear and moved towards Lei Mubai, one step at a time.

At this time, Lei Mubai was kneeling on the floor, the light in his eyes dim and his mouth wet with blood. He still remained conscious, but because his injuries were too heavy and he had consumed too much blood essence, he was on the verge of teetering over on the floor.

Seeing Lin Ming walk towards him, Lei Mubai’s once dim eyes turned a bright blood red. His murderous intent and will to kill burst forth. He wanted to open his mouth to spit out several words, but as he tried to speak, all that came flowing out was blood, and he simply couldn’t say a word.

Today’s shame had forever etched itself into Lei Mubai’s heart. If he didn’t avenge this disgrace, this would become a barrier in Lei Mubai that would frustrate his spirit and stymie his every effort.

Those that cultivated in the demonic path were much more focused on making sure that their thoughts flowed freely and their spirit was unburdened. The demonic path had always been synonymous with doing whatever one wished, unlike the righteous path where there were still many morals and principles one had to follow.

Those that cultivated the demonic path took the world as their enemy and went against all living beings. If they didn’t act in a manner that satisfied their own desires, then what was the point of cultivating the demonic path? They may as well pray to Buddha!

Lei Mubai couldn’t speak, thus he only cursed in his heart. ‘On the day that Divine Phoenix Island is exterminated, I will have you beg for death. I will waste your martial arts, break your four limbs and stick you in a box. I will have you watch as I freely use all of the resources that Divine Phoenix Island has accumulated. I will also waste Mu Qianyu and Mu Bingyun’s martial arts, and strip their clothes naked in front of you. I will ravage them, humiliate them, and obtain their bloodlines!’

As Lei Mubai thought this, his lips curved up in a smile. The destruction of Divine Phoenix Island would happen sooner or later, that day was not too far away.

As he saw Lin Ming’s eyes contain a murderous intent that wished to kill him, he sneered. ‘Pitiful. No matter how talented you are, you’re still trapped in the fourth-grade sect that is Divine Phoenix Island. This is no different than placing shackles on your feet. You will never ascend to the heavens!’

“Lin… Ming… one day… I will avenge today’s shame!” Lei Mubai said with a true essence sound transmission. With his current condition, even using a true essence sound transmission was very difficult.

Lin Ming acted as if he didn’t even hear Lei Mubai’s true essence sound transmission. Instead, he brightly smiled as he sauntered over and placed his hand on Lei Mubai’s shoulder, a friendly gesture as if he wanted to help lift him up.

Lei Mubai’s entire body stiffened, “You…”

“Before, I had said that you didn’t understand the situation you were in. And even now, you still don’t understand just what situation you’re in. Avenge the shame of today? I’m sorry, but it seems that you’ll never have the opportunity to do so.” Lin Ming’s lips moved, his bone chilling true essence sound transmission sounding in Lei Mubai’s ears, making him feel like he had fallen into an icy sea.

“You’re… crazy…!”

“Now die!”

Lin Ming’s smiling face suddenly turned cold. He lifted his palm and smashed it down on Lei Mubai’s chest.

Pulse Cutting Palm!

Peng!

Lei Mubai’s body shook. He was already weakened to the point that he could no longer resist. Lin Ming’s brutal power broke into his meridians, shredding them all to pieces!

Puff!

Lei Mubai crazily spat out blood, his mind filled with incredible disbelief. This Lin Ming, he was utterly mad!

This incident had happened so suddenly that when Lin Ming had struck Lei Mubai with his palm, none of the Revolving Core masters were able to stop him. Everyone thought that Lin Ming was about to support Lei Mubai up by his arm, but none of them thought that Lin Ming would take advantage of this time when Lei Mubai had lost all strength to resistance to lay down such a heavy strike. What was he doing? Was he trying to provoke a war between Divine Phoenix Island and the Five Element Region?

Divine Phoenix Island was already in a very precarious situation. If they provoked such outrage and stirred up a war with the Five Element Region, they would absolutely die!

Lin Ming’s actions were only digging his own grave! Even if he was a character that was destined to become a Peerless Emperor in the future, at this moment, Divine Phoenix Island would not dare to protect him!

“Boy, you are seeking death!”

No one was more enraged than Lei Jingtian. Lei Mubai was the Saint Son of the South Sea Demon Region! He was the future leader of the South Sea Demon Region!

If he died here, the South Sea Demon Region would vent their rage upon him. Even if the South Sea Demon Region didn’t bother with him now because of their war with Divine Phoenix Island, they would not pardon him in the future. As for his dreams of the ancient Devil Tome, that had all fallen apart!

Lei Jingtian had never felt so angry before. His hands flashed with a purple electric light and his palm slammed down towards Lin Ming. This palm strike was able to instantly kill a late Xiantian realm master; Lin Ming would absolutely die.

Everyone was too surprised to even call out. Lei Jingtian’s palm was already coming down. Under the violent compression of energy, the space around Lin Ming tightened as if it were rooting him in place, not allowing him to move. But the truth was, even if Lin Ming could freely move, he still wouldn’t be able to dodge.

“Lei Jingtian, what are you doing!?”

At this critical moment, Mu Yuhuang appeared like a blaze of flame on the stage, her palm coming up to meet Lei Jingtian. A loud thunderclap roared through the square!

Bang!

Lei Jingtian was forced back several steps. As for Mu Yuhuang, she shook for a moment before firmly steadying herself.

Lei Jingtian’s was shaking with fury. “What am I doing!? I should ask you what you are doing! Mu Yuhuang, are you planning on allowing your disciple to recklessly murder others!?”

At this moment, Mu Yuhuang had a very ugly complexion. In the moment that Lin Ming had taken action, she had heard a true essence sound transmission from him, “Lei Mubai is a spy from the South Sea Demon Region!”

Lin Ming had completely taken action first and worried about consequences later. Mu Yuhuang hadn’t even had the time to respond!

Even the strong-willed Mu Yuhuang was in a complete mess. The consequences of this incident were simply too great; six of the seven great sects of the Five Element Region were present today and closely watching. This boy Lin Ming, how was he planning on revealing everything!?

If he didn’t have proof to back up his thoughts, even Divine Phoenix Island wouldn’t be able to maintain his life!

She wanted to rebuke Lin Ming, but now was not the time to reprimand him. Since what had happened had happened, first, she had to resolve this issue.

The Elders of the Five Element Region’s sects had also stood up, anger on their faces as they glared at Lin Ming. No matter what, the Five Element Region’s seven great sects of metal, wood, water, fire, earth, wind, and thunder were all connected to each other; how could they tolerate something like this occurring?

At this point, Lei Mubai already seemed to be dying, the faint embers of his life flickering away. All of his meridians had been shattered, but he still clung to his single breath and didn’t faint. He wasn’t even able to make an expression of anger on his face. He could only relentlessly stare at Lin Ming, unadulterated hatred in his eyes; it was absolutely alarming!

Lei Mubai hadn’t yet realized just what Lin Ming had done to him. He only felt that the meridians in his body had broken in many places. Although it was difficult to treat damage to the meridians, a fifth-grade sect still had the means to do so. It would only require him to stay in bed for several months.

Of course, this was only Lei Mubai’s one-sided wishful thinking.

Lin Ming completely ignored the hate within Lei Mubai’s eyes and faced the anger from the Elders of the Five Element Region’s six sects. He confidently cupped his hands across his chest in a polite ritual and said, “Thunder Sovereign said that I killed him. But that is wrong. Even though my method was extreme, Lei Mubai is still alive.”

Lei Jingtian didn’t think that these would be the first to come out of Lin Ming’s mouth. He began to tremble with anger. “You shattered all his meridians and yet you speak such sarcastic words! Today, this old man will beat this little bastard to death!”

Lei Jingtian’s momentum exploded. But with Mu Yuhuang in front of him, there was nothing he could do.

Lin Ming said, “All of the actions I’ve taken naturally have a reason, and that is that Lei Mubai is from the South Sea Demon Region. Don’t tell me that the Thunder Sovereign doesn’t know this fact!”

“What!?”

With Lin Ming’s words, the entire audience was startled, their minds shaking. Even Lei Jingtian was filled with disbelief. How was this possible? How had he discovered this!?

However, he had lived for several hundred years and managed not to lose his composure. He immediately denied this. “What irresponsible fiction! Mubai is the genius that I personally discovered within the northern domains three years ago! His background is clean; how could he possibly be a spy!?

Although Lei Jingtian was very skilled at covering his expression, there was still a slight true essence fluctuation that he emitted from the shock of a moment ago. All of this was keenly captured by Mu Yuhuang’s senses.

Chapter 388 – Alliance

Lin Ming coolly divided the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal into thirds, and then gave one third to the Golden Bell Mountain Elder and another to the Arctic Ice Palace Elder. These two were still confused about what was happening, so Elder Jin asked, “Lin Ming, what’s the meaning of this?”

Lin Ming faintly smile and said, “Once you swallow this Shattered Demon Heart Crystal, you will be able to feel the energy of the Netherworld Great Emperor. When that happens, you two will discover that this energy is the same as Lei Mubai’s!”

“Mm!?” Elder Jin’s expression chanced. If Lin Ming was willing to use his life as the stake in this matter, he was most likely confident in this!

Elder Jin gave Lei Jingtian a deep look. After he saw the ugly expression of Lei Jingtian, he already had certain conclusions made up within his mind.

Lin Ming bowed and said, “Since this matter is related to my life, I would like to kindly request that two seniors take a pledge to their heart of martial arts that their words will ring true.”

Taking a pledge on one’s heart of martial wasn’t truly effective for any situation. When it came to matters that were extremely important to oneself, one could still break it. But in this situation, the two Elders naturally wouldn’t renege on their word.

“That’s understandable here. Then, this old man will swear on his heart of martial arts that every word I say will be true.” Elder Jin frankly said.

After Elder Jin made his pledge, the female Elder from Arctic Ice Palace followed him.

The two of them fused their blood with the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal and prepared to swallow it. The Shattered Demon Heart Crystal only had a very small effect on a Revolving Core elder. But, it would still be able to slightly increase their cultivation.

After the two of them swallowed the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal thirds, they sat in meditation and steadily breathed. The two of them had a cultivation at the middle Revolving Core realm. Naturally, once the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal’s energy was released into their bodies, it wouldn’t be dangerous at all.

The two Elders had agitated expressions. They too had seen the same scene as Lin Ming. They saw the Netherworld Great Emperor as he fought against countless demons. This sort of boundless and unreachable magnificence and momentum that resounded through the universe really made one’s mind tremble in awe.

A moment later, Elder Jin let out a long breath; he was the first to open his eyes.

Mu Yuhuang’s eyebrows rose. Mu Qianyu’s heartbeat also quickened. At this moment, everyone’s eyes were focused on Elder Jin.

Lin Ming was silent. He only quietly watched Elder Jin, waiting for his final judgement.

Elder Jing meaningfully looked at Lin Ming. He didn’t directly respond, instead asking, “Lin Ming, have you swallowed the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal? Otherwise, there is no way you would have known this so clearly.”

Lin Ming nodded, acknowledging this.

“Haha! You are truly a thousand year talent of the South Horizon Region. You only have a cultivation at the mere Pulse Condensation period, yet you can swallow the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal. This old man is too surprised!”

Elder Jin heavily sighed, and then spoke in a clarion tone that resounded through the square, “What Lin Ming said is true. This old man truly felt the energy of the Netherworld Great Emperor come from Lei Mubai’s body. This kind of energy can only originate from a bloodline legacy. If this old man guesses correctly, then this so-called Lei Mubai is most likely a direct descendant of the Netherworld Great Emperor!”

As Elder Jin spoke, the entire audience was petrified. Lei Jingtian’s face was already colored like liver. As for Shi Zhongkun, he also had a very ugly expression. He had come up to antagonize Lin Ming, but he was once again humiliated by him.

Arctic Ice Palace’s Elder Bai also opened her eyes at this moment, slowly nodding, fully agreeing with Elder Jin’s words.

Mu Yuhuang was finally able to relax, her heart calming down. She looked at Lei Jingtian and coldly asked, “Lei Jingtian, do you have anything to say about this? Lin Ming just asked you a question a moment ago, and you said that his parents had been mortals.”

“But according to this old woman, the Netherworld Great Emperor’s descendants had all ran away to the South Sea Demon Region, now becoming the core of that evil sect. This old woman had never once heard that there were any mortals that had this bloodline, and had also died in the chaos of mortal wars!”

Lei Jingtian was forced speechless by Mu Yuhuang’s words, he simply had no way to respond to this. He finally clenched his teeth and said, “Everything that I knew about Mubai’s background was told to me by him, how was I supposed to know what is true or false? Moreover, even though Elder Jin was likely correct in his assumption, that doesn’t mean that it is absolutely true.”

Elder Jin glanced at Lei Jingtian with contempt. At this time, he was still speaking his useless sophistry and attempting to leave a way to back out by saying that he may have been wrong.

Compared to Lin Ming’s fuzzy judgement, Elder Jin was much more clear in his assessment. Lin Ming had swallowed the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal a long time ago. As for Elder Jin, he was able to contrast the energy within the Shattered Demon Hearty Crystal with Lei Mubai in front of him. Naturally, his assurance of the facts was much greater.

Seeing Lei Jingtian quibble over such minor issues, Lin Ming grinned and said, “Thunder Sovereign, I just happen to know some methods of torture that are good at extracting information. If Thunder Sovereign isn’t opposed, I can attempt to try these methods on Lei Mubai, and perhaps we may be able to obtain some ‘unexpected’ information.

As Lin Ming bit out the word ‘unexpected’, Lei Jingtian suddenly felt a cold chill run down his spine. This boy, he was actually threatening him!

As Lei Jingtian looked at this dead-eyed Lei Mubai who was lying on the ground like a dead dog, he felt fear grip him. He wasn’t able to guarantee that this fellow wouldn’t randomly bite him in his desperate state.

The South Sea Demon Region had a very vile reputation. If Lei Jingtian was known to have formed an alliance with the South Sea Demon Region for his own personal gain, then everything he had ever done would be vilified. He would lose any face he had, and he would be held in contempt by everyone.

Lei Jingtian’s face changed colors, alternating between red and blue. As he stood on the stage, there wasn’t a single word he could say!

Lin Ming whispered some words into Mu Yuhuang’s ear, and Mu Yuhuang suddenly smiled. She waved her hand to release the true essence sound transmission inhibiting enchantment, allowing Lei Jingtian to speak.

“Boy, what do you want to do?” Lei Jingtian asked with a true essence sound transmission. At this time, Lei Jingtian was fuming with outrage. He was a proud and dignified Sovereign of a fourth-grade sect, and yet he was actually pushed to this point by Lin Ming. He even had to humbly talk conditions with Lin Ming; how could he not be angry?

“Thunder Sovereign, perhaps you can speak with Senior Mu about creating the alliance again. How about it?”

Although Lin Ming hoped that he would be able to cripple Lei Jingtian, this was only a fanciful thought. Even it was proven beyond a doubt that Lei Jingtian had secretly made deals with the South Sea Demon Region, he wouldn’t be able to do anything to him. At most, he could only ruin his reputation forever.

After all, Lei Jingtian was the Thundercrest Sovereign, and also an almighty Revolving Core Supreme Elder. What could Divine Phoenix Island do against him? If they killed him here, that would rouse retaliation from the Thundercrest Sect.

“Are you threatening this old man!?”

“Threatening you?” Lin Ming smiled. “Does the Thunder Sovereign still believe that your deal with the South Sea Demon Region can continue in these circumstances?”

Lei Jingtian grit his teeth.

As for Mu Yuhuang, she was smiling. She had never expected that this banquet competition would have such a dramatic result. Lei Jingtian had fallen into his own trap. Just thinking about made her feel extremely satisfied.

Mu Yuhuang intentionally spoke in the presence of everyone, “It seems as if Thunder Sovereign has been deceived by Lei Mubai. If I were the Thunder Sovereign, I would immediately kill Lei Mubai here and clean the sect of this trash.”

Mu Yuhuang’s words had instantly placed Lei Jingtian into a dilemma. If he killed Lei Mubai, that would directly make him an enemy of the South Sea Demon Region. If he didn’t kill Lei Mubai, everyone would suspect that he had an unclear and dangerous relationship with him.

Lei Jingtian clenched his teeth, and sent a true essence sound transmission to Lin Ming and Mu Yuhuang, “Don’t push things too far! Early tomorrow morning I will speak to the Five Element Region’s Elders again about forming the alliance! Now, give me Lei Mubai!”

Now that matters had devolved to this point, Lei Jingtian only wanted to obtain the ancient Devil Tome in Lei Mubai’s spatial ring. Although it was only the first volume and the rest would be impossible to obtain, it was still better than nothing.

Lin Ming said, “Lei Mubai can be handed to Thunder Sovereign, but he cannot be brought down the mountain. As for Lei Mubai’s Thunder Soul and spatial ring, these will be left behind.”

Lei Jingtian frowned, “You still want to loot in this chaos? Most of what is in Lei Mubai’s spatial ring belongs to my Thundercrest Sect! Why should I give anything to you!?”

Lin Ming smiled. “Thunder Sovereign is really forgetful. Before, didn’t Thunder Sovereign say that Lei Mubai’s Thunder Soul and cultivation method were found in some ancient ruins somewhere? Thunder Sovereign also added that since ancient times, geniuses had always had great destinies fall on their bodies. Since what Lei Mubai has doesn’t belong to the Thundercrest Sect, and Lei Mubai is also a spy who was captured by me, then according to this, it stands to reason that everything he has should belong to me. What does Thunder Sovereign think of this?”

As Lin Ming leisurely spoke, his words almost caused Lei Jingtian to vomit blood on the spot.

Lei Jingtian felt that today he had been made into a complete fool, being led in circles all day. He pointed at Lin Ming, his fingers shaking, but ultimately didn’t say anything. Finally, he grit his teeth and turned around to leave. As the Thundercrest Sect disciples saw Lei Jingtian’s anger that was like a billowing inferno, none of them said anything, only quickly following behind him.

Only Zhou Xiaoling was left, slumped over on her chair. She watched Lei Mubai, who was lying prone on the ground like a dead dog, and her eyes glazed over.

Lei Mubai was defeated by Lin Ming… Lei Mubai was a spy… Lei Mubai’s meridians had all been wasted by Lin Ming…

As her mind echoed with these thoughts, she felt as if she was going crazy.

Zhou Lie glanced at his little sister and deeply sighed, not saying anything. He knew that at this moment, no matter what he said, she wouldn’t listen to him.

On the stage, the only Elder left was Shi Zhongkun. His expression wasn’t much better than Lei Jingtian’s. He also felt like he had been made into a clown. He had stupidly jumped onto the stage to get some revenge, but not only did he fail, he also attracted scorn and ridicule.

“Elder Shi, is something wrong?” Lin Ming asked with a smile.

Shi Zhongkun coldly humphed, “Truly, heroes come from the young. Young Hero Lin, this old man admires you very much!” After Elder Shi said this, he quickly walked offstage. As for the Deep Earth Sect disciples, they began to file out of the square. At this time, there were only disciples of the four other sects left over. Because of the fight between Lin Ming and Lei Mubai, all of the tables had been overturned and the dishes had all been shattered. Naturally, there was no way to continue the banquet celebrations.

The other four great sects bid their farewells and also left.

Mu Yuhuang was in an extremely good mood. Even if tomorrow’s alliance didn’t work out, the fact that she could ruin Lei Jingtian’s face today also made her feel fabulous.

Not only that, now that she had his weakness, it was highly likely that Lei Jingtian would yield tomorrow. The reason that the last meeting with the six great sects from the Five Element Region hadn’t worked out was because Lei Jingtian had bit down and wouldn’t let go, not allowing concessions anywhere. Since the other sects didn’t want to lose out, the whole negotiation had broken down.

But as long as Lei Jingtian would seal his loud mouth, the negotiations could smoothly proceed.

Mu Yuhuang looked at Lin Ming, revealing a grateful and happy smile. Lin Ming was truly Divine Phoenix Island’s lucky star. At today’s banquet celebrations, Lin Ming had single-handedly earned the greatest merit!

Lin Ming had not only displayed a magnificent performance as he defeated all the heroic elites that challenged him, allowing Divine Phoenix Island to gain face, but he had also made Lei Jingtian eat his own sh*t, making it so that he had no choice but to renegotiate with Divine Phoenix Island. This reversal of fortune that was impossible for Mu Yuhuang to accomplish had actually been accomplished by Lin Ming.

Chapter 390 – Absorbing the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder

At the central region of the bonfire party, there was a bevy of six or seven young girls excitedly speaking as they formed a circle. Along with everyone else, it was simply packed tight with people close enough to push each other.

“Lin Ming.” A woman’s crisp and clear voice sounded.

Lin Ming turned his head to see that the one who spoke was Mu Qianyu.

All the disciples that were sitting around the fire quickly rose up to salute. Compared to an Elder of Divine Phoenix Island, Mu Qianyu’s status was even higher than some.

Mu Qianyu smiled and said, “Lei Mubai is locked up in the dungeon, would you like to go and see him now?”

Lin Ming was slightly stunned, then he happily said, “Alright.”

Before this, Lin Ming had been called over to Mu Yuhuang, and they had conversed for a good two hours. He didn’t even have time to spare a thought to Lei Mubai.

When Mu Qianyu arrived, the entire atmosphere of the party became wary. Mu Qianyu glanced at all the young girls that surrounded Lin Ming and faintly smiled, sending him a true essence sound transmission, “Do you think my Divine Phoenix Island is heaven on earth for male disciples?”

Lin Ming’s voice paused. He ruefully smiled. “Miss Mu, please don’t joke with me. It was just a short time but I’ve already had to make many promises to them.”

“Haha,” Mu Qianyu chuckled, “from now on you may call me Senior-apprentice Sister. Honorable Master has already received you as a disciple. Also, Master Ancestor would like to see you.”

“Mm.”

“Master Ancestor should probably want to discuss the matter of entering the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm. That’s right, weren’t you interested in all those things that Lei Mubai had?”

“I am indeed interested.” Lin Ming honestly replied.

“Mm. Master said to hand everything to you as long as you don’t kill him.  As I remember, your methods were sufficiently ruthless. The elder that was healing Lei Mubai used a great deal of top medicines, but that fellow is still lying half-dead without much hope to live longer. All of the meridians in his body have been depleted and shattered, and his martial arts have been wasted.” Mu Qianyu looked at Lin Ming, a deep expression in her eyes. This was the first time that she had seen such a martial arts crippling technique. She had no idea where Lin Ming could have studied this from.

Lin Ming laughed twice and didn’t answer. The Realm of the Gods’ Pulse Cutting Palm was an extremely sinister and cruel move. As for wanting to heal the damage, well… not even the miracle medicines of the Realm of the Gods might be effective, much less anything that could be found within the Sky Spill Continent.

“Let’s go.”

The two of them left the Parasol Tree Pavilion together and walked towards Divine Phoenix Island’s dungeons.

The Divine Phoenix Island dungeon was located within the hillside and extended several hundred feet deep. Within the depths of the dungeon was an array formation. Once this array formation was fully activated, its defensive capabilities were strong enough to withstand even the full bombardment of a Revolving Core master.

Within the deepest reaches of the dungeon, there was a sealed stone chamber. Lei Mubai was lying there on the ground as if he were dead, his complexion was wan like he had lost all his blood. His spatial ring had already been taken out and placed on a table where it was sealed up, and the Great Desolate Blood Halberd replica was also set aside.

Lin Ming looked at Lei Mubai in this state and knew that his heart had already died. A proud man whose arrogance had sunk into his bones, and had vainly dreamed to one day rule the world and control the fate of all others in his hand, had suddenly suffered such a great attack. In this situation, losing all hope was a completely normal event.

“Lin Ming, you seemed to care about the Thunder Soul in Lei Mubai, right?” Mu Qianyu asked.

“Mm.” Lin Ming nodded.

Mu Qianyu’s eyebrow arched up. “If I’m not wrong, the final move that you defeated Lei Mubai with not only used a Thunder Soul, but also a Flame Essence?”

Mu Qianyu had a special physique and was very sensitive to anything related to fire. Lin Ming’s Thunderfire Annihilation had passed in an instant, but the energy of the Flame Essence had been sensed by Mu Qianyu.

Lin Ming hesitated a bit before honestly acknowledging this. He would be in contact with Mu Qianyu for a long time. Sooner or later, she would find out his secret. Lin Ming said, “My body is special. I can absorb many Thunder Souls and Flame Essences.”

Although she had speculated about this earlier, hearing Lin Ming’s affirmation caused Mu Qianyu to take a deep breath. Just what kind of bloodline did Lin Ming have? He was actually able to absorb multiple Thunder Souls and Flame Essences? This was simply unheard of!

Normally, as a martial artist’s strength grew, they would need to replace the Thunder Soul or Flame Essence within their body. After someone had a Thunder Soul or Flame Essence within their body for a long time, they would be able to smoothly utilize its strength. But once they traded it in for another, more powerful one, they would need to adapt to the new properties of the Thunder Soul or Flame Essence, completely learning and developing new skills. This was a process that took a very long time.

But, Lin Ming was actually able to absorb multiple Thunder Souls and Flame Essences. Not only would he be able to avoid the hassle in this aspect, but he could also increase the power of thunder and fire within his body. This was simply a talent that defied the heavens!

Mu Qianyu looked at Lin Ming as if she were looking at some spooky monster. “Just how many Thunder Souls and Flame Essences can you absorb?”

“This… well, I don’t really know.” Lin Ming didn’t know whether or not the Heretical God Seed had an upper limit. The Supreme Elder of the Realm of the Gods hadn’t possessed this secret skill for a long time. Before he could thoroughly research it, he had been reduced to ashes. Now, everything was left over for Lin Ming to ponder himself.

Not wanting to continue this line of questioning, Lin Ming took out a small crystal bottle from his spatial ring. There was a small red crystal sphere sealed within.

“That’s right, this is for you…”

Mu Qianyu looked at the small crystal bottle and a surprised expression crossed her face, “This is the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal? You still have it?”

Mu Qianyu saw that this Shattered Demon Heart Crystal looked complete, very different to the one third he had left from proving Lei Mubai’s guilt. This sort of treasure would make Xiantian masters of any sect jealous; how could Lin Ming have so many?

“Mm, this is a gift for you.”

Lin Ming placed the small crystal bottle in Mu Qianyu’s hand. He smiled, jokingly saying, “Since I entered the sect and have a master now, I should give Senior-apprentice Sister a gift on the first meeting.”

Mu Qianyu was in the process of breaking through to the Revolving Core realm. Although reaching the Revolving Core realm was only a matter of time, if she had the help of the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal, she might be able to make her breakthrough several months earlier. To a top genius, several months was an incomparably precious amount of time.

Mu Qianyu stared at the small crystal bottle that Lin Ming had placed in her hand and muttered, “I really don’t know what sort of special body you have. You actually ate this Shattered Demon Heart Crystal!”

“Mm, I ate a bit more than half.” Lin Ming casually said.

Mu Qianyu already felt a bit numb. This was a top miracle medicine that even a Xiantian master had to be careful when taking. As for Lin Ming, he had swallowed half with a mere Pulse Condensation period cultivation. Really, this special body of his was too abnormal.

She eventually took the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal. She had wanted to say some word of thanks, but as the words reached her lips, she felt a bit sentimental and decided not to say anything. As she thought back, Mu Qianyu remembered that just half a year ago, she and Lin Ming were strangers. But now, their relationship had developed to the stage where she could accept such a gift without needing to thank him. It was just like they were close siblings.

As she realized they had such a close relationship, Mu Qianyu felt warm in her heart. She looked at Lin Ming with a trace of happiness in her eyes and smiled. “Are you going to absorb the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder? Would you like me to help?”

“Mm. It would be great if you could stay around, just in case something happens.”

As he opened the dungeon seal, Lin Ming went to investigate Lei Mubai’s condition. At this point, his cultivation had already dropped to the Flesh Training stage. Not only was that, but the residual true essence in his body continued to dissipate. Sooner or later, it would all disappear. After another day or two, Lei Mubai would become a cripple; his body would even be worse than a normal mortal’s.

“Lin Ming…” Lei Mubai’s eyes opened as he looked towards the heavens, his mouth spasming as he spat out this hateful name that had become unforgettable to him.

Lin Ming didn’t respond. Instead, he undid the seal on the table and took Lei Mubai’s spatial ring.

“You will die! Wait until the day that the South Sea Demon Region tramples over Divine Phoenix Island! On that day you will be flayed alive and destroyed without even a body to bury!”

Lei Mubai’s life was at its end, and his heart was like dying embers. Now, the only thing that supported him was his undying and eternally utter hatred of Lin Ming.

Lin Ming grabbed onto Lei Mubai’s arm and began to link his true essence to the Heretical God Seed. As he clearly felt the energy coming from the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder, the Heretical God Seed within him began to restlessly spin about.

This was a low-grade earth-step Thunder Soul that was no worse than his Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder. If it wasn’t for the fact that Lei Mubai’s cultivation was completely wasted at this time, it would be impossible to seize it.

The Heretical God Seed began to excitedly whine. Lin Ming poured true essence into Lei Mubai’s body, turning it into a net of true essence that covered the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder.

Because of Lei Mubai’s weakened state, the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder didn’t have much ability to resist. After a quarter of an hour passed, Lin Ming’s true essence net had finally tightly wrapped around the Thunder Soul.

The Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder fiercely struggled under the true essence shackles. However, under the formidable coercive pressure of the Heretical God Seed, there wasn’t much trouble it could cause.

Puff!

With a light sound, the blood red Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder was violently pulled out. Lei Mubai’s entire body fiercely trembled and he vomited a mouthful of blood. He immediately went limp on the ground as if someone had pulled out his spine.

All of Lei Mubai’s ambitions and hopes had come to an end. As Lin Ming looked at his pitiful and wretched appearance, he didn’t feel a single ounce of pity or compassion in his heart. Someday, if Lei Mubai ever became an extreme Revolving Core Supreme Elder or even a Peerless Emperor powerhouse, there was no telling how many rivers of blood would flow or how many people would die because they had been used for him to cultivate his martial arts.

As the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder appeared, it was just like a red serpent. Crimson energy recklessly erupted from it, as if it wanted to fly into Lin Ming’s body and suck up all his blood essence.

Lin Ming locked his hands together, and according to the method of sealing a Thunder Soul, drew up dozens of runes. All of these runes fell onto the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder, causing its radiance to dim by a few degrees. After several breaths of time, Lin Ming was able to galvanize his azure true essence into forming a cage, imprisoning the savage Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder.

The deep red Thunder Soul smashed against the cage that imprisoned it. However, it was unable to break through the endless azure true essence.

“This really is a sinister and evil Thunder Soul.”

Lin Ming let out a light breath. Even though it was trapped in a cage, he could still clearly feel the rich blood energy and atmosphere that emitted from the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder. It was as if he had been caught in a hellish blood pond, and all the blood vitality in his body was being sucked out.

“There’s a quiet room at the side. I’ll guard you.” Mu Qianyu said.

“Mm.”

After he walked into the nearby quiet room, Lin Ming sat down on the stone bed and placed a hand on the cage. Suddenly, the true essence he was revolving erupted. A powerful force filtered through the Heretical God Seed and began to influence the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder.

In that moment, the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder that was crazily smashing against its cage suddenly felt uneasy. The vast pressure coming from the Heretical God Seed was causing it to feel fear.

As the immense cover of pressure began to fall down, the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder felt increasingly uneasy. Its manic efforts of breaking out of the true essence cage increased as it impacted the cage again and again. A crack had actually developed in the endless azure true essence, spreading out!

“Do you need me to help?” Mu Qianyu asked. Lin Ming had to handle the last and final absorbing process himself. But, she could still assist in suppressing the Thunder Soul at the start.

“No need!” As the azure true essence cage finally broke, Lin Ming reached out a hand and grabbed the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder. Then, he pressed it into his chest!

Chapter 403 – Endless Trial

Mu Yuhuang coldly glared at Yan Yusheng. In normal times, she wouldn’t even bother to play along with his nonsense. But now, facing the pressure from the Council of Elders, she had no choice but to explain, “During the assessment in the Ancient Phoenix Main Hall, bloodline density is the most important influencing factor. In order to obtain greater lucky chances in the Ancient Phoenix Main Hall, one’s bloodline must naturally be more purer!”

“To give Lin Ming great lucky chances, you took the risk and gave him so much Vermillion Bird blood essence? Then what about the other disciples? Their bloodline purity is almost sufficient enough to practice the core sections of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. They put so much effort into their cultivation, all for a single chance to become a fish that passes through the dragon gate. Isn’t this just too unfair to them?”

Yan Yusheng’s voice wasn’t as emboldened or energetic as Mu Chihuo’s when he was arguing with Mu Yuhuang. He only spoke in a calm and moderate pace, but there was sharpness to his words that cut to the point.

Mu Yuhuang’s eyes became increasingly cold. “Elder Yan! If you find this unfair, then you may say so to the High Ancestor. The Vermillion Bird blood essence was personally granted to Lin Ming by the High Ancestor herself!”

Mu Yuhuang was very clear that the reason that Mu Chihuo and Yan Yusheng were launching verbal attacks against her together was to demand more authority.

There would be more Vermillion Bird blood essence in the future, and they wanted to the authority to control it. At least, they wanted to use this incident as a pretext to diminish Mu Yuhuang’s power, and request for the distribution of the Vermillion Bird blood essence to be left to the Council of Elders to decide, as opposed to the Vermillion Bird Faction Sovereign singularly controlling it.

It had to be known that the next Vermillion Bird Faction Sovereign would be Mu Qianyu. Mu Qianyu was also someone who stood by Mu Yuhuang. Mu Qianyu’s natural talent was outstanding, and in the future she would most likely reach the extreme Revolving Core realm. Once she held power, it would last for seven to eight hundred years!

If this happened, then Mu Chihuo’s faction would never be able to stand up!

If no master was born in a faction, then they would slowly decline and wither away. Eventually, they would even degenerate into a collateral branch.

After Mu Chihuo, there were also many Elders in the same faction that spoke. To them, Lin Ming’s death was a prelude to an intense internal power struggle.

The other unrelated Elders mostly stayed silent during this. They didn’t want to involve themselves or stir up any trouble in the struggles of internal factions. They could only regret that such a great genius of Divine Phoenix Island had been lost.

……………..

Within a small guest room at one of the mountain peaks of the Divine Phoenix Mountains, Lei Jingtian was meditating when suddenly a fire lit in front of him. As the message passed to his ears, he suddenly let out happy laugh. “Lin Ming fell within the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm? Haha! The heavens truly favor me! This boy, I’m glad he died early!”

The Five Element Region and Divine Phoenix Island’s negations were still continuing. Such an important negation involved massive benefits, and even involved the rise and fall of a sect. It wasn’t a matter that could be decided in just a few days. With both sides cooperating, there were also many details that needed to be hammered out. Negotiations had continued for half a month, and both sides had made concessions. However, they hadn’t yet reached a final agreement.

Lei Jingtian naturally stayed in Divine Phoenix Island and hadn’t left yet. Now that he heard the news of Lin Ming’s death, he was overjoyed!

“The heavens are righteous; he is finally dead! Divine Phoenix Island’s destiny is only this. They thought that they could soar into the heavens, hehe, but now it’s unknown whether or not they can survive this South Sea crisis!”

As Lei Jingtian received news of Lin Ming’s death, the other sect Elders of the Five Element Region also received it. The Golden Bell Mountain Elder was filled with deep emotion; such a singular talent of a generation had fallen. As for the Deep Earth Sect’s Shi Zhongkun, he was the same as Lei Jingtian, taking pleasure in this news. To him, Lin Ming’s death was a matter worth celebrating.

Out of the entire Divine Phoenix Island, only Mu Qianyu believed that Lin Ming was still alive. When Lin Ming had first entered the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, he hadn’t left behind a destiny soul jade slip. This sort of jade slip required a martial artist to separate a sliver of their own soul and seal it into a jade slip. When the main body died, the jade slip would shatter.

However, separating a wisp of one’s soul would cause an extremely great soul wound. Normally, only the mediocre would leave behind a soul jade slip. A true genius would never do such a thing.

Without clear evidence from something like a destiny soul jade slip, Mu Qianyu would not believe that Lin Ming had died.

…………………………..

Bang!

Within the battlefield of the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, Lin Ming’s spear burst through a rock puppet, causing its body to explode into flames. He supported himself up with the Purple Comet Spear, partly kneeling on the ground. His back was covered in blood, and the bones of his left hand had been broken. The right hand that held the spear was also trembling.

He had finally crossed the second wave!

The first wave of rock puppets was the easiest to kill and the easiest to pass. Lin Ming had only need to kill them using his overwhelming strength. But the second wave of rock puppets was a notch stronger. The first time that Lin Ming had attempted to massacre all the rock puppets, he had been seriously wounded and almost died, eventually failing to finish them off. He had returned to his cave to heal his wounds, but unexpectedly found that the puppets he killed off were all being rapidly regenerated by the array formation.

As Lin Ming recovered, so did the rock puppets!

The second time that he attacked, Lin Ming had gained experience from the previous attempt and had barely managed to kill them. He had also been grievously wounded as before.

The third wave was absolutely not something he could defeat!

Lin Ming clenched his teeth, and swallowed down a healing pill.

At this moment, the array formation started to revolve, and the crimson blood colored runes began to light up one at a time. These past 10 days, Lin Ming had already discovered the rules of the smelting trial; soon, new rock puppets would appear. He launched his movement technique and quickly returned to the cave.

If he wanted to pass this smelting trial within the year, he would need to do everything possible to increase his strength.

This was the general level smelting trial of the Ancient Phoenix Clan. Lin Ming’s talent far surpassed other juniors within the South Horizon Region, but when he compared himself to those of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, he wasn’t so sure of himself. The Palace Spirit had stated that during the entire time it had guarded the Ancient Phoenix Main Hall, only a single person had passed the smelting trial within a year. Not only that, but this person had come from the Royal Family, and had only been relegated to the general level smelting trial. The other general level talents hadn’t been able to achieve this.

Lin Ming revolved the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, and within an hour the true essence in his body had been restored.

Then, Lin Ming took out a vial of viscous red liquid. This liquid was a Shattered Demon Heart Crystal.

Before, Lin Ming had obtained 10 Shattered Demon Heart Crystals. He had eaten half of one, given Mu Qianyu one, and had used part of another when he was revealing Lei Mubai’s secret identity. Now, he had a bit over eight left.

This was an extremely brutal and potent medicine. The first time that Lin Ming had taken this, nearly all the blood in his body had been drained away.

With his current strength, he wouldn’t end up in such a pitiful state. Still, he didn’t dare to absorb too much. Not just that, but if there was too much energy, he wouldn’t be able to absorb it. The safest way would be to take half of a Shattered Demon Heart Crystal every few days and refine it in the heat of battle.

Lin Ming took out a medicinal inscription symbol that he had drawn up when he had been at Dark Moon Island. This medicinal inscription symbol had been used to increase the potency of the Heaven Opening Pill. Although this medicinal inscription symbol was a bit too low level for the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal, it was still better than nothing.

As Lin Ming drank the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal, his entire body began to burn with a scalding heat. In his mind, the scene of the Netherworld Great Emperor fighting against countless demons appeared once more. But this time, Lin Ming wasn’t lost in the immersive dream like before. He quickly broke through the illusion, manipulating the energy of the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal, and began the process of tempering his marrow!

The Tempering Marrow boundary. This was the most important factor he would depend on to complete this smelting trial within a year!

Chapter 404 – Strange River

Even though Lin Ming’s current cultivation had reached the peak of Pulse Condensation, controlling the energy of the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal to temper his marrow still caused the same aching pain as before. It was as if a saber was being twisted into his very being!

This kind of energy contained the remnant will of the Netherworld Great Emperor. It was cruel, brutal, arrogant and unruly. In order to force it to yield so that Lin Ming could use it for himself, he had to erase this will.

What Lin Ming could do was use his own soul and slowly wear down the remnant will of the Netherworld Great Emperor.

Lin Ming grit his teeth as sweat streamed down him. Periodically there would be small amounts of energy that escaped from his pores, but this energy was all imprisoned by the power of the medicinal inscription symbol and contained within his body.

The principle behind this medicinal inscription symbol was to reduce the loss of medicinal efficacy. This medicinal inscription that was able to be fully utilized on the Heaven Opening Piil could still slightly affect the Shattered Demon Hearty Crystal.

Thus the energy within Lin Ming’s body was increasingly manic and savage.

Lin Ming forcefully used the tempering marrow method found within the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ and urged the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal energy to enter his skeleton a bit at a time. The energy was thick and heavy like mercury, and also extremely pervasive. Even though Lin Ming’s bones were extremely dense, the energy easily penetrated through.

As the energy entered the marrow, Lin Ming could hear ‘chi chi chi’ sounds coming from his bones. This was the energy burning his marrow, slowly refining it and changing its very nature. This was similar to when a blacksmith had to fry a wooden spear shaft in a massive wok of oil in order to cause all the impurities within them to explode. This pain was deep within his bones and utterly agonizing.

Lin Ming’s forehead was dripping with sweat. But compared to the last time that he had absorbed the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal, he was in a much better condition. The first time, almost all of his blood had been drained out, forming a bloody carapace that covered his body. But this time, there was only pain and sweat.

In the sweat, there were traces of faint gray substances, but only a small amount. These were the impurities within Lin Ming’s body. After Lin Ming had gone through several experiences of washing down his marrow and muscles, this was the result. Although Lin Ming’s bodily purity couldn’t compare with someone like Mu Qianyu, he also didn’t have many impurities left within him.

Time passed slowly. Finally, a full two hours had passed, and Lin Ming absorbed the last of the energy. He opened his mouth and vomited a mouthful of black blood.

This vomit actually didn’t stop. Lin Ming kept vomiting blood until the entire ground was covered in blood. It was quite a disturbing sight. Finally, it ended, and Lin Ming wiped his mouth. He looked within himself and found that the blood within his blood vessels was extremely bright red, and thick like mercury.

Marrow and blood were inextricably linked. Marrow produced blood, and blood rejuvenated the marrow. In order to temper one’s marrow, one needed to create new blood.

After Lin Ming ate half of the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal, the golden color of his marrow was much richer than before; he had come closer to completing Tempering Marrow by another 5% or so.

Half of a Shattered Demon Heart Crystal was 5%, and a whole one would be almost 10%. Now, Lin Ming’s Tempering Marrow was around 25% complete. Even though the future medicinal efficacy of these pills would weaken, once he finished eating the eight Shattered Demon Heart Crystals, Lin Ming estimated that he should complete Tempering Marrow by around 60 to 70%.

Tempering Marrow was a great boundary. Completing it was much more difficult than Lin Ming had previously assumed. He didn’t know just how strong he would be after completing Tempering Marrow.

As Lin Ming sat in meditation for half an hour, his stomach began to growl in hunger.

Before Lin Ming had entered the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, he had filled his spatial ring with all sorts of food. As he took out cured meats and dry rations, he heard a faint trickling sound coming from within the cave, as if there was water nearby.

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. He put away the dry rations and began walking into the cave. After he walked several hundred feet, he saw that there really was an underground river in the cave.

The river water was incomparably clear and beautiful. However, Lin Ming felt that there was something not quite right. As he reached out his hand to scoop some up, he suddenly sucked in a breath of cold air. This river water was very heavy. At least, it was no lighter than mercury. Not only that, but the temperature of the water was terrifyingly high; it was already several times above boiling.

As Lin Ming was cupping the water, he found out that during that time a great amount of the true essence that protected his body had melted away.

“What kind of river is this!?”

Lin Ming’s complexion wasn’t too good. Everything he found within this Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm was strange and dangerous.

“Mm? What’s that?”

Lin Ming discovered that there were actually creatures within the river. These creatures looked like giant crabs, and their whole body was covered with red bony armor as they lurked underneath the water. They stared at him with wide eyes.

The two claws were over two feet long!

“If it can survive in this place, then it’s not some friendly animal.” The temperature was several times the boiling temperature, but these crabs could still survive here. Even Lin Ming wouldn’t be able to do so. He could stay under the water for a long time, but he would eventually have to give up after his true essence was exhausted. But these crabs took this river as their home, and simply didn’t fear the high temperatures.

A giant crab with a four or five foot tall body suddenly rose up. It brandished its two foot long claws as it tried to clamp down on Lin Ming, as if it wanted to cut him off at the waist.

“It takes me as prey?”

Lin Ming sneered. He punched out with the Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist; azure true essence erupted!

Bang!

The crab flew backwards, rolling around. It finally stopped, jumped up and ran away.

“It didn’t die?”

Lin Ming was shocked. This punch was able to kill a late Houtian martial artist. But this big crab had actually resisted it!

Too strong!

Soon, seven or eight giant crabs gathered in the river. Lin Ming was stunned for a moment, and then realized that the crab fellow had gone back to gather its buddies.

These crabs were the overlords of the river. They had never suffered a loss like this before. Now, they swore to eliminate Lin Ming!

Pu! Pu!

Seven or eight giant crabs ran out of the river together, rushing to kill Lin Ming!

This time, Lin Ming no longer held back. He took out the Purple Comet Spear and fused the Divine Demon Thunder Soul into the shaft. The power of thunder exploded, and with a flourish of the spear, the entire cave was basked in a radiant purple light.

Kacha!

Seven or eight bolts of thunder dropped down from the sky, each one striking a giant crab. All of the crabs were instantly killed by Lin Ming.

As Lin Ming looked at the giant crabs on the ground, he suddenly remembered something. The Palace Spirit had said that this cave was the residence for those participating in the general level smelting trail; was this the food and water that were supplied?

Lin Ming hesitated for a moment, and then walked over to a giant crab. He grabbed it, and then used a great deal of effort to smash its palm-thick shell. Inside was glisteningly tender red and white meat. He dug out a big chunk and began to roast it over a fire.

Lin Ming had already become accustomed to bringing along salt and other seasonings. He casually sprinkled some onto the crab meat, and a delicious fragrance began to waft out.

Lin Ming took a careful bite. This strange giant crab’s meat was extremely savory and tender, yet still chewy.

Lin Ming took his time. After he carefully determined that there weren’t any side effects, he began to heartily chow down.

This strange giant crab’s meat was very resistant to high temperature. No matter how he roasted it, it would not char or become over burnt. As he tasted it, its flavor was extremely delicious, and was even better than the dishes found within famous restaurants.

“This is the good stuff.”

Even Lin Ming, a connoisseur who was relatively picky about food, couldn’t help but praise this strange crab meat.

“Mm? The crab meat in my stomach seems to nourish my body’s true essence?” Lin Ming was surprised to discover. As the crab meat entered his stomach, a low heat began to flow out and dissipate. This was an extremely comfortable feeling. He felt the fire-attribute true essence in his body slowly strengthening.

The magnitude of enhancement from this crab meat was far less than eating pills, but it absolutely won in terms of purity. There were no impurities and toxins contained within.

It was equivalent to eating spiritual vegetables and spiritual grains. However, the effects were at least 100 times greater than the spiritual foods found within Divine Phoenix Island!

Lin Ming was shocked. This was what participants in the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s general level smelting trial ate?

The Ancient Phoenix Clan. Lin Ming only needed to hear this name to roughly guess that they would have the bloodline of a God Beast within them; it was difficult to imagine just how formidable their talent was. In addition, they studied the techniques and skills of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, they had training grounds like the smelting trial in the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, and also all sorts of amazing medicines and foods.

How could their talent not be outstanding?

It was no wonder that the weakest and most inferior king-level talent within the Ancient Phoenix Clan could also complete the general-level smelting trial within a year.

“Maybe… only the king-level are true members of the Ancient Phoenix Clan. And, the so-called general level is only for the subordinates of the Ancient Phoenix Clan!

As Lin Ming realized this, the original contentment in his heart vanished.

The road he walked was still inestimably long!

However, the more it was like this, the more it aroused the competitive spirit within Lin Ming’s heart. If he had already stood at the top of all the geniuses of the 3000 infinite universes, then, with no goal to pursue, he would feel desolate and bored.

But now, it looked like he fell far short.

After he ate a giant portion of crab meat, Lin Ming drank the water from the river. The river water also had similar effects to the crab meat; it was able to moisten and refine the true essence within his body.

“Even water has this effect. Not just that, but the fire-attribute true essence here is much richer than the outside. If I wish to practice actual combat, there is still a giant battle waiting outside for me. This is truly a great place to practice!

Within the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, if one wanted to battle there were countless opponents outside. If one wanted to cultivate, there was extremely rich fire-attribute true essence; even eating or drinking would increase one’s strength. What place would be quicker to cultivate in than here?

After Lin Ming drank his fill, he felt the crab meat and water turning into heat within his body and scurrying around. His body flushed with a frantic energy. If he didn’t release this energy soon, he would be feeling unwell for a while. Lin Ming couldn’t wait to go out and fight!

Lin Ming took out the Purple Comet Spear from his spatial ring and launched his movement technique, directly flying out of the cave. Outside the cave, several hundred rock puppets had already gathered on the plains. But this time, the flaming rock puppets were in the majority. These flaming rock puppets were much stronger than the ordinary rock puppets.

As he saw this vast number of rock puppets, Lin Ming’s fighting spirit shot up. He trod forwards, his body shooting out like an arrow, creating a perfect arc as he landed in the midst of a puppet group.

The rock puppets roared, and columns of flames came blasting towards Lin Ming. He faintly smiled and instantly activated Golden Roc Shattering the Void. He was like a swallow within a storm, dancing in the midst of the crowded flames, like thread through the needle!

Hu hu hu!

All of the columns of fire passed by Lin Ming. A 1000 foot distance was crossed in the blink of an eye. As Lin Ming arrived in front of the first flame puppet, the Purple Comet Spear came sweeping down!

Bang!

With a loud explosion, the flaming puppet was broken apart by Lin Ming’s spear!

As strength flowed through his entire body, Lin Ming could hear his bones popping and snapping; this inestimably comfortable feeling made him want to groan and shout!

Fight!

After tempering his marrow and eating a massive amount of crab meat, Lin Ming felt energy crashing throughout his entire body. If he didn’t vent this energy, then he would never feel comfortable.

Peng peng peng!

A spear thrust out. Arcs of lightning shot out into all directions, blazing flames jetted into the sky, and an azure light sliced through the void. Wherever the Purple Comet Spear went, crushed stone would fly!

Chapter 408 – Exit

After experiencing a full ten months in the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, the current Lin Ming looked like an utter mess. He was in rags, almost completely naked. Lin Ming had originally brought several sets of clothes to change into in his spatial ring. When his clothes were all torn apart in battle, he would switch them for new ones. Soon, all of them were torn. Lin Ming just left a single set of relatively complete clothes for the time that he would leave this place. Thus, that was why Lin Ming was left but nothing but his body and some rags.

Lin Ming’s hair had originally been long. But now it was scattered and messy, and it had grown longer, reaching just past his waist.

The Palace Spirit floated in front of Lin Ming like a wisp of ghostly fire, and then condensed into a white human face. It had a somewhat surprised expression.

“I passed the smelting trial?” Lin Ming asked the Palace Spirit.

“All that remains before you is the last smelting trial. Before, I had said that if you are still alive by the time you complete the fifth smelting trail, then you would be able to obtain a midway reward, and that I would awake at that time.”

Lin Ming was surprised for a moment, and then remembered that the Palace Spirit had spoken such words at the very start. However, he had been in an incredibly tense and difficult situation where he had slaughtered countless enemies. Because of this, he had already mostly forgotten these words and relegated them to the back of his mind.

“The fifth smelting trail. I’ve only completed the fifth smelting trial?”

“Yes. Every stage of the smelting trial is very long. You have only one last smelting trial left – the sixth smelting trial. It is the shortest, but it is also the hardest. If you can complete it then you may leave. And at that time… I shall give you the blood of the Ancient Phoenix!” The Palace Spirit deeply and solemnly looked at Lin Ming. If Lin Ming could do so, then he would be the first person who wasn’t from the Royal Family that would have completed this general level smelting trail within a year!

Lin Ming was overjoyed. He finally saw the light at the end of the tunnel! Although his strength had progressed quickly here every day, after going through endless battles and endless trials, all he felt was endless loneliness. Lin Ming had nearly become nothing but a killing puppet. If this continued, there would definitely be a problem with his mental state.

“Now, I shall grant you the reward for passing the fifth smelting trial. Since you have completed it in 10 months, you can obtain the highest rewards. You may choose from the Vermillion Bird blood essence, a cultivation method jade slip, as well as a fire-attribute miracle medicine. Of these three, you may choose one.”

Vermillion Bird blood essence, a cultivation method jade slip, as well as a fire-attribute miracle medicine!

Lin Ming first eliminated the Vermillion Bird blood essence, since he wanted to fight for the Ancient Phoenix bloodline and also because the Vermillion Bird blood essence would only have a limited effect.

Then, he also removed the cultivation method jade slip. Lin Ming didn’t lack any sort of top quality cultivation method.

The fire-attribute miracle medicine seemed to be the best bet. If this was a medicine from the Ancient Phoenix Clan, it definitely wasn’t ordinary. Perhaps it might be able to enhance his Tempering Marrow boundary by another 20 to 30%. If that happened, then his Tempering Marrow would be 80 to 90% complete, and he would be close to Perfection.

However, just to be prudent, Lin Ming asked, “What sort of cultivation method jade slip and fire-attribute miracle medicine is it?”

This was just a random question, but the response of the Palace Spirit caused Lin Ming’s heart to nearly jump out of his chest, and to have a shortness of breath. The Palace Spirit said, “The cultivation jade slip is the first eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ cultivation method manual. The fire-attribute miracle medicine is the 3000 year Nine Revolution Fire Lotus Grass…”

The first eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’!

Lin Ming was beyond shocked.

That’s right, he should have realized this sooner. Divine Phoenix Island’s ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ and ‘Blue Luan Abstract Phantom Code’ were both obtained by the founder after she went to the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm. That he would be able to obtain the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ within the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm was only natural!

The Divine Phoenix Island founder’s ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ that she had obtained was riddled with flaws. According to Lin Ming’s knowledge, there were only the first five layers of the cultivation method!

Even with so many flaws, the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ was no worse than cultivation methods from fifth-grade sects!

It had to be known that the higher one went in a cultivation method, the more terrifying its power was. A true and complete ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ would be a top cultivation method even within the Realm of the Gods. Within the legends of the Ancient Phoenix cultivation methods, it was said that after completely practicing it, one could bathe in the fires of nirvana and rebirth themselves, becoming endless and immortal!

If one could really achieve this effect, then he feared that this cultivation method might even surpass the Heretical God Force.

The ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ was extremely significant to Lin Ming. Within the memories of those Supreme Elders from the Realm of the Gods, there were many different types of cultivation method manuals. However, not all of them were suited for Lin Ming to cultivate. For instance, ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’. Lin Ming had practiced this for such a long time, and yet had only been able to touch the second layer, and he still struggled. In terms of speed, Lin Ming wasn’t some monstrous genius. Back during the Seven Profound Valleys’ Total Faction Martial Meeting, he had even by suppressed by Jiang Baoyun in speed.

Ultimately, ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’ simply wasn’t a suitable technique for Lin Ming. Much less, Lin Ming didn’t even have wind-attribute true essence fusion compatibility.

But, the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ was different. With the support of the Heretical God Force, when Lin Ming practiced the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ he was even quicker than Mu Qianyu.

This miracle medicine would only benefit Lin Ming by himself, and there would always be chances to obtain more rare medicines in the future. But, the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ was actually very difficult to find. If he could obtain the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ jade slip, then not only would it help Lin Ming, but it would also help Mu Qianyu, and eventually even Divine Phoenix Island would benefit.

If he took out the first eight layers of this cultivation method, then it was likely that many people of Divine Phoenix Island would go crazy for it!

Lin Ming took a deep breath and then asked, “How many layers does the complete ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ have?”

“Nine layers! However, the final layer is only for the Royal Family; it cannot be rewarded. Therefore, you cannot obtain it.”

Lin Ming felt this was a touch tragic. But still, just the first eight layers was incredible in itself!

“I want the cultivation jade slip!” Lin Ming said without any hesitation.

“As you wish!”

A red light flashed, and then a crimson blood-like jade slip appeared in Lin Ming’s palm. When it touched his palm, it was very warm. It was twice the size of a normal jade slip, and very heavy in his hand.

Lin Ming casually swept through it with his sense, and suppressed the impulse to immediately read it. He first stored it in his spatial ring.

Since there was only one stage left and it was also the shortest, Lin Ming had to rush past it with overwhelming force. Now, he didn’t have the time to practice the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, and his heart wasn’t calm enough to do so.

At this moment, the smelting trail array began to revolve once again!

With a rumbling sound, the earth split and a massive blood red demon with a huge axe appeared, crawling out of the earth.

This demon was 20 feet high, and had chains wrapped all around its body. Its face had two large fangs just like a wild boar, and its fiery crimson hair wantonly hung all over it.

Lin Ming looked in shock. This demon… actually looked very much like the Netherworld Great Emperor!

It was only that this demon was twice the height of the Netherworld Great Emperor, and its skin was a deep red as opposed to the Netherworld Great Emperor’s blue.

“What’s going on here?”

Lin Ming had some suspicions in his mind and wanted to ask the Palace Spirit. But at this time, the white light flashed and the Palace Spirit had already disappeared.

Lin Ming also didn’t bother to think about this. In short, this was an enemy, and he would do everything he could to defeat it!

He wasn’t in a hurry to go onto the battlefield. First, he controlled his breathing and sat down in meditation. He mixed the Shattered Demon Heart Crystal with his own blood essence and swallowed it.

Lin Ming could now absorb an entire Shattered Demon Heart Crystal with ease. He had long gotten used to suppressing the remnant will of the Netherworld Great Emperor. He began the familiar and easy technique of directing the crystal’s energy to temper his marrow……………..

……………………………………..

Half a month later, within a remote mountain of Divine Phoenix Island, there was a deafening explosion. Rocks cracked, dirt flew everywhere, and an vortex appeared that had enough strength to send an early Xiantian realm guard flying away!

“Enemy attack!”

“The South Sea Demon Region has arrived!”

“What!?”

It was a scene of chaos. This was a sacred ground of Divine Phoenix Island, and also the fundamental basis for the existence of Divine Phoenix Island that it relied on – the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm. For them to encounter the enemy attack here was terrifying.

“You… you are…” The Xiantian realm guard’s mouth dropped down, slack jawed as he stared disbelieving at this youth in front of him. This youth was tall, straight, with a handsome and delicate appearance. His face seemed to have been hewn by sabers, and his two eyebrows were straight and slanted upwards. There was a very clear flame mark between his eyebrows that looked like a natural scar.

This person’s hair was a mess. In comparison, his clothes were fairly clean. The more the guard looked, the more this youth seemed like…

How… how was this possible!?

Bang!!!

Dust rose from everywhere. The youth had actually flown into the sky and soared away. His speed was fast enough to shame every Xiantian master present.

“I… I’m not wrong!”

“That youth, didn’t he look like Lin Ming?” The guards present had all seen Lin Ming before when he had first entered the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm.

“That’s right. That youth was just a bit taller than Lin Ming, and also has those flame marks between his eyebrows.”

A year ago, Lin Ming was a handsome, somewhat pretty boy. Now, Lin Ming had become a heroically handsome young man.

“Could it really be…”

The complexion of everyone present change.

Lin Ming was alive!?

They hurriedly took out a sound transmitting talisman to report such a massive matter.

Lin Ming’s speed was extremely fast. Before the several guards had passed out the sound transmitting talismans, he had already arrived at Divine Phoenix Island’s Vermillion Bird Main Hall. His speed was amazingly fast, and this was not just because of his outstanding movement technique. I was also because his true essence was too thick; it was thick to the point that even Xiantian masters couldn’t compare to it!

“Who are you? This is a restricted area…halt! You may not enter!” A young woman cried out. She was the guard of the Vermillion Bird Main Hall’s entrance. She drew her sword to block Lin Ming, but a sudden gust of wind stopped her, forcing her back. In the blink of an eye, Lin Ming had already entered the Main Hall.

Lin Ming was incomparably anxious at this moment. He didn’t know what had happened while he was in the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm. But, as he listened to the surprised words from the guards, he was able to discern that the South Sea Demon Region had already started its war with Divine Phoenix Island.

First he hurried over to find Mu Qianyu or Mu Yuhuang, to understand out what the present situation was.

Also, Lin Ming worried over another matter, and that was whether or not his parents had received news that he had died. Lin Ming was their only child, and also their only hope. If something had happened to his parents because they thought that he had died, he would never be able to live with the consequences!

By the time Lin Ming entered the Main Hall, the sound transmitting talisman flame had just extinguished in front of Mu Yuhuang.

Mu Yuhuang had learnt what had happened from the guards. Still, she could not believe her own eyes as she watched a 17 year old Lin Ming walk through the entrance!

Looking at the heroic and comely youth that seemed to shine with inner spirit, Mu Yuhuang, who could watch a mountain collapse without blinking an eye, was completely and thoroughly shocked.

Lin Ming had stayed within the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm for a full 10 and a half months, and he had actually survived and come out! Not only that, but his cultivation had actually reached the late Houtian realm!

Heavens!

A 17 year old with a late Houtian realm cultivation!?

Even when Mu Qianyu was the same age she was only at the early Houtian realm!

“Honorable Sect Master.” Lin Ming was in too much of a hurry to bow, “What is the situation now? Do my parents think I have died? How about Senior-apprentice Sister Mu?”

Mu Yuhuang was stunned. She caught her bearings and said, “Yu’er… has gone to the battlefield. As for news of your death, it has already spread…”

Lin Ming’s mind sank, panic almost setting in. He could not imagine what condition his parents were in now. First, he had to immediately find Qin Ziya and see his own parents.

Chapter 410 – Destination: Blood Demon Island

The sea breeze swept past him, and the strings that were broken shivered. Qin Ziya stood up on the beach, still like statue.

This was Lin Ming’s sound transmitting talisman?

Lin Ming hadn’t died!?!?

Qin Ziya was petrified for a long time. The contents of the sound transmitting talisman were very simple. Lin Ming asked about his parents’ situation and whether or not they had received news of his death, and whether anything had happened to them because of a broken heart. Then he left behind a new sound transmission mark and asked Qin Ziya to wait for him on the island. Soon, he would fly over and meet him.

Lin Ming was alive!

Qin Ziya took a few deep breaths to calm himself. Then, he took out a long distance sound transmitting talisman from his spatial ring that was used to report on military situations. He gave a simple and brief summary of the current situation and then with a shake of his hand, the talisman ignited.

……………

10,000 miles away, a mass of flames appeared in front of Lin Ming but was instantly left behind by Fireshine’s terrifying speed. The message briefly echoed in Lin Ming’s ears…

“Lin Fu and Lin Mu are well, there is no need to worry about them. Yang Lin has been overthrown and Yang Zhen has ascended to the throne. Marshal Qin has been placed under house arrest, and Ouyang Boyan used the threat of the Qin Family’s lives to compel Qin Xingxuan into a certain death dead end on the open sea battlefield’s Blood Demon Island. It has already been one month since then… my ability is weak, and because of a military command, I have been trapped on Star Coconut Island, and cannot leave this place to rescue her…”

After hearing this message, Lin Ming’s complexion instantly paled.

Ouyang Boyan!!!!!!!

Lin Ming’s heart burned with a raging anger. When he left the Seven Profound Valleys, he had also left behind this dangerous serpent. It wasn’t that he didn’t want to kill him, it was just that he didn’t have the ability to.

Ouyang Boyan represented the Seven Profound Valleys’ Acacia Faction and the Ouyang Family Clan. The forces that supported him from behind were far too great, and his cultivation had already been at the peak of the early Xiantian realm for dozens of years. Against such a character, there simply wasn’t anything he could do.

Lin Ming had deliberately arranged for the safety of his parents and Lin Xiaodong, but he didn’t expect that Ouyang Boyan would actually target Qin Xingxuan!

Qin Xingxuan was a disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys. Without a reason, he couldn’t visibly deal with her. But now, he had secretly trapped all the lives of the Qin Family, and had held onto Qin Xingxuan’s weakness!

“Damn!”

Lin Ming’s fists tightened until loud popping sounds could be heard from them, and flashes of electricity sparked up from his hands. Even the flame mark on Lin Ming’s forehead turned an angry red.

“First I will rescue Qin Xingxuan. Then, Ouyang Boyan, I will have you pay the deepest price for your actions!”

Lin Ming bent down and touched Fireshine’s back, continuously injecting true essence into Fireshine’s body. “Fireshine, hurry, as fast as you can!”

Lin Ming was incomparably nervous. The South Sea region was a vast, endless land. Even with Fireshine’s speed and transmission arrays, it would still take time to reach her!

He didn’t know whether or not a calamity would befall Qin Xingxuan during this time.

…………………….

“Elder Qin, where are you going to?” An Acacia Faction disciple asked with a bright smile. This disciple was sent by Ouyang Boyan to monitor him, and his cultivation was at the middle Houtian realm.

Qin Ziya looked at the hourglass in the corner, estimating his time. Without caring for the middle Houtian Acacia Faction disciple behind him, he walked into the operations room and picked up the sea map, wrapping it up.

As he picked up the sea map, all the little flags that were on top fell onto the floor.

The Acacia Faction disciple’s expression was immediately ugly, “Qin Ziya, what is the meaning of this?”

“No meaning. I’m just going to go out for a few days. I’m borrowing this sea map, and then in a few days I’ll return it.” Qin Ziya casually said.

“Qin Ziya, are you planning to rebel?” The Acacia Faction disciple was angry, but as he thought about it, he sneered and said, “Humph, this is also good. Since you are defying military orders, you are just digging your own grave. Don’t blame me for what I’m going to do. I’ll write down all your crimes and report you to the sect. When that happens, they’ll impeach you! Mm, what’s with that look? What are you thinking of doing? You want to kill any witnesses to your crime?”

The Acacia Faction disciples derisively smiled. Although his cultivation was only at the middle Houtian realm, he had the support of Ouyang Boyan. Not just that, but he was also part of the Acacia Faction; he didn’t necessarily need to fear the Zither Faction’s Qin Ziya.

Qin Ziya looked at this man with pity. At this moment, a shrill phoenix cry sounded in the skies. The Acacia Faction disciple jumped in shock and then rushed out. He saw flames and wind coming from all directions, as a massive Vermillion Bird landed outside of the command post. The phoenix extended its huge, fiery wings, covering the entire courtyard.

As for who the Vermillion Bird was carrying on its back, it was actually a red-robed youth. His hair was disheveled and flew everywhere, and his eyes flashed with thunder. His appearance was outstanding, and his momentum was utterly threatening. Between his forehead was a flame mark that caused those who saw it to feel their heart palpitate with fear.

“This… this…” The Acacia Faction disciple was stunned. Just what was going on?

As the Acacia Faction disciple looked more closely at the red-robed youth, his eyes became increasingly dazed.

“This… doesn’t this person look like…” The Acacia Faction disciple’s eyes met Lin Ming’s, and he suddenly felt as if he had fallen into a massive black vortex. In just a few breaths of time, his mind shook as he turned white, and then spat out a massive amount of blood!

Lin Ming hadn’t intentionally hurt him. It was just that he had learned of Qin Xingxuan’s situation, and his innermost murderous intent was overflowing everywhere, spilling out and covering the world. After almost an entire year of trials within the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, he had experienced an endless scene of slaughter and his murderous intent had reached the degree where it could manifest in reality.

Now this murderous intent could spill out depending on his mood. His vision was like a flash of thunder that could directly pierce through an ordinary martial artist’s spiritual sea.

This Acacia Faction disciple’s cultivation was at the middle Houtian realm. But with just a single glance from Lin Ming, he had been injured by Lin Ming’s killing intent!

“You… you are… Lin… Lin Ming!?” The Acacia Faction disciple’s legs began to shake.

Lin Ming frowned, and the black vortex in his eyes began to spin once again.

“Allow me.” As Qin Ziya spoke, he took out a long zither from his spatial ring and then played a few notes. The Acacia Faction disciple’s legs went soft, and he tumbled onto the ground.

Qin Ziya said, “He won’t remember you. Now we won’t alarm the Seven Profound Valleys.”

Lin Ming nodded. Now wasn’t the time to make public the news that he was still living. Once this news spread, Ouyang Boyan would be able to prepare in advance. Maybe, when that happened, Ouyang Boyan might even run away.

“Let’s go!”

Qin Ziya jumped onto Fireshine’s back, and Fireshine spread its great wings, soaring into the sky!

“Martial House Master Qin, what is Xingxuan’s sound transmission mark?” As the strong winds blew against Lin Ming’s hair, his eyes were frosty and determined.

Qin Ziya sighed, “After Qin Xingxuan went Blood Demon Island, her sound transmission mark was cancelled. Now, I cannot reach her.”

If Ouyang Boyan wanted to deal with Qin Xingxuan, then he naturally had to shut off all ways for her to contact Qin Ziya.

Lin Ming’s mind sank, and his killing intent thickened by several degrees. “Without the sound transmission mark, then how will I find Xingxuan on the vast Blood Demon Island?”

“I already expected that she would be pushed into a dead end. So I had her separate a sliver of her soul and sealed it into a jade slip to create a soul jade slip. I had wanted to use this to know whether or not she was still living, but this soul jade slip can also be used to determine her position by sensing it.” Qin Ziya took out Qin Xingxuan’s soul jade slip.

Lin Ming looked at it and then felt his heart tighten. A soul jade slip’s soul sliver was connected to the main soul. It could be used to determine the current situation of its owner.

Lin Ming could feel that Qin Xingxuan’s life was like a flickering candle in the wind. This was an extremely bad situation!

Qin Ziya sighed. “Blood Demon Island has an incomparably rich blood demon energy. Even without considering how much she has probably been fighting, but even if she didn’t, that blood demon energy would still slowly corrode her, causing her life to continuously weaken. A Houtian martial artist would be relatively fine, but Xingxuan is only at the early Pulse Condensation period.

Lin Ming didn’t speak, he only remained silent. The strong gales howled in his ears, but the air around Lin Ming seemed to completely stop without a single trace of air flow. This was result of the amount of killing intent that he was emitting, which almost formed a domain around him. The thickness of this killing aura was even enough to make Qin Ziya feel suppressed.

Qin Ziya gasped. A while ago, he had been in a hurry and hadn’t carefully probed Lin Ming’s situation. But now that he looked, he only felt a simmering fear and cautiousness; this youth was like a raging Demon God!

If God blocked him, then he would kill God. If Buddha blocked him, then he would kill Buddha!

He couldn’t imagine that the one standing beside him was a late Houtian realm martial artist. Just what had Lin Ming experienced in this past year!?

The atmosphere was tense for a very long time. Qin Ziya thought of something to say, and then hesitated before saying, “About the Qin Family and Lin Family’s situation, I wrote a letter to Her Highness Mu Qianyu, and even sent two, but there was no response from her…”

Lin Ming frowned. He didn’t doubt Mu Qianyu’s character. If she knew that this was happening, then she wouldn’t idly stand by.

In fact, Mu Qianyu didn’t know of the grudge he had with Ouyang Boyan. Not just that, but currently Divine Phoenix Island was embroiled in a war. After confirming that he had died, she would most likely send some gifts to Green Mulberry City’s Lin Family, but would never have thought that someone would try to deal with his friends and family.

However, Qin Ziya had written a letter. So where did that letter go?

Lin Ming’s voice sank as he said, “Martial House Master Qin, I understand Mu Qianyu’s nature very well. She owes me a favor, so she would never do something like this. Your letter disappearing and coming to nothing would absolutely not be her intention. I will investigate this matter!”

Lin Ming’s voice was somewhat cold. He knew that ever since he appeared in Divine Phoenix Island, not everyone appreciated his presence. There were many people that were intensely jealous of him. Not just that, but he had taken their resources, and even the vial of Vermillion Bird blood essence; he had no idea how many people were madly resentful of him!

This time, because of what had happened, Lin Ming had learnt a crucial lesson. Against all his enemies, he must be ruthless!

“Lin Ming, 6000 miles up ahead is a new transmission array that is set up by the Five Element Region’s Thundercrest Sect that can directly send us to Blood Demon Island. If we go from there, we can arrive at Blood Demon Island in just a few hours, and save an entire two days.”

The South Sea was incomparably vast. During this great war, every sect had to find ways to easily transport themselves, thus there were many temporary transmission arrays that had been set up. The reason Qin Ziya had taken the sea map a while ago was to determine the positions of every transmission array and plan the quickest route.

“I got it.” Lin Ming poured true essence into Fireshine’s body, speeding up Fireshine. At this moment, in his heart, his killing intent had risen to a monstrous level!

6000 miles passed before too long. With Fireshine’s full speed, it took a mere two hours to reach there. In Lin Ming’s field of vision, an island appeared just as stated on the sea chart.

Chapter 411 – Demon God

At the transmission array on the island, there were seven or eight youths, men and women, sitting in a circle.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Zhang, what a great harvest! Haha, over 600 medium-grade true essence stones, and also a Blood Demon Crystal. That Blood Demon Crystal is a great treasure!”

Around a unibrow man there were several 20 something year old youths looking at a small wooden crate in front of the unibrow man, their faces full of envy.

This small wooden crate was packed to the brim with medium-grade true essence stones. And on top of the true essences stones, there was a finger-sized gem the color of blood. This gem was the Blood Demon Crystal. This Blood Demon Crystal was the core that an almost 1000 year old Blood Demon had condensed; it was extremely beneficial to Xiantian masters.

The unibrow man was very satisfied with himself, this harvest was truly great. He said, “To be honest, much of this is thanks to this temporary transmission array. Otherwise, it’s impossible for me to have such a high efficiency rate. If I didn’t have this transmission array and also a Golden-winged Heavenly Wind Eagle to ride, then going back and forth would be a 10 day round trip.

Around Blood Demon Island, the sects of the Five Element Region had laid down their own respective transmission arrays. This sort of long-distance transmission array cost a fairly great price to construct, and also had a limited lifetime of use. Every sect cherished their own long-distance transmission array and constructed one themselves. But this sort of construction was expensive, thus the disciples that came from Blood Demon Island to had to take out parts of their own harvest as the price to activate it.

The Thundercrest Sect and the Seven Profound Valleys were different. The disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys had relatively low strength, and when they came to Blood Demon Island it was nearly certain death. But, disciples of the Thundercrest Sect had a much high chance of survival. Although their probabilities of dying were still high, their harvest was also correspondingly enormous.

To the common disciples of the Thundercrest Sect, medium-grade true essence stones were very rare and valuable. Thus, there were some desperate disciples that pursued treasures and came to Blood Demon Island at their own risk.

These people present were basically all in this situation.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Zhang, I think that before you are 30 years old you’ll be able to step into the extreme Xiantian realm! Your cultivation speed isn’t much worse than that Lin Ming from a year ago!” A flattering youth nonsensically said.

“Haha!” Although this was clearly irrelevant drivel, the unibrow man still enjoyed this. He seemed to suddenly realize something, and then traced his mustache and shook his head, saying, “Although Lin Ming was a genius, he still died. No matter how great he was, or how heaven defying he was, a genius that falls from the sky is no longer a genius.”

During Revered Master Tianguang’s birthday banquet, this unibrow man had personally witnessed Lin Ming’s performance. He was an accompanying Xiantian disciple and had been sitting in the banquet’s corner.

“Come on, you can each take four or five of these medium-grade true essence stones. Consider it your reward.”

“Thank you Senior-apprentice Brother Zhang.” These disciples were overjoyed and each took five medium-grade true essence stones.

These young disciples were all in their twenties and most had a cultivation at the Houtian realm; there were some that were still at the Pulse Condensation period. To them, these five medium-grade true essence stones were enough to last them for half a month.

The unibrow man enjoyed being the center of attention. In the Thundercrest Sect, an inner court disciple like himself simply had no presence at all in front of a core disciple or direct disciple. But, to these weaker inner court disciples, or even outer court disciples, he was their absolute big brother. Much less, these people’s cultivations were all lower than his.

At this moment, he suddenly saw a red dot rapidly approaching from the distant skies.

“Mm? Who is it?”

The unibrow man stood up, and the other disciples did the same. During a time of war, they naturally had to be vigilant of any sudden surprises.

“Vermillion Bird?” The unibrow man was shocked, “It’s someone from Divine Phoenix Island!”

Bang!

The 100 foot wingspan Fireshine landed on the ground, and a massive cloud of dust and mist erupted into the air. There were even some Pulse Condensation period disciples that were blown back several steps before steadying themselves.

Damn!

The unibrow man was furious, these fellows simply didn’t know the rules! This was their Thundercrest Sect’s domain!

His vision swept past Qin Ziya who was atop Fireshine, and the unibrow man frowned. The other party had dropped down so roughly and rudely – obviously they had ill intentions!

“Who are you?” The unibrow man called out. Although his cultivation and Qin Ziya’s were about the same, he wasn’t afraid. Not too far behind him was the Thundercrest Sect’s station, and there were also several Xiantian masters that had been garrisoned there.

“I would like to borrow your transmission array!” Lin Ming stepped forwards, and with a single step, his momentum erupted. His eyes were like a bolt of thunder that instantly locked onto the unibrow man.

With these two eyes locked on him, the unibrow man felt as if a saber had pierced through his heart. A cold chill swept up his back.

“This… this person is…”

The unibrow man saw Lin Ming’s face, and he froze on the spot, his expression distorted. For a time, he was in utter disbelief and his face switched through various expressions.

He hadn’t died? How was he alive? Was his death only a smokescreen that Divine Phoenix Island released?

There was a dream he could never forget. Almost one year ago during the banquet competition, this youth had battled Lei Mubai, another youth who was like a reincarnated Demon God. Yet, that Lei Mubai was defeated under Lin Ming’s spear! It had to be known that Lei Mubai was in truth the Saint Son of the South Sea Demon Region. That was the Saint Son of a true fifth-grade sect! And yet, Lin Ming had jumped realms in order to eliminate him!

Not just that, but Lin Ming had also swept the ground with the Deep Earth Sect’s Elder Shi Zhongkun as well as the Thundercrest Sect Sovereign. After whatever plans they had were ruined, Lei Mubai had suffered a miserable fate.

This was definitely a man who could not be crossed!

And what was most terrifying was that Lin Ming’s cultivation at the time was only at the late Pulse Condensation period. Now, he had actually reached the late Houtian realm!

Heavens! What had happened this past year? In less than a year he was able to jump an entire realm!

Lin Ming had already been such a terrifying monster when he was at the late Pulse Condensation period. At that time, his strength was comparable to a Xiantian master. But now that he had reached the late Houtian realm, just what kind of abnormal existence was he?

The unibrow man fell listless as he thought this, But, the disciples behind him didn’t notice the change in the unibrow man. They only heard two people wishing to borrow the transmission array, and then began to laugh in anger.

“Did I hear it correctly? They want to borrow the transmission array?” A disciple carelessly said, his words full of derision.

“What an idiot. This transmission array is for our sect’s use. If an outside wants to borrow it, then no way!”

“Those two are mentally ill. They come down so aggressively and cover this father’s face with dirt, and yet want to borrow the transmission array. Just who the hell do they think they are?”

Lin Ming’s complexion sunk. At this moment, his heart was overflowing with murderous intent. He was like a powder keg that could explode at any moment. With just the slightest provocation or accident, he would erupt!

“I will repeat myself one last time. Let me borrow the transmission array!”

Lin Ming’s voice began to turn frosty. The unibrow man who bore the brunt of this began to sweat all over.

“I am speechless. To think I met…a…crazy…”

“Shut up!” As a disciple was speaking, the unibrow man fiercely cut him off midway. “Shut up and open the transmission array!”

The disciple was stunned for a moment, “Senior-apprentice Brother Zhang, why… huh?”

“Hurry up!”

The unibrow man’s forehead was already dripping with sweat. He had seen with his own eyes just how terrifying this Lin Ming truly was. At that time, he was at the Pulse Condensation period and was so horrifying. The unibrow man simply couldn’t imagine what Lin Ming’s current strength was after he reached the late Houtian realm. Just by being locked down by Lin Ming’s aura, he felt as if a serpent was poised to strike at him!

The disciples around the unibrow man were confused. Just what was boss doing? How were these people scary? One was at the early Xiantian realm and the other was at the late Houtian realm. Although that late Houtian fellow had a pretty intense momentum, there were four or five Xiantian masters not too far away behind them. Any one of them could turn this fellow into mush.

The unibrow man saw a disciple extremely reluctant in placing a true essence stone on the transmission array. A fire lit in him, and he suddenly walked over and kicked him away.

“Motherf*cker! Have you not eaten enough? Stop being so greedy!”

The unibrow man kicked away the hapless disciple, grabbed his true essence stone and personally placed it down. When he had faced Lin Ming’s murderous intent alone, he felt that he could have died at any moment.

This man was simply a demonic villain. Under the lockdown of such a murderous intent, the unibrow man was extremely afraid that if he didn’t hurry up, Lin Ming would instantly kill him in the next moment.

“You seem to know me.” The unibrow man stiffened. Lin Ming’s true essence sound transmission had reached his ear.

“I… I know. I was also present at the banquet competition.”

“I hope that you won’t spread any news of me being alive. Otherwise, I will take your life!”

“Yes… yes… I swear, I will never speak of this.” The unibrow man quickly made a pledge. Normally, it was an unimaginable matter that a late Houtian martial artist would threaten an early Xiantian martial artist, not to mention that the unibrow man was a disciple of the Thundercrest Sect. But the unibrow man didn’t doubt that as long as Lin Ming was given more time to grow, he might even be able to kill his way through the Thundercrest Sect!

The transmission array was finally activated. Lin Ming inspected it for a moment. After he determined there wasn’t a problem, he stepped on with Qin Ziya and Fireshine.

As a curtain of light was enveloping him, Lin Ming sent out a true essence sound transmission. “Today I, Lin Ming, have to rush to Blood Demon Island. I owe you a favor.”

Then, Lin Ming’s figure vanished. The unibrow man waited for Lin Ming to completely disappear before he let out a long sigh of relief, wiping away all the sweat on his forehead. Thank the heavens, this scary Demon God had finally left. The unibrow man had a very strong suspicion that even if all the Xiantian masters that were stationed here joined together, they might not necessarily be Lin Ming’s match!

“Senior-apprentice Brother Zhang, who was that?”

“Why did you allow him to use the transmission array?”

“Just using this transmission array once takes a large amount of resources. Even we are reluctant to use it whenever we need to!”

These Houtian and Pulse Condensation disciples found this unbearable, so they all opened their big mouths and repeatedly asked.

The unibrow man was speechless, he simply couldn’t say anything about Lin Ming’s identity. He clenched his teeth and bit out, “That person was my relative.”

Even he couldn’t believe this ridiculous lie. Obviously, these low level disciples wouldn’t be tricked either.

Relative? A relative caused you to break out in a cold sweat?

Facing the doubts of these disciples and even some contempt, the unibrow man felt extremely wronged. F*ck! These fellows simply knew nothing! He should have let these idiots suffer a moment ago and let them personally find out just what sort of calamity he had let pass them.

As he felt that the big brother image had had set up had already collapsed, the unibrow man was disinclined to explain any further. He simply coldly snorted and said,  “Cut the nonsense, if you have so much time to speak, then go practice! No one will speak of what happened today or I will take back your true essence stones!”

Chapter 412 – The Sound of Broken Jade

On Blood Demon Island, within the thousand miles of the island, the entire land was covered with a hazy, thick blood-red fog all year round. This fog had magical properties. If it touched a wound, it would be like a leech that dug into a person’s body, corroding their blood essence.

Thus, if someone were to be seriously injured on Blood Demon Island, they would quickly die if they didn’t receive prompt treatment!

At this time, the sun was high in the sky. On Blood Demon Island’s Thundercrest Sect transmission array, there was deafening thunderclap. A blaze of flames scattered out, sending several Houtian disciples that had been defending the location flying away by the forceful and intense winds. Fireshine spread its massive 100 feet long wings and shot into the sky.

“What… this… what is happening!?”

A disciple flew in, his eyes filled with complete disbelief as he watched the giant Vermillion Bird shoot up into the sky. What was going on? How could a Vermillion Bird have come out of their transmission array?

Fireshine was far too fast. In the blink of an eye, it had already turned into a dot in the horizon.

The group of stunned Thundercrest Sect disciples were left puzzled, entirely unsure of what was happening…

………………

“There’s a response from the jade slip…” Qin Ziya looked at the soul jade slip in his hand, the sliver of soul inside was dimming even further.

“It’s most likely in that position.” Qin Ziya pointed. The soul jade slip could only make out a vague direction when it came to long distances.

“Give me the jade slip!” Lin Ming received the soul jade slip, controlling which direction Fireshine was flying.

Blood Demon Island had a thousand mile diameter. If the jade slip could accurately indicate which direction she was in, he could quickly find Qin Xingxuan.

At this moment, Lin Ming’s mind began to shake. He slowly lowered his head to look at the jade slip in his hand, and heard a ‘ka ka ka’ sound emit from it. This light ‘ka ka ka’ was as if the jade slip was under a tremendous pressure and was about to shatter at any moment.

Lin Ming’s complexion completely changed, and his heart stopped beating for a moment. As he held the jade slip in both hands, even his fingers began to tremble.

If this soul jade slip broke, that was proof that Qin Xingxuan had died!

The jade slip slowly shook for several breaths of time, and then finally stopped. The gentle glow of the soul sliver within the jade slip had completely vanished. Qin Ziya’s face was full of lament. “Qin Xingxuan is still alive. It’s just, Xingxuan now…”

Qin Ziya didn’t continue speaking. A soul jade slip was connected to a martial artist’s soul. Even if they were physically injured, had their limbs broken or even arms cut off, the soul jade slip would not emit sounds that it was breaking!

The only reason was if the soul of the martial artist themselves was on the verge of collapsing, or if their blood essence was seriously damaged!

Whatever the situation was, both of these were extremely bad results.

It could be said that Qin Xingxuan’s life was no different from a dying candle in a stormy ocean; it could disappear at any moment!

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a killing light filled with carnage. He silently placed the soul jade slip into his chest pocket, letting it touch his skin. He swore to himself, “Ouyang Boyan, if Xingxuan dies, I will bury your entire Seven Profound Valleys’ Ouyang Family Clan as tribute!”

Suddenly, the murderous intent of Lin Ming’s body erupted like a cataclysmic volcano. Even Qin Ziya, who had a cultivation at the early Xiantian realm, felt suffocated by this killing intent, like he could drown at any time within a sea of blood. Qin Ziya thought that in the moment that Lin Ming had witnessed the dimming of the soul jade slip, it was like he had turned into a demon of war!

The Vermillion Bird let out a deafening cry; flames appeared all around it, forming a swirling storm of fire. All of the blood demons around were forced to run away by this momentum that seemed to pierce the heavens, and none of them dared to approach.

There were even some slower blood demons that couldn’t run away in time, and they were rapidly engulfed in these burning flames and incinerated to ashes!

………………….

At this time, in a corner of Blood Demon Island, six martial artists were being besieged by dozens of blood demons within a clearing in the mountains.

Blood demons. The more people died, the more blood essence they could suck, and the more powerful they would become.

At the start of the war, both sides would fight each other on Blood Demon Island. Occasionally, they would also fight blood demons. But as more and more people died, at this point, often both sides would be slaughtering blood demons!

This sort of situation could not presently be resolved. They could only wait until the end of the war, and the side that won in the end would organize a party of masters to completely clear out the blood demons.

The blood demons were only four to five feet high. They looked like humans, but they were like beasts that crawled on the ground with four limbs. Their facial features were blurred, and mostly only a big mouth and dark glowing green eyes were left behind, like a wolf stalking at night.

Blood demons were like sharks – they were able to sense the smell of blood. They had surrounded these six martial artists and were ready to pounce at any given moment!

However, every time a blood demon rushed over, they would bounce off a clear, shining barrier. Any part of their body that touched this barrier of light would be instantly charred!

“Senior-apprentice Brother Ou, if this continues we won’t be able to last much longer!”

These six individuals were disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys. The one that spoke was from the Array Faction. This great array had been laid down by him in advance. Although Array Faction disciples had poor combat strength, if they were able to lay down their arrays in advance, they could play a huge role in positional battles.

This Senior-apprentice Brother Ou was Ou Xiong. The reason he had come to Blood Demon Island was to monitor Qin Xingxuan, and also to trap her. Since it was convenient, he would also take away all the medium-grade true essence stones that Qin Xingxuan had obtained.

As for mining for medium-grade true essence stones on Blood Demon Island and killing his way through blood demons to do so, Ou Xiong had never thought of this. To him, it was not worth the risk. He hadn’t lived long enough! As a disciple of the Acacia Faction, Ou Xiong had seven or eight concubines, and also more than a dozen pleasure maids. How could Ou Xiong ever give up such a wonderful arrangement?

However, when Ou Xiong saw that the disciples of the Five Element Region had obtained a Demon Blood Crystal, he couldn’t help but feel his heart stir with greed.

Blood Demon Crystal!

This was a very useful treasure to a Xiantian realm martial artist. If he could obtain a Blood Demon Crystal, he would be able to exchange it for a minimum of two or three Heaven Opening Pills with the sect!

With Ou Xiong’s talent, it was unlikely he would be able to break through to the Xiantian realm. The only chance he had would be if he swallowed down three or four Heaven Opening Pills. Only then would he have a chance of stepping into the Xiantian realm!

However, Ou Xiong’s last name was Ou, not Ouyang; who would give him three or four Heaven Opening Pills? Ou Xiong had already lost all hope of entering the Xiantian realm, but now, this opportunity had appeared in front of him. How could he not be tempted by this!

Within the Seven Profound Valleys, a Xiantian master was an Elder. The treatment that an Elder received was beyond that of a normal disciple. All those proud and arrogant women that had looked down on him with disdain…if he were an Elder, he could recklessly push them all down to serve his crotch!

Thinking of this, Ou Xiong became incomparably excited. Not just that, but a Xiantian realm martial artist removed the foul Houtian air from their bodies, and their life was a hundred years longer than a Houtian real martial artist. If he had an extra hundred years of life, he could enjoy blissful days for another hundred years, and play with beautiful women for another hundred years!

Thus Ou Xiong had decided to take a risk, and enter Blood Demon Island with this Seven Profound Valleys squad.

Within this squad, besides Ou Xiong, there were also two Acacia Faction disciples, one Array Faction disciple, a Zither Faction disciple, and finally Qin Xingxuan.

Qin Xingxuan was in an extremely bad situation, her lips and face had already lost all traces of color. This was the result of accumulated loss of blood essence over time. Not just that, but this time, she had been sneak attacked by a blood demon and had been bitten on the right arm, having a massive amount of blood essence sucked out of her.

Once a martial artist lost their blood essence, it was extremely difficult to recover!

When a martial artist lost blood essence, that also meant a loss of strength and life!

On Qin Xingxuan’s right arm, her sleeve had been completely ripped off, revealing an open wound that dripped with blood. This wound caused her life to continuously pour out of her.

The blood essence within her body was being continuously corroded. With her present ability, there was no way she could prevent this from happening.

Qin Xingxuan mirthlessly smiled; perhaps today, here, she would finally fall.

Even if she managed to return by a stroke of luck, she would not last another month. She had lost a massive amount of blood essence, and the source of her life was like a lamp that had run nearly completely dry…

“Senior-apprentice Brother Ou, the array formation will not last much longer. At most it can continue for another half an incense stick of time. We have to break through the encirclement afterwards!” The array faction disciple said.

Of everyone present, besides Ou Xiong who was at the middle Houtian realm, everyone’s cultivation was either at the peak Pulse Condensation period or even half-step Houtian realm.

Only Qin Xingxuan was at the early Pulse Condensation period. Her cultivation was the lowest, and her situation was also the worst.

“Break through…” Ou Xiong grit his teeth. Outside of the array formation, there were dozens of blood demons waiting to attack. There were even two higher level blood demons that weren’t much weaker than him. To break through this trap wouldn’t be easy at all.

“Blood demons are fast. If we have to break through, we have to have some people protect the rear and stop them from following.”

As Ou Xiong spoke, his eyes swept past everyone and fell on Qin Xingxuan.

Qin Xingxuan’s eyes were chilling. But, the one who actually became angry for Qin Xingxuan was the Zither Faction girl. “Ou Xiong, what are you trying to say!? Junior-apprentice Sister Qin is already severely injured. You want her to bring up the rear? Are you still human!?”

Ou Xiong callously shook his head, saying, “She cannot escape from here, her blood vitality is too weak. Whether or not she guards the rear, she will die. So if she is going to die, then why not make a sacrifice for the sect?”

“You…!” The Zither Faction girl’s eyes shot open, “You are shameless! Sacrifice for the sect! Maybe the one who should be sacrificed for the sect is you!”

Ou Xiong coldly sneered, “Since that is what you think, then you can go ahead and stay with her. Do as you wish!”

“Ou Xiong, you cruelly harm a fellow disciple and have violated the rules of the sect. Once I return to the Seven Profound Valleys, I will report this to the Elders and have them punish you for your crimes!”

After Ou Xiong heard these words, he frowned and his eyes flashed with killing intent. “Violate the rules of the sect? Have I killed you? Have I harmed you? I have not. Do you not want to break through? Dream on! Qin Yao, since you say so, then do not follow me when I break through this encirclement, you can stay with Qin Xingxuan!”

The Zither Faction girl shook with rage. She turned to look at the other disciples but found that they were avoiding her eyes. In a life or death situation, they would first think of themselves. Who would still bother to care for the fate of others?

Of everyone present, the one with the highest cultivation was Ou Xiong. With Ou Xiong, they had a slim hope for survival. Without him, they would undoubtedly die.

Ou Xiong looked at Qin Xingxuan and sent her a true essence sound transmission, “I really feel sorry for you. You are beautiful and talented, just don’t take this personally. You’ve lost your blood essence. Even if you can escape from here, you won’t last another month. And for you, escape is simply not possible. So, I have a pill here for you. This is a Blood Burning Pill. It can stimulate all the potential in your body. Once you eat it and you guard the rear, I can guarantee that your Qin Family will be safe. You should know that Elder Ouyang wants to deal with you and the Lin Family – he simply doesn’t care for the Qin Family.” As Ou Xiong spoke, he handed Qin Xingxuan a blood-red pill.

As the Zither Faction girl saw Ou Xiong give this pill to Qin Xingxuan, her complexion immediately hung. “Blood Burning Pill! Junior-apprentice Sister Qin, do not take it, this is simply a suicidal pill!”

Ou Xiong glanced at the Zither Faction girl and sneered. He continued to speak through a true essence sound transmission, “Junior-apprentice Sister Qin, I am willing to take an oath on my heart of martial arts. As long as you can bring up the rear when we break out, I will guarantee the safety of your family. Although my promise is not too valuable, it is still an oath that I make. I won’t damage my heart of martial arts just for the lives of a few mortals. Much less, I have no enmity with your Qin Family.”

Chapter 419 – Take Your Life

In the center of the white marble stage, a sword light flashed, and a Seven Profound Valleys disciple gave a miserable cough as he was sent flying off the stage.

“Fierce Flood Sect’s Liu Xuan, victory!” The referee deeply looked into Liu Xuan’s eyes as he announced the result.

“Fierce! This Liu Xuan has won three continuous matches!”

“And he still has strength remaining.”

“The younger generation is really spilling forth with heroic elites. Liu Xuan, Ye Tian, Zhang Yan – all are more powerful than the last.”

“But the truly fierce ones are the masters of the Seven Profound Valleys. The ones that have followed Liu Xuan up are the inner court disciples. Although they lost, the difference between them isn’t too great. If the Seven Profound Valleys’ core disciples or direct disciples enter the stage, then I have no idea what those battles will be like!”

A disciple sighed. Everyone couldn’t help but glance over at Ouyang Ming, and were surprised to see that he had a clear, dreamy expression on his face as if he simply didn’t care about these fights that were occurring onstage.

Obviously, battles of this level – even those including Liu Xuan – simply didn’t enter Ouyang Ming’s eyes.

Those who glanced at him to gave birth to an an extremely deep and profound feeling.

“Just how far does the degree of Ouyang Ming’s strength reach?” Some people couldn’t help but ask.

“I cannot fathom. In short, all I can tell is that he is surpassingly strong. Perhaps he is even stronger than our sect’s Sovereign.” The one who spoke was a disciple from a small sect. His sect’s Sovereign had already reached the peak Houtian realm.

“Stronger than your Sovereign? Isn’t that just too exaggerated!?”

……………..

At this time, Ouyang Boyan was sitting atop the main island, watching the stage as the battles progressed and listening to the sounds of gently instruments float to his ear. He had a very enjoyable expression on his face, as if he was taking in all the luxuries of life. He had beautiful women swaying by his sides. These were his concubines and his maids. As these beautiful women weaved around him, it was a truly beautiful sight.

Today was the happiest day Ouyang Boyan had ever experienced.

Lin Ming had died. Qin Xingxuan would suffer a miserable and painful death. The Qin Family and Lin Family, both would be destroyed. And soon, Qin Ziya would quickly be penalized. All of Ouyang Boyan’s thoughts were smooth.

Not just that, but during this banquet there was even a second-grade sect that had offered him 12 Pure Yin girls.

These 12 Pure Yin girls had to have a talent above the third-grade and also be below 20 years of age. And most importantly, they also needed to be beautiful, virgin women. The most demanding requirement was their date of birth; it was extremely difficult to collect these 12 girls. Initially, Zhang Guanyu had offered a batch of 12 Pure Yin girls to Ouyang Dihua for his assistance. And, the final result of this was that Ouyang Dihua had instead lost his own life.

12 Pure Yin girls were extremely beneficial to one’s cultivation of the Divine Acacia Power. Ouyang Boyan had already looked over these 12 young and beautiful girls and he was extremely satisfied by what he saw. Tonight, he would take their virginity and use it to enhance his own cultivation.

Thinking of this, Ouyang Boyan’s thoughts began to heat up with lust; his mind had already drifted onto the bodies of those 12 beautiful girls.

But at this moment, a flame suddenly lit in front of him. It was a sound transmitting talisman.

Ouyang Boyan heard the message from this sound transmitting talisman and was shocked, “Someone from Divine Phoenix is forcing their way into the Seven Profound Valleys?”

Ouyang Boyan doubted this for a moment, and then heard the clarion cry of a phoenix. Ten miles away, a massive Vermillion Bird cut through the skies, leaving a path of flames that burned the heavens!

Ouyang Boyan stood up.

The Vermillion Bird was the absolute symbol of Divine Phoenix Island. If one saw a Vermillion Bird, they would know without a doubt that it was Divine Phoenix Island. But, why would someone from Divine Phoenix Island come to the Seven Profound Valleys? They couldn’t be coming to congratulate him right? Divine Phoenix Island had countless Xiantian masters. To them, Ouyang Boyan who had just broken through to the middle Xiantian realm wasn’t even worth a fart. So how would they possibly come here to celebrate?

Everyone present also saw the massive Vermillion Bird approaching. No one was allowed to fly over the Seven Profound Valleys’ entrance, but no one dared to stop this Vermillion Bird!

Lin Ming flew straight towards the Profound Sky Mountains. There were several small spirit boats that approached him, wishing to inquire about who he was, but they were instantly thrown off by Fireshine. Fireshine’s speed was even quicker than a Revolving Core master.

“Heavens! Is that a phoenix!?”

“A phoenix! I’m not seeing things!”

“It’s coming down! It’s coming down!”

Several thousand pairs of eyes were wide as they stared into the sky. Everyone stood. Most of the people present were only from second-grade sects, when could they ever witness the advent of a Saint Beast!

They could not distinguish the difference between a phoenix and a Vermillion Bird.

A 100 foot long wingspan and a body entirely wreathed in roaring flames; strong gales formed a vortex, making it difficult to breathe for everyone below. Fireshine closed its massive wings, and looked down on the world with utter impunity as it dropped straight down!

Bang!

Flames combusted in all directions. Fireshine fell directly onto the middle of the lake island, and the hot streams of fiery wind smashed away all the furniture. Those martial artists with weaker cultivations were even forced back several steps by this strong wind!

All of those present were frightened. Fireshine was Mu Yuhuang’s Vermillion Bird. It was a grown Vermillion Bird. Compared to Mu Qianyu’s Little Flame, it was over double the size!

“Is that Divine Phoenix Island’s envoy?”

“Divine Phoenix Island also sends congratulations to Elder Ouyang? Elder Ouyang’s face is truly great!”

The many disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys were excitedly speaking amongst themselves. They assumed that the reason Divine Phoenix Island had sent an envoy here was to congratulate Ouyang Boyan. This sounded improbable, but during the last Seven Profound Valleys’ Total Faction Martial Meeting, Divine Phoenix Island had also sent an envoy to visit.

In their limited worldview, it was possible that Divine Phoenix Island would send someone to congratulate Ouyang Boyan for breaking through to the middle Xiantian realm.

Of course, Ouyang Boyan never entertained such a fanciful idea. His expression was solemn, and his eyes had already turned onto the several figures that were being carried on the Vermillion Bird’s back…

A youth jumped down. In that moment, every single Seven Profound Valleys disciple fell silent.

Several thousand eyes turned their gazes towards this youth, completely stunned.

This person wore black clothes, and his long hair was recklessly scattered. He held a deep purplish-red long spear in his hand.

His handsome face seemed as if it was hewed by a saber, and his two straight eyebrows slanted up. His eyes were deep and profound as if they contained the endless night sky! He only stood there, but yet a giant, invisible wave of pressure rushed out from him like a tide; even those people hundreds of feet away could clearly feel this aura. It caused them to find it hard to breathe and their hearts to palpitate!

At this moment, that youth standing in the center of the square was like a heavenly God of War.

“Who?”

“Who is that?”

The second-grade sect disciples began to speak amongst themselves. They had heard Lin Ming’s name, but they had never seen Lin Ming before.

However, the Seven Profound Valleys’ disciples were bewildered. Many of them subconsciously rubbed their eyes, thinking that they were hallucinating.

Lin Ming!

It was really Lin Ming!

He hadn’t died!?

Ouyang Ming’s face had completely changed. The calm smile of before had vanished, replaced by a deep awe and reverence that stemmed from the depths of his being. He would never forget the events of a year and a half ago. At the Total Faction Martial Meeting, the early Pulse Condensation period Lin Ming had completely defeated him, he didn’t even have the slightest bit of ability to resist!

Now, over a year had passed, and Ouyang Ming had reached the early Houtian realm. He once believed that Lin Ming had died, but never thought that he would stand in front of him here today. Not just that, but his cultivation had risen to the late Houtian realm!

In just a year and a half, Lin Ming’s cultivation had risen by an entire realm and half!

At the beginning, Lin Ming’s cultivation was weaker than Ouyang Ming’s. But presently, Lin Ming had cast Ouyang Ming far behind!

If a early Pulse Condensation period Lin Ming already had the ability to defeat the peak Pulse Condensation period Jiang Baoyun, then how terrifying was the current late Houtian realm Lin Ming?

Could he have strength equal to the early Xiantian realm?

Ouyang Ming only felt his mind tremble, he no longer dared to imagine the possibilities!

Ouyang Boyan’s eyes fiercely twitched, his fists tightening and his palms sweating.

Lin Ming hadn’t died!

Why!?

Why didn’t he die!?

Not only was he alive, but his cultivation had actually reached the late Houtian realm! In just a year and a half, how could this have happened!?

Ouyang Boyan screaming in his heart!

He hated!

He was unwilling!

He feared!

It was impossible that Lin Ming hadn’t discovered what he had done these past months. Perhaps Lin Ming might not be able to threaten him with his current strength, but what about later?

If his growth continued at this breakneck speed, then in a year, Lin Ming might even be able to kill him!

When that time came, he couldn’t count on anyone in the Seven Profound Valleys raising their head to defend him. Under the suppression of absolute strength, even the Seven Profound Valleys would not hesitate for a second to sacrifice him.

That meant all he could do was escape. If he stayed in the Severn Profound Valleys, all that awaited him was death.

Ouyang Boyan coldly looked at Lin Ming. He did not do something foolish or useless like apologizing. In the moment that Lin Ming had dropped down, he was able to feel the thick and overwhelming killing intent surging from his body. Ouyang Boyan knew that Lin Ming had already resolved to kill him!

Unfortunately, Lin Ming was far too impulsive. If he had just patiently waited for another year, then he really might have been able to kill him.

In that moment, many thoughts flashed through Ouyang Boyan’s heart. He didn’t lose his calm. Instead, he stood there steadily like a tree.

“Elder Ouyang! How have you been since we last met? I hope you’ve been well!”

Lin Ming’s expression was blank as he spoke. But, his voice was like a cold wind that billowed up from the ninth layer of the abyss. The entire atmosphere of the banquet suddenly chilled to subzero degrees.

Many of those who were from second-grade sects didn’t know who this youth was standing before them. But what they could understand was that this person absolutely did not come to congratulate them, but instead to ruin the scene!

Who was this? He dared to force his way into the Seven Profound Valleys? But looking at the Saint Beast, this youth was definitely not common. Perhaps he came from some large family clan or sect. Many of those in the Seven Profound territory only knew that the greatest power was the Seven Profound Valleys – they didn’t know the existence of Divine Phoenix Island. This wasn’t surprising. After all, only those that stood at the top would be exposed to a greater world. Initially, Lin Ming hadn’t known of Divine Phoenix Island’s existence either.

Ouyang Boyan’s expression was ugly. He wanted to smile, but eventually stopped trying. “You are not here to celebrate with this old man!”

Lin Ming held his spear down, and lazily traced a full moon on the white marble square. He chuckled, and then slowly and unhurriedly said, “Of course not. I’m here to take your life!”

With this sentence, the entire audience was shocked. Most of the Seven Profound Valleys disciples didn’t know that Ouyang Boyan had enmity with Lin Ming. As for those second-grade sect individuals, they didn’t even know what Lin Ming looked like, let alone something like that.

“What!?”

“Take Ouyang Boyan’s life!? Did I hear wrong?”

No one was able to understand what was happening. This was the Seven Profound Valleys’ domain, and someone dared threaten to take the life of a Seven Profound Valleys Elder? Were these words that a normal person would say?

Not just that, but this youth’s cultivation was only at the late Houtian realm. Even though his momentum was formidable, just what would he able to do?

Even Ouyang Ming, who acknowledged Lin Ming’s strength, also felt that Lin Ming was being naïve. With so many Acacia Faction Elders present, how could Lin Ming possibly kill someone in front of them? In fact, he probably wouldn’t be able to defeat Ouyang Boyan.

Qin Ziya forced a smile.

Ultimately, it seemed that they couldn’t escape this result…

Chapter 422 – Acacia Sovereign Ouyang

At this moment, a loud shout rolled out like thunder, “Stop!”

Everyone in the square followed the source of the loud voice. One thousand feet away, they could see a white-clothed man quickly closing in at an extreme speed. Even though he was 1000 feet away, he was able to cross a hundred feet in an instant. All of the Acacia Faction disciples were immediately overjoyed.

“It’s the Sovereign! The Sovereign has come!”

The Acacia Faction’s Sovereign was Ouyang Shenxiu. His cultivation was at the extreme Xiantian realm. Within all of the Xiantian masters of the Seven Profound Valleys, his strength was ranked in the top four.

However, Lin Ming didn’t care about Ouyang Shenxiu’s warning; he still drove the Divine Demon Thunder Soul towards Ouyang Boyan for the killing blow!

“Insolence!”

Ouyang Shenxiu was still a few hundred feet away. It wouldn’t be easy for him to stop this Divine Demon Steel Needle.

“Go!”

Ouyang Shenxiu slashed out with his sword and a red sword energy accurately struck the Divine Demon Steel Needle. However, this move was too hasty, and it was too far away. Although the Divine Demon Steel Needle fiercely trembled, a massive power of thunder still fell onto Ouyang Boyan’s body like a typhoon.

In the blink of an eye, the fragile true essence that protected Ouyang Boyan was torn to shreds. He gave a pitiful scream, and then his body was tossed high into the air. His hair was completely singed off, and he crashed back down like a pheasant that had been shot, his entire body covered in blood.

Ouyang Boyan’s body twitched, and then he vomited out a large pool of blood. He had already lost a great deal of energy, and now there was almost nothing left.

As Ouyang Shenxiu arrived at the square, his saw Ouyang Boyan’s pitiful state and his complexion sunk. He had warned in advance, but Lin Ming had still turned a deaf ear and cast down a heavy-handed attack!

Pu! Pu!

Closely following behind Ouyang Shenxiu were two white-clothed men. They were both disciples that Ouyang Shenxiu had received many years ago. They had just broken through to the early Xiantian realm about 10 years ago, and could be considered among the most shallow and weak of Elders.

As one of them saw Ouyang Boyan’s current state, his eyes turned red. He was someone who shared a father and mother with Ouyang Boyan, his blood brother, Ouyang Boxu. He instantly appeared at Ouyang Boyan’s side and fed him some life maintaining pills. As Ouyang Boxu stood up, his eyes were filled with a murderous intent, no different from a raging vicious beast.

“Lin Ming! I’ll kill you!”

Ouyang Boxu raised his sword and was about to rush forwards when Ouyang Shenxiu coldly snorted and said, “Draw back!”

Ouyang Boxu immediately paled. He grit his teeth and drew back a single step. But, his eyes still flashed with fury and bone-deep loathing as he kept them glued to Lin Ming.

…………..

“Lin Ming, you’ve returned!”

Ouyang Shenxiu indifferently looked at Lin Ming. During the Seven Profound Valleys’ Total Faction Martial Meeting, Ouyang Shenxiu had once casually met with Lin Ming. He had even invited Lin Ming to join the Acacia Faction, but had eventually let it go.

“Sovereign Ouyang.” Lin Ming said as he faced Ouyang Shenxiu. His expression was the same.

Lin Ming did not fear Ouyang Shenxiu. He knew that sooner or later this old man would jump out of the woodworks; he was the only enemy here that he needed to take seriously.

Before this old man appeared, Lin Ming was trying to reserve as much strength as he could. He would never have used Thunderfire Annihilation a moment ago if he didn’t have to fend off the combined attack of five Elders. But even though he had used that move, he had only used 30% of its total strength. There was still 70% of the power of thunder and fire left within the Heretical God Seed, and it was also recovering at a breakneck pace.

“Lin Ming, the Seven Profound Valleys has been good to you. You studied at Sky Fortune Kingdom’s Seven Profound Martial House, and afterwards you became champion of the Total Faction Martial Meeting. The Seven Profound Valleys even granted you a Heaven Opening Pill. But you still forced your way into the Seven Profound Valleys and severely wounded and crippled Elders of my Acacia Faction. Just what is your reasoning behind this?”

“Has been good to me?” Lin Ming coldly sneered. “The Seven Profound Valleys plundered the martial cultivation resources of Sky Fortune Kingdom, making it so that the martial artists of Sky Fortune Kingdom wouldn’t have resources available to them. To them, even breaking through to the Pulse Condensation period is something they can only vainly aspire towards. The Seven Profound Martial Houses are just a form of returning some of the resources that you lot have plundered, and the so-called fostering talents is so that the Seven Profound Valleys can use them for themselves. Is it some form of graciousness? Hardly.”

“A year and a half ago, I was of great value to the Seven Profound Valleys, so the Seven Profound Valleys naturally treated me well. But, after the Seven Profound Valleys heard news of my death, Ouyang Boyan finally decided to take revenge for personal grudges between us. He repeatedly acted and plotted against Qin Xingxuan, the Qin Family, Lin Family, and everyone else involved with me. Weren’t these deeds all done through the connections of your Ouyang Family Clan? When I left the Seven Profound Valleys, Divine Phoenix Island already paid a high enough price for me. I no longer owe the Seven Profound Valleys anything. The reason that I came here today is to demand that justice be served. Ouyang Boyan must die!”

Ouyang Shenxiu deeply frowned. He had rushed to the scene and yet Lin Ming had let out this raving rant in front of him. If he allowed Lin Ming to kill Ouyang Boyan here, then how would he be able to establish himself in the martial arts world?

“This old man is not clear about what matters you speak of!” Ouyang Shenxiu was not lying. As a top figure of the Seven Profound Valleys, he naturally wouldn’t concern himself over these minor matters. But, he believed that Lin Ming was mostly speaking the truth, and he also had a certain understanding of Ouyang Boyan’s character. Someone like him could absolutely do what Lin Ming had described.

“Even if what you said is true, isn’t that young girl behind you Miss Qin? Even if Ouyang Boyan had tried to harm her, she is safe and sound. Yet you actually cut off Ouyang Boyan’s arm and severely wounded him, completely wasting away his road of martial arts! Haven’t you just gone too far?”

“Haha!” Lin Ming chuckled. “Safe and sound? What a well said ‘safe and sound’! By holding the lives of the Qin Family in his hands, Ouyang Boyan forced Qin Xingxuan to go to Blood Demon Island for over a month! When I arrived there, Qin Xingxuan’s body had already been exhausted of all the blood essence she had, and her life was at its end. If it wasn’t for me using miracle medicine that is sufficient to create several Revolving Core masters, then she would have already turned to ashes. And that is what you call ‘safe and sound’?”

Lin Ming’s words caused the entire audience to gasp in shock. Sufficient miracle medicine to create several Revolving Core masters?

Heavens!

If what Lin Ming said was true, then using such amazing medicine that could create several Revolving Core masters on a Pulse Condensation period junior was simply a careless waste of heaven’s treasures!

Ouyang Shenxiu’s lips twitched. Even he had distant hopes to one day step into the Revolving Core realm. But these were only hopes, and were in reality an unachievable dream. In this generation of Seven Profound Valleys Elders and Sovereigns, only the Sword Faction Sovereign Jiang Wuji had a slim chance to break into the Revolving Core realm, but, it was more likely that he would fail.

The one with the greatest hopes of stepping into the Revolving Core realm was currently the Sword Faction’s chief disciple, Jiang Baoyun.

Ouyang Shenxiu couldn’t help but ask Ouyang Guang a question through a true essence sound transmission, “How strong is Lin Ming?”

Ouyang Guang thought deeply about this for a moment and then responded, “He should be equal to a late Xiantian realm master. Just a moment ago, me, Ouyang Boyan, and three other Elders collaborated in a joint attack on him, but we were actually defeated in a single move. And that move should also be Lin Ming’s final decisive ability. “

“Late Xiantian realm…” Ouyang Shenxiu’s complexion sank. Ouyang Guang’s strength was already at the peak of the middle Xiantian realm. Yet even though four other Elders had joined forces with him and combined their attacks, they were defeated by Lin Ming’s counterattack. Lin Ming’s strength had absolutely reached at least the late Xiantian realm!

A 17 year old with strength at the late Xiantian realm! That was simply an unimaginable dream! Within the Seven Profound Valleys, there were nearly 100 Xiantian masters, and over half of them were stranded at the early Xiantian realm. 20 to 30 were at the middle Xiantian realm, and as for those at the late Xiantian realm or extreme Xiantian realm, there were only a mere handful of Elders. In fact, there weren’t really more late Xiantian realm masters than there were extreme Xiantian masters. The Acacia Faction only had two Vice Sovereigns that had been able to reach the late Xiantian realm. They had gone to participate in the South Sea war and still hadn’t returned.

Thus, one could see just how rare the late Xiantian realm was.

If it were possible, Ouyang Shenxiu wouldn’t want to make Lin Ming his enemy. But now he was unable to back down. He had ridden the tiger, and there was no disembarking from this wild ride. If someone were freely allowed to sweep away his Acacia Faction at such an important occasion without any punishment, then how could his Acacia Faction further establish themselves in the future?

Ouyang Shenxiu grit his teeth and said, “Since that’s the case, Ouyang Boyan has already paid a sufficient price. Relinquish this matter and I will no longer pursue it. But, since you forced your way into my Acacia Faction’s greatest peak and also injured so many Elders and disciples, I have no choice but to punish you! Take my three moves. If you can take my three moves, then regardless of whether you live or die, I will consider everything settled.”

“Relinquish this matter and you will no longer pursue it?” Lin Ming’s eyebrows rose and then he sneered. “I am the one that Ouyang Boyan had tried to deal with, just what qualifications do you have to say that you will no longer pursue anything at all? Today, I will take Ouyang Boyan’s life! As for anyone who tries to stop me, from now on they will only be my mortal enemy!”

“Lin Ming!” Ouyang Shenxiu’s complexion was extremely ugly. He had already taken a step back and tried to resolve matters. Although he had said regardless of life or death, the truth was that he didn’t dare to kill Lin Ming. The most he would do was severely wound him. As long as Lin Ming was just injured, he would be fine after resting up. This matter would be settled, and he would also gain face for being able to resolve matters like this. But, he hadn’t expected that Lin Ming would be contemptuous and try to bully others like so. This caused Ouyang Shenxiu to burn with anger.

“Lin Ming, do you really think that there is no one in my Acacia Faction that can stop you!? Good! I had originally planned to just give you a light little spanking, but since you insist on being so arrogant and pushing things beyond your limits, then today I will have to personally see whether or not you can take Boyan’s life!!”

As Ouyang Shenxiu finished speaking, he took a fierce step forwards. His aura erupted, and waves of roiling blood surged out, overwhelming the world!

Whether or it was the Elders or disciples, everyone nearby was forced back by this suppressive aura.

There were already those that had learned their lesson. The lower level disciples had already experienced this before, and besides several Great Elders, all the other disciples launched their fastest movement techniques to flee from the main island to avoid being collateral damage.

Even Ouyang Ming was forced back and retreated all the way to the edge of the main island. As for the proud Liu Xuan from the Fierce Flood Sect, he naturally couldn’t lose face by running. He wanted to stay on the main island, but after looking at the Ouyang Shenxiu’s intimidating aura, he grit his teeth and returned to a pavilion that floated on the water. The shockwaves of Lin Ming’s Thunderfire Annihilation had already forced him to use every bit of his strength to just barely be able to resist it. Now, in the face of this even higher level battle, Liu Xuan realized that he didn’t have the qualifications to stand nearby.

“Lin Ming, you are far too unruly, not respecting others and acting like you can dominate anyone you cross. Even if you have the backing of Divine Phoenix Island, I will still teach you a lesson. In these three moves, I will not hold back. Whether you live or die, that will be the price that you pay!

Lin Ming held the spear horizontally in his hands, silent. His eyes were like the stars in the deep night sky – bright and calm. However, at this time Lin Ming was actually feeling the blood boiling within his body; his fighting spirit was brimming over!

Extreme Xiantian!

Not too long ago, he had believed that those at the extreme Xiantian realm were top masters. Shi Zongtian, Ouyang Shenxiu, Jiang Wuji, which one of these characters weren’t gods among men that could shake the entire Seven Profound territory with but a single word!?

A year and a half ago, facing these characters, he could only vainly look up at them. But now, Lin Ming was standing right in front of an extreme Xiantian master, ready to fight!

When an ant became a fierce tiger, he would look back on the road he walked and inevitably feel vibrant and ambitious after seeing just how far he had come.

“In this battle, by exchanging blows with an extreme Xiantian master, I’ll be able to find out just what martial arts realm a 65% Tempering Marrow boundary can bring me to!”

Chapter 426 – Auspicious Sign of the Heavens

The corrosive Fallen Star Flame Flame Essence drilled straight through Ouyang Guang’s stomach, piercing through his dantian and shooting out from behind!

Ouyang Guang grabbed onto the shaft of the Purple Come Spear. He slowly looked down at the hole in his stomach that was pouring out thick, black blood, his face colored with disbelief.

He extended his hand out, waving it in front of him as if he wanted to grab onto something. However, his eyes relaxed and dulled, and the light faded from them.

Ouyang Guang fell to his knees, and then softly plopped onto the floor.

So far, of the seven Elders and Sovereign from the Acacia Faction, some had died, some were severely wounded, and some had escaped; there were none left!

The entire main island was emptied, even Ouyang Ming had returned to a small island. Now, on the main island, the only one left standing was Lin Ming.

With his own strength, not even the seven Great Elders of the Acacia Faction had been able to stop him. Such a frightening strength caused all the surrounding martial artists to hold their breath, afraid that they would attract the attention of this monster in human form.

Lin Ming took the Purple Comet Spear and walked in front of Ouyang Boyan. At this time, Ouyang Boyan only had a single breath of life left. He glanced at Lin Ming, but his eyes had already glazed over.

The Purple Comet Spear flashed with a cold light, and there was a light piercing sound as a gaping hole appeared in Ouyang Boyan’s stomach, followed by a shower of blood.

All of the surrounding martial artists from small sects jumped, feeling faint at heart. Just a moment ago, this had been a lively and grand celebratory banquet. Ouyang Boyan had been filled with happiness and elation due to his breakthrough, but now, that happy man had been slaughtered in a way no different from a farm chicken!

Such a great contrast caused everyone to feel a deep sense of awe and dread.

Lin Ming placed Ouyang Boyan’s corpse into his spatial ring. He wanted to verify something. Was a Xiantian martial artist’s blood essence able to open the Magic Cube once again?

“Lin Ming! You’re alright!” Qin Xingxuan ran over to Lin Min and helped support him, her face filled with worry and concern. Lin Ming’s appearance was just too horrible at the moment. He was bruised all over, and his true essence had been overdrawn.

“I’m alright.” Lin Ming brightly smiled at Qin Xingxuan to reassure her at let her feel more at ease. He said, “Come on, let’s go home…”

…………………………………

“Senior Master… Ouyang Boyan had died.”

In the back mountains of the Seven Profound Valleys, Shi Zongtian stood outside of a cave mansion, his face solemn.

As the Seven Profound Valleys’ Valley Master, the only one that Shi Zongtian would refer to with such respect would be the Highest Elder of the Seven Profound Valleys, Jiang Huan.

Jiang Huan was now 500 years old. He had been stranded at the early Revolving Core realm, and was reaching the end of his life. In these past many years, he had gone into closed seclusion.

The reason that Jiang Huan was in seclusion was not because he wanted to break past the early Revolving Core realm; he was well aware that his life was nearly exhausted, and breaking through was nothing but a wild dream. Jiang Huan had used this method of seclusion in order to delay the embers of his flickering life from fading. He greatly hoped that he would be able to maintain his feeble existence and linger on in the world until the day that Jiang Baoyun made a breakthrough to the extreme Xiantian realm.

Only such a super powerhouse like that would be able to guarantee the stability of the Seven Profound Valleys.

Therefore in these past years, regardless of any matter, Jiang Huan rarely left his cave mansion, and that why was rumors had been passed along in the smaller sects that Jiang Huan was in life or death closed door seclusion.

“I know…”

As Jiang Huan slowly spoke, his voice had a faint dying energy.

In fact, Jiang Huan had already been made aware of the situation ever since Lin Ming had broken into the Seven Profound Valleys, and was very clear on the entire process of what had happened.

Shi Zongtian hesitated and said, “Should I go and speak with Lin Ming?”

Although the Sword Faction and Acacia Faction had many disagreements, and even many areas in which they were complete and polar opposites, they were still in the same sect. Lin Ming had killed one after another within the Acacia Faction, and this would ruin their Sword Faction’s reputation too. If this spread out, then others would say that the Seven Profound Valleys had been invaded by a 20-something year old baby, and no one dared to even admonish him.

Jiang Huang said, “There’s no point in you going. Since Lin Ming came to the Seven Profound Valleys, he naturally has something to rely on. If it’s as you said and Lin Ming truly does have a reason to take revenge, then Ouyang Boyan wouldn’t have sat idly by. I thought that he would rely on the Acacia Faction and pay off Lin Ming with some high price, but I never thought that he would underestimate Lin Ming’s strength to this degree. In truth, it wasn’t just him who underestimated Lin Ming, but also me. I never would have dreamed that Lin Ming’s strength was already formidable to this degree!”

Shi Zongtian listened silently, not speaking. He had a certain understanding of Lin Ming’s personality. Even if he went, he would just lose face in the end no matter what he did. If that was the case, then he might as well not go. Not just that, but Lin Ming also came here riding a Vermillion Bird. The Vermillion Bird represented Divine Phoenix Island and wouldn’t recklessly attack the Seven Profound Valleys, but it was still a form of deterrence.

Thinking things over, Shi Zongtian sighed. Finally, he decided not to involve himself with this matter. Everything would be settled by Lin Ming and the Acacia Faction.

…………………..

On the highest peak of the Acacia Faction, a resonant phoenix cry echoed through the heavens. The Vermillion Bird shot into the sky. Nobody dared to stop Lin Ming. In the view of the surrounding martial artists, Lin Ming had forced his way into the Acacia Faction and killed several of their Great Elders. But, the other six factions of the Seven Profound Valleys hadn’t even appeared, and Lin Ming had cockily sauntered his way out.

The banquet naturally couldn’t continue. The martial artists from the small sects quickly excused themselves and left. After the seven Great Elders had been completely wasted by Lin Ming alone, the one with the highest status left on scene was Ouyang Ming.

The martial artists quickly spoke their farewells to Ouyang Ming. Ouyang Ming ruefully smiled, he never thought that the celebratory banquet the Acacia Faction held today would have such a result.

Ouyang Ming was no longer inclined to think about Lin Ming. He and Lin Ming were destined to follow different paths and tread on different worlds. He wouldn’t take Lin Ming as his goal in life; instead, he would just believe that Lin Ming no longer existed.

The wind howled.

Lin Ming, Qin Xingxuan, and Qin Ziya all stood atop the Vermillion Bird. They had already left the range of the Seven Profound Valleys’ mountains.

Lin Ming said, “Martial House Master Qin, what are you planning to do in the future?”

Qin Ziya thought for a moment and then said, “I will stay in the Seven Profound Valleys in the future. There were already many conflicts between the Zither Faction and the Acacia Faction. Although I have offended the Acacia Faction this time, it won’t affect me much.”

“Martial House Master Qin, how about switching sects? For instance, joining Divine Phoenix Island?”

“Divine Phoenix Island… consider it finished. In my life, I pursue the zither with my heart and soul. I can only do this within the Zither Faction, Divine Phoenix Island does not suit me.”

Lin Ming nodded. What Qin Ziya said was right. He had spent half his life cultivating the zither, it was impossible for him to branch out and practice other cultivation methods again.

“Then, I must separate with Martial House Master Qin. When I was stranded within the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, it was all thanks to Martial House Master Qin that Xingxuan remained safe for as long as she did. I, Lin Ming, will engrave this kindness onto my mind.”

Qin Ziya laughed and said, “If it wasn’t for you, I would never have stepped into the Xiantian realm. If we are speaking of kindnesses, then yours is greater than mine. This time in helping Miss Qin, the truth is that I didn’t play much of a role, I could only do as much as I could in order to not frustrate my thoughts.”

To those from the Zither Faction and Sword Faction who were mostly honest and held a greater value towards integrity, they would never feel comfortable if they owed anyone anything. Only when they returned the favor would they feel at peace. So in general, these individuals didn’t often owe favors to others.

“Lin Ming, this is where we part. I bid you farewell, take care of yourself.” Qin Ziya waved his sleeves, and then leapt down from the Vermillion Bird. His white clothing quickly vanished within the strong heavenly winds.

Lin Ming watched as Qin Ziya’s figure disappeared. He cupped his fists across his chest and said, “Martial House Master Qin, please take care…”

“Lin Ming… where will we go to?” Qin Xingxuan asked as she stood beside Lin Ming.

She had already prepared to follow Lin Ming to the edges of heaven and the ends of the earth.

“First we’ll go home, and then we’ll go to Divine Phoenix Island. You can cultivate within Divine Phoenix Island.”

“Mm, then let’s do as you say.” Qin Xingxuan bit her lips, feeling incomparably at peace. With Lin Ming, she no longer worried about anything at all.

……………..

Sky Fortune Kingdom was several hundred thousand miles away from the Seven Profound Valleys. Transferring news was often a very slow and arduous process. In order to activate a sound transmission array once, it required a great amount of true essence stones, and would also wear down the limited integrity of the array formation, shortening its life.

In normal circumstances, the current Seven Profound Martial House Master who was also Ouyang Boyan’s disciple would only make a report to Ouyang Boyan once a month. Now that Ouyang Boyan had died, there was no longer anyone to manage this chess piece he had left within Sky Fortune Kingdom.

In fact, besides Ouyang Boyan, not many people knew that Yang Zhen and this cloaked man were followers of Ouyang Boyan. These people were on a very low level. The Acacia Faction Elders naturally wouldn’t bother with them.

The news of single-handedly killing his way into the Acacia Faction and wrecking them hadn’t yet spread out. Before the second-grade sect disciples had returned to their sect, Lin Ming had already arrived back at Sky Fortune Kingdom. With the Vermillion Bird’s astoundingly extreme speed along with the use of two transmission arrays, Lin Ming had managed to return to Sky Fortune Kingdom in a single day and night.

On this day, all of Qin Xingxuan’s anxieties and fears had been clearly seen by Lin Ming’s eyes. The Qin Family members’ lives were all at stake, so of course Qin Xingxuan was nervous.

It was an ordinary morning in Sky Fortune City. The sun had just risen, and the fresh and bright sunlight had just started spreading throughout the city. The common peasant workers held their hoes across their shoulders as they headed to the fields outside the city to farm. Merchants sold their wares in their shops. At this moment, a bright red light flashed on the horizon. From afar, it was like a massive group of flames was burning the air.

This flame was at first very small, but it began to grow at an alarming speed. Everyone quickly realized that this wasn’t a group of flames, but rather a fiery bird!

Everyone couldn’t help but stop whatever work they were doing and stare at the sky, dazed.

A resounding phoenix cry spread through the horizon. The massive Vermillion Bird with its 100 foot wingspan cut across the limitless blue sky!

All of Sky Fortune City’s residents were shocked!

“Phoenix!”

“Heavens! Is that a phoenix!?”

“Am I dreaming?”

To mortals, a phoenix was an existence that they had only heard about in ancient stories and legends. In the legends, when an emperor had united the dynasty and performed a great deed, a phoenix would appear unto the world; this was the so-called auspicious sign of the heavens.

“The phoenix is flying to the Royal Palace!”

With that, people quickly came to their senses. This must be related to the great deeds of the newly crowned emperor!

Thinking of this, everyone quickly kneeled on the ground, prostrating themselves in worship as they stared at this phoenix in the sky.

At this time, in the vast grand hall of Sky Fortune City’s Royal Palace, Yang Zhen was meeting his court. Within 30 days of ascending the throne, he had summoned the representatives of the difference provinces and was to meet with them.

Under the grand podium, hundreds of leaders and officials from the various provinces were kneeling. Yang Zhen was sitting grandly above them. At this moment, he heard a shrill cry as someone entered…

A court eunuch burst into the grand hall, a great smile on his face as he shouted, “Emperor! This is a great occasion, a great occasion! An auspicious sign of the heavens has come! An auspicious sign of the heavens!”

Chapter 428 – Opening the Magic Cube Again

Sky Fortune City, Marshal Quarters –

The Marshal Quarters had been surrounded for over a month by the army, and not even servants were allowed to leave. But now, within a quarter of an hour of Yang Zhen’s death, those officials that had realized the vast changes that were about to sweep through the nation instantly lifted the order of house arrest for Qin Xiao.

Undoubtedly, Crown Prince Yang Lin would make a return and ascend to the throne. As for Qin Xiao, he would be restored to his position as one of the highest officials, and his status would be even more terrifying than it was in the past.

During this time, anyone who didn’t try to curry favor with these two would be fools.

Qin Xiao was surrounded by many officials that had come to the Marshal Quarters. They discussed plans to pave the way for a smoother future.

Even those who accompanied Qin Xiao received a high level of respect. Even nobles dared not to disrespect them. These nobles constantly referred to them as ‘little brother’ or ‘old master’ in case they be seen as not paying their due respects.

Especially those nobles that had defected to Yang Zhen’s side before. They were all in absolute fear, and they all wished that they could cut out their hearts and let Qin Xiao know the depths of their newfound loyalty.

It had to be known that in a struggle for authority, the winning side would often engage in a bloody purge. As for all those that had followed Yang Zhen, they might also be exterminated.

In this situation, how could they not be afraid? They all wished to take Qin Xiao as their own father and venerate him in the same way.

As Qin Xiao and the group of nobles that followed him entered past the gates of the Qin residence, they saw a massive Vermillion Bird fly down onto the courtyard. Its brilliant red feathers burned with radiant flames as it sent out a pulsing aura; all of the nobles’ throats twitched as they stared as this magnificent creature.

“Master! Master! Mister Lin has brought the Young Miss back, they are waiting for you in the rear courtyard.” A middle-aged steward said.

“Xingxuan…” Qin Xiao shook, and his heart filled with a surge of emotion. He thought that he would never have the chance to see his precious granddaughter ever again. But who knew that in just one night, the situation would change so much.

Qin Xiao followed the steward to the rear courtyard. The other nobles stayed back. They were aware of their own status. What kind of existence was Lin Ming? How could they possibly have the qualifications to see him? To someone like Lin Ming, nobles, royalty, or even the emperor himself were nothing but clouds of smoke, merely meaningless existences.

Therefore these people very casually greeted the housekeeper and sat down in the lobby, drinking tea and chatting with each other.

………………

“Grandfather!”

As soon as Qin Xiao entered the rear courtyard. Qin Xingxuan gave a loud cry and threw herself into Qin Xiao’s arms. She had anxiously worried over her grandfather’s condition for over a month. Now that she saw her grandfather safe and unharmed, Qin Xingxuan couldn’t suppress all the pain and worry she had been keeping down until now; tears flowed down her cheeks like strings of crystal beads.

“Grandfather is alright.” Qin Xiao patted Qin Xingxuan on the back. At this age, Qin Xiao had already lived through many great storms. In this world, there was very little that could cause Qin Xiao to feel great sorrow or great happiness. Now, what Qin Xiao worried about was only the legacy of his Qin Family, as well as his most precious children and grandchildren.

Qin Xiao looked at Qin Xingxuan, his eyes full of grandfatherly love. To have such an outstanding granddaughter was truly the blessing of the heavens.

Qin Xiao glanced at Lin Ming. Towards this amazing young man in front of him, Qin Xiao wasn’t sure what to feel. Gratitude, happiness, fear, awe… all sorts of emotions intertwined in the same place. Qin Xiao didn’t even know what he should call Lin Ming.

Before this, he had received the news that the current Seven Profound Martial House Master had already been slain by Lin Ming in a single instant.

The young and respectful youth in front of him was a man that even the Seven Profound Valleys’ Valley Master had to pay three points of respect to! This was a level that had already surpassed Qin Xiao’s understanding.

He hoped that he could urge Qin Xingxuan and Lin Ming to wed. But, this sort of matter wasn’t something he could ask. He no longer had the ability to arrange or manage his granddaughter’s life.

“Marshal Qin, please catch up with Xingxuan. I will leave first for a moment.” Lin Ming bowed as a respectful junior would, and then left the room…

………..

Outside of the room, the middle-aged steward was waiting for him.

“Mister Lin, there is someone waiting to see you.”

“See me? I thought I said I didn’t want to see anyone?” Lin Ming didn’t want to see the nobles of Sky Fortune City. All they wanted to do was to kiss up to him and shower him with gifts, he had no interest towards any of this.

“Well… she said she was an old acquaintance of yours.”

“Old acquaintance?” The first one Lin Ming thought of was Lan Yunyue. However, when he saw who it was he was a bit taken aback. The one waiting for him was a young, delicate looking girl who had an air of elegance.

This was… Bai Jingyun.

Bai Jingyun and Murong Zi were called the Seven Profound Proud Pair, and they were also top characters within the Seven Profound Martial House. Lin Ming and Bai Jingyun didn’t have much contact with each other, it was just that he had helped her make several inscription symbols for treasures before. Towards Bai Jingyun, Lin Ming didn’t have a deep impression, and had nearly forgotten who she was.

When Bai Jingyun saw Lin Ming, she faintly smiled and bowed, “Mister Lin.”

Lin Ming was a bit awkward at being called Mister Lin. He said, “Please refer to me as you used to. After all, we used to be fellow disciples.”

“Mm… then I’ll call you Brother Lin.” Bai Jingyun smiled. “To be honest, when I first saw Brother Lin enter the Seven Profound Martial House, I thought that Brother Lin had infinite potential to grow. But, I never thought that in just a few years, Brother Lin would have already reached this point…”

Bai Jingyun couldn’t help but see. The first time that Lin Ming had rushed into the Ten Thousand Killing Array, his rank had been lower than hers. But now, even the Seven Profound Martial House Master had been instantly killed by him.

This was simply like a dream.

“Mm, I’ve obtained some great opportunities. My luck has been too good.”

“Destiny is also a part of talent.” Bai Jingyun shook her head, and then looked unsure, as her eyes flashed with a strange light, “Brother Lin, may I ask you a question?”

“Please ask.”

Bai Jingyun hesitated, and then slowly asked, “A year and a half ago… were you the one… that killed Ouyang Dihua?”

There were only a few people within the entire Sky Fortune City that knew of the grudge between Lin Ming and Ouyang Dihua. Besides Yang Zhen, the cloaked man, and some others, no one else was aware.

People didn’t even know that Yang Zhen had drawn relations with the cloaked man. They only assumed that Yang Zhen had gained the backing of some great figure within the Seven Profound Valleys. As for who it was, no one knew.

Bai Jingyun naturally didn’t know. However, she was able to trace some clues and make a guess. For instance, in the past before Lin Ming had left the Sky Fortune Kingdom, he had his parents moved away. The new Martial House Master came from the Acacia Faction, Ouyang Boyan had once visited Sky Fortune Kingdom, and after news of Lin Ming’s death spread, Yang Zhen began to move against the Qin Family…

This series of events were all related. Bai Jingyun managed to connect them, and therefore she had come to ask Lin Ming to verify this.

At this moment, Lin Ming didn’t have any reason to hide it. He nodded and said, “I was the one who killed Ouyang Dihua.”

After Bai Jingyun heard Lin Ming’s words, she let out a long breath. Her eyes gently closed, and her eyelashes trembled.

The pressure that had been on her heart and mind for this past year and a half seemed to vanish. Although this matter was now complete, and she had obtained a truth that had no significance behind it, she still felt tired.

As her eyes opened, Bai Jingyun was calm once again, “Thank you, Brother Lin…”

Lin Ming shook his head, “There is no need to thank me. The reason that I killed him was because he had the intention of killing me first.”

Humans were all different. In truth, the Acacia Faction was not so terrible to female disciples. If they could lay down their modesty and pride, then they would be able to obtain many things that they desired from the Acacia Faction. There were even many girls that only had ordinary talent, but were still considered beautiful, that were desperately trying to join the Acacia Faction in order to obtain wealth and longer youth.

Lin Ming sighed, and then took out a pair of pill bottles from his spatial ring. He said, “Senior-apprentice Sister Bai, of these pill bottles, one is for you. As for the other, could you pass it to Lan Yunyue if you see her? These medicines have very mild properties, and if you eat them carefully, it will guarantee that you step into the Pulse Condensation period…”

Bai Jingyun’s talent was considered good within the Seven Profound Martial House. As a martial artist, she also hoped that one day she would be able to break through to the Pulse Condensation period. But now, as she looked at these pill bottles, Bai Jingyun didn’t feel any joy. After experiencing a number of things, it was as if she no longer wished to pursue these things.

Bai Jingyun hesitated and then silently received the pair of pill bottles. She said, “Miss Lan has been managing her fabric shop in the northern end of town for the last few years. About Brother Lin returning, she is probably already aware…”

Bai Jingyun was implying that Lan Yunyue didn’t want to see Lin Ming. Now that things had changed between them, there was no longer any meaning in them seeing each other. It would just make things embarrassing for the both of them.

Lin Ming was silent, and then sighed in his heart. Perhaps these calm and peaceful days were much more suitable for Lan Yunyue… this bottle of pills that he gave to her could be considered the last of their karma. From now on, all that was between them would completely vanish into nothing…

After Lin Ming bid Bai Jingyun farewell, he returned to his room alone. He had already told the steward that no one was to disturb him, not even to deliver meals.

Like this, Lin Ming entered the ethereal martial intent and sat in meditation for three or four hours.

When he opened his eyes, it was already evening.

Lin Ming stood up and then took out a small jar from his spatial ring. There was a thick red liquid within this small jar; this was the blood essence that he had taken from Ouyang Boyan as well as Ouyang Boxu!

From the last time that Lin Ming had touched the Magic Cube with the blood essence of a Houtian master and opened it to today, it had been nearly two years.

In two years, Lin Ming’s strength had reached the extreme Xiantian realm!

What he wanted to know was: could a Xiantian master’s blood essence open the Magic Cube once more?

Lin Ming impatiently wanted to verify this hypothesis.

Lin Ming ruefully smiled and then shook his head, mocking himself, “My mind is too messy. This mentality isn’t suitable for opening the Magic Cube…”

The more valuable something was, the more he needed his heart and mind to be at peace. Otherwise if his heart was spurred by greed, it might expose all sorts of flaws in his mind.

Currently, Lin Ming wasn’t too desperate or desiring of the legacies within the Magic Cube. What he wanted the most was to explore the secrets of the Magic Cube. Where did it come from? Who created it? How was it made? What was it guiding him to do?

Lin Ming always felt that the Magic Cube was sentient. It was only that this Magic Cube seemed to stand at the height of all existence, and looked down on everything with indifferent disdain, including even Lin Ming himself.

This so-called heartless to all of heaven and earth, taking all of existence as nothing but straw dogs; to the Magic Cube, it cared about nothing. It was indifferent to everything, and would stay this way despite any change to the world…

As Lin Ming’s mood calmed down again, he stripped off his clothes, exposing a strange symbol on his left chest. This pattern was the mysterious inscription of the Magic Cube…

Chapter 430 – Returning to Divine Phoenix Island

As Sky Fortune City entered fall, the days began to be filled with a faint chill.

In the ninth month, Crown Prince Yang Lin ascended to the throne. The grand ceremony continued for a total of nine days. Before this, all of the officials that had been purged and were still living were once again restored to their former glory. They entered the palace again and again, being promoted continuously.

As for officials that had followed Yang Zhen, some were demoted and some were exiled. Even though Yang Lin was a naturally kind-hearted man, after becoming emperor he would also begin to gradually show a ruthless side.

In the middle of the ninth month, Lin Ming brought Qin Xingxuan back to his hometown of Green Mulberry City.

Before this, Yang Lin had already sent summons to meet Lin Ming’s parents.

Yang Lin was clear that his life was protected and he would finally be able to ascend the throne all because of Lin Ming. Although this was a great graciousness of Lin Ming, there was no way that Yang Lin could return the favor. What he could offer Lin Ming were common things such as authority and money. However, these things no longer held any significance to Lin Ming.

However, Yang Lin was still a wise and smart character who knew the best way to do things in any situation. Since he couldn’t offer Lin Ming anything he wanted, he would then give a title to Lin Ming’s parents.

He titled Lin Ming’s father as the Duke of Lu County with a scope of land over 500 miles wide. This Lu County also included Green Mulberry City within its borders. Henceforth, Green Mulberry City was the home grounds of the Lin Family.

As for Lin Ming’s mother, she was titled as a first-class madame. Even Lin Xiaodong was given the title of a first-class viscount.

These titles were extraordinary. Whether it was a duke or a first-class madame, neither of them had official government power, but they were titles that were still only inferior to a prince or king, and were top characters among any noble circles.

These titles were also hereditary. Once titled, they would not be removed unless there was a major crime that was committed. Thus, the Royal Palace would not easily bestow these noble titles onto others. Besides times of great war or in the founding of the nation, they would almost never be given. If one thought that they could receive this title during times of peace, then that was simply nonsense.

It had to be known that the title of viscount within Green Mulberry City would include a 30 mile manor as well as 1000 servants.

As for the several great families of Green Mulberry City, besides the Zhu Family who had obtained some status because their daughter had become the empress concubine, the other family heads were not even second-rate barons. As for the commoners, the best among them could be considered the wealthy gentry of the countryside.

Between the common people and the nobility there was an insurmountable gap. The nobility represented the most honored positions. Although great merchant families were large and powerful, within the minds of the common people, their social status was inferior to nobles’.

Thus, to Lin Ming’s parents, being able to receive a title and become a duke or a madame was simply a dream come true. This was an event worthy of a grand celebration, and would also bring great honor to their ancestors.

As Lin Ming saw the happy look on his parents’ faces, he was deeply satisfied. He didn’t think that such a common title of the mortal world would let his parents become this pleased. The last time that Lin Ming had come back, even the pills that he had given them that would let them extend their lives by a hundred years hadn’t caused his parents to be so happy.

As Lin Ming’s mother affectionately felt the imperial decree, her smile went from ear to ear. She decided that she would have a beautiful sandalwood box made and then place the imperial decree within. Later, when she passed onto the next world she would be able to raise her head high when she saw her ancestors. Lin Ming wasn’t sure whether or not to laugh or cry when he heard these ideas.

As Lin Mu happily spoke, the cry of a little baby was suddenly emitted from the west wing of the residence.

This baby was Lin Ming’s little sister.

Lin Ming had been stranded within the Divine Phoenix Mystic for nearly a year. Under Qin Ziya’s protection, Lin Ming’s parents hadn’t even heard the news of Lin Ming’s death from the beginning to the end. They had lived an entire year happily in peace, and had even popped out a little sister for Lin Ming.

This could all be accredited to Lin Ming’s pills. This couple that had worked hard for half a lifetime suddenly felt much younger. The wrinkles on their skin vanished, and their bodies constantly improved. Now, the husband and wife were no different from anyone else in their early thirties.

Lin Ming’s little sister was only a few months old and was still nursing. Her name was Lin Xiaoge, and her nickname was Little Pigeon.

This little girl had surprisingly large eyes and wasn’t afraid of strangers. As she saw Lin Ming, she stared at him with her bright black eyes shining, intently watching him.

Lin Ming was very fond of this cute baby. He took out a soul jade pendant from his spatial ring and placed it around Lin Xiaoge’s neck.

This little baby had arrived right on time. Lin Ming was worried that his parents would be lonely after he left, but now that Little Pigeon was here, that wouldn’t be the case. Perhaps in the future there might also be another little brother or sister, and they would also be able to inherit the family title. As for Little Pigeon, she might marry into the Royal Palace and become an empress in the future. At that time, his parents should no longer have any regrets…

Lin Ming hadn’t been planning on telling his parents what had happened this year, but after the couple had been home for a while, they learned what happened. After Lin Mu heard this news, she was frightened out of her mind.

Especially after she had heard that Lin Ming was soon leaving Sky Fortune Kingdom again, and this time it would be a very long time before he returned. Lin Mu’s originally happy mood fell, and she didn’t speak for an entire day.

She didn’t know what Lin Ming’s experiences were when he went out, but what she knew was that it would undoubtedly be dangerous. Not just that, but she wouldn’t be able to see her son for several years. Lin Mu wasn’t happy at all.

The only one who could make Lin Mu smile was Qin Xingxuan. Although Lin Ming was only friends with Qin Xingxuan, in Lin Mu’s opinion, since Lin Ming had brought her back to his home, that was the same as bringing a woman back to meet the in-laws. No matter how Lin Mu looked at it, she was very satisfied with this future wife. Qin Xingxuan had a good background, she was intelligent, kind, well-mannered, and also very beautiful.

Lin Mu made several insinuations, asking many times when Lin Ming would marry and produce some grandchildren that she could hold. Lin Ming didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. She might as well wait for Little Pigeon to grow up and have some children herself.

A martial artist traveled throughout the world and had no fixed home. It was simply impossible for them to look after their own child. This was also the reason why most martial artists had children at a very late stage in their life. Normally only when they had reached the end of their potential and stabilized at whatever boundary they were at would they consider having children. Normally, a Revolving Core Supreme Elder wouldn’t have children until they were at least a hundred years old.

Lin Ming lived at home quietly for half a month. During this time, he didn’t cultivate much. Most of his time was spent accompanying his parents or teasing the Little Pigeon.

It was only late at night that Lin Ming would meditate over the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’ left from the Demon Emperor. The more he pondered it, the more incomparably profound he discovered this cultivation method was, and he also encountered many difficulties.

Finally, the day to depart arrived. Lin Ming had to return to Divine Phoenix Island, and Qin Xingxuan would follow him there. As for his bonds with the Seven Profound Valleys, they could already be considered finished.

Next day, early morning –

The fall wind blew, the leaves were withered and yellow, and flocks of birds flew through the bright blue sky to the south. Lin Ming stood under the massive wings of Fireshine, all of his clothes flapping in the breeze blown by the flames.

Behind Lin Ming, Lin Mu covered her mouth, unable to help the tears streaming down her cheeks.

Lin Fu also sighed. He was proud to have a son like this, but to have a son like this also meant that his son was destined to not stay by their side. Otherwise, he would never be able to fly high.

“Father, Mother, take care!” Lin Ming knelt down and bowed his head to the ground three times. Then he jumped onto Fireshine’s back. Fireshine opened its massive wings and shot up into the sky with Lin Ming and Qin Xingxuan onboard.

The Vermillion Bird soared into the heavens. The wind howled, and flames dyed the skies red…

Those that walked the road of martial arts were doomed to be alone. They lived long lives, and it was impossible for them to spend their years together with their family.

This was also the reason why many Supreme Elders – such as the Sorcerer of the Southern Wilderness – would return to their homeland after many years and finish the causal bonds that they held with the world they once knew.

“Lin Ming, are we going straight to Divine Phoenix Island?” Qin Xingxuan asked from atop the Vermillion Bird.

“Yes, we’re going straight to Divine Phoenix Island!”

Chapter 433 – Blood Red Jade Slip

After hearing that Lin Ming would compensate for the 10 drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence, not only did Great Elder Mu Chihuo laugh, but all the other Elders thought this was farcical. A red-robed old man coldly snorted and said, “The value of a single drop of Vermillion Bird blood essence is inestimable. This old woman wants to see whether or not you have anything worthy of compensating for it!

This red-robed old woman was the one that had just called Qin Xingxuan a piece of trash.

“The reason that Divine Phoenix Island gave you the Vermillion Bird blood essence was not for you to give it to others, and especially not to waste it to court some random hussy! Exactly what qualifications do you have to do this!?”

This red-robed old lady spoke aggressively and also recklessly sent out her aura, directly pressuring Lin Ming. If it wasn’t for her grandson lacking some Vermillion Bird blood essence, he would have absolutely been able to break through to the Revolving Core realm. This caused the red-robed old woman to feel a deep resentment. Now, with Lin Ming’s words, she used her aura to pressure Lin Ming!

For a middle Revolving Core Supreme Elder to send out an aura to oppress a Houtian master, it would be able to frighten him out of his wits!

But this red-obed old woman knew that Lin Ming wasn’t an ordinary Houtian master. She wouldn’t be able to kill him with her aura. The most she could do was embarrass him and make him wet his pants. Thus she did not lighten her hand at all, releasing her aura with full force.

As soon as Mu Yuhuang saw this her complexion changed. She immediately wanted to stop this, but as she raised her hand halfway, she noticed that Lin Ming had induced too much onto himself; she simply couldn’t resist the outrage that had been stirred up in order to protect Lin Ming. Not just that, but Mu Yuhuang was also very dissatisfied with what Lin Ming had done this time.

As for the Great Elder, he wasn’t bothering to hide his smile, he was waiting for Lin Ming to make a fool of himself.

However, Lin Ming sat still tightly in his seat. His face was not red, and his heart wasn’t palpitating – he didn’t even look troubled. It was as if the red-robed old woman’s aura was just like the air.

Mm?

The red-robed old woman was shocked. She had released her full aura in order to suppress a junior, but now she was being completely ignored? How was this possible!?

It had to be known that even within the boundaries of the Revolving Core Elders, if an early Revolving Core master was being suppressed by a middle Revolving Core master, they wouldn’t be able to be so relaxed!

She thought that Lin Ming would be overwhelmed, unable to withstand the pressure and begin to grit his teeth and sweat. But she didn’t expect that he would simply ignore her. What face did she have left?

Unable to stop from embarrassment, the red-robed old woman revolved all of her true essence and began to galvanize her aura to the extreme. Seven of the fire flowers near her had their petals blown away by her momentum. But Lin Ming only coldly looked at her, remaining completely unmoved.

All of the Elders present were awed. The red-robed old woman was a top ranked Elder among those present. Lin Ming was strong, but there was no way he was strong to this degree. How was this possible?

Lin Ming calmly stood up, his eyes coldly glaring at the old woman. He slowly said, “I, Lin Ming, have truly used the Vermillion Bird blood essence to save a girl. This girl was forced into a desperate situation because of me. She was alone and in despair. Not only that, but I also owe her graciousness for her kindness to me in the past. Even if it wasn’t so, I would still not sit idly by and do nothing at all. If it’s as Senior says, then in the relationships between people, is the only important factor how valuable they are? Is the only measure in which they can be evaluated how much they can be used?”

Lin Ming’s words were combative. As he spoke, the Ancient Phoenix bloodline from within his eyebrows naturally emitted, releasing a pulsing aura that caused everyone’s hearts to quicken. The woman in red bore the brunt of this momentum, and her heart suddenly stopped for a moment. She didn’t know why, but at the time, she felt the very depths of her being tremble. It was as if this was… bloodline suppression.

Hu-

An incredible scene took place. The red-robed old woman’s aura was like late winter snow. In just a few breaths, it completely melted away!

Mm?

All of the Elders present turned to Lin Ming, the look in their eyes changing.

Lin Ming calmly stood in front of the table as before. He indifferently said, “Divine Phoenix Island has been kind to Lin Ming. I was originally planning to freely offer something to Divine Phoenix Island, but since everyone intends to be so calculating about ‘worth’ and ‘value’, I shall offer this object to Divine Phoenix Island as per the rules. Great Elder, if Lin Ming is not wrong, then the rules of Divine Phoenix Island state that after entering the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, any treasures obtained belong to whoever obtained them, and they could also be exchanged with Divine Phoenix Island for resources of an equal value. Am I correct?”

“That’s right!” Mu Chihuo’s eyes jumped. He was still startled thinking about the scene where Lin Ming so easily broke apart an Elder’s aura.

“Since that’s the case, I shall hand out part of this object in exchange for 10 drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence. As for the rest, we shall negotiate further!”

“What!?”

With these words, everyone was shocked.

Hand out part of an object in exchange for 10 drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence and then negotiate for the rest!?

Listening to Lin Ming’s words, he seemed think that whatever he had to offer was actually equal to at least 10 drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence?

The Great Elder’s expression sank, “Lin Ming, this old man wants to see just what you can take out!”

“Then I shall have to ask Honorable Sect Master to take a look.”

As Lin Ming spoke, he took out a blood red jade slip from his spatial ring. This jade slip was twice as large a normal jade slip, and the face of the jade slip was crisscrossed with crimson lines. It looked extremely mysterious.

Mm? Jade slip?

Cultivation method?

All of the Elders present were startled. As for the Great Elder Mu Chihuo, his eyes were riveted to the jade slip. No matter how he looked, he didn’t know what to think.

This jade slip was obviously from the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm!

What could it be?

Cultivation method? Martial skill?

Mu Yuhuang deeply looked at Lin Ming before she took hold of the jade slip. As she held it, she felt as if she were holding onto an object from ancient times. Brilliant flames shined on the jade slip, and it emitted a very ancient and profound energy – this was certainly an extraordinary object!

Mu Qianyu was sitting beside Mu Yuhuang. As she looked at this jade slip, she turned to look at Lin Ming, her heart racing. She silently waited for Mu Yuhuang to reveal the results of her investigation.

As Mu Yuhuang slipped her sense into the jade slip, her heart suddenly shook; the beginning of the jade slip was the first layer of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’.

Could it be…

Mu Yuhuang suddenly realized a possibility, and that was that this jade slip Lin Ming had brought back was able to fill in the flaws of the current ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle!’

If this was so, the value of this jade slip was difficult to imagine.

As she silently looked down, Mu Yuhuang swept past the fifth layer of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. As she saw the sixth layer, she gasped, her eyes flickered and her breathing became rapid!

With Mu Yuhuang’s understanding of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, she was certainly able to determine whether this cultivation method was real or fake.

The founder of Divine Phoenix Island had obtained only the first five layers of the cultivation method. But even with so many flaws, the ‘Vermilion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ was not inferior to any cultivation method of a fifth-grade sect, or even a Holy Land! It was only that one needed the Vermillion Bird bloodline in order to practice this cultivation method. Thus, this cultivation method was not coveted by fifth-grade sects.

The higher this cultivation method went, the more terrifying its might was. With the first six layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, it would become a top cultivation method capable of creating an Emperor level powerhouse!

If this cultivation method was obtained by Divine Phoenix Island, then there was a possibility that they could become a Holy Land!

This was certainly not something that several drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence could compare with. Even if it were a few dozen drops, or even a hundreds drops, it simply could not compare!

However, at this moment, the unbelievable occurred. After the sixth layer of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, there was actually the seventh layer!

Heavens!

The seventh layer of the cultivation method!

Mu Yuhuang’s hands actually began to slightly tremble. As the Elders present saw this, their eyes began to change. They looked at the jade slip in Mu Yuhuang’s hands – just what did Lin Ming bring back that could cause her to have such a violent reaction?

Then, after she looked at the seventh layer of the cultivation method, Mu Yuhuang’s heart nearly stopped for a moment. After the seventh layer of the cultivation method was shockingly…

The eighth layer of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’!

Eighth layer…

Mu Yuhuang felt cataclysmic waves going off in her heart and mind, as if the world itself were overturning. How powerful the eighth layer of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ was, she simply could not imagine.

Mu Yuhuang’s fingers trembled and she had to use her hand to support herself on the table. She looked at Lin Ming with absolute amazement in her eyes.

“Sect Master, just what is in that jade slip?” The red-robed old woman who had been arguing with Lin Ming couldn’t help but ask as she saw Mu Yuhuang’s violent reaction.

Mu Yuhuang laid down the jade slip and closed her eyes in order to restore her tranquil mood. After a long time, she handed over the jade slip and said, “See for yourself.”

As the red-robed old woman received the jade slip, she was already able to faintly guess what it was. There was probably only a single situation in this world that could cause Mu Yuhuang to react like this.

Her sense swept down. Suddenly, the red-robed old woman’s heart shook – it was true!

However, as she continued, her expression became increasingly stunned, shocked, and awed. Finally, she felt completely slack-jawed.

Although she had prepared in advance, she had never imagined that this jade slip would contain the eighth layer of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle!’

“What is it?” The surrounding Elders asked together.

“The ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’…” The red robed old woman whispered. She turned to look at Lin Ming, and then after several breaths of time, she haltingly said, “The first eight layers of the cultivation method!”

“What?”

“First eight layers?”

All of the Elders were shocked beyond measure. When they had seen Mu Yuhuang react like that, they already had some faint guesses in their heart. But when the red-robed old woman spoke the truth, they finally realized that they had far underestimated just how terrifying this jade slip was.

Third Elder Mu Yanzhuo looked completely befuddled. He looked at Lin Ming and felt an increasing amount of awe in his heart. When the founder of Divine Phoenix Island had first entered the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, she had found a great lucky chance and obtained the first five layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ cultivation method. After that, she had founded Divine Phoenix Island. But now, Lin Ming had taken out the first eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ from the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm. How!? He simply couldn’t imagine the circumstances.

The Great Elder also looked gloomy. As he looked at the blood red jade slip in Mu Yuhuang’s hands, his fists clenched together; he didn’t know just what to think.

The other Elders had various looks. If it was just the complete first five layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ cultivation method, then they would already be delighted. It had to be known that they had all reached the fifth layer of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. However, many of them were still stranded at the early Revolving Core realm or middle Revolving Core realm. If they wished to break through to a higher step, they had to reconsolidate the fifth layer of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ in order to purify their understanding of this cultivation method and try to make a breakthrough.

This was all because they did not have the sixth layer of the cultivation method!

Chapter 434 – Sitting and Gathering Treasures

If they had the sixth layer of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, they would be able to directly cultivate to the sixth layer. Even if their foundation was bad, it was still far faster than repeatedly consolidating and building up the first five layers!

Anyway, these Elders no longer hoped or expected to become an Emperor level powerhouse, what did it matter to them if their foundation was bad?

To achieve the late Revolving Core realm or even the extreme Revolving Core realm was already their life’s greatest goal.

Thinking this, everyone’s eyes became eager and ardent. Some people were extremely regretful that they had tried to argue with Lin Ming a moment ago. In the end, the struggle for Vermillion Bird blood essence was a matter of juniors. If they could make a breakthrough, increase their strength and also extend their lives by a few hundred years, then whatever struggles the juniors went through were irrelevant!

Compared to the eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, 10 drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence were simply nothing to speak of!

Everyone’s eyes unanimously focused on Lin Ming, their vision earnest.

According to the rules of Divine Phoenix Island, everything that was obtained from the Divine Phoenix Island smelting trials fully belonged to the one who obtained it. Not only could they exchange it to the sect, but they could also exchange it to the Elders as long as both sides were satisfied with the term.

Of course, these Elders didn’t expect to solely own this blood red jade slip, it was already enough to be the first one to enjoy it. As for the jade slip, there was only one. Meanwhile, there were over a dozen Vermillion Bird Faction Elders. If an Elder meditated over a jade slip, it would at least take a month or two. For all of them to have a look, it would take one or two years.

All the Elders that had been glaring at Lin Ming seemed to have completely forgotten the embarrassing scene from a moment ago. A white-haired old woman asked, “Nephew Lin, what are you planning on exchanging that jade slip for with the sect?”

“This old man has a 900 year old Sunfire Flower. I wonder if Nephew Lin is interested?”

As another Elder butted in, everyone looked at him with contempt.

A mere 900 year old Sunfire Flower? Really? This old man actually had the gall to bring up something like that?

The atmosphere was becoming increasingly fiery, even Great Elder Mu Chihuo had an extremely ugly expression. Of course he greatly desired to study the eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ too, but how could Lin Ming possibly give it to him?

Mu Chihuo grit his teeth and said to Lin Ming, “Lin Ming! What do you want in exchange!?”

Lin Ming faintly smiled. “Before, I was planning on freely offering this as a gift to Divine Phoenix Island. But now, I have changed my mind! I will lend this jade slip to Divine Phoenix Island for 100 days, and that should be sufficient for the value of 10 drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence!”

“What!?”

Mu Chihuo’s complexion sank. Lin Ming was actually only lending the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ jade slip to Divine Phoenix Island for 100 days!

Pondering a jade slip through meditation was an extremely slow process. In order to understand it, meditating over it for one or two months was nothing strange. If Lin Ming lent this jade slip out for 100 days, at most that would only be enough time for three people to study it!

However, even having said that, before Lin Ming had obtained the this jade slip, if the Elders present knew that they could exchange three drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence in order to study the first eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ for a month, they would have been tripping over themselves to rush for this chance.

But now that Lin Ming had brought the jade slip back, the Elders had regarded this jade slip as property of Divine Phoenix Island. To trade 10 drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence for 100 days, how could they possibly agree to that?!

Lin Ming didn’t seem affected. He unhurriedly said, “I’m not done speaking. After this 100 days, for the rest of the time, if any Elders wish to study it, we can continue to discuss terms. If both sides are satisfied then the jade slip can be continued to be lent out.

And also discuss terms?

With these words, all of the Elders present wanted to cuss out Lin Ming. This move of his was just too black-hearted! He wasn’t exchanging the jade slip, he was lending it out! From now on, if an Elder wished to meditate over this cultivation method, they would have to pay a massive price.

The Great Elder coldly snorted and said, “You’ve really thought this out well! The Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm is part of my Divine Phoenix Island! For my Divine Phoenix Island to exchange for the jade slip that you took out of the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm is already showing great tolerance and doing everything possible to accommodate you, and yet you are insatiable. After being given an inch, you want to take a yard? You think you can just sit there and gather all the treasure?”

Lin Ming coldly smiled and said, “According to what I know, the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm was a smelting trial land laid down by the Ancient Phoenix Clan. But, the disciples of Divine Phoenix Island are not the subjects of the Ancient Phoenix Clan. In comparison, when I entered into the Ancient Phoenix Main Hall, I managed to obtain the approval of the Palace Spirit, thus I was granted this jade slip with the first eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. It’s difficult to say just who is the owner of the Divine Phoenix Mystic realm. To say the least, even if the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm belongs to Divine Phoenix Island, I still want to ask a question. When Great Elder was young, did Great Elder also enter the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, and just what did the Great Elder obtain?

As Lin Ming calmly spoke, it was like stabbing with needles until they were bloody. Especially that last sarcastic question, it caused the Great Elder’s face to turn liver red. When the Great Elder had entered the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, he also had a lucky chance. But when compared to the first eight layers of  ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, it wasn’t even worth a fart.

“The first eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ cultivation method have always been within the Ancient Phoenix Main Hall for the last 3000 years, and have been guarded by the Palace Spirit. Those who have the ability to do so many take it away. If anyone thinks they can just take this jade slip, then they are nothing but idiots spouting nonsense! Since the Great Elder said that the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm belongs to Divine Phoenix Island, I wonder if Great Elder has any personal disciples that can enter into the Ancient Phoenix Mystic Realm and obtain the first eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’?”

Lin Ming’s refutation caused Mu Chihuo to be bamboozled! All of the other Elders stayed silent. They were still watching Lin Ming, obviously refusing to give up.

Lin Ming sneered in his mind. In the presence of all these Elders, he pushed the blood red jade slip towards Mu Yuhuang. “Honorable Sect Master, this disciple is busy with practice, so this cultivation method will be temporarily placed with Honorable Master. Anytime anyone wishes to rent out this jade slip, Honorable Master may do so in place of disciple. Is this alright?”

Lin Ming was well aware that the significance of this jade slip for Divine Phoenix Island was too great. According to the rules of Divine Phoenix Island, the jade slip should be controlled by Lin Ming. However, when it came to objects that were important, following this rule wasn’t possible.

Thus, Lin Ming had already planned to hand this jade slip over to Mu Yuhuang to deal with, and she could also decide what the terms would be. It was already enough that he would receive a portion of the exchange.

Not just that, but this was equal to delivering a huge graciousness to Mu Yuhuang. If Mu Yuhuang controlled this jade slip, then she would have the authority over who could see it and also have the power that followed. This was equal to holding the weak point of all the Elders; who would dare to oppose Mu Yuhuang?

As for the Great Elder, if he wanted to stir up trouble, he would have to deal with someone much stronger than himself in order to do so. Now that Mu Yuhuang had the jade slip in her hands, it would be extremely difficult for him to form an alliance to deal with her. Nobody would try to offend Mu Yuhuang at this time.

Not just that, but if the Great Elder wanted to practice the first eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, he would also have to obtain permission from Mu Yuhuang and Lin Ming. Thinking of this, Mu Chihuo felt sick to his stomach like he had swallowed a fly.

Chapter 444 – Zombie Guard

As a black-armored man saw the slaves’ medicine baskets growing heavy, he smiled and said, “Big Brother, we’ve really hit it big this time. There are many more medicinal herbs than we expected. Once we return, we’ll receive a great number of military exploit points. Not just that, but us brothers will also be able to keep a bit! When that happens, Big Brother’s status will surely rise within the family clan!”

“Yah! We’ve already been in this bird shit land for half a year, finally we’ll be able to accomplish something!”

“When we head back, I can’t wait to see just what those old fool Elders’ expressions will be like!”

The several black-armored men enthusiastically spoke. They were from a third-grade martial family clan that was subordinate to the South Sea Demon Region. The South Sea Demon Region covered countless large and small islands, and there were even many strange and foreign races within them. There were dozens of third-grade sects and martial families, and some of those third-grade sects were formidable to the point that they surpassed even Peacock Mountain and came close to becoming fourth-grade sects.

In this great war between the South Sea Demon Region and Divine Phoenix Island, the larger the scale of the opponents, the greater the scope involved. All of these small sects under the South Sea Demon Region participated in order to grab a share of the spoils.

This also meant that more and more Xiantian martial artists came to the South Sea battlefield. A massive number of squads were formed for this war, and some of them weren’t even part of either side; they were fully private and voluntary squads that were created to seek fortune in the chaos of war. For these most basic martial artists, even picking up the junk left behind by powerhouses was enough for them to live for several years.

………………..

In the dense, dark jungle, when the Demon Region martial artists’ squad was about seven or eight miles away, Cool Foam suddenly stopped. “I’ve found them. There are around seven to 10 powerhouses, and also some weak life fluctuations – those should be the herb gatherers.”

Normally, the person in the squad with the best perception was also the strongest. However, the Fire Ax Squad was an exception. Cool Foam was very talented in this aspect, and as for Fire Ax, although he was strong, his perception was his greatest weakness.

“Mm, good job. Let’s get ready to ambush them. Violet Rain, you and me will hold back the Xiantian masters. As for everyone else, concentrate your efforts on finishing off the peak Houtian martial artists. We’ll follow the same plan as we’ve done before. Wild Halberd, this is your first time coming to the battlefield with us, so you don’t need to be in front. Just wait for a good opportunity to attack!” Fire Ax glanced at Lin Ming as he spoke. Normally, the new recruit would inevitably be nervous during his first foray on the battlefield, and it would lead to abnormal reactions. Even if they were a veteran of war, they would still be a burden due to this. This time he would allow Lin Ming to adapt to the situation, no one expected that he would be able to accomplish much.

“Haha, no need to be nervous. It’s alright, since it’s your first time on the battlefield, let’s compare our strength!” The bearded big fellow laughed as he patted Lin Ming’s shoulder.

Lin Ming smiled. “Okay.”

“Everyone prepare for battle!” As Fire Ax issued his order, everyone else extracted their weapons. “Go!”

Woosh!

Nine people ran out. Under the full speed impact of a master’s speed, this wasn’t a long distance at all!

“Mm? The enemy is here!”

The leader among the eight black-armored soldiers turned around, his complexion changing, “Prepare to meet them!”

Cha cha cha!

Eight spears pointed towards the Fire Ax Squad together. But at this point, Captain Fire Ax had already reached the front, “Mountain Splitting Ax!”

Bang –

A red inferno burst forth like a volcanic eruption. Fire Ax’s ax chopped down, his strength exploding to the limit. This was Fire Ax’s way of fighting: lacking finesse, but sweeping away all opposition with absolute strength.

Clang!

The captain of the black-armored soldiers crossed his spear to block Fire Ax’s strike. However, Fire Ax’s attack was too strong, the powerful impact forced the black-armored soldier to take a step back, directly miring his feet in the ground.

“Die!”

Fire Ax chopped down with his ax again!

The black-armored martial artist waved his lance to fight again, but he was sent flying backwards dozens of feet.

At this time, Dark Sword, Violet Rain, and the rest of them were all locked in battle. Dark Sword was the third Xiantian realm martial artist of the Fire Ax Squad. His cultivation was at the most early Xiantian realm and the weapon he wielded was a darksteel heavy sword.

As for Violet Rain, she didn’t use any weapon, but her hands flashed with purple thunder. Her entire body was wrapped in glittering electric lights. With just a touch, a black-armored soldier was paralyzed. The power of thunder entered into his meridians, wreaking absolute havoc!

Violet Rain’s palm thrust towards the spot between the enemy’s eyebrows!

“Woman, I am your opponent!”

With a thick murderous intent flowing out from him, a black-armored martial artist thrust his spear towards Violet Rain’s chest, forcing her to take several steps back. The one who attacked her was another Xiantian master of this Demon Region squad.

The black-armored squad had two Xiantian martial artists, one less than the Fire Ax squad.

Because of this, no one was able to stop Dark Sword.

“Ah!”

With a miserable scream, the weakest black-armored soldier’s stomach was pierced by a jet black sword. The sword twisted, shattering his dantian; he died right on the spot.

Of the eight black-armored soldiers, one of them had died to a sneak attack and now there were only seven left. But the Fire Ax Squad had nine people, and they also had an extra Xiantian master; the disparity in their combat strength was already obvious.

The Fire Ax Squad’s bearded big fellow and the rest had already anticipated this and stepped in front of black-armored soldiers, blocking their escape. Even if they couldn’t kill all of them, they would at least kill half!

“You really think that we are fish on the chopping block, hm!?” The captain of the black-armored soldiers wiped the blood from his lips and savagely smiled. He didn’t seem to care that they was ambushed by others. Since he was carrying out missions on South Aurora Island, he knew that every moment there was one more moment on the precipice of life and death. At any moment it was possible that they would be surrounded and ambushed. Every soldier had to be ready to fight at all times, and also know that death could come for them at any time.

“Mice of the Wartime Alliance, since you’ve come today, you won’t be leaving!”

The black-armored captain swiped his spatial ring and two large wooden boxes appeared. These were actually two coffins.

As the coffins hit the ground, they began to violently tremble. There was grating sounds coming from within, as if zombie corpses were scratching at the coffin lids with their nails.

“Zombie guards?”

Fire Ax’s complexion changed. Within the cultivation methods of the demonic path, refining the corpses of the dead into a zombie guard was an extremely notorious one.

“You will all die here today!” The black-armored soldier’s face flashed with a mad grin.

The coffin lid began to shake more and more. Two groups of black fog rose from the coffins, forming into two thin ghost claws. These claws were completely black and were sharp like sabers. The hands were full of bone spurs, and between the spurs were boiling pustules.

After the ghost claws extended, they suddenly turned and ripped opened the lid of the coffins. Two zombie guards stiffly stood up from the coffins, their bodies covered in bubbling pustules and bone spurs.

As their withered eyes opened, they revealed two scarlet eyes. In the middle of the night they were especially vivid.

Lin Ming’s heart stirred as he saw these two zombie guards, ‘So that’s how it is. The Seven Profound Valleys’ Puppet Faction’s corpse puppets are in reality a demonic path cultivation method used to make zombie guards.’

Refining a corpse into a puppet was in truth creating a zombie guard. Mugu Buyu had even transformed a part of his body into that of a zombie guard; no wonder Mugu Buyu had grown up into such a creepy mummy-like appearance.

“Peak of early Xiantian zombie guards!”

Fire Ax’s complexion sank. At this moment, the number of enemy Xiantian masters now outnumbered them by one!

“Violet Rain, you handle the zombie guards. Your power of thunder is best at suppressing the dead!” Although the current battle had flipped around, Fire Ax was still calm. “Wild Halberd, you’re also a thunder-attribute martial artist. Support her from a distance, and do not approach!”

Fire Ax darkly sighed in his heart. ‘To think that his first battle would be so fierce, this is truly a brutal test for Wild Halberd. Whether or not he can persist is difficult to say.’

“Let’s go!”

Fire Ax loudly shouted, and grasped his ax as he rushed over to the black-armored captain. His entire body’s true essence was revolving to the limit. If he could kill this enemy captain, the battle was as good as won!

Hong hong hong!

Fire Ax and the black-armored martial artist fiercely battled. Fire Ax was a bit stronger, but to defeat his opponent in a short period of time was impossible.

Violet Rain’s exquisite eyebrows pressed together. She said to Lin Ming in a low voice, “Follow close to me. Do not leave my electrical net of protection. Otherwise I won’t be able to distract myself and save you!”

As Violet Rain spoke, she shot towards the two zombie guards. The purple electrical network around her expanded, becoming wider and allowing Lin Ming to move around.

Lin Ming steadily followed. Although he had only known these people for a few short days, these fellow squad members had been very good to him.

As for the other Fire Ax Squad members, they were all engaged in fierce combat with the other black-armored soldiers.

Dark Sword was facing the other black-armored Xiantian martial artist. Although he was a bit weaker, he wouldn’t be defeated so easily.

As for the others, they were almost equally matched. But, the greatest pressure was on Violet Rain. Because the black-armored squad now had one more Xiantian realm master, she had to face two enemies in order to protect the squad behind her.

Even though the power of thunder had a great effect on restraining the corpse energy, going one against two was still going to be extremely tricky.

In front of Lin Ming, Violet Rain took out a blue soft sword. As purple arcs of electricity sparkled on the blue sword, it was like bright flowers blooming at night!

Chi!

Violet Rain’s sword cut down on a zombie guard’s claw. The power of thunder ignited the corpse, causing faint traces of black smoke to appear.

Violet Rain frowned – she couldn’t cut through!

The early Xiantian realm zombie guard had been fused with tough metals from top to bottom; its body was comparable to a treasure. Although Violet Rain’s power of thunder was able to burn away the corpse energy around the zombie guard, destroying it was another matter altogether!

“Rahh!”

The zombie guard issued a hoarse growl and was forced back by Violet Rain. Another zombie guard rushed forward at Violet Rain, its chilling claws grasping towards her chest.

Violet Rain gave a loud shout and purple lightning erupted around her body. It concentrated on the top of her longsword, manifesting into a large blue bird!

“Thunder Shock Sword!”

The three foot long soft sword carried the blue bird as it chopped down on the zombie guard. The zombie guard was enveloped by the blue bird, causing blue flames to erupt all over its body. It fiercely trembled, and then was sent flying back by the shaking!

But at this moment, the other zombie guard had already rushed in front of Violet Rain. The nails of its black claw were over a foot long and emitted a sickening black light. Once she was grabbed, it would create five bloody holes.

Violet Rain’s complexion changed. She didn’t have time to draw back her sword and defend against this attack. She could only use her foot to kick away the zombie guard!

Flesh and blood against a zombie guard’s claw! Once they collided, Violet Rain would inevitably be injured!

Lin Ming’s eyebrows jumped. He flicked his finger, and two small arcs of purple electricity instantly shot into the zombie guard’s eyes. Lin Ming was deliberately restraining his power. But even so, the power of thunder that contained the will of the Divine Demon Thunder Soul was not something that the frail zombie guard’s eyes could resist.

The zombie guard shook, and it suddenly slowed down. But at this moment, Violet Rain had enough time to heavily smash her foot into the zombie guard’s face, directly kicking it away!

Chapter 445 – Behead

Bang!

Violet Rain’s kick sent the zombie guard flying away. With some disbelief, she turned around to look at Lin Ming in surprise.

Violet Rain was extremely sensitive to thunder energy changes. A moment ago, it was clearly this youth’s lightning strike that had delayed the zombie guard’s attack! This thunder attack wasn’t strong – it had only been one tenth of the power of thunder that she had released. But even though the power of thunder was weak, it was unusually concentrated and sharp. Once it was shot into the zombie guard’s eyes, it was able to completely disrupt its attack!

To have such precise control and accurate judgement on the battlefield… Violet Rain couldn’t believe it. Was this really a new recruit?

“Wild Halberd, you…” Violet Rain didn’t know what to say at this time.

“Senior-apprentice Sister Violet rain, they come.” Lin Ming coolly said. The power he had displayed just a moment ago wasn’t strong, it was just that the utilization was clever; it wasn’t enough to arouse any suspicious.

Violet Rain clenched her teeth and suppressed any questions she had. She turned round to meet the two zombie guards. Of the two zombie guards, one had been struck hard by Violet Rain and the other one’s eyes had been injured by Lin Ming. However, neither of them had suffered any great losses.

As Lin Ming saw Violet Rain courageously rush up to meet the two zombie guards, he sighed. In the end, Violet Rain was only from a small sect; the grade of the Thunder Soul she had absorbed was low. Because of this, her attack power was also low. Even if Lin Ming created a good opportunity for her to attack, Violet Rain wouldn’t be able to cause heavy damage to the two zombie guards.

This fight couldn’t drag on for too long, Lin Ming had to find an opening. Otherwise, the Fire Ax Squad members might have casualties. These past few days, the Fire Ax Squad had been very kind to Lin Ming. Lin Ming didn’t want any of them to fall here.

Xiu! Xiu!

Violet Rain slashed out twice in a row. Because she was inspired by Lin Ming, this time she chose to target the zombie guard’s eyes.

However, this wasn’t as simple as Violet Rain thought it would be. The electricity that shot into the zombie guard’s eyes injured it, but it still mercilessly attacked Violet Rain as before.

In fact, zombie guards didn’t rely on their eyes to sense the enemy. They used their perception to feel the enemy’s ‘life force’. Even if they didn’t have eyes, they would still be able to determine the exact location of their enemies.

Violet Rain and the zombie guard attacked each other twice, and she was forced back several times. She began to feel some panic in her heart. What Lin Ming had done a moment ago seemed simple, but now that she tried it herself, how was the result like this?

Lin Ming said, “Senior-apprentice Sister Violet Rain, I will infuse the power of thunder into your body and coordinate with you, it may have a good effect.”

There was no other way. Violet Rain’s attack power was simply too low. If the battle dragged on, she would be killed by the zombie guards after a war of attrition. Lin Ming could use this method in order to increase Violet Rain’s attack power.

“Alright, assist me.” Violet Rain deeply looked at Lin Ming. She had already recognized that this little junior-apprentice brother of hers was not simple at all.

As Violet Rain flicked the sword in her hands, the electric net around her suddenly contracted, now only protecting her own body instead of also covering Lin Ming. Violet Rain understood now that Lin Ming probably didn’t need the electrical net to protect himself, what she had done was purely superfluous. If she gathered the power of thunder closer to her, she would be able to increase her attack power by a bit.

“Roar!”

The two zombie guards rushed towards Violet Rain at the same time. After several exchanges of blows, their bodies were already burnt black. Even though nearly all their corpse energy was burnt away, their bodies were still as hard as a treasure, and they were fundamentally undamaged.

“Thunder Shock Sword!”

A dazzling blue bird manifested atop Violet Rain’s longsword again. At the same time, Lin Ming pressed his hand against Violet Rain’s back. Power of thunder that contained the will of the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder began to continuously flow into Violet Rain’s body.

Although Lin Ming was suppressing his strength and he only poured a very small amount of power of thunder into Violet Rain’s body, in terms of purity, it was far above what Violet Rain’s low grade Thunder Soul could compare with.

If Violet Rain’s power of thunder was a sword, then the bit of power of thunder that Lin Ming had poured into her was like covering her dull blade with the sharpest steel.

In that instant, as Violet Rain released the blue bird, it seemed to have a soul of its own as it let out a shrill cry. The first zombie guard was struck by the blue bird, and the blue bird directly tore through its body!

Zi zi zi!

Arcs of lightning danced. The zombie guard began to violently twitch. The area of its stomach which the blue bird had passed through began to wither away at a speed visible to the naked eye.

Ca!

Violet Rain slashed backwards with her sword, her slash sending the zombie guard flying backwards! Blue smoke began to issue from the zombie guard’s body.

She won?

Violet Rain was shocked. In that instant, she had been able to feel the purity of Lin Ming’s power of thunder. That was absolutely not something that someone from a small sect could have. Was Lin Ming a martial artist from a large sect coming out for adventure?

Violet Rain wasn’t able to indulge herself in daydreams in the chaos of battle. Although the first zombie guard had been severely damaged and could no longer fight, the second zombie guard had already rushed over to Violet Rain.

Violet Rain had just used the Thunder Shock Sword a moment ago. She wouldn’t be able to use it again so quickly. She released purple arcs of lightning from her body, trapping the zombie guard in an electric cage.

During this open time, Lin Ming glanced over the situation of everyone else fighting. There were seven black-armored soldiers against nine members of the Fire Ax Squad. Besides Lin Ming and Violet Rain fighting against the two zombie guards, there was enough for a one on one for everyone.

Fire Ax was suppressing the enemy leader. And although Dark Sword was a bit weaker, he wasn’t in any danger.

However, as Lin Ming saw Green Tree, Green Forest, and Cool Foam, his eyebrows furrowed together. These three were specialized martial artists – their true combat strength was relatively weak. In just a few moves, they were already in danger.

“Damn! These fellows are really tough!”

A saber forced a black-armored martial artist back. The bearded big fellow was running out of breath. The armor of these Demon Region fellows was made out of some unknown material. They had high defensive capabilities and were able to resist his saber energy.

“Big Beard, hurry and finish your opponent so you can help Cool Foam – that boy won’t be able to last much longer!” Enchanting Shadow’s true essence sound transmission sounded out near the bearded big fellow’s ears.

The bearded big fellow looked over at Cool Foam. After exchanging several moves with his opponent, his face was already pale. He was apparently being shaken by his opponent’s true essence.

If this continued, Cool Foam wouldn’t be able to last much longer!

The bearded big fellow clenched his teeth and gave a loud shout. The muscles all over his body bulged out, and the thick saber in his hands seemed especially epic at this moment. Obviously, he had used some sort of secret skill at this time.

“Die!” The bearded big fellow forced back his black-armored opponent and shot towards where Green Tree, Green Forest, and Cool Foam were.

“Green Tree! Green Forest! Cool Foam! Run to me!”

Ping ping ping!

His great saber struck against the enemy spears and sparks scattered everywhere. The bearded big fellow was releasing an unusually overwhelming amount of power. With just his strength, he was able to share the burden of Green Tree, Green Forest, and Cool Foam.

The three black-armored martial artists simultaneously retreated.

“Humph! He’s looking for death! Does he think he’s invincible just because he’s turned crazy!?”

“Since this fellow wants to die so badly, let’s concentrate our attacks and kill him first!”

“Kill!”

Three spears thrust towards the bearded big fellow at the same time!

These three black-armored martial artists were battle-hardened masters that were experienced on the field. Their spears were like cunning snakes. As the bearded big fellow chopped down, two spears were aimed towards his heart and another towards his dantian.

“Be careful!”

Green Tree shouted out. At this time, he didn’t have much combat strength left.

“F*ck off to your grandma!”

The bearded big fellow crossed his saber horizontally, took a step forwards, and slashed out at two black-armored martial artists.

“Big Beard!”

Cool Foam’s complexion changed. His perception was the most sensitive here. In that split second he was able to instantly judge that Big Beard’s saber strike absolutely wouldn’t be able to block the simultaneous attacks of both black-armored martial artists!

This situation naturally fell into Lin Ming’s eyes. At this critical moment, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed, and two black swirling vortexes appeared in the depths of his pupils.

Samsara martial intent!

Bang!

A chaotic tsunami of thoughts and scenes appeared within the spiritual seas of the two black-armored martial artists. Their minds shook, and their eyes glazed over, losing all focus.

“Die!”

The bearded big fellow slashed out with his saber; his saber slid past the spears and directly beheaded both black-armored martial artists!

Pu! Pu!

Two heads soared through the air, and columns of blood erupted like fountains. Two of the black-armored martial artists actually had their heads severed by the bearded big fellow in a single strike!

Green Tree and Green Forest were shocked. Even the bearded big fellow appeared in complete disbelief as he blankly stood there and stared at the saber in his hands.

Although he was a bit sloppy and rough, that didn’t mean that he couldn’t tell the difference between his attacks and his enemies’. In that moment, the saber attack had exhausted most of his strength, and he realized he should have been in a dangerous situation clashing against two spears like that. How could this have happened?

“This is… what happened?”

The bearded big fellow mumbled. It seemed as if the two opponents had deliberately let him attack.

As for Cool Foam, he was looking a bit thoughtful after seeing the expressions of the two black-armored martial artists before they had died.

If a person’s neck was quickly cut off by a saber, their expression should retain a fright and unwillingness. However, those two had dulled, glazed eyes, and their expressions were slackened. It didn’t seem as if they were terrified of the bearded big fellow’s saber slicing off their heads at all. What happened here? Could it be that the devil arts they cultivated backfired at this critical moment? That was just too much of a coincidence.

“Holy shi*t, did this father’s crazy attack level up?” The bearded fellow couldn’t figure out a reason, so he attributed it to this. “Whatever, I’ll kill off the rest of these damn turtles first before I figure it out.”

The bearded big fellow flourished his large saber and entered the fray again.

………

“Mm!?” In this fierce battle, the black-armored captain occasionally released his sense to determine the general situation. At this moment, he was completely shocked. Two of his squad had died, and even a zombie guard had been ruined!

How was this possible!?

His squad’s combat strength was absolutely higher than the opponents’, and they even had an extra Xiantian master. How did they lose?

How could they possibly lose!?

Should he give up everything and escape?

With his strength, he had absolute confidence that he would be able to escape. But, his men would not be able to do so. Another Xiantian master might be able to escape with him, but the rest would most assuredly die here!

These people were all his direct subordinates. In the future, they would return to his family clan and help him contribute. Most of those here were future Xiantian masters.

There was no need to mention the loss of his subordinates, but even the medicinal plants would all vanish!

Even his military exploit points would be reduced.

He was not willing!

He had gone through countless life or death situations and suffered for half a year in the flames of war on South Aurora Island. How many times had he fought? He had done it all in order to exchange it for a chance to soar into the skies. How could things have come to this?

Chapter 446 – Demon Emperor’s Letter

Bang!

A blazing electric light illuminated the night sky, the second zombie guard was also slain under Violet Rain’s sword!

Seeing this, the black-armored captain felt his heart go completely cold.

He had to run, otherwise even he would die here!

“Split up and escape!”

As the black-armored captain shouted out this order with difficulty, his swept out his lance, knocking back an incoming ax and then turned around and ran.

The other martial artists also turned tail and fled.

How could the Fire Ax Squad let them escape so easily? Enchanting Shadow, Big Beard, Dark Sword, and all the others immediately went all out in their attacks. Several black-armored martial artists were pressed down, unable to run.

Chi-la!

Violet Rain slashed out with her sword and purple thunder flashed in the dark, severely injuring a black-armored warrior. To take such heavy damage at this time meant that they could only wait there to die.

Lin Ming also flung out a few arcs of electricity. Two black-armored martial artist were struck by them, and their bodies went completely numb for a moment. The bearded big fellow laughed and said, “Wild Halberd, well done!”

The heavy saber cut down and a head flew high!

“Damn!”

The black-armored captain’s heart bled as he heard the miserable screams from behind. But there was nothing he could do. If he slowed his pace by even a bit, Fire Ax would catch up to him!

“Haha, how fun!” The last peak Houtian black-armored martial artist was killed by the joint effort of Enchanting Shadow and the bearded big fellow. The black-armored squad’s last Xiantian martial artist was also exterminated by Dark Sword and Violet Rain’s combined attack.

Besides the captain, the entire black-armored squad had been completely wiped out!

Fire Ax hadn’t been able to block the black-armored captain from escaping. If he pursued too deep into this spiritual forest, he was bound to encounter some lurking danger.

“Record the military exploits and then we’ll go!”

As Fire Ax issued his order, the bearded big fellow and the rest took out their military medals and began to record the military exploit points they would receive.

“What about these people?” Enchanting Shadow pointed to the edge of the battlefield where a group of frightened slaves were trembling in fear. These slaves looked to be around 20 years old, and some even looked 14 or 15 years old. Whether it was the men or the women, they all had slender bodies and delicate features.

“Bring them with along. They are part of the Forest Fairy race; they’ve been slaves since birth.” As Fire Ax said this he sighed. A race that was born to be slaves was truly a sorrowful tale.

“Forest Fairy?” Lin Ming was a bit taken aback. After he left the Divine Phoenix Province, Lin Ming became increasingly aware of just how vast and complex the Sky Spill Continent was.

“They have some bloodline relationship to the Fey race. The Fey, whether it is men or women, are born extremely beautiful. After they were plundered by the South Sea Demon Region and brought up in captivity, and their mindset is no different from slaves’. Those with high talent are even used by others to practice their devil arts.”

Lin Ming felt his heart quiver in sympathy. To be reared like an animal in captivity… this fate was truly pitiful.

“Let’s collect the medicinal herbs and board the spirit boat, it’s best not to stay here too long.”

These medicinal herbs from the spiritual forest were naturally good materials; of coruse they wouldn’t leave it out here to rot.

As they boarded the spirit boat, the bearded big fellow glanced at the seven military medals as well as the piles of herbs. He heartily laughed and said, “Big Brother, we’ve hit the jackpot this time!”

“Mm, we’ve gotten a great harvest this time?” Fire Ax also couldn’t conceal a happy smile, “Oh, I forgot to ask since we we’re in a hurt, but our strength should have been inferior to them; just how did you win?”

Fire Ax had been completely concentrated on his fight with the enemy captain. In a battle between masters, diverting his attention even a bit meant a possible catastrophe; he simply wasn’t able to notice anything else on the battlefield.

“Big Beard killed the most, ask him.” Enchanting Shadow threw her hands up. From start to finish, she  had only killed a single black-armored martial artist.

Big Beard scratched his head in embarrassment, “Oh I don’t know. I chopped at them with my saber and they all died!”

“Mm?” Fire Ax frowned. How could this be possible? All of those black-armored martial artists had a very high combat strength.

“Violet Rain, how did you win?”

Fire Ax remembered that Violet Rain had killed two peak early Xiantian realm zombie guards by herself. Although it was well established that the power of thunder restrained corpses and ghosts, the suppressive effects shouldn’t have been so great. Originally, Fire Ax would have been happy if Violet Rain was able to stall the two zombie guards for a moment.

“Well…this is all thanks to Wild Halberd.” Violet Rain turned to smiled at Lin Ming, “Wild Halberd first attacked the zombie guard’s eyes to save me. Then, he fused his power of thunder into my body to strengthen the power of my martial skill. Wild Halberd is definitely a genius from some large sect; his Thunder Soul is even better than mine.”

As Violet Rain spoke, everyone was startled. Wild Halberd’s Thunder Soul was even stronger than Violet Rain’s? Violet Rain’s Thunder Soul was a high-grade human-step Thunder Soul. If Lin Ming’s was better, that meant that his Thunder Soul was at the peak of the high-grade human-step level. Or, perhaps it even approached the earth-step.

A Thunder Soul was far more precious and valuable than a Flame Essence. If a martial artist didn’t have a deep background it was basically impossible for them to obtain this level of Thunder Soul.

And even in a large sect or family clan, if one didn’t have enough talent, then no one would waste such precious resources on them.

So, there was only one possibility, and that was that Lin Ming was a top talent from a large sect or family clan. This sort of talent would absolutely have the combat strength of a half-step Xiantian martial artist at just the late Houtian realm; he could even protect himself in front of a Xiantian master.

Thinking of this, everyone began looked towards Lin Ming with eagerness in their eyes. In this brutal and violent war, if a strong new companion was added to their squad, that meant that their chances of surviving would be that much higher. And from the looks of it, Lin Ming had great potential to grow.

“Wild Halberd, you must have participated in life or death battles before. Otherwise, there’s no way you could be so calm; your aim is even better than mine!” Violet Rain was naturally referring to the two small bolts of lightning that Lin Ming had shot out to injure the zombie guard’s eyes. This move appeared simple, but Violet Rain knew that it wasn’t something she could accomplish in a similar situation.

“Mm, I’ve been in a few tight situations before.”

“Haha, you should have said so earlier! You made me worry over you in vain. I thought that you were some new rookie that hadn’t seen true battle yet.” The bearded big fellow gently patted Lin Ming’s shoulder. Normally, a martial artist trained in a sect would have a great deal of experience fighting. However, they would rarely have experienced true life or death struggles. In times of peace, there wouldn’t be others at the same level that tried to kill them.

Everyone returned to base in a jubilant and ecstatic mood. During this battle, they had obtained complete victory without losing anyone on their side. They had also obtained a massive amount of military exploit points and precious herbs.

However, what they didn’t know was that the seven black-armored martial artists that were killed by them were all arranged onto a list of names. This list of names passed through several hands and was finally delivered to an isolated island deep within the South Sea Demon Region.

Of course, this list was just a trivial one in a thick stack that just wasn’t worth mentioning.

Pa!

A pair of long black fingernails came down with a heavy slap atop the stack of papers.

“In these past 10 days, within the South Horizon Region, Five Element Region, and us, there have been a total of 80 Xiantian martial artists and over 400 Houtian martial artists that have died!”

The owner of this hand was a handsome and middle-aged man. He had a feminine air whenever he spoke. If one just listened to this voice, it would be hard to tell whether this person was a man or a woman.

“What’s the matter; you aren’t satisfied with these figures?” A lazy voice sounded out from in front of the feminine man; the one who spoke was an enchanting beauty that was reclining back in a relaxed posture. It wasn’t known what material her clothes were made of, but she was tightly wrapped in shining, black leather. Her collar was exaggerated to outrageous proportions, and stood up very high. The collar extended deeply, all the way to the bottom of her stomach, revealing a good portion of her round and plump snow-white breasts, causing the imaginations of anyone who looked to run wild. At her throat hung a small red snake. If it weren’t for the fact that it flicked out its tongue every now and then, it would really seem as if this small red snake was a necklace.

This woman was the Sovereign of the South Sea Demon Region’s Western Faction. Although she had a sexy and enchanting appeal, the truth was that she was immeasurably cruel and merciless; she could kill without batting an eye.

“This figure is indeed lacking, but….we can also improvise still. After all, we aren’t ready yet. Take your time, we aren’t in a hurry.

The enchanting woman laughed, her laughter were as clear as silver bells ringing, “You should hurry up the preparations. If things drag on, then that old bag Mu Fengxian might come here to see what the problem is!”

“Humph, that Mu Fengxian is a mere first order Life Destruction. Even if she knew what happened, there is nothing she can do! This past year she’s paid every price to create alliances and make war preparations within the South Sea. She even organized the Wartime Alliance. It’s as if she thinks my South Sea Demon Region really cares about her little island’s resources and women!”

“Hohohaha!” The enchanting woman laughed in a salacious manner. “Would you say that you aren’t tempted by that proud pair within Divine Phoenix Island – Mu Qianyu and Mu Bingyun?”

“Those two women…hehe……” The feminine man licked his lips, “I really do want them, but it’s not worth the price! Not just that….but their cultivation is too low. Once they break through to the Revolving Core realm, plundering them and ravaging them will be much more interesting!”

“But having said that, that old fool Mu Fengxian has been diligent in helping me prepare. All those martial artists who have joined the Wartime Alliance make the best fertilizer.”

“Mu Fengxian isn’t an idiot! Don’t look down on her, otherwise we will suffer a loss. If it weren’t for the fact that the last time we entered the South Sea Ancient Mystic Realm and obtained the ancient Devil Tome and the jade slip with the Demon Emperor’s letter, then we would never have know so many secrets.”

As the enchanting woman spoke to here, the feminine man’s expression sank. As she mentioned the ancient Devil Tome, the feminine man could not help but remember his disciple Xuan Ji.

Xuan Ji was his personal disciple and also his great grandson. After they had entered the Ancient Mystic realm and obtained the ancient Devil Tome and Demon Emperor’s letter, the feminine man had immediately cultivated the ancient Devil Tome to the third layer. After he had cultivated enough, he was just barely able to reproduce the first layer of the ancient Devil Tome so that Xuan Ji could practice it.

The feminine man had a harem with over 3000 beauties and he was also over a thousand years old. He had countless sons, grandsons, and an even greater amount of great grandsons. However, Xuan Ji had been different from all of them. Xuan Ji had inherited the perfect Giant Demon bloodline, his talent was almost at the eighth-grade, and he had an astonishingly high thunder origin energy fusion compatibility. He had cultivated the halberd arts within the ancient Devil Tome and with just his early Houtian cultivation, he was able to compare to an early Xiantian master’s combat strength. It could be said that he was the greatest talent that the South Sea Demon Region had seen for the last 500 years!

The feminine man had personally taught Xuan Ji. He hoped to raise Xuan Ji into a Divine Sea Supreme Elder, and once again restore the majesty that the South Sea Demon Region had experienced 3000 years ago.

But delicate flowers grown in the greenhouse could not withstand the wind and rain. When Xuan Ji was 15, the feminine man had sent him out to adventure and experience the world. But, Xuan Ji did not disappoint him. He had obtained the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder by himself during his adventures, and his cultivation had broken through to the Houtian realm, further increasing his strength.

But, no one had expected that he would actually fall at the hands of a youth named Lin Ming! All of the efforts that the feminine man had spent for the last many years had been completely wasted!

How could he not hate!

Chapter 448 – Blood Springs

“The most outstanding aspect of the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’ lies in its killing potential. When Lei Mubai had practiced the ancient Devil Tome, it had only been a miniscule portion of the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’s’ cultivation method. In terms of cultivation method, the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’ is far inferior to the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. If I use the cultivation method of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ along with the killing techniques of the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’, there are some places that don’t really match…”

Lin Ming thought out loud. Although his cultivation method was top class, it was a bit complicated; there would inevitably be areas in which things didn’t mesh well.

However, Lin Ming didn’t worry too much. The reason that he studied the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’ was solely because of its techniques. Once his techniques reached the extreme of perfection, it would become a Law.

For instance, when Lin Ming had used the Primeval Halberd Strike as well as the move that made time spin around chaotically, those had both been similar to the use of Laws. It was just that Lin Ming’s perception and cultivation weren’t high enough for him to comprehend the Laws used. He could only rely on the energy of the Blood Drinking Seals to achieve an effect similar to Laws.

Even so, the power was absolutely amazing. If it wasn’t for the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’, Lin Ming would have at most been able to kill two Xiantian masters – everyone else would have managed to run away.

“I don’t know how much longer this war will last. I wonder how Miss Mu and Xingxuan are doing…” As Lin Ming was thinking, he glanced at his intelligence jade slip and began to look for the next target…

……………………….

At an island 3000 miles away from Divine Phoenix Island, Qin Xingxuan just happened to be sitting down on a cushion in a martial arts cultivation room. Fire origin energy swirled around her, forming a vortex with her in the center and steadily converging into her body.

After her body was thoroughly quenched with 10 drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence, Qin Xingxuan had gained the talent necessary to practice the more core sections of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. In addition, Qin Xingxuan was already a natural sixth-grade martial talent. Although her cultivation speed wasn’t heaven defyingly fast, she was still making new changes every day, and her progress was extremely fast.

In these few months, Qin Xingxuan’s cultivation was nearing the middle Pulse Condensation period.

This was mostly because Qin Xingxuan had just started to practice the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, and it required that she slowly accumulate fire origin energy. If she had practiced for a longer time and at a higher realm, she would probably have made a breakthrough.

“Miss Qin, how are you feeling?”

Mu Qianyu was all smiles as she entered into the martial arts cultivation room. As she looked at the vortex of fire origin energy swirling around Qin Xingxuan, she had a very satisfied smile on her face.

Although Qin Xingxuan’s rank in Divine Phoenix Island was only the lowliest maid disciple, she actually had maids and servants serving her, and she didn’t need to do any labor. The status of a maid disciple was only a title in order to reduce the pressure of public opinion on her. With Qin Xingxuan’s status and talent, the fact that she had obtained 10 drops of Vermillion Bird blood essence could easily arouse criticism from others.

A drop of Vermillion Bird blood essence was indelibly related to a martial artist’s lifespan and future; who wouldn’t be utterly jealous of Qin Xingxuan?

Qin Xingxuan usually followed Mu Qianyu around, and all questions she had were personally answered by Mu Qianyu. She had servants taking care of her daily living needs, and her cultivation speed was at least two or three times faster than when she had been at the Seven Profound Valleys.

“Senior-apprentice Sister Mu.” As Qin Xingxuan saw Mu Qianyu enter, she immediately stood up. Although they had already been together for two months, she still felt a sense of restraint when facing Mu Qianyu.

“Miss Qin, Lin Ming has sent a letter.” Mu Qianyu smiled. When the two met each other, they would always maintain a respectful manner.

“Ah?” Qin Xingxuan called out in surprise, a light fluttering feeling of happiness in her heart.

Mu Qianyu laughed and then took out a paper letter from her spatial ring, handing it over to Qin Xingxuan. In these past two months, Lin Ming would always send out three letters at a time. He would send one to Mu Yuhuang, Mu Qianyu, and Qin Xingxuan. Although Qin Xingxuan’s letter only contained trivial musings and some other matters, the content of the letter was unimportant. Qin Xingxuan mainly wanted to know that Lin Ming was safe.

……………………..

As the days passed by, Lin Ming killed more and more Demon Region martial artists. His cultivation was still at the late Houtian realm, but his combat strength had risen by leaps and bounds. He still had 13 Blood Drinking Seals, but they were even more vivid and vibrant, and even more lethal.

As Lin Ming killed more people, the name of Blood Demon began to sound like thunder within the ears of those on South Aurora Island. His spotlight was even brighter than the Demon Region’s Big Three!

Normally when the Demon Region’s Big Three killed squads there would be a few survivors. With three to five Xiantian masters escaping in separating directions, it was difficult to kill them all. However, no one escaped the Blood Demon, there were simply no witnesses!

To be attacked by the Blood Demon meant utter and total annihilation.

There had even been one occasion when two Demon Region squads had joined together. Although they weren’t considered top squads, there were still 15 martial artists in total including five Xiantian masters – one middle Xiantian master and four early Xiantian masters. But even with a squad of this size, after encountered the Blood Demon, they were all killed! Not a single one had managed to escape!

After this news spread out, all of South Aurora’s martial artists were shocked. Fifteen martial artists killed, and all of their blood essence sucked dry. There were even many of them that had been killed a thousand steps away. Obviously, they had all been prepared to escape. However, what was most horrifying was that all five Xiantian masters had escaped in separate directions, but they were still all killed!

What sort of strength was necessary to achieve this?

Even with five Xiantian masters combined together, they still couldn’t survive. Besides the squads of the Demon Region’s Big Three, what other squad had confidence they would be able to survive the terror of the Blood Demon?

After that, the Demon Region martial artists rarely  went past a hundred miles outside of their headquarters. The deterring effect of the Blood Demon was actually greater than all of the squads of the Wartime Alliance combined!

This sounded like an exaggeration, but it was the truth. In this month, there were more Demon Region martial artists that died at the hands of the Blood Demon than at the combined hands of every other martial artist within the Wartime Alliance squads.

It had to be known that during an encounter, although the battle would be fierce, not many people would actually die. If half of them died, that would be considered an extremely fierce life or death fight. But, once a squad encountered the Blood Demon, that was certain annihilation. There wasn’t even a chance to escape. This just made people despair too much. This also caused the squads of the South Sea Demon Region to not even have the courage to bring up the Blood Demon’s name.

…………………

It was deep into the night. In a hidden cave within South Aurora Island’s spiritual forest, Lin Ming had quietly snuck in. As soon as he was there, he grabbed a handful of spatial rings from his pocket. With just a thought, everything within these spatial rings poured out.

Because of the war, these Demon Region martial artists were extremely wealthy. Of course, these were all treasures of ordinary Xiantian masters. Lin Ming wasn’t particularly attracted to many of these things.

However, a little made a lot. If everything was exchanged into true essence stones, it would be a massive fortune. Although Lin Ming didn’t use true essence stones now, he never knew when he would need to in the future. If he saved up some money now, it would help avoid any complications in the future.

“Around 3000 medium-grade true essence stones and a massive number of treasures and pills. Most of these are ghost streamers, demon runes, blood treasures and so forth. These things are mostly used by martial artists of the demonic path, they aren’t that useful to me.”

Lin Ming practiced the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’, and it required him to gather and refine fresh blood essence. All of these treasures and objects that had stored blood essence for a long time were simply useless to him.

Lin Ming casually and quickly divided everything. True essence stones were placed in one ring, valuables in another, and objects that weren’t worth much in yet another.

After Lin Ming gathered everything back up again, he launched his movement technique and returned to base.

“Wild Halberd! You went out to practice again, haha!” The bearded big fellow happily greeted. If he greeted anyone else on the squad, he would always joke around and give them a lesson that actual combat was better than cultivating and other nonsense. However, he usually never said these things to Lin Ming.

In these past months, Lin Ming’s strength had become obvious to everyone. It wasn’t just that one time in the spiritual forest, but every time that Lin Ming would go to battle with the Fire Ax Squad, he would have spectacular and outstanding performance. In fact, there had been a time that if it wasn’t for the timely actions of Lin Ming, Enchanting Shadow and the bearded big fellow would have already had their heads chopped off. Whether it was individual combat prowess or insight on the battlefield, Lin Ming was at the top of the class. Everyone was naturally happy to have such a great member on their squad.

Unfortunately, Lin Ming didn’t have much time or opportunities to do much else with the squad; he was always out practicing his martial arts by himself.

“Captain, I think that Wild Halberd’s true strength is much more awesome!” The bearded big fellow loudly said as he drank a large cup of wine and poured himself another.

“Mm, Wild Halberd’s true strength is very deep and profound. He should be able to defeat an early Xiantian master by himself. In fact, he might even be stronger than Violet Rain. But Wild Halberd likes to remain low-key, you just have to see how he did on his original strength test to know. He had only gotten a bit more than 100,000 points, just enough to reach the standard for a first class soldier.”

“He should be a direct disciple of some large sect, or even the last disciple of some high master. He isn’t really interested in whatever can be exchanged with military exploit points.”

“Haha, mentioning no interest in military exploit points, I wonder which master that Blood Demon is. In these recent days he has killed countless Demon Region martial artists – the military exploit points he would have accumulated would be terrifying. South Aurora Island’s Demon Region martial artists won’t even show their faces because they are scared of being killed by him.”

“Blood Demon should be an extreme Xiantian genius from a sect. A Revolving Core master wouldn’t do something so frivolous.”

“Mm, I think so too.”

Even though Lin Ming and the existence known as the Blood Demon had appeared on South Aurora Island at nearly the same time, nobody ever expected that Lin Ming was the Blood Demon. Lin Ming’s cultivation was true. How could Fire Ax or anyone else believe that a late Houtian martial artist would have such abnormal combat strength like the Blood Demon?

……………

At this time at the South Sea Demon Region’s stronghold, a martial artist that was as skinny as a corpse was holding a wine glass in his hands. The cup was filled with a thick and bright red liquid that emanated a bloody energy; this liquid was shockingly actually blood.

In front of the skinny martial artist sat a man with pale skin. This pale-skinned man’s eyes were closed, “Many martial artists have already left South Aurora Island. The existence of the Blood Demon had already made the situation untenable, it is simply unprofitable to stay there.”

Because of Lin Ming, many martial artists squads didn’t dare to go out alone. Naturally, this meant that less and less were willing.

As the skinny martial artist emptied the glass of blood, he licked his lips and said, “I’d like to meet this Blood Demon. It’s just that this fellow seems intent on avoiding us. Otherwise, there is no way he would have been able to avoid our intelligence. If he has the guts, he would have come for us sooner! In other words, he is afraid of us!”

“He might not be afraid of us, but rather afraid that he won’t be able to kill us all… have you found that whenever the Blood Demon moves, he won’t leave any witnesses? It’s as if he has some secret that he’s scared of being discovered…”

Chapter 454 – The Title of Blood Demon

In the midst of the battlefield, Lin Ming held the Great Desolate Blood Halberd. The 10 foot long blood halberd extended straight out. The two foot long blade edge gleamed with a cold light, and the pole was like a thick python.

At that moment, the figure of Lin Ming standing there was like a deadly halberd. His aura was staggering and his flowing murderous intent was breathtaking!

All of the surrounding martial artists trembled at this presence. If Lin Ming had just barely managed to defend against Xuan Chang’s probing strike, they would have been able to accept that. But now Xuan Chang had used a martial skill and Lin Ming had still blocked it, instead forcing Xuan Chang to take several steps back. This was simply unbelievable.

It had to be known that Lin Ming’s cultivation was more than an entire boundary worse than Xuan Chang’s!

How could such a person have been unknown and unremarkable all this time?

Violet Rain bit her lips, her eyes shining, “Captain, has Wild Halberd been hiding his cultivation?”

Fire Ax was silent, hiding his cultivation? If Wild Halberd wanted to hide his cultivation in front of them, that could only be possible if his cultivation was higher. But now, it looked like even Xuan Chang had recognized that Wild Halberd was a Houtian realm martial artist. Could Wild Halberd be a Revolving Core Supreme Elder? But why would a Revolving Core master hide amongst them? Was it for fun or something?

Fire Ax’s eyes were radiant as he looked at the Great Desolate Blood Halberd in Lin Ming’s hands. He whispered, “Maybe Wild Halberd is the Blood Demon…”

Hearing Fire Ax’s hypothesis, Violet Rain was shocked.

Blood Demon?

Yes, Wild Halberd’s might match the strength that the Blood Demon was rumored to have. Also, Wild Halberd and the Blood Demon appeared on South Aurora Island at nearly the same time. With both of these truths combined together, it meant that Wild Halberd and Blood Demon were almost certainly one and the same!

At this time, not only did Fire Ax make this guess, but the Demon Region’s Big Three, Lu Huo, and other perceptive martial artists also thought of this.

Lu Huo’s eyelids fluttered. If Wild Halberd was the Blood Demon, then was it possible to have Wild Halberd take the lead and engage with the South Sea Demon Region in a final life or death showdown?

Even if they had the Blood Demon on their side, this battle would still be dancing upon the razor-thin edge of death!

But if they didn’t fight, wouldn’t they perish anyway?

Nightmare’s lips moved as he sent Xuan Chang a true essence sound transmission.

Xuan Chang frowned, Blood Demon?

He wasn’t satisfied with this answer. Where did Blood Demon come from? How could such a ridiculous genius randomly appear out of thin air? He had to have some sort of origin, unless he was a martial artist who came from a distant land.

This Blood Demon’s cultivation method was absolutely a top cultivation method of the demonic path. In that one collision a moment ago, the energy within wasn’t too great, but that strange rotating power made Xuan Chang feel as if he was unable to resist at all. This cultivation even surpassed the legacies of the South Sea Demon Region!

If he took one step back and thought about it, there was only a single talent within the South Horizon Region that could compare to a genius like this, and that would be Divine Phoenix Island’s Lin Ming. Both of them were at the late Houtian realm, and both also had such outrageous combat strength…

Mm, could it be…

Thinking this, Xuan Chang’s eyes widened.

As he thought of Lin Ming, even Xuan Chang felt frightened. A year ago, Lin Ming had defeated Xuan Ji, who had disguised himself as Lei Mubai!

Xuan Ji was the most radiant and outstanding talent that had appeared in the South Sea Demon Region for the last several hundred years. He reached the Houtian realm at a mere 17 years of age, and he also had the perfect Giant Demon bloodline. His talent was almost at the eighth-grade, and he also had an extremely high thunder origin energy fusion compatibility. He cultivated the ancient Devil Tome’s Halberd Arts, and with his just Houtian cultivation, he could defeat an early Xiantian martial artist from a large sect!

Against Xuan Ji, Xuan Chang simply didn’t have the courage to compete. But this sort of monstrous genius was actually defeated by Lin Ming, who had even jumped realms in order to do so!

If this Blood Demon was Lin Ming…

“It shouldn’t be possible. Lin Ming uses a spear and Blood Demon uses a halberd. Not just that, but there is a great stylistic difference in their cultivation methods. Blood Demon practices a top demonic path cultivation method, but Lin Ming practices Divine Phoenix Island’s cultivation method…”

‘No matter where this fellow comes from, as long as I can kill him here today, I will be able to forever rid myself of this future calamity!’ As Xuan Chang thought this, his entire body flowed with true essence.

Netherworld Devil Arts – Universe of Bloody War!

The Netherworld Devil Arts was the original cultivation method that the Netherworld Great Emperor had used to become infamous. Although it was inferior to the ancient Devil Tome, it wasn’t that much worse. With Xuan Chang’s cultivation as an extreme Xiantian warrior, he would undoubtedly be able to display the formidable power of the Netherworld Devil Arts.

Suddenly, waves of surging blood appeared. All of the surrounding space was filled with the thick energy of blood, and some weaker martial artists felt extremely ill.

If the shockwave was so powerful, then facing this head on would truly be an inconceivable terror.

Lin Ming’s vision was profound; he stimulated his Tempering Marrow true essence to the limit. In this battle, he wouldn’t be able to hold back at all. Perhaps even his status would be revealed.

Xuan Chang waved his halberd. True essence wrapped around the waves of blood, rushing towards Lin Ming, breaking the earth wherever it went.

“Blood Seal Twisting Murder!”

Lin Ming clenched his right hand and stabbed out the Great Desolate Blood Halberd with indomitable momentum! Atop the blood halberd, 13 blood seals crazily spun around.

This was still a spinning force, except this time it was spinning outwards.

This halberd strike that contained a spiraling power was like a thin steel needle as it tore apart the waves of blood, dispersing them all. This was the inherent style of the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’. If it wasn’t for the Blood Drinking Seal’s spinning power, Lin Ming would have to spend at least twice the true essence to scatter the waves of blood.

“Mm? This style…!”

Xuan Chang was shocked. Even the ancient Devil Tome’s Halberd Arts was left in the dust in terms of the exquisiteness of the technique.

As Xuan Chang saw Lin Ming’s halberd piercing towards him with a spinning force, he quickly raised his halberd to block. But at this moment, an amazing scene took place. Lin Ming’s halberd seemed to penetrate through the space itself, instantly arriving in front of Xuan Chang!

‘What!?’

Xuan Chang’s expression completely changed. At this life or death moment, he gnashed on his tongue, “Explode!”

Bang!

Waves upon waves of blood instantly blew up. Many surrounding martial artists were sent flying back in the air, several of them spitting out blood.

“Be careful!”

“Withstand it! Do not step back!”

The martial artists quickly intensified their protective true essence. At this time, everyone would rather withstand the explosive waves of blood and be injured than escape to the periphery of the group. Who knew what sort of invisible space cracks were around them. If they stepped into a space crack, that meant certain death!

A massive amount of bloody fog filled the air, shrouding Lin Ming and Xuan Chang within. No one could see or hear within; even perception was being torn apart by the spiraling power.

All of the martial artists felt their heartbeats quicken in nervousness.

“Die!”

Within the bloody fog, Xuan Chang swept his halberd towards Lin Ming!

Lin Ming didn’t say a single word as he similarly swept his halberd.

On the blade!

13 crimson blood seals blocked Xuan Chang’s halberd blade, grounding it in place.

“Mm? This is…” Xuan Chang felt as if someone had poured molten metal onto his halberd; there was a great resistance that acted on it.

In this moment, Lin Ming thrust his halberd towards Xuan Chang.

“Humph, explode for me!”

Bang!

True essence erupted, washing away all of Lin Ming’s Blood Drinking Seals. Xuan Chang howled, raising his halberd and slicing down at Lin Ming!

Clang!

Two halberds crossed. Lin Ming felt a strong force transmit through him and his right leg pushed down, crushing all the rocks beneath him. He was forced a step back, the blood in his body tumbling.

Chi-la!

The clothing on his chest was ripped apart, exposing his smooth and firm muscles. There was also a layer of bloody energy attached to him, constantly corroding Lin Ming’s body.

This bloody fog… Lin Ming’s inner true essence vibrated, scattering all the bloody fog. He looked up and saw Xuan Chang take a step back; his situation was much better than Lin Ming’s.

Indeed, if Lin Ming didn’t open the Heretical God Force, then in terms of absolute strength he would be inferior to Xuan Chang. However, facing so many enemies at the same time, Lin Ming didn’t dare to rashly open the Heretical God Force.

“This is tricky!”

Lin Ming’s eyebrows tightened. He did have a lot of final master moves he could use, but he didn’t dare to use any of them casually. Any one of those moves consumed a great deal of energy. If he had to use it, he must ensure that Xuan Chang would be severely injured; otherwise he would be in danger.

Xuan Chang looked at Lin Ming, his heart becoming increasingly perturbed. ‘Just what cultivation method is this? Is this the legacy of some other great demonic path sect?’

‘The Blood Demon’s style is extremely bizarre. It has many similarities with the ancient Devil Tome, but it seems to be even stronger than the ancient Devil Tome!’

Thinking this, Xuan Chang’s heart suddenly shook!

Could it be…

As he carefully looked at the Great Desolate Blood Halberd in the Blood Demon’s hand, it looked exactly the same as Xuan Ji’s. Not just that, but although the cultivation method that the Blood Demon used was different from the ancient Devil Tome, it was truly somewhat similar! It was as if… as if his cultivation method was derived from the ancient Devil Tome, a higher evolution!

Could it be that… Lin Ming had obtained Xuan Ji’s Great Desolate Blood Halberd and also the first layer of the ancient Devil Tome cultivation method, and then proceeded to independently practice and perceive its secrets to this degree???

Heavens!

Did he improve upon the cultivation method of an ancient Supreme Elder? Just what sort  of monstrous perception was this, to be able to improve the cultivation method that an ancient Supreme Elder had created!?

Thinking of this, Xuan Chang’s complexion completely changed, and beads of sweat began to roll down his forehead. He was simply stunned by Lin Ming’s monstrous talent.

Nightmare, Blood Bone, and Viper were all unclear as to why Xuan Chang’s expression had changed so suddenly. It was as if he had just discovered something terrible a moment ago…

The surrounding martial artists also weren’t clear as to what was happening.

Xuan Chang’s complexion became increasingly grim and solemn. If this Blood Demon truly was Lin Ming, then he must kill him now! Otherwise, with Lin Ming’s monstrous perception and talent, he would probably be able to instantly kill him in another six months!

This sort of person was an abnormal being that couldn’t be stirred up.

But, the key of all this was – could he kill Lin Ming?

Although Xuan Chang also had many finishing blows he hadn’t used, he was aware that Lin Ming had even more methods!

If he was stronger than Lin Ming by a bit, then with the help of the Demon Region’s Big Three he could suppress Lin Ming. But if Lin Ming turned around and escaped, in this world with space cracks everywhere, stopping him would be hard!

If he rashly pursued him into a space crack, he would lose his head!

If he couldn’t chase and kill Lin Ming, and Lin Ming found an exit, then that abnormal youth could find a place to cultivate for a few years. In the meantime, Xuan Chang would be living in constant fear and unease, until the day that Lin Ming returned to kill him!

Xuan Chang suddenly found that he had jumped on the tiger and could no longer back down; just what should he do?

As Nightmare saw Xuan Chang’s ugly complexion, he couldn’t help but ask with a true essence sound transmission, “Sir Envoy, this person is a bit tricky. Would Sir Envoy permit me to help in secret? Although I cannot deal with him alone, I can use my soul force to secretly attack his spiritual sea. I have complete confidence that I will be able to slow or restrain his movements. When that happens, Sir Envoy can kill him with ease!”

Xuan Chang’s heart stirred. Nightmare excelled at soul attacks, this plan was indeed feasible. If he was successful, he could stop Lin Ming from running. But… this was a gamble. Should he make this gamble or not?

Chapter 455 – I Was Impulsive

Although Xuan Chang was proud, since this involved his life, he still wasn’t above admitting defeat and apologizing in the presence of everyone. This was something he was still willing to do. However, what Xuan Chang was afraid of was that even if he capitulated and apologized, Lin Ming would still bear a grudge against him in the future.

Perhaps in several years, or even less, Lin Ming would be able to crush him like an ant. At that time, his life or death would all depend on Lin Ming’s mood! Xuan Chang was unwilling to hand his fate over to others like this.

Xuan Chang clenched his teeth and gripped the blood halberd in his hands. He didn’t need Nightmare’s soul attack to wound Lin Ming. As long as Lin Ming hesitated for just a second… he would be able to kill him!

“Nightmare, when I attack, you join in; use everything you have to kill him, leave nothing behind! Otherwise, we won’t have another chance!”

Xuan Chang had an extremely grim expression. This sort of attack that took one by surprise could only be used once. The second time, Lin Ming would have protective measures in place and there wouldn’t be much of an effect. And if he escaped in advance, then in this broken world full of space cracks and other dangers, whether it was chasing or running or hiding, everything was a death-defying act.

All of it would depend on one one’s destiny. And Xuan Chang was not confident to the point where he thought his own destiny was greater than Lin Ming’s.

“Alright.” Nightmare was a bit surprised, Xuan Chang seemed to take this Blood Demon especially seriously. Did he know the identity of this Blood Demon?

“Netherworld Devil Arts!”

Xuan Chang shouted, and true essence erupted from him like a volcano. He activated the third layer of the ‘Netherworld Devil Arts’ cultivation method. Xuan Chang had just managed to trace the threshold of this third layer. When trying to control the overbearingly savage and violent demonic path cultivation method, if his technique or control was insufficient, it was highly likely that he would end up suffering a backlash and wounding himself. He might even drive himself to madness. For Xuan Chang to use this now proved just how desperate he was!

As Xuan Chang’s dreadful aura flooded out, his hair billowed in the wind. At this moment, he was like an all-powerful war god that no one could defeat, looking down at the world with arrogance!

All of the surrounding martial artists felt their backs turn cold as they witnessed Xuan Chang’s power. Even the South Sea Demon Region’s Big Three were alarmed and frightened.

“This is too terrifying! Were Xuan Chang’s early moves just tentative attacks?”

“His strength suddenly rose up so high. All of us are at the extreme Xiantian realm, yet the difference is so great!”

“Who can resist Xuan Chang like this?”

All of the Wartime Alliance martial artists felt despair fill their hearts, even Lu Huo had dispelled his thoughts of teaming up with the Blood Demon to deal with Xuan Chang. With Xuan Chang and the Big Three of the South Sea Demon Region, whether it was quality or quantity, they were stronger. If they resisted, they would all die!

Lu Huo sighed. Just how many people would be able to survive this impending disaster?

…..

Lin Ming’s pupils contracted. He naturally knew that his opponent was planning on going all-out with everything he had. As for his own card that he had in hand, it was a pure killing move he could only use once – he was saving it for a situation in which it would absolutely be successful. But this time he had no way of holding back, otherwise he would be severely wounded here. If he couldn’t escape, then he would die soon after.

“When I faced Ouyang Shenxiu, I only opened the Heretical God Force – I didn’t burn the blood of the Ancient Phoenix. And after the battle, my condition wasn’t at its best. But now that I’m facing Xuan Chang, my strength has greatly increased and I’m also in top condition. I wonder just how far I can go!”

Lin Ming began to seethe with fighting spirit!

Hou!

The blood of the Ancient Phoenix combusted! The flame marks between Lin Ming’s eyebrows began to shine with a golden flame light. The most potent ability of the Ancient Phoenix’s blood was that it was able to bathe in flames and be reborn. This mean that the blood of the Ancient Phoenix could be burnt without limit, and none of it would be lost!

“Die!”

Xuan Chang tightened the grip on his blood halberd and all of his upper body clothes tore apart. His red hair scattered in the air, and with every step he took, the ground shattered. A vast surge of true essence turned into a giant red eagle, flying towards Lin Ming!

Ka ka ka!

A halberd was wielded; the surrounding space seemed like it was being torn apart.

Lin Ming’s eyes were deep. His true essence touched upon the Heretical God Seed.

Heretical God Force – open!

A vast amount of terrifyingly compressed true essence erupted from the Heretical God Seed. In that instant, the true essence of Lin Ming’s body was like a vast and endless ocean, turbulent waves of true essence ceaselessly crashing into the world!

All of the surrounding martial artists paled as they experienced this crazily fierce aura. Even Fire Ax didn’t dare to believe his own eyes. He knew that Blood Demon was strong, but he never would have imagined that he was strong to this degree. Was that violent battle from a moment ago just a small part of his strength?

Nightmare’s complexion turned white. He originally thought that Xuan Chang wouldn’t even need his help, but now it looked as if it might not even be enough!

Nightmare revolved true essence within his body. At this critical moment, he stared at Lin Ming. His spiritual sea rushed forwards, his soul pierced out!

At this time, Lin Ming no longer cared about hiding his status. The highly compressed power of thunder and fire within the Heretical God Seed exploded forth. At this moment, his entire body flashed with arcs of thunder and blazed with soaring flames. At the same time, Nightmare’s soul attack pierced Lin Ming’s spiritual sea!

Mm?

Lin Ming’s mind stirred; sneak soul attack?

Lin Ming barely even bothered to react. The savage and wild power of thunder that had been slumbering within his spiritual sea burst forth and attacked this strange and sneaky soul attack!

Meanwhile, a swirling black vortex appeared in the skies of Lin Ming’s spiritual sea – this was the Samsara martial intent!

This martial intent that was formed from experiencing 100 Samsaras came from the legacy of the Sorcerer Pagoda’s seventh floor. How could it allow its territory to be desecrated?

Peng!

The swirling black vortex was like the massive maw of a demon, directly tearing that fragment of soul energy to pieces.

“AhhhHHH!”

Nightmare screamed, falling to his knees as he clutched his head and collapsed. Just a moment ago he had attacked Lin Ming with his soul force per Xuan Chang’s instructions. He had exhausted all of his strength in that attack. A soul was a martial artist’s most fragile aspect. If a martial artist attacked someone who had a strong soul force defense with an all-out attack, it was no different from smashing a rock with an egg; they would suffer a horrendous backlash!

Many martial artists heard Nightmare’s pitiful screams. But at this time, no one could reflect on just what this meant; Xuan Chang’s halberd was already coming down.

But at this time, the Great Desolate Blood Halberd  in Lin Ming’s hand had at some point been exchanged for a red and purple spear!

A manic power of thunder and flame interweaved into a singularity – Thunderfire Annihilation!

Bang!!!

In this dark and desolate world, a gorgeous purple sun seemed to rise into the air. All sound was swallowed, and a blazing light flooded the vision of everyone present!

All of the surrounding martial artists were considered extraordinary geniuses of their generation and lands. But facing such a dangerous explosion, they were like leaves in a storm. All of them were blown away, scattered about in disorder.

In that maelstrom of thunder and fire, Lin Ming and Xuan Chang both flew backwards.

But, the difference was that Lin Ming balanced himself and fell to one knee, his face paling. As for Xuan Chang, he smashed into the ground, vomiting a giant mouthful of blood.

Seeing this, all of the martial artists were awed, especially the scene of Nightmare suffering a backlash. None of them could believe their eyes. The extreme Xiantian Nightmare was infamous throughout the South Sea battlefield for his soul attacks. But a moment ago, Nightmare had sneak attacked Lin Ming during the chaos, and not only was Lin Ming alright, but Nightmare was severely wounded in return!

Viper and Blood Bone both had extremely difficult expressions. They best understood Nightmare and knew just how strong his soul attacks were. After suffering the piercing of his spiritual sea, let alone attacking as usual, even standing would be difficult.

However, Lin Ming seemed to have shrugged off this attack with no response. Not only did he resist Nightmare’s soul attack, but he had accepted Xuan Chang’s strongest strike and had also beaten him into vomiting blood!

Was this really a human?

“He is too terrifying!” Blood Bone’s lips twitched. Against Lin Ming, he simply couldn’t muster the courage to face him!

“Luckily… we didn’t encounter Blood Demon earlier.” Viper gulped, his forehead sweating. If they had really encountered Blood Demon earlier, it wouldn’t have been strange if one or two of them had died! Thinking of this, he was horrified.

Everyone was in complete silence. Xuan Chang crawled up from the ground, his face white. As he smeared the blood off his lips, he glanced at Nightmare who was twitching on the floor, and his complexion became even uglier.

Xuan Chang had overdrawn his true essence to make an all-out strike. During this time, Nightmare had also used his soul attack. However, not only was his attack blocked, but he had been beaten into such a miserable state!

How was this possible?

How could this Lin Ming be formidable to this degree?

Was he really only 17 years old? Was his cultivation really only at the late Houtian realm?

Xuan Chang’s heart filled with waves of despair. Let alone forcing Lin Ming to stay on scene, it didn’t seem as if he could even defeat him!

He knew that several months ago Lin Ming had killed his way into the Seven Profound Valleys and had slain several Great Elders of the Acacia Faction. He had even fought the Acacia Faction Sovereign and severely wounded him, causing him to lose blood essence. Finally, he had killed his own enemy with his own hand in front of all the Acacia Valley Elders. But the Seven Profound Valleys’ Valley Master didn’t dare to stop him or publically reveal this information

If he didn’t kill Lin Ming today, then maybe a dozen or so years from now, Lin Ming would have the ability to kill his way into the South Sea Demon Region, and in the presence of the sect Elders, squash him like a bug!

But… could he kill Lin Ming?

It was looking more like he would be killed by Lin Ming!

Thinking of this, Xuan Chang felt his intestines turn green with regret; how could he have provoked such a dark star!

To come to such an insignificant South Aurora Island and run into Lin Ming, his luck was truly the ultimate trash.

Lin Ming wiped off the blood from his lips and slowly stood up. The truth was that the actual situation wasn’t what Xuan Chang had imagined.

For Nightmare to suffer a counterattack in his soul attack, that could be considered his bad luck. With the Heretical God Seed’s Thunder Soul in addition to his Samsara martial intent, Lin Ming’s soul defense was formidable to the point of being utterly abnormal.

For Nightmare to try and pierce Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, that was simply a suicidal action.

As for the Thunderfire Annihilation a moment ago, because he still had so many enemies to face, he didn’t dare to use the complete Thunderfire Annihilation. Even so, he had still consumed around 30% of his true essence.

But this strike had only severely injured Xuan Chang, his opponent still had a high combat effectiveness left.

As Lin Ming took stock of himself, whether it was opening the Heretical God Force or burning the blood of the Ancient Phoenix, neither could be sustained for too long. If this lasted, then at most both he and Xuan Chang would be severely wounded. As for the South Sea Demon Region’s Big Three, he absolutely wouldn’t have the power to resist them!

What should he do?

Lin Ming already expected that this would be a difficult uphill battle, but he had no choice other than to fight. As for escaping from here, Lin Ming also dreaded those space cracks that existed everywhere.

At this time, an incredible scene happened. Xuan Chang abruptly lowered the halberd in his hands and said, “I admit defeat. I…was impulsive in my actions a moment ago, and I apologize for that. Forgive me.”

What?

Lin Ming was shocked.

It wasn’t just Lin Ming, but all the surrounding martial artists were dumbfounded.

Just what had happened?

Chapter 457 – Ancient Transmission Array

Elder Zhou and everyone else’s reactions were well within Xuan Yuqie’s expectations; who wouldn’t be tempted by something like this?

After she had the Elders hungrily hanging onto her words, she slowly said, “The Nirvana Dragon Root can increase the chances of crossing Life Destruction by 20 to 30%. Not just that, but… the enhancement is permanent!”

20-30% increased chances, permanently!

This so called ‘permanence’ was that after successfully washing the marrow, every time one attempted to cross through the stages of Life Destruction, their chances would increase by 20-30%, all the way until they successfully broke through to the Divine Sea realm!

Elder Zhou felt as if he was going crazy. 20-30% seemed like an astounding exaggeration, not to mention that this was a permanent increase.

Normally, those martial artists that could cultivate to the Life Destruction boundary were all top talents. Of course, even among the top talents there were differences. Those that had a better foundation had a greater chance of crossing Life Destruction. As for those that had a worse foundation, their chances might be just 10-20%.

Elder Zhou wasn’t considered too bad. With his original 40-50% chances, along with the Nirvana Dragon Root and some other precious materials, he would have a near certain chance to cross Life Destruction. It would be blessedly safe.

If he didn’t dare to cross Life Destruction with an over 80% chance of success, then he might as well not practice martial arts and retire, waiting for his life energy to exhaust itself and then die in peace.

“How about it? Is Elder Zhou satisfied with this answer?” The one who spoke was Xuan Wuji. He was the Great Elder of the Demon Region Western Faction and also the previous Demon Region Western Faction Sovereign. He was older than Xuan Yuqie by several hundred years, and he had crossed through the third stage of Life Destruction.

“If this precious medicine is able to increase the chances of successfully passing through the Life Destruction stages, this old man naturally desires it.” Elder Zhou deeply looked at Xuan Wuji. The two of them had never been on the best of terms. But Elder Zhou was aware that with his status in the South Sea Demon Region, he would already be content to obtain a Nirvana Dragon Root.

As for the other treasures, even if it were a heaven-step treasure, Elder Zhou didn’t desire those much. Any treasure paled in comparison to his own life.

“I heard Sovereign Xuan say that besides the medicine garden there was also another treasure. Just what would that be?”

Xuan Yuqie said, “The second couldn’t be considered a treasure, it is the Demon Emperor’s familiar. This familiar is named the Giant Leviathan. When the Demon Emperor flew into the Realm of the Gods, his familiar remained within the mortal world. This Giant Leviathan is an extremely formidable beast, its body contains a vast space. For these past tens of thousands of years, it has been slumbering in perpetuity within the ancient battlefield. If we can summon it, then it will become a part of our war strength!”

“Giant Leviathan?”

Elder Zhou’s mind jolted. In the legends, the Giant Leviathan could grow to thousands of miles, it was an ancient Saint Beast of the past. If the Giant Leviathan floated to the surface, its back would be like an endless mountain range with great gales of wind. Its body was broad like an island, and in the legends, the Giant Leviathan would enter into deep hibernation for tens of thousands of years at a time. During this long period, the Giant Leviathan’s back would be covered with dust and dirt, and even plants would grow there. People would think that this Giant Leviathan was a real island, and they would live upon it for generations.

This legend and all the others were really shocking.

If they could tame this Giant Leviathan, the war strength of the South Sea Demon Region would vastly increase. But, to Elder Zhou, the significance of this wasn’t too great; he only cared about the Nirvana Dragon Root. ‘I don’t know whether or not what Xuan Wuji and Xuan Yuqie say is true, but my request isn’t too high. I just need to obtain a small cut of the Nirvana Dragon Root to assist me through the third stage of Life Destruction. As for other things, I simply do not need them.’

…..

In the broken world, pieces of thick clouds were suspended in the air. Under these ink black clouds, hundreds of martial artists were cautiously walking forwards. There was a massive group of zombie guards in the front. These zombie guards were skinny and their eyes were glazed over. The held treasures in their hands, vacantly waving them around in order to detect any space cracks in the way.

If a treasure weapon was suddenly sheared off, then that would indicate that there was a space crack located there. The zombie guard’s master would then command the zombie guard to leave a mark there.

However, every so often, there would be a small space crack that was as fragile as thin glass. Once it was knocked a bit by a treasure, it would cause this small space crack to collapse, twisting any zombie guard near it into bits and pieces.

There were also some times when there would be a large space crack and it would have a great pulling power. When a zombie guard approached, it would be directly sucked in, and then torn apart by the space storm.

Thus, over half the zombie guards had been ruined so far.

Xuan Chang’s complexion wasn’t too good. They had already touched upon space cracks several times, this meant that the collapsing world wasn’t too big. If it was completely sealed up, then he would simply vomit blood.

“Mm? That is…”

Xuan Chang looked up, his eyes widening. A bit more than 10 miles away, there was a huge altar. This altar was hidden in the hazy fog, so they couldn’t clearly see it.

“Brother Wild Halberd, let us go have a look.” Xuan Chang said from not far behind Lin Ming. Throughout this entire way, Xuan Chang had been exceptionally polite towards Lin Ming, continually referring to Lin Ming as Brother Wild Halberd. Whenever something came up, he would politely discuss it with Lin Ming. Lin Ming simply didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry. He knew the chances were that Xuan Chang knew who he was, and was a afraid of his status.

The truth was that he couldn’t blame Xuan Chang for being so timid. Seeing was believing. Xuan Chang had fought Lin Ming and had even overdrawn his true essence in his attack. In addition, there was also Nightmare assisting him. Yet, he had been defeated and Nightmare was put into a miserable state. Xuan Chang naturally didn’t dare to become enemies with Lin Ming anymore.

“Let’s take a look!” Xuan Chang said to the South Sea Demon Region martial artists. He immediately ordered those that controlled the zombie guards to head over to the altar.

What was surprising was that as they approached the altar, there were less and less space cracks present. Obviously the space here was relatively more stable.

After they approached, the discovered the this altar was over a hundred feet high, and it was forged from gray rock. On the rock, there were many different kinds of beautiful and exquisite reliefs carved.

As they walked up the stairs, they saw that there was a vast flat space atop the altar. There were many lines traced into the ground; it was incomparably mystical and mesmerizing.

As the several hundred martial artist saw this altar and the relief images etched upon it, they were all keenly interested. But as for Lin Ming, as soon as he saw these lines, his heart stirred – he recognized these.

These lines were runes from the Realm of the Gods. Carved atop this giant altar was actually a massive array formation.

Lin Ming pondered. It seemed as if… in ancient times, the Realm of the Gods was inextricably linked to the Sky Spill Continent.

Whether it was the ancient array formation jade slip that Ancestor Chi Yan had found, or all the different kinds of arrangements within the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, and now even this massive altar within the ancient battlefield, they all involved the Realm of the Gods. It was as if the Realm of the Gods had once been present here, but with the changing flow and ebb of time, all the legacies from the Realm of the Gods had been slowly lost.

‘Tens of thousands of years ago, the martial arts world of Sky Spill Continent was much more magnificent and glorious than it is now. All sorts of Emperors had emerged, such as the Southern Wilderness’ Sorcerer and the South Sea’s Demon Emperor. At that time, that was just the South Horizon Region; other areas certainly had characters as strong, if not stronger. I don’t know what happened all those years ago, but it seems as if the once great martial arts world slowly declined, and now within the entire Sky Spill Continent, Emperor level powerhouses rarely appear. There are only a dozen or so known, and with all the ones hidden, there might be around a hundred of them. Not just that, but these Emperor level powerhouses can’t hold a candle to the Sorcerer and Demon Emperor of the past!’

Lin Ming sighed, shaking his head. He no longer thought about this things. Rather, he began to observe the altar, carefully inspecting the array formation. As he glanced over the runes and general pattern, he slowly began to discover that this was an ancient array formation.

Looking at the massive scale of the transmission array as well as the complex array formation inscribed upon it, Lin Ming was unable to restrain a gasp. There were even over 100 slots for true essence stones on the edges of the array formation! ‘I wonder just how far this massive transmission array goes to. It shouldn’t be like those of the South Sea that send one tens of thousands of miles away. This one should work for hundreds of thousands, or even millions of miles!’

What sort of concept was that? Lin Ming simply couldn’t imagine it.

After Lin Ming had absorbed the memories of the Realm of the Gods array master, he had come to understand a great deal about the Realm of the Gods’ array formations. Although he couldn’t arrange his own massive array formation, understanding the principles behind it wasn’t too difficult.

After a quarter hour, Lin Ming finally understood the approximate theory and principle behind this ancient transmission array. For a single use, not only did this transmission array require 72 medium-grade true essence stones, but also 36 high-grade true essence stones! One also had to pay particular attention to placing down these true essence stones. If one didn’t understand the rules of arranging them, they would never open this transmission array.

‘Seventy-two medium-grade true essence stones as well as 36 high-grade true essence stones. A high-grade true essence stone is worth 100 medium-grade true essence stones…’

Lin Ming was secretly flabbergasted. The price to open this transmission array just once was astonishing. If he hadn’t killed so many people at the South Sea Demon Region and taken their belongings, he never would have even come close to being able to activate this. This transmission array was from so long ago, could it still start?

As Lin Ming was calmly thinking about this, he suddenly felt a wetness on his face – a drop of rain had clearly fallen on his cheek.

“Mm?” Lin Ming looked up to the skies and found that the dark clouds were becoming increasingly thick. But he remembered that when he had entered into this broken world, the sky was pitch black but it was clear; he could even see the countless bits of rock suspended in the air. But now, these dark and dense clouds had swallowed up all the suspended rocks.

“Rain? This world also has rain?”

The surviving martial artists also looked up to the skies. In the skies, the dark clouds were growing larger, and countless raindrops pattered onto the floor as they fell in a deluge. It was like they were in the middle of a monsoon.

Even if two people were just a few dozen feet away, they still couldn’t see each other because of the great curtain of rain. One could even see the water gathering on the altar at a visible speed. What sort of rain was like this? It was simply like standing in the midst of a waterfall.

Lin Ming’s mind stirred…

He stretched out his tongue, tasting the rainwater. It had a slight salty taste to it.

It was true!

This wasn’t just rain, but it was seawater that had been sucked up by the swirling gray vortex!

The seawater was shredded by the space storm until it became a fine mist that floated in the air. Eventually, it condensed into dark clouds. Once the dark clouds grew too heavy, they turned into rain that fell down.

If this was true and he wasn’t mistaken, there should be a pathway in the air!

Yes, they had searched the ground all this time, but they had forgotten to search the air.

Chapter 465 – Bloody Wilderness

As Xuan Wuji was thinking, he saw a black light flash past him. The Black Flood Dragon Clan Patriarch suddenly sank and turned into a violent black typhoon that shot towards the Demon God Imperial Palace!

The Black Flood Dragon Patriarch’s cultivation was already at the second stage of Life Destruction. In his opinion, any defensive measures or array formations that were left behind at the Demon God Imperial Palace would have already failed after these tens of thousands of years.  Still, even so, as a precaution he galvanized his true essence to the max. Behind him, the faint phantom of a Black Flood Dragon appeared.

As Xuan Wuji saw this he was unmoved. He only sneered and thought to himself, ‘Idiot!’

Hua!

As the Black Flood Dragon Patriarch was about to burst into the main entrance of the Demon God Imperial Palace, a red light flashed. At the entrance of the palace, a shining halo appeared out of thin air, rushing out like an overwhelming tide and smashing into the Black Flood Dragon Patriarch’s body.

With a dull thump, the Black Flood Dragon Patriarch was kicked backwards like a rubber ball. He was sent flying backwards, spitting blood!

As the other Life Destruction powerhouses saw this, their complexions changed. This palace that had been abandoned for tens of thousands of years actually still had the protection of an array formation? Not just that, but this array formation was astoundingly strong! Even the second stage Life Destruction Black Blood Dragon Patriarch spat blood in the collision!

Although the Black Flood Dragon’s true essence had been suppressed to 20% of its normal potency because of the rules that governed this world, it had to be known that this was only a single defensive array that protected the entrance to the Demon God Imperial Palace!

If a single defensive array was able to cause the Black Flood Dragon Patriarch to spit blood, then wouldn’t an offensive array violently and instantly kill them?

All of the Life Destruction powerhouses were alarmed. This Demon God Imperial Palace was too terrifying. They thought if this palace hadn’t already decayed for tens of thousands of years, they would have suffered an even more miserable fate.

The Black Flood Dragon Patriarch wiped the blood from the corners of his lips. As he looked at the still flashing defensive array, his face was gloomy. What in the world was this ghostly array formation? It was actually able to maintain itself for tens of thousands of years? And not just that, but it was still so powerful. Was this really something that could be created by someone?

………………..

In the forest, there was hidden murderous intent everywhere. As the group continued running, there were constantly martial artists that died. Two hours later, as they finally made their way out of the forest, around 30% of the martial artists had perished.

“This place is…”

In front of the crowd were endless plains of dark red, bumpy land. There were thick bones half buried in the ground, and all around were dark gray stone tablets that were stuck in the land. There were big and small stone tablets, and each one had been engraved with all sorts of intricate symbols. These symbols were different from the symbol system that existed on the Sky Spill Continent; the martial artists weren’t able to understand what they meant or represented.

These dark red plains gave off an extremely oppressive feeling. Even the sky was a dark red, and it glowed faintly with a bloody light.

From the virgin forest to this bloody wilderness, the intense visual difference was shocking to the mind.

With the experiences of the forest still fresh in their minds, everyone present maintained 120% vigilance as they faced these strange red plains.

At this point, continuing on was dangerous, but staying in the forest was also dangerous. If they had to make a choice then they had to proceed; they might even be able to find a lucky chance here.

“Let’s go.” The first one to step onto the dark red plains was the hawk-nosed old man from the South Sea Demon Region. He was the South Sea Demon Region Elder, Lian Chengji. His cultivation was at the middle Revolving Core realm. The South Sea Demon Region side had two middle Revolving Core realm Elders and also nine early Revolving Core powerhouses. Of those early Revolving Core masters, two or three of them had already reached the peak of the early phase. With their strength, the South Sea Demon Region was the strongest force amongst the sects present, so they were also the most confident.

As soon as Lian Chengji stepped onto this vast red plain, his complexion changed. This blood wilderness was even fiercer in suppressing his true essence; he could actually only use 25% of his true essence efficacy.

“Another 5% of true essence is suppressed!” Lian Chengji dismally said.

“The laws of this world are too strange. If this continues then the situation will only become more dangerous.” Another Elder also appeared worried. He decided that if his true essence was suppressed below 20%, he would no longer go forwards. Otherwise, there was a possibility that he really might be killed by these powerful and strange vicious beasts.

After the South Sea Demon Region martial artists walked forwards, the other sects’ martial artists followed them onto the bloody wilderness. Many of them had already activated a protective cover to detect space cracks. There was no life here, none of them knew whether or not this was caused by those terrifying rifts in space, so it was better to activate preventive measures just in case.

Everyone continued carefully, maintaining their minds at full alert. No matter how they looked at it, this bloody wilderness was stranger than the forest and even more dangerous.

However, they didn’t expect that after they walked for half an hour, they actually hadn’t encountered any dangers.

Some people couldn’t help but whisper to themselves. At this time, the hawk-nosed South Sea Demon Region Elder suddenly swiveled, his hand slapping downwards.

There was an explosive sound as the ground was split open. The martial artists behind were all shocked. They thought there was a surprise enemy attack, but they didn’t think that after the earth had burst open, a thick greatsword would come flying out.

This five foot long sword was jet-black as if it were made from ink, and the aura that it emitted was comparable to a high-grade earth-step treasure!

“What!?” All of the martial artists’ eyes shined. That Elder had just casually taken an item from the ground, but it was a high-grade earth-step treasure!? No… this wasn’t right… it wasn’t a high-grade earth-step treasure. From the energy fluctuations, this should only be a medium-grade earth-step treasure. Yet, it was several times better than a normal medium-grade earth-step treasure. This should be amongst the rarest of medium-grade earth-step treasures.

Lin Ming traced his jaw. He thought to himself, ‘This is a normal medium-grade earth-step treasure that was forged by an ancient refining master. It is several times superior to an ordinary medium-grade earth-step treasure that is forged by the refining masters of the current era.’

A medium-grade earth-step treasure was exceedingly valuable and precious. The Great Desolate Blood Halberd replica that Lei Mubai had used was also a top medium-grade earth-step treasure.

Lin Ming had very high standards. Naturally, he didn’t think too much of this weapon. But all of the martial artists at his side had widened eyes filled with greed. Most of them used low-grade earth-step treasures. Seeing such a rare medium-grade earth-step treasure in front of them, they were all envious.

After passing through that gauntlet of dangers and surviving, they finally saw a lucky chance appear!

This was the thought that most martial artists present had.

This bloody wilderness may have seemed dangerous, but the truth was that it wasn’t dangerous at all. Instead, there were all sorts of buried bones and treasures here. It was like this was an ancient battle site.

If they followed behind the ass of the South Sea Demon Region, they wouldn’t be able to pick up anything. If they fought with them, they also couldn’t win.

Thinking this, many of the martial artists began to part ways in small groups, quietly changing directions and leaving the main group. Out of precaution, these martial artist had at least an extreme Xiantian master leading them, or even two or three late Xiantian realm masters.

As the main group continued, more and more martial artists left, and even the South Sea Demon Region martial artists began to spread out on their own. Everyone wanted to pick up some treasures. If they followed behind Lian Chengji, they wouldn’t even be able to obtain scraps.

“Let’s go towards that side.” Lin Ming said to Mu Qianyu. As there were fewer and fewer people in the group, the image of Lian Chengji in front of them became increasingly dangerous.

“Mm.”

Mu Qianyu and Lin Ming left the group together. They didn’t know whether or not this bloody wilderness was truly safe!

Most of those present also understood this. But, they were all blinded by greed. As they saw Lian Chengji pick up a top medium-grade earth-step treasure in front of their eyes, none of them were able to resist the temptation to go off by themselves.

Perhaps this ancient battlefield had not only treasures, but also other things. For instance, they might even pick up a spatial ring that contained the complete worth of a top master. At that point they would really rise up in power.

Mu Qingshu watched Lin Ming and Mu Qianyu’s backs from a distance, and bitterly ground his teeth together. He even wanted to hire someone to kill them. But if he did that, the bloodline in his body would completely melt away within half a year, and he would lose all of his cultivation.

Since he didn’t have any means to retaliate against Lin Ming, he could only helplessly watch as Lin Ming walked closer and closer to Mu Qianyu, seeming to be very intimate and close to each other. He felt like he could vomit blood at this sight.

As Mu Yanzhuo watched this from afar, he could only sigh.

Reality was cruel. The result was already obvious, but many times, not everyone was willing to accept the truth in front of them, especially when someone’s object of desire was stolen away. The taste of this feeling was truly hard to swallow…

………..

Lin Ming cautiously made his way forward, completely opening his perception. In this strange world, Lin Ming was only able to extend his sense to around 200 feet. If it was underground, it was even shorter at around 100 feet.

And this 100 feet of earth was completely flooded by a massive amount of skeletal bones.

“There are so many bones!” Lin Ming gasped. These skeletons and bones came in all sizes. Some seemed ordinary and had turned to oil after tens of thousands of years underground, but there were also those that hadn’t changed in the least, still remaining a jade-like translucent color. There were even some bones that shined like a rainbow. Obviously, this was related to the cultivation method that the deceased had practiced before their death.

“There is also a spatial ring…”

Lin Ming discovered that there was a hand bone with a spatial ring on it. With a wave of his hand, the spatial ring flew up from underground. However, as he investigated it with his soul force, he shook his head in disappointment. The mini dimension inside of the spatial ring had already collapsed upon itself.

This sort of man-made world was originally unstable. Normally, the world inside a low-grade earth-step spatial ring would last for several thousand years before disintegrating.

It wasn’t just the spatial ring, but many treasures had decayed. Those treasures that could be buried in the earth for tens of thousands of years and remain pristine and everlasting were quite special. Lin Ming walked for a quarter of an hour but still hadn’t discovered one.

“Mm? That seems to be…” Mu Qianyu’s mind stirred. As she looked several hundred feet in the distance, there were actually exotic looking flowers there.

In this vast blood wilderness, this bunch of flowers was very unexpected.

“Blood Ghost Flower? I didn’t think that something like that would appear here…” A Blood Ghost Flower was a sort of spiritual flower that loved to grow in lands that were filled with dark and bloody influences and had gone through great periods of carnage. Only under those circumstances would they be able to nurture themselves and germinate, slowly growing. Normally it would take millennia to flower, and that was why it was extremely rare within the Sky Spill Continent, and to think that there would be such a large bunch of them here.

However, the ruins of this ancient battlefield had already been rich with bloody and demonic influences. Not just that, but no one had appeared here for tens of thousands of years. It wasn’t strange for such a large batch of these flowers to be born here.

“These Blood Ghost Flowers will be of great help to Little Flame’s evolution! This is really a lucky chance!” Mu Qianyu was delighted. As she went forwards to pick them up, she suddenly stopped in her steps and frowned. She could clearly feel the energy of a few people hidden in the vicinity of the Blood Ghost Flowers. They gave of a faint murderous aura like a tiger that was crouching in the brush.

This energy belonged to a human. It was most likely one of those ‘companions’ that had just been in their group, and was also a Revolving Core powerhouse.

“They want to use the Blood Ghost Flower as bait and kill us to rob our possessions?” Mu Qianyu sneered.

Chapter 478 – Escape Symbol

Floating above them, this old man had sword-like eyebrows that slanted outward, and he wore a purple robe embroidered with seven stars! Around his body, countless arcs of electricity flashed, sending out faint ‘chi chi chi’ sounds. This was the intense shaking of thunder origin energy.

This person was the Sovereign of the Thundercrest Sect, Lei Jingtian!

“He’s flying in the air!”

Mu Qingyi’s complexion changed. After they had entered this broken world, they hadn’t gone far before they had lost the ability to fly and were forced to descend to the ground. But this Lei Jingtian in front of them had actually maintained the ability to fly.

This was just how formidable a late Revolving Core realm master was.

Beginning from Revolving Core, the gap between every small jump in boundaries was enormous. Passing ranks to fight someone at a higher cultivation was extremely difficult. Even Saint level talents like Mu Bingyun and Mu Qianyu would only be able to jump two small boundaries to fight after they reached the Revolving Core realm.

To them, a late Revolving Core martial artist was an invincible existence.

“When did you come in!?” Mu Qingyi clearly remembered that Lei Jingtian hadn’t been among those present when they had entered into the broken world.

“Hehe, this old man’s status is now a bit sensitive. That old fool Xuan Wuji has already blamed Lei Mubai’s death on me. Naturally, I wasn’t able to openly appear. After every large sect entered into the ancient battlefield, there were still several hundred disciples left over and they were all over the place. It wasn’t too hard for me to hide among them!” Lei Jingtian proudly said with a smirk.

“What do you want?” Mu Qingyi asked as she went on alert. She wasn’t naïve enough to think that someone like Lei Jingtian just came over to greet them.

“Hehe, what do you think?” Lei Jingtian’s lips curved in a smile, and suddenly the power of thunder in his body erupted. A vast purple net of lightning fell over everyone!

The purple lightning grid was several hundred feet wide and was extremely fast; it was like a dream.

Mu Qingyi hadn’t thought that Lei Jingtian would suddenly attack.

“Break for me!” Mu Qingyi drew her longsword and slashed out at that purple electric net.

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank and he instantly took out the Purple Comet spear from his spatial ring, thrusting towards that flashing purple net. At that same time, the Mu sisters, the Seventh Elder, and newly recovered Ninth Elder also attacked.

Chi chi chi!

Six different true essences slashed open the purple net of electricity. However, after this electric net was cut apart, it didn’t fade away. Instead, it turned into countless small arcs of lightning that rained down on everyone.

Electric light flashed, falling onto the bodies of over 20 lower order disciples. After they were struck by this power of thunder, their eyes instantly glazed over with countless scenes. Some early Xiantian martial artists weren’t able to bear this sort of crazy imagery and softly plopped onto the ground.

This was followed by the middle Xiantian martial artists, late Xiantian martial artists…

In just several breaths of time, besides the six martial artists that had strength equal to a Revolving Core master, the remaining 20-some disciples had all fallen unconscious on the ground.

Mu Qingyi’s complexion was completely dark. What Lei Jingtian had just used was a soul attack. She had already heard that Lei Jingtian had a very unique sort of Thunder Soul, named the Disenchanting Dream Light.

In legends, The Disenchanting Dream Light was a Thunder Soul that was bred within the body of an ancient thunder-attribute sea beast. Its natural ability was to destroy the soul. With Lei Jingtian’s late Revolving Core cultivation, it was simple for him to cause 20 some Xiantian martial artists to lose consciousness.

Mu Qingyi tightly gripped her sword, her forehead becoming damp with sweat. If they really battled here, their situation would be extremely bad. Lin Ming had already eaten a Scarlet Blood Pill, and it was impossible for him to take another in such a short period of time.

If someone had to use a Scarlet Blood Pill, it would have to be herself, Mu Qianyu, or Mu Bingyun.

The younger one was, the stronger their life force was. If they ate a Scarlet Blood Pill, the side effects they would experience afterwards would be smaller. If someone several hundreds of years old like Mu Qingyi ate a Scarlet Blood Pill, her situation would be perilous afterwards. Her cultivation would drop, and there was the chance she might even lose her life!

Not just that, but the Scarlet Blood Pill’s effects weren’t heaven defying. Lin Ming was a singular exception. If Mu Qingyi ate the Scarlet Blood Pill, her strength would only barely touch the middle Revolving Core realm. It was difficult to say whether or not she could deal with Lei Jingtian at that point.

“Just what do you want?”

“Hehe, I was asked by others to eliminate their troubles.” As Lei Jingtian spoke, his eyes moved until they came to Lin Ming, shining with interest.

Seeing Lei Jingtian’s vision on him, Lin Ming sneered inwardly; this old man had really come for him?

Mu Qianyu’s heart went cold and she subconsciously kept Lin Ming behind her. In this critical moment, Lin Ming wasn’t in his top condition. If they really fought with Lei Jingtian, then their side would be at a great disadvantage.

As Mu Qingyi looked at Lei Jingtian, she seemed unsure.

Asked by others?

The first ones she thought of were Mu Chihuo and Mu Yanzhuo.

Were they insane? Their hate had reached the point that they no longer cared about their cultivation or bloodline? Not to mention that they weren’t sworn enemies or anything like that. Even if they killed Lin Ming, just what would they be able to do? If they openly betrayed the sect, they would suffer the fatal criminal punishments of Divine Phoenix Island. Was this worth it?

No matter how she thought about it, Mu Qingyi couldn’t figure how any way that they could evade the punishment of the bloodstain contract.

“So that’s how it is.” Lin Ming’s face held a touch of irony. His hands turned, swapping out the Purple Comet Spear for the Great Desolate Blood Halberd. “I really am your common enemy. The enemy of an enemy is a friend. Mu Chihuo had already plotted with you long ago. You made the weaker disciples faint but didn’t harm them, this was probably at the behest of Mu Chihuo. It seems like he does have some scruples after all; he doesn’t dare to openly slaughter so many others. Our current position was also given to you by Mu Chihuo, right, Thunder Sovereign?”

Mu Chihuo was originally the leader of the Divine Phoenix Island forces. It wasn’t strange for him to have some sort of location method.

Lin Ming didn’t have the mindset of Mu Qingyi that no one would be able to defy the bloodstain contract, and thus no Elder would be able to rebel. Lin Ming had never placed any faith in this bloodstain contract. Thus, he was able to simply and clearly see things for what they were.

At this moment, bawdy laughter came from afar. In the distant ruins, two old men and one young man strolled out; the one in front was Mu Chihuo.

At this time, Mu Chihuo had a victorious expression. Behind him, Mu Yanzhuo appeared a bit grim and restless. As for Mu Qingshu, he looked extremely pleased with himself, as if he were already imagining the way that Lin Ming would die.

“Haha, boy, well said. It is exactly this old man that wants to take your life! As long as I live, all the other disciples and future disciples will submit to me. Naturally I will not harm them!”

“Oh? So you seem to have some way to break the bloodstain contract?” As Lin Ming watched Mu Chihuo’s confident expression, he didn’t know just what his plan was in the end. Even if he could break the bloodstain contract and smoothly kill him without problems, what would he be able to do? Mu Fengxian would never forgive them for this.

The only method was if he killed everyone here, silencing every witness to this crime.

However, if Mu Chihuo would kill so many outstanding talents of Divine Phoenix Island just because of some hatred, then it could only be said that he had lost all rationale and had descended into madness.

“Mu Chihuo! Are you crazy!? You want to rebel against the sect!?” Mu Qingyi’s heart burned with anger. Her eyes blazed as she glared at Mu Chihuo, wishing she could cut him to bits and pieces.

“Rebel against the sect? No, of course not!” Mu Chihuo shook his head, “This old man’s bloodline lies within Divine Phoenix Island, so why would this old man rebel against the sect? No, I only wish to take back those things that belong to me!”

“What belongs to you?”

“Power! Status! Authority! Cultivation methods!” As Mu Chihuo spoke to here, his eyes flashed with thick hatred. He had been excluded from the eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’; how could he not hate!

“Mu Qingyi, I only wish for Lin Ming to die and do not want to harm you. If you step back, I will let you leave here.”

“Dream on!” Mu Qingyi flourished her longsword, her eyes decisive.

“Humph! It looks as if you no longer care about your life!” Mu Chihuo’s eyes turned to the others, “And you? Do you wish to die too?”

There was no need to mention the Mu sisters’ decision. As for the Seventh Elder and the Ninth Elder, they did not respond. They only took out longswords from their spatial rings and quietly stood in front of Lin Ming. Their intent was already obvious.

If this was the battle from before against the South Sea Demon Region, then perhaps they would waver in their decision. However, during that battle, Lin Ming had eaten a Scarlet Blood Pill and had fought a bloody battle with courage in order to turn the tide.

On the other hand, Mu Chihuo and Mu Yanzhuo had run away at a crucial moment. Then, a few days later, they had actually looked for Lei Jingtian to deal with them. If they surrendered to the enemy and betrayed their morals here, they might as well not be human.

“Hehe, well then, I have nothing else to say. I don’t want to hurt you, but swords are blind.” Mu Chihuo took out his longsword. If it were possible, he had hoped that Lei Jingtian would have been able to use his Disenchanting Dream Light to force them into unconsciousness, but unfortunately they were too strong. The only path left now was a battle.

Mu Qingshu savagely smiled, “Lin Ming, this time you will die. Lei Jingtian, Great Elder, and my grandfather are also here. With the three of them together, I wonder just how your ragtag group of useless trash will be able to stop them! Lin Ming, rest assured that I will not kill you. I will cripple your martial artists and have you suffer a life worse than death. I will take care of Senior-apprentice Sister Mu for you, and have you watch with wide eyes as I play with her.” Mu Qingshu spoke in a true essence sound transmission so only Lin Ming could hear.

Although Lin Ming had always thought of Mu Qingshu as an idiot, he was right about one thing. There was no way that his group would be able to stop the combined effort of Lei Jingtian and Mu Chihuo.

Not to mention that Lin Ming could not eat a Scarlet Blood Pill, but even if he did eat a Scarlet Blood Pill while simultaneously opening the Heretical God Force and burning the blood of the Ancient Phoenix, he would still be suppressed by Lei Jingtian. Not just that, but he would only be able to last around 30 breaths of time. No matter what he did, he would lose!

That was just Lei Jingtian. With Mu Chihuo and Mu Yanzhuo tacked on, there was absolutely no chance of victory.

Lin Ming’s expression was solemn. If this was so, there was only one way…

His hand moved, and a plain ancient jade talisman appeared in his palm. Lin Ming lightly moved his lips, sending a true essence sound transmission to Mu Qianyu, “Has Master Ancestor given you an Escape Symbol?”

“Escape Symbol? What’s that?” Mu Qianyu was stunned.

As Lin Ming heard Mu Qianyu’s surprised words, his heart suddenly sank.

When Lin Ming had first gone to the South Sea battlefield, Mu Fengxian had given Lin Ming three pills, and also a silk bag. The three pills were two Yang Reversion Pills and a single Scarlet Blood Pill. But in the silk bag was an Escape Symbol. After it was used, it would teleport the user several hundred miles away. This extremely precious talisman was discovered by Mu Fengxian in some ancient ruins. It was no exaggeration to say that this talisman was another life.

Lin Ming had thought that Mu Qianyu and Mu Bingyun might have their own. But he didn’t think that he would be the only one.

This was bad… Lin Ming’s palms oozed with sweat as he held the jade talisman in his hands. He did not dare to leave Mu Qianyu here while escaping on his own…

Chapter 483 – White Light

The Divine Demon Thunder Soul scattered into pieces. But a blackened scorch mark was left behind on the hell dog’s claws; this was the result of the power of thunder.

After all, countless years had passed since the Demon Emperor’s soul was torn apart. The power of the Demon Emperor’s remnant consciousness was extremely weak.

The hell dog glanced at its claws and growled, baring its fangs; this was the same anger as being bitten by an ant.

“Roar!”

The hell dog howled and rushed straight towards Lin Ming! It vowed to tear apart this little bug that had caused it pain!

At this time, Lin Ming’s vision was blurred as he had an agonizing headache as countless chaotic images entered into mind. He bit down on his own tongue to force himself awake from this aching pain. As he saw the blood-colored eyes of the hell dog closing in on him, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a savage color.

He grit his teeth and thrust out his hand. The Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder and Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder that had scattered into the air suddenly converged onto his hand, forming a purple and red spear of thunder. The torn pieces of the Samsara martial intent turned into countless tatters that swirled around the spear.

Between Lin Ming’s eyes, the flame mark ignited in dazzling brilliance. Behind Lin Ming, the twin phantoms of an Azure Dragon and Ancient Phoenix appeared. In that instant, Lin Ming had overdrawn his complete will and soul into this life or death attack!

As the hell dog rushed towards him, it brought billowing waves of bloody wind. Lin Ming shouted out, his feet bearing down on the void. His hands gripped the purple and red thunder spear and pierced towards the jaws of the hell dog!

Kacha!

Under this great pressure, the spear of thunder broke apart!

However, the broken thunder spear was like a thorn in the hell dog, piercing through its upper jaw and towards its brain!

“Awoo!”

The hell dog howled, falling to the ground. On top of its head, the wound from the thunder spear made ‘chi chi chi’ sounds as it burned its flesh, almost etching a big hole.

“%@#!”

The hell dog spat out a line of unknown language. Its eyes were blood red as it lifted its two front paws and tried to grab the broken thunder spear in its jaws; it wanted to pull it out!

Even this didn’t kill it…

Lin Ming ruefully smiled. His ears and nostrils were already bleeding out, and after overdrawing his soul, he no longer had the strength to resist again. He fell to his knees and his surroundings began to blur, and all sound completely disappeared as if the world was fading away from him.

In his dim vision, he saw the sphere of light in the center of the void begin to emit a white mist. Then, Lin Ming completely lost consciousness.

Countless visions crossed Lin Ming’s mind, and his thoughts first returned to his childhood. His parents, Lin Xiaodong, Lan Yunyue, Qin Xingxuan… he vividly recalled these people one at a time, as if he was once again experiencing the trial of 100 Samsaras. Then, Lin Ming felt as if he was bathed in a pleasantly war sunlight, just like a baby in its mother’s womb… he was incomparably peaceful and relaxed.

As his blurry vision began to slowly clear, Lin Ming opened his eyes and found that he was still in his spiritual sea. But, the sort of aching tiredness in his mind had already disappeared. As for the hell dog, it was still howling pitifully, but this time, it seemed to be very crestfallen, its entire body torn to pieces.

This is….

Lin Ming was shocked. He didn’t think that his spear of thunder would have this effect. As he recalled that misty white light from a moment ago, he suddenly realized something.

Lin Ming withdrew his consciousness from his spiritual sea and looked over to the center of the Magic Cube space. There, the one foot wide sphere of light was quietly floating, surrounded by countless soul fragments that endlessly rotated around it…

It was this!?

Lin Ming carefully released his senses, feeling the space around the sphere of light. He was able to feel a faint white light that was warm and comforting. If he wasn’t wrong, then this sphere of light was what had released the white mist.

This sphere of light was like the spirit of the Magic Cube, and the Magic Cube seemed to have a will of its own because of this sphere of light. Ever since he had obtained the Magic Cube, Lin Ming had never had any communication with it. But Lin Ming was certain that the Magic Cube was intelligent and had a will of its own.

As for that white sphere of light, Lin Ming always had a guess.

All of the surrounding soul fragments that drifted around this sphere of light were from the Realm of the Gods powerhouses. Their souls were torn to pieces by the Magic Cube and sent into this space. Then, the Saintess that had controlled the Magic Cube also had her soul twisted into the Magic Cube. Could her soul be at this center point of the space?

Lin Ming tried to communicate by sending out his sense, but whenever anything touched the sphere of light, it would sink in and disappear.

Lin Ming finally gave up. At this time, he felt his mind stir and he returned to his spiritual sea. To his amazement and dismay, he found that the hell dog that had been torn to pieces was trying to reattach itself!

“So stubborn!”

Lin Ming was startled. This remnant soul fragment from a Realm of the Gods Supreme Elder was just a tiny fraction that had gone through countless years of weakening, and yet it was still terrifying to this extent. If it was the complete consciousness of a Supreme Elder, then he couldn’t imagine what sort of horror it would be. It probably wouldn’t fade away even without hundreds of thousands of years of being sealed away!

But the Magic Cube, in just an instant, had twisted apart the souls of thousands of Realm of the Gods powerhouses… just what sort of earth-shaking existence was that…

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath. The stronger he became, the more he understood just how great the gap was between him and these Realm of the Gods powerhouses.

As he looked at those wiggling pieces that were trying to crawl towards each other, Lin Ming coldly snorted. The hell dog wanted to fuse into one whole again; how could Lin Ming allow it to do that?

He waved his hands, and the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder appeared in his left and the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder appeared in his right. Thunder flashed, and the purple and red thunders turned into bolts of thick lightning that fell onto the hell dog like a shower of deadly rain!

The power of thunder was the best at suppressing the strength of spirits. The hell dog that was trying to fuse back into a whole again was blown apart by Lin Ming, its soul sizzling.

Right after, Lin Ming used the Samsara martial intent. A black vortex crashed onto the fragments of the hell dog’s will, sending out ‘ka ka ka’ sounds like bits of metal that had been dropped into a meat grinder. However, no matter what Lin Ming did, these remnant pieces of consciousness refused to be annihilated!

“It’s really tough.”

Lin Ming didn’t think he could finish off these pieces of remnant consciousness. The difference in their levels was really just too great.

And ridding himself of this consciousness was the same as giving up on the soul fragment he had absorbed. Naturally, Lin Ming was reluctant to do this.

‘I’ll have to individually seal away these pieces of consciousness. As long as they don’t re-fuse together, they won’t be able to affect me.’ After thinking it over, Lin Ming chose this risky path. When he became stronger in the future, he would be able to slowly wear away these fragments.

Lin Ming thrust out his hands, the purple-red power of thunder tightly wrapping around him like gloves. Then, Lin Ming began to carefully separate the pieces of consciousness from the black vortex. His fingers moved, surrounding the pieces of consciousness with threads formed from the power of thunder.

After these threads turned into a thick cocoon around the remnant consciousness, completely isolating it from the rest, Lin Ming tossed it into his spiritual sea.

Like this, Lin Ming slowly wrapped every other pieces with the power of thunder, and submerged them in different areas of his spiritual sea. This was so that one day, if Lin Ming’s spirit was ever weakened for some reason, these pieces of will wouldn’t have a chance to take advantage of him.

“Finally done…”

Lin Ming let out a long breath and withdrew his mind from the Magic Cube space. At this time, he was incomparably tired, and just wanted to have a good rest without caring for anything else.

But, time was urgent. Lin Ming wasn’t sure how many hours had passed. He sat in meditation for a moment to catch himself, and then endured the headaches as he looked through the memories of the Demon Emperor’s soul fragment…

…………..

At this time, since Lin Ming had escaped, it had already been four hours.

Lei Jingtian and the rest of them had been engaging in a full on onslaught against the illusionary killing array until their hands were tired. But the protective barrier of the array formation was like an unshakeable mountain; there was just no response!

In this situation, Lei Jingtian was already feeling a despair like the world was collapsing. A late Revolving Core master, a middle Revolving Core master, and two early Revolving Core masters had joined together to ceaselessly attack for four hours and yet there was still no effect. This little array formation from a sixth-grade sect was already comparable to a great protective land array from a fourth-grade sect.

“This damn law suppression.” Even the normally calm Mu Chihuo was angry, and he suddenly stopped his attacks. Mu Chihuo wavered on his feet. His true essence was in chaos, his body was shaky, and he could barely stand.

All of this fell into Mu Qingyi’s eyes. Mu Qingyi sneered and said, “Mu Chihuo, this suffering is what you have reaped. The bloodstain contract within you is already beginning to take effect. Within a month, 30% of your Divine Phoenix bloodline will fade away. Half a year from now, it will completely vanish, and your life force will exhaust itself and you will perish!”

“My Divine Phoenix bloodline?” Mu Chihuo smiled with disdain before laughing out, “The so-called Divine Phoenix bloodline is nothing more than the thin bloodline of the Vermillion Bird, losing it is nothing pitiful. As long as I can kill Lin Ming, I will be obtain to obtain the true Divine Phoenix blood in his body!”

As Mu Chihuo spoke, Mu Qingyi was shocked, her heart immediately shaking! She finally understood just why Mu Chihuo would risk everything in order to kill Lin Ming.

Ever since Lin Ming had emerged from the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, his body had been emitting an aura that made her heart palpitate. Between Lin Ming’s eyebrows, there was also a faint and peculiar flame mark. During the battle with the South Sea Demon Region, that flame mark had ignited. In that moment, Mu Qingyi was able to clearly feel a deep fear that originated from the depths of her bloodline!

If she was right, then it was highly likely that Lin Ming had obtained a very rich and pure bloodline within the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm. This bloodline far surpassed what the Divine Phoenix Island Founder had received when she entered the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm.

And Mu Chihuo’s goal was Lin Ming’s bloodline.

The bloodstain contract only had the power to bind the descendants of the Mu Family Clan based on their bloodline, it wasn’t able to restrict Lin Ming. As long as Mu Chihuo was able to obtain Lin Ming’s bloodline, then he would naturally be able to free himself from the restrictions of the bloodstain contract. As for losing the Mu bloodline, if it was lost then it was lost – he simply didn’t care about it.

Mu Qingyi realized she had been wrong from the beginning. The reason that Mu Chihuo had tried to kill Lin Ming was not for revenge, but rather to obtain a higher power. If he could steal Lin Ming’s bloodline and also snatch away the first eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’, then all he had to do was wait for Mu Fengxian’s life to eventually end of old age. At that time, he would be able to rule the entire Divine Phoenix Island with his strength!

Perhaps Mu Chihuo might have had this all planned out before he came into this broken world!

Thinking of this, Mu Qingyi felt a sense of despair.

If she had to blame someone, she could only blame herself for thinking that the restrictions of the bloodstain contract were infallible.

Chapter 492 – Cosmic Melting Furnace

“What’s going on!?”

All those old fellows reached out with their perception, but were unable to detect anything.

From the sound a moment ago, whatever had happened had only occurred only two or three miles away. Even though their senses were suppressed in this world, they were still able to clearly investigate this distance. But they actually didn’t sense anything. This was extremely unusual to these old Life Destruction fellows.

“Let’s go take a look!”

All of the old fellows instantly set out. Xuan Wuji also stood. Compared to everyone he else, he seemed much calmer and unaffected. He coolly patted the dirt from his clothes and also headed over.

The two to three mile distance was crossed in the blink of an eye. As they reached the site of cry, everyone was amazed to find that at the edge of the medicine garden was a giant cave.

The cave was located underneath a common looking hill. As everyone approached this cave, bursts of roiling heat waves billowed over them, forming a sharp contrast with the extreme cold that was coming from the Demon  Emperor’s medicine garden.

As the cold and heat mingled together, even though everyone present were masters, it still made them feel uncomfortable.

“This cave is able to shield against perception.” A South Sea Demon Region martial artist said. If it weren’t so, then they would have already discovered this cave.

“Mm? This is….”

As the Black Flood Dragon Clan Patriarch walked into the cave, he suddenly shook after seeing the scene inside.

The space inside the cave was enormous. It had a radius of hundreds of feet, and in the center of the space was a giant 30 foot pill furnace. This pill furnace was surrounded by eight flaming red columns,and these fiery columns had statues of Horned Dragons carved into them. The eight Horned Dragons aimed their wide maws at the pill furnace. Waves of red tinted energy breathed out from the statues, enveloping the pill furnace and creating an image like a rising dawn.

The 30 foot high pill furnace was about equal to the height of four men standing on top of each other. This was the first time that Lin Ming had ever seen such a massive pill furnace. On the surface of the pill furnace, there were many intricate designs and reliefs carved into it. Among these was a chart of the heavens and earth, with a red Golden Crow design in the center.

The reliefs on pill furnace seemed rough, but if one looked carefully, they could sense an ancient, boundless aura, a savage and primal energy that rushed out. The things that were carved into this furnace were not images, but rather true worlds!

A top treasure!

All of the old fellows present were knowledgeable individuals. With just a look, they were able to determine that this giant pill furnace was an incredible treasure!

It was very possible that this was an extremely valuable treasure to the Demon Emperor!

They were unable to distinguish just what rank of pill furnace this was, and that was because they hadn’t come into contact with such a high ranking treasure before. But, they could tell that even if this furnace were placed within the entire Sky Spill Continent, it would absolutely be a top treasure!

“Cosmic Melting Furnace… it’s really here.” As Xuan Yuqie saw this pill furnace, she sent a faint true essence sound transmission to Xuan Wuji.

“Mm… unfortunately, we cannot even obtain the Nirvana Dragon Root right now, much less this Cosmic Melting Furnace. If we could obtain the Cosmic Melting Furnace, then the Nirvana Dragon Root wouldn’t be too important…”

“Haha! This was the first divine furnace of the Sky Spill Continent. It’s impossible for us to seize something like this. But, there might be a slim chance for us to take some of the treasures inside.

In the end, the Cosmic Melting Furnace was a pill furnace, but it was also considered a fire-attribute treasure.

A treasure on that level naturally wouldn’t be considered as valuable as a heavenly material like the Nirvana Dragon Root.

However, the precious value of the Cosmic Melting Furnace didn’t lie solely in it being a furnace, but rather the treasures and pills that were contained inside. The Demon Emperor’s letter hadn’t specified just what sort of treasures were within, but without a doubt they were extremely valuable.

Casually taking any one of these out would start a bloody battle within the Sky Spill Continent.

However, if one wanted to obtain the Cosmic Melting Furnace, they had to pass the surrounding Eight Dragon Jade Light Array that protected it. The Demon Emperor’s letter had given no clue on how to bypass this array formation.

The Demon Emperor’s medicine garden array formation was only able to defend. If one couldn’t break it, then the worst that would happen was that the Nirvana Dragon Root would remain unreachable.

But, this Eight Dragon Jade Light Array that surrounded the Cosmic Melting Furnace was actually a true killing array!

A single mistake meant death!

“Mm… this is…” As the Black Flood Dragon Clan Patriarch saw the ashes on the ground, a foreboding feeling rose within him. He quickly turned to glance at the clansmen behind him, and his heart sank as he counted them. A moment ago, because of that scream, all of the martial artists had ran over to this cave. But his Black Flood Dragon Clan was actually missing the Seventh Elder.

Without a mistake, these ashes on the ground were those of the Black Flood Dragon Clan’s Seventh Elder…

“Old Seven…” The Black Flood Dragon Clan Patriarch felt a stinging pain in his heart, and finally sighed. He took out a jade box and with a wave of his hand, collected the ashes with his true essence, completely receiving them into the jade box and then placing it back into his spatial ring.

In an instant, a first stage Life Destruction powerhouse had perished. In the Realm of the Gods, the existence of a Life Destruction powerhouse was simply nothing at all.

Lin Ming shook his head. The pursuits of fortune often led to death. This Old Seven from the Black Flood Dragon Clan was undoubtedly the first one to discover the Cosmic Melting Furnace. At that time, his thoughts must have been that he could take this furnace by himself, and keep it as his own.

A first stage Life Destruction master must have experienced many things to reach that stage, so how could they not have known of the dangers surrounding this Cosmic Melting Furnace? However, they had been blinded by greed. Even though they knew it was dangerous, they still decided to take the risk. The result of this was that they were now nothing more than ashes on the ground.

As for the other Life Destruction powerhouses, they all looked at the Cosmic Melting Furnace and pondered, lost in thought. After seeing the fate of someone else, they were even more cautious.

Lin Ming stood within the crowd, sifting through the incomplete memories.

The second Demon Emperor soul fragment had very few memories of the Cosmic Melting Furnace. He was only able to faintly remember that there was a highly valuable furnace within the Demon God Imperial Palace. As for where this furnace was or how valuable it was, he could not remember.

Lin Ming had some vague memories of this Eight Dragon Jade Light Array, but relying on just these blurry memories to break through the array would not be easy.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but glance outside of the cave. At this time, he was surprised to see that there was not a single person left over in the Demon Emperor’s medicine garden; everyone had gathered at the Cosmic Melting Furnace. Lin Ming immediately had an impulsive idea to open the array formation within the Demon Emperor’s medicine garden, but as he thought about it some more, he pushed down the idea. The ancient array formation in the medicine garden was simply too close. Also, the commotion from opening the array formation wouldn’t be small. There was no way he could conceal this from these old Life Destruction fellows.

Lin Ming constantly thought of many possibilities, but ultimately had to reject them all.

At this time, a South Sea Demon Region Elder put out a zombie guard. He pointed towards the Cosmic Melting Furnace and said to the zombie guard, “Go!”

The straight zombie guard’s eyes flashed with a red light, and it walked over to the Cosmic Melting Furnace without fear of death. The closer it was to the pill furnace, the higher the temperature was. When the zombie guard was around 100 feet away, it was like being in the furnace itself. Billowing waves of heat smashed into the zombie guard, creating ‘chi chi chi’ sounds.

As the zombie guard reached 50 feet away, it was just about to step onto the platform where the eight coiling dragon columns were. At this time, a flaming red light shot out, striking the zombie guard. There was only a crackling sound as the zombie guard was sent flying backwards, instantly turning into ashes!

With this, everyone was able to understand just how the Black Flood Dragon Clan Elder had died.

“Hehe.”

A Life Destruction Elder from a smaller sect laughed with self-deprecation. He turned around and walked away. This Eight Dragon Jade Light Array was even more terrifying than the ancient array formation that protected the Nirvana Dragon Root. He was quite aware of just how capable he was. In any case, this pill furnace had nothing to do with the likes of him. He had no reason to join in on the fun. If he was struck by a shockwave of that red light and was killed, then that would really be an injustice.

As this Life Destruction Elder left, many other Elders from small sects hesitated for a moment, and then began to quietly draw back.

They went back to the river edge to search for more medicinal herbs. Although nearly every herb had been plucked after several sweeping passes, it was still better than nothing. If they could find one, it wouldn’t be as valuable. But, their sect’s wealth was not comparable to that of a fifth-grade sect, and even far off from Divine Phoenix Island. They naturally had to be prudent in this.

As the Elders from several small sects left, Nanyun Wang and Abbot Whitebrow remained nearby the Cosmic Melting Furnace. Obviously, they had some designs on this treasure.

Nanyun Wang couldn’t help but glance at Xuan Wuji.

Xuan Wuji’s eyes were closed, a ‘do as you wish’ air coming from him.

Nanyun Wang couldn’t hold it in. “Old thief Xuan, you never told me that you knew this was here before.”

Xuan Wuji opened his eyes and slowly said, “This old man naturally knew that this was here. But, this old man is also aware of his own strength. Nanyun, let me advise you for free. If you don’t want to die, then don’t bother to have any ideas on this Cosmic Melting Furnace! A greedy snake might eat himself to death. Even if an Emperor level powerhouse came here, they still wouldn’t be able to move this stove!”

It was rare for Xuan Wuji to speak the honest truth. He certainly didn’t care for whatever happened to Nanyun Wang. However, he also needed him and Abbot Whitebrow to assist him in breaking open the defensive barrier. If Nanyun Wang died here, then he feared it really would take 100 years to open up the ancient array formation in the medicine garden.

“So this furnace is called the Cosmic Melting Furnace.” Nanyun Wang licked his lips, his eyes flashing with a touch of greed and unwillingness to give up. Although he understood that what Xuan Wuji said was mostly true, there weren’t many people in this world that could remain unmoved after seeing such a precious treasure placed in front of them.

After an incense stick of time, another old Life Destruction fellow put out another puppet and used it to cautiously approach the Cosmic Melting Furnace. The result was that this second puppet was also burnt to ashes.

With these two tests, everyone discovered a rule of the Eight Dragon Jade Light Array. As long as one didn’t step onto the platform where they were, then they would not be attacked by that red light.

At this time, Abbot Whitebrow suddenly moved. He put away his staff, took off his cassock, and then slowly walked over to the Cosmic Melting Furnace.

As everyone saw this, their eyes widened. Even though the situation had already been clearly spelled out in front of them. Abbot Whitebrow had still decided to try. He must have some method to rely on.

Xuan Wuji was even more on guard. Both his eyes were unblinking, as his hands that were at his back were now loosely hanging down, his expression filled with doubt and alert.

Chapter 493 – Terrifying Red Light

Xuan Wuji certainly wanted to obtain the Cosmic Melting Furnace. However, the Demon Emperor’s letter hadn’t contained any records of the Eight Dragon Jade Light Array that surrounded the Cosmic Melting Furnace. Xuan Wuji’s only choice was to suppress the rising greed in his heart. Originally, he had thought of using this Cosmic Melting Furnace to pit everyone against each other, but now that he wasn’t even able to break through the barrier that guarded the Nirvana Dragon Root, he had to give up on that line of thinking.

However, as he saw Abbot Whitebrow move towards the Cosmic Melting Furnace, Xuan Wuji began to stand alert.

If no one could obtain the Cosmic Melting Furnace, then there was nothing else to say. But if Abbot Whitebrow had a method to open the Cosmic Melting Furnace and a treasure appeared, he would snatch it there and then. Whatever treasure it was, it would be no worse than the Nirvana Dragon Root!

Abbot Whitebrow slowly walked. After every step, he would take a full ten breaths of time before taking the next one. At the same time, he revolved his true essence to the limit. A blazing halo of golden light surrounded him, filled with faint Buddhist seals that circled around. This was a secret Buddhist technique – Diamond Vajra Body.

The Buddhist martial arts focused on tenacity and extreme defense. But, they were relatively weak in attacks. This time, Abbot Whitebrow was displaying the mighty defensive techniques of the Buddhist martial arts to the limit.

But could such a defense even have the possibility of resisting that piercing red light?

This question filled everyone’s mind. In the past, the Elders of the Demon God Imperial Palace were Emperor level powerhouses. So, this Eight Dragon Jade Light Array should be able to injure Emperor level powerhouses too.

However, tens of thousands of years had passed. The Eight Dragon Jade Light Array’s power must have weakened by a considerably great amount. Because of this, this sort of reddish dawn light shouldn’t be as terrifying.

Abbot Whitebrow arrived just a small distance away from the platform that contained the coiling dragon columns. If he took another step forwards, he would activate the attack of the Eight Dragon Jade Light Array.

Abbot Whitebrow closed his eyes, feeling the flow of energy throughout the array formation. A brief moment later, he suddenly opened his eyes, his palms shooting forwards.

“Bright Buddha Palm Seal!”

With a loud explosion, a massive golden Buddha phantom appeared behind Abbot Whitebrow. That massive Buddha moved its hand, a giant palm stretching towards the Cosmic Melting Furnace!

Bright Buddha Palm Seal! This was a top ability of the Great Zen Temple’s highest holy technique, ‘Great Zen Mantra’. It was difficult to learn and difficult to control, but those who did would wield a great power. The giant hand that formed was said to be able to churn the sea, shake the earth, control the heavens, and even pluck out the stars and moon from the sky.

‘This old bald donkey is really a sly snake!’ Xuan Wuji cursed. Obviously, Abbot Whitebrow had discovered that he wouldn’t activate the array formation as long as he didn’t step on the platform with the coiling jade platforms. Then, as long as he didn’t step foot on the platform and instead used his secret Buddhist technique to grab the object from a distance, there wouldn’t be a problem!

‘If this old bald monkey has cultivated the Bright Buddha Palm Seal to Perfection, then he really might be able to move the Cosmic Melting Furnace!’

Xuan Wuji’s complexion changed. If Whitebrow wasn’t able to take the treasure, then it wouldn’t matter. But if he did, just what should he do?

He hadn’t even obtained the Nirvana Dragon Root yet. If there was a falling out in the alliance here, then that was equal to giving up on the Nirvana Dragon Root. But if Whitebrow obtained the treasure, then that also wasn’t good. It was unknown whether or not he could obtain the Nirvana Dragon Root, but this treasure would already be in hand.

If it was a heavenly material, then there was no need to mention its value. It would not be any less rare or precious than the Nirvana Dragon Root.

If it was an offensive or defensive treasure, then even though its value would be lower, it would still be able to greatly increase one’s strength in the short run. In the near future, it would give Whitebrow an enormous advantage in competing for the Nirvana Dragon Root.

Although Xuan Wuji was a meticulously careful and prudent person, he couldn’t think of a foolproof countermeasure in such a complex situation.

At this time, that giant golden Buddha palm phantom had already hit the Cosmic Melting Furnace. Although Abbot Whitebrow hadn’t cultivated the Bright Buddha Palm Seal to Perfection, he could still easily crush a mountain peak from 10,000 feet away!

And Abbot Whitebrow was only 40 to 50 feet away from the Cosmic Melting Furnace. The power of using the Bright Buddha Palm Seal at such a close distance could be imagined! If it wasn’t the Cosmic Melting Furnace but rather a normal earth-step pill furnace, then this attack from Abbot Whitebrow could twist it into bits!

The great golden palm wrapped around the Cosmic Melting Furnace, trying to raise it up. Abbot Whitebrow wanted to grab the entire furnace!

“Humph! Dream on!”

Xuan Wuji sneered. This old bald monk donkey was far too greedy. Did he really think the Cosmic Melting Furnace was something that was his for the taking? He even wanted to grab the entire thing. This old man was really greedier than a snake.

Sure enough, as the great palm wrapped around the Cosmic Melting Furnace, the furnace was entirely still. Instead, Abbot Whitebrow’s face flushed red. Obviously, he was making a great effort.

Abbot Whitebrow frowned and then moved the palm to the next best thing. He grasped towards the Cosmic Melting Furnace’s lid!

The Cosmic Melting Furnace had three feet and two handles. The lid was round and also engraved with a Golden Crow image. As Abbot Whitebrow grabbed it, there was a loud smashing sound like a morning bell being struck. The incomparably heavy lid actually began to shake!

Although it was only an extremely slight vibration, it was enough to change the complexion of everyone present!

It shook!

Prior to this, all of the Supreme Elders from nearby had used their most powerful moves in an attempt to break through the ancient array formation that defended the Nirvana Dragon Roots. But, they weren’t able to make even a tiny bit of progress. This had caused an idea to be planted in everyone’s hearts that nothing in the Demon God Imperial Palace could be touched!

But now, Abbot Whitebrow had actually caused the lid of the Cosmic Melting Furnace to move; it filled everyone with hope.

As Abbot Whitebrow saw this, a light flashed in his eyes. He revolved the ‘Great Zen Mantra’ to the extreme, his bones emitting popping sounds!

“Rise for me!”

Abbot Whitebrow gave a loud shout, and blue veins stuck out from his forehead. The golden Buddha palm seemed to manifest into reality at that moment, firmly grasping the lid of the Cosmic Melting Furnace and pulling up!

Angg!

In the moment that the lid shook, the Cosmic Melting Furnace suddenly issued a sound like a dragon roaring. It was a resonant cry that pierced into the heavens, a rumbling thunder that echoing throughout the world. A massive wave of pressure fell down on everyone. All of the Life Destruction Supreme Elders were forced back by this pressure, their hearts filling with fear and horror!

In that split second, they were able to feel a vast, primal, wild energy rush out from the Cosmic Melting Furnace. It was as if the Cosmic Melting Furnace contained a vast world, and that lid was only the door to this endless world where limitless, infinite mysteries were sealed.

The moment that the lid shook, two shining lights of red and blue shot out, followed by another dragon’s roar. These two fist-sized red and blue lights swirled in the air.

“Mm? What is that!?”

As everyone saw these red and blue lights, they were on alert, their eyes fixated on these objects. The red light seemed like a thick red liquid, no different from blood.

For this object to remain in the Cosmic Melting Furnace for tens of thousands of years and for the blood to not dry out, the value of it could be imagined!

As for that blue light, it wrapped around a blue-hued pill. Waves of icy cold energy emanated from the pill. It was hard to imagine that such a freezing cold object could exist within the blazing heat of the furnace.

This is…

Several Life Destruction Elders with sharp senses instantly realized what this ancient icy cold energy was. This energy of from tens of thousands of years past was 80 to 90% similar to the Nirvana Dragon Root!

Was it possible that this blue pill was a medicine refined with a Nirvana Dragon Root!?

The Nirvana Dragon Root was already a heaven-defying treasure. If more heavenly materials were added in and further refined into a pill, just what sort of effect could it have?

Could it completely wash one’s marrows, or even cause one to directly pass through stages of Life Destruction?

If this was so, then it wouldn’t be hard at all to cultivate for another few hundred years and become an Emperor level powerhouse!

As everyone realized this, their thoughts became hot and fiery. If the Nirvana Dragon Root was a treasure they dreamed of, then this Cosmic Melting Furnace was enough to make then go crazy and lose all rational reasoning!

Several Life Destruction Elders couldn’t help but move forwards several steps. But on the Great Zen Temple’s side, a big-headed monk suddenly jumped out, his entire body crackling with popping sounds. A great golden Buddha phantom also emerged from behind him, only much blurrier than the one that Abbot Whitebrow formed.

“Senior-apprentice Brother, I will help you!”

The big-headed monk’s expression flashed with a crazy greed. His palms were flat as he shot them out, and a massive golden palm reached towards the two red and blue lights!

But at this moment, something changed!

Atop the platform, the eight coiling dragon columns trembled, and then a deluge of red lights came shooting out!

Sou sou sou!

The red dawn light shot out at a speed that was hard to fathom. Abbot Whitebrow’s complexion immediately changed and he hastily drew back. At the same time, his palm came slamming downwards. The Bright Buddha Palm Seal struck the red lights, but in that instant, those red lights instantly penetrated the Bright Buddha Palm Seal that was at a realm near Perfection!

“Ahhh!”

Abbot Whitebrow burst into a roar, his body contorting, twisting at an unbelievable angle in the air. The red light finally sizzled past Abbot Whitebrow’s right chest. His secret Buddhist technique, Diamond Vajra Body, instantly exploded. Abbot Whitebrow’s right chest was charred black!

However, other people didn’t have the cultivation that Abbot Whitebrow did; they were completely helpless against this rapid red light. There was simply nothing they could do!

As for that big-headed monk that helped Abbot Whitebrow to take the treasures, the red light directly pierced through his head!

With a light flashing sound, the big-headed monk’s upper body instantly turned to ash. All that was left over were two fat legs that were stuck into the ground like radishes.

But several rays of red light still shot out. Two of them randomly swept towards the Life Destruction powerhouses closest to the Cosmic Melting Furnace. Without any delay, the people weren’t even able to cry out before they were directly burnt to ashes!

In the blink of an eye, four Life Destruction powerhouses violently died. As for the third stage Life Destruction Abbot Whitebrow, whose defensive power far surpassed everyone present, he was also severely wounded!

Bang!

Abbot Whitebrow smashed into the ground. His right side had been scorched black, and his face was white, sweat streaming down it.

With trembling hands, he took a pill from his spatial ring and swallowed it. Finally, some color returned to his face.

As everyone saw this, they fell into complete silence, a cold sweat dripping down their backs.

A moment ago, if they had also subconsciously drawn a few steps closer because of their greed, then they too would have suffered a similar fate!

This was far too horrendous!

Chapter 501 – The Great Escape

“No! This father just lost everything! I only have a soul body and I can’t even use anything in the Cosmic Melting Furnace besides the blood of the Giant Demon!” The pug muttered to himself with an extremely unhappy expression.

At this time, Lin Ming couldn’t even be bothered about this. From the time that those old Life Destruction fellows rushed away until now, it had almost been an entire incense stick of time. He had to leave as soon as possible.

However, just running away like this wasn’t good. If others suspected that Lin Ming was the culprit, then even if he managed to successfully run away, he would still bring a great calamity upon Divine Phoenix Island…

Lin Ming quickly reactivated the eight coiling dragon columns of the Eight Dragon Jade Light Array.

After several breaths of time, the eight horned dragons began to emit a sparkling dawn light again, and the Eight Dragon Jade Dawn Array was once again active.

Then, Lin Ming took out a corpse from his spatial ring. This corpse was that of the South Sea Demon Region Revolving Core Elder that he had killed. Afterwards, when Lin Ming had opened the Magic Cube again, it was with the blood essence of this Revolving Core Elder.

Lin Ming took off one of his own spatial rings and slipped it onto the Revolving Core Elder’s finger. Then, he stepped back four or five steps and casually tossed the corpse towards the Eight Dragon Jade Light Array.

Chi!

The burning dawn light flashed once, and the corpse was directly struck, instantly turning to ashes!

Thus, besides the two piles of ashes from those old Life Destruction masters, there was a third pile of ash. As for Lin Ming’s charred-black spatial ring, that was also mixed within the ashes.

The pug glanced over at Lin Ming with some surprise, “Boy, you’re quite the clever one. If you do this then you really might have the good luck to muddle your way away.”

As the pug thought of all those old Life Destruction fellows and what a great price they must have paid to come here, and yet the true greatest treasure here was pocketed by this boy while they didn’t even know just what had happened and who had done it…

Thinking of this, the pug subconsciously traced its own stubby nose. If he really stayed with this body then one day he might be the one to fall in the ditch…

As the pug was lost in his thoughts, he found that Lin Ming had already moved towards the cave entrance.

“Hey, wait up! Wait for this Saint!” The pug barked out before hurrying along.

According to the memories of the Demon Emperor, on the other side of the Demon Emperor’s medicine garden, there was another transmission array not too far away. If he went through this transmission array, he would be able to directly leave the Demon God Imperial Palace.

If Lin Ming was outside, he would be able to cross the distance to the transmission array in just several breaths of time.

But, he had to be much more cautious within the Demon God Imperial Palace.

“Hey, are there any traps or spells here?” Lin Ming asked the pug, abruptly swallowing the word ‘pug’ before it came out.

“This Saint is not called ‘hey’! This Saint’s true body is that of a holy three-headed demon dog! My title was Saint Lord Demonshine! I reached the Saint Lord realm 100,000 years ago and roamed the endless void, crossing everywhere! At that time, your grandfather hadn’t even been born yet!”

As the pug said this, he proudly raised his head, as if he had found a point of pride.

Although this story didn’t seem too reliable, Lin Ming was aware that this pug truly was skilled as he boasted, otherwise he wouldn’t have had the qualifications to be embroiled in the fight for the Magic Cube.

“Saint Lord? What’s that?”

“Just like your Sky Spill Continent has so-called Emperor powerhouses, a Saint Lord is also the title given to powerhouses of a certain boundary. In the past, this father was also a Saint Lord!”

“Didn’t you just say you were a holy three-headed demon dog? How come you only have one head now?” After leaving the Demon Emperor’s medicine garden, Lin Ming was much more relaxed. He had obtained the Cosmic Melting Furnace and Nirvana Dragon Root; he was in an excellent mood.

As he mentioned this, the pug deflated like a sad rubber ball, all of his previous bravado erased. “If it wasn’t for that horrifying woman destroying this Saint’s Large Success diamond form divine body, sucking my divine soul into the Divine Crystal Magic Cube and sealing it away for countless years, then how could I end up like this? This Saint’s mind was once a trinity, but now this Saint’s mind is singular and incomplete; how could I possibly maintain my original state?”

As the pug spoke, he entire face was flushed red with anger.

“So that’s what happened. By the way… were you the Demon Emperor’s soul pet?” Lin Ming nonchalantly asked.

“What do you mean ‘soul pet’, that is such a rude term! This Saint was the Demon Emperor’s contract soul beast. Humph, if it wasn’t for the Demon Emperor tricking me in the past, then how would this Saint sign a contract with him? If he didn’t have this Saint, the Demon Emperor would have already died countless times within the Realm of the Gods!” The pug grunted. But, it had inadvertently revealed that it didn’t have an equal relationship with the Demon Emperor in the past. It seemed that they once had a master and servant contract.

“Demonshine, does this path have any danger?”

“Humph, the Demon God Imperial Palace is so big, and this Saint only stopped by here for a very short time, so how would I be so aware of any of this!”

Hearing the pug’s capricious words, Lin Ming was speechless. All he could do at this moment was open his perception and sense as far away as possible.

However, unexpectedly the two to three mile distance was very calm. As they made their way, nothing happened. Lin Ming followed the directions in his memory, and finally arrived at a low hanging stone platform. This platform didn’t have any dangerous spells on it. After he walked up the platform, it became clear it an ancient transmission array. The transmission array was fully intact and could be started at any time.

As Lin Ming saw this, he was immediately filled with happiness.

Lin Ming only needed several breaths of time to decipher the symbol order to start the ancient transmission array. After he reconfigured the symbols, a hazy white light flashed out. Lin Ming stepped into the heart of the array, and his form quickly faded away…

………

After a quarter hour – Demon Emperor’s medicine garden…

Within the empty Demon Emperor’s medicine garden, several old men stood by where the Nirvana Dragon Root had once been, their expressions grim.

The ugliest one was Xuan Wuji! In the fight against Abbot Whitebrow and Nanyun Wang a moment ago, he had shown his low-grade heaven-step treasure and had even used countless accumulated aces from the 3000 year long history of the Silent Demon Emperor City. Yet, he had been constantly forced to retreat by Abbot Whitebrow and Nanyun Wang.

It had to be known that the legacy of the Great Zen Temple was only slightly less compared to that of the perished Silent Demon Emperor City. As for Nanyun Wang, although he was a loner, he still had a talent that surpassed the will of the heavens. In terms of individual strength, he was the strongest of the three.

Originally, even if Xuan Wuji lost in the outside world, he would still be able to calmly escape.

But since he was sealed within the Demon God Imperial Palace, he had nowhere he could run. Not just that, but the Demon God Imperial Palace was filled with countless dangers. If he randomly fled in any direction then that would be no different from committing suicide!

Finally, if it wasn’t for Xuan Wuji taking out the God Extinguishing Thunder Pearl that the Netherworld Great Emperor had left behind from long ago and also used the combustion of his blood essence as a threat, he really would have been killed by Abbot Whitebrow and Nanyun Wang!

The truth was that even if Xuan Wuji was pushed to the brink of desperation and used every last card in his hand, he would most likely die here. But, it was only that Abbot Whitebrow and Nanyun Wang would also pay a steep price. This caused them to feel a faint fear and also to hold back their hand.

In the end, Xuan Wuji was forced to hand over the main stem of the Nirvana Dragon Root, and all he was left with was two thick root hairs.

And thus, they had come to a truce.

Xuan Wuji felt like his heart was bleeding.

He had always felt as if something was just a bit off. That is, he had spent so much effort to open up the ancient array formation and yet it remained close, so why would it suddenly open on its own?

If someone had told him that one of those array masters had accidently opened it by chance, then that was too far-fetched a story!

Once the transmission array that he had inspected before had suddenly malfunctioned in a key moment, Xuan Wuji had a strong premonition that he had been tricked by someone!

However, Abbot Whitebrow and Nanyun Wang had attacked him without giving him a chance to explain, wanting to take advantage of him during this time period and finish him off; he simply didn’t have time to think about this.

But now that he came back to the Demon Emperor’s medicine garden, the truth was finally revealed. Xuan Wuji felt like his lungs were about to burst from rage!

Luring the tiger from the cave… with such a simple strategy, he had been forced to give up another Nirvana Dragon Root!

If Xuan Wuji felt that his lungs were about to explode after seeing that the second Nirvana Dragon Root was missing, then after he arrived at the cave and saw that that the Cosmic Melting Furnace had vanished from the platform even as the Eight Dragon Jade Light Array was still active, he only felt an immense dizziness, almost falling to the ground!

Abbot Whitebrow and Nanyun Wang also paled. They had originally been counting on obtaining the treasures within the Cosmic Melting Furnace, but now they had lost everything. Even the furnace itself had been taken away!

“Who!? Who was the one that did this!?” Xuan Wuji’s eyes were bloodshot as a dark light shined as an ominous light shined in his eyes. “Who was still left over in the Demon Emperor’s medicine garden? Who!?”

Xuan Wuji‘s glare was ruthless as his eyes swept over everyone. Mu Fengxian shrank back, but she didn’t reveal any difference in expression.

However, as Xuan Wuji saw Mu Fengxian, he was also reminded of Lin Ming. He took a hard step forwards and the full aura of a third stage Life Destruction powerhouse swept out, immediately suppressing Mu Fengxian. “Lin Ming! Where did that boy go off to! He didn’t leave the medicine garden!”

“I do not know!”

Mu Fengxian stoically replied. But, her thoughts were actually extremely confused; just where did Lin Ming go? What had happened to him?

Was it possible that others had ransacked the Demon Emperor’s medicine garden and Lin Ming had encountered an accident?

It wasn’t just Mu Fengxian that thought so, Mu Yuhuang’s heart was also filled with an extremely disturbing premonition that made her feel restless and incomparably panicked.

“Xuan Wuji! A thief like you shouldn’t be crying ‘stop thief’!” Nanyun Wang coldly snorted. His eyes shined as he glared at Xuan Wuji, “I do not believe that a little late Houtian baby boy would be able to break the Cosmic Melting Furnace’s killing array and also steal it away. Don’t you think it’s rather ridiculous to push this all onto him!?”

“Nanyun, are you saying you suspect that this old man was the one who took the Cosmic Melting Furnace?”

“Hehe, didn’t you say it yourself? Since you are the only one that has seen the Demon Emperor’s letter, you also know how to up the ancient array formation and also the method to take the Cosmic Melting Furnace! A quarter hour ago, you completely drew all of us out from the Demon Emperor’s medicine garden. If you weren’t the one responsible for stealing away the second Nirvana Dragon Root and the Cosmic Melting Furnace, then just who is!?” Nanyun Wang stepped forwards, his eyes shining.

“Nanyun! You…” Xuan Wuji was angry to the point that he wanted to vomit blood. The second Nirvana Dragon Root had been stolen and even the Cosmic Melting Furnace was missing. He had labored for ten hard years, paying an immeasurably steep price and effort, and finally all he ended up with was two root hairs.

Not just that, but he had been tricked by someone and had taken the blame for everything! If such an unlucky mattered happened, it would cause anyone to seethe with rage!

Chapter 505 – In the Rain

This cold and salty rain was from the waters of the South Sea. It was sucked into this broken world by the space storms and then turned into countless sprays of mist. After it condensed in the skies, it formed dark and thick clouds. These clouds had already gathered for over 10 days, and they were waiting to spill over. Now, they blotted out the sky as they formed curtains of overwhelming rain, hard enough that it was even difficult to open one’s eyes.

In just several breaths of time, the water was already deep enough to reach the ankles. As the rain scattered throughout the bloody wilderness, it fell onto the stone tablets, washing over them and causing the crimson symbols to glow even brighter.

Mu Qianyu’s entire body was soaked. In this cold and unforgiving shower of rain, her bright and clean dress was now stained with dirt.

She didn’t know how long she had stayed in this position. For the last six days, she hadn’t slept, eaten a grain of rice, or drank a drop of water.

In that moment when she had been enveloped in the white light of the Escape Symbol, his facial features lingered in her mind, haunting her.

She had never missed someone with such an insane intensity. If it was possible, she was willing to give up all of her cultivation to see him again.

However, the slim hope she held in her heart became increasingly endangered. It had been so long… if he was fine, then why hadn’t he come to the bloody wilderness to find her?

Only now when she had lost something dear to her did she feel this unforgettable pain.

Mu Qianyu had lost her parents as a child. Growing up, she had followed her master. Besides her master, Mu Yuhuang, Lin Ming had undoubtedly occupied the most important position in her heart.

Maybe… this was what people called love.

Mu Qianyu reflected on herself. If she could just live a plain and ordinary life with Lin Ming, then even as a mortal it would be a warm and happy life…

The rain fell in this vast world until it overflowed to the knees. Then, Mu Qianyu suddenly heard the faint sound of water parting behind her, as if someone were wading through.

Mu Qianyu suddenly woke from her stupor. She turned back in shock to see, in that endless curtain of rain, a blurry figure stepping over the water towards her.

Mu Qianyu’s breath caught in her throat. In the misty weather and with the laws of this world that suppressed perception, it was impossible to tell just who this other person was. But even so, as Mu Qianyu saw this figure, her body stiffened and tears began to roll down from her eyes.

She did not need to guess, she did not need her eyes to see, nor did she need her perception to sense this figure. A deep and throbbing feeling in her heart was all that Mu Qianyu needed to recognize this person. This faint figure, was exactly the person that she had been dreaming of for the last six days…

“Lin Ming!”

Mu Qianyu forgot everything. In that moment, she was no longer the lofty and proud Saintess, nor was she an extreme Xiantian master. At this moment, she was just a girl. A simple girl who was affected by thoughts towards her lover.

In this pouring rain, she desperately rushed into Lin Ming’s embrace.

Her white arms were like white lotus roots that clung to Lin Ming’s back, as if she wanted to melt into him…

“I’m back.”

Lin Ming bent over and softly spoke in Mu Qianyu’s ear.

“I know… I know…” Mu Qianyu buried herself in Lin Ming’s chest, unable to stop the tears from falling.

In this incomparably icy torrent of rain, Lin Ming could clearly feel warmth in his chest.

As the pair tightly hugged each other, in this world – besides the heavy rain – there was not a single sound. It was as if this curtain of rain isolated everything from the world, and all that was left were their hearts, closely nestled together.

After an unknown period of time, the two of them began to slowly separate. At that moment, a loud ‘kacha’ split the air, and a crimson bolt of lightning cut through the skies, as if a god in the heavens was casting down spells.

This lightning was completely reflected in Lin Ming’s eyes. In the bright flash of light, one could see a deep and thick murderous intent flowing forth.

At this moment, Mu Qianyu’s heart stirred as she saw Lin Ming’s eyes. She never knew that the world was so dark before. Lin Ming’s eyes were as bright as the stars; they were dazzling enough to illuminate this world.

Lin Ming closed his eyes, and then opened them once more. As the lightning dissipated, his murderous intent also receded back into his body. He said in an extremely calm tone, “Let’s go. Come with me… to kill.”

These simple words contained a dominating confidence and arrogance as if he was able to hold life and death in his hands. They caused Mu Qianyu’s heart to stir.

She discovered that in these last six days, Lin Ming’s cultivation had actually broken through to the Xiantian realm!

Not just that, but Lin Ming’s body seemed to emanate a mysterious and powerful aura. Even though she couldn’t recognize just what it meant, it was enough to make her heartbeat quicken!

“Lin Ming, you…”

“I went to the Demon God Imperial Palace and obtained the Nirvana Dragon Root.” Lin Ming didn’t plan on hiding anything from Mu Qianyu. He couldn’t, wouldn’t, nor was there any need to.

“What!?” Mu Qianyu was shocked. The Nirvana Dragon Root? Heavens! Wasn’t that a miracle medicine that those Life Destruction Supreme Elders were competing over? How could it possibly have ended up in Lin Ming’s hands?

“It’s a long story. I can’t really explain it, but this is for you…” Lin Ming took out a rectangular jade box from his spatial ring. After opening the jade box, one could see a dry root within, as if it were an exquisite wild ginseng that had been dried.

“This is…” Mu Qianyu found this unbelievable. This root was exactly like the Nirvana Dragon Root listed out in the ancient manual that the Revolving Core master from the South Sea Demon Region had. It was very similar to the drawing, except that it was much drier and more withered-looking.

Lin Ming said, “This is the Nirvana Dragon Root. I boiled it to make medicine, and 80 to 90% of the medicinal efficacy is gone. What’s left over is 10 to 20%, but it is still far superior to those broken root hairs from the Nirvana Dragon Root!”

The main stem of the Nirvana Dragon Root accounted for 70% of its essence energy. As for the nine root hairs, that was only 30%. The Nirvana Dragon Root inherently contained a very rich and pure essence energy. Once it was broken or damaged, a massive amount of this essence energy would dissipate. A root hair was originally only a tiny portion of the Nirvana Dragon Root. If it were also broken off and the essence energy dissipated, then it truth there wasn’t much left. At least, it would be far, far inferior to this complete withered Nirvana Dragon Root that Lin Ming had boiled once to make medicine.

“If Master Ancestor Fengxian wishes to break through into the second stage of Life Destruction, she can boil this Nirvana Dragon Root to make medicine, or she can even directly consume it.” Lin Ming pressed the Nirvana Dragon Root into Mu Qianyu’s hand. This Nirvana Dragon Root was meant for Mu Fengxian. And when Mu Qianyu finally came to a point that she too needed to use a Nirvana Dragon Root, Lin Ming has absolute confidence that he would be able to refine a far superior Tempering Marrow medicine for Mu Qianyu.

Lin Ming pulled Mu Qianyu’s hand into his, “Come with me. Let us bring an end to all of this!”

………….

At this time, 100 miles away, at the ruins of the inner court disciple housing of the Demon God Imperial Palace…

The torrential downpour had already begun to slowly stop. Although the clouds hadn’t cleared yet, faint rays of light now shined through.

Above the illusionary killing array platform, Lei Jingtian saw that it was completely empty, and his face filled with a terribly grim expression!

With Lei Jingtian’s initial late Revolving Core strength, even if he combined forces with Mu Chihuo, Mu Yanzhuo, and everyone else here, they still wouldn’t compare to half of a Life Destruction Supreme Elder.

Originally, the 30 some Life Destruction old masters had gathered together at the Demon God Imperial Palace. They had spent a great deal of strength, and even with Xuan Wuji’s secret technique they were barely able to break through the defensive barrier of the palace.

Although the array formation of this temple was far weaker than the array formation of the palace, it still couldn’t be broken so easily.

Lei Jingtian had joined forces with Mu Chihuo and Mu Yanzhuo, and had continuously attacked this array for the last six days. Still, they had failed to break through this illusionary killing array every time.

But now, the heavy rain had turned the tables in their favor.

The power of thunder from this rainstorm was actually not suppressed by the laws of this world. Lei Jingtian had used his own ability to control thunder, and with another array formation, he was able to make enough preparations to direct the heavenly thunder to strike down at the illusionary killing array, becoming the final strike needed to shatter it.

But when the illusionary killing array had been broken, Lei Jingtian and Mu Chihuo saw that it was completely empty; there was not even a single shadow left over!

Mu Qingyi let out a long breath of relief as she saw this. Lin Ming had finally managed to escape. It was good. Otherwise, she would have spent the rest of her life blaming herself, unable to repent for her sins.

“That bastard!” Lei Jingtian wanted to vomit blood. As for Mu Yanzhuo and Mu Qingshu, they felt as if they were about to faint. They were unsteady on their feet as they almost fell over. Even the usually placid Mu Chihuo found himself unable to maintain his calm, his heart racing in panic.

All of his plans were based upon the precedent that he would be able to smoothly kill Lin Ming. If he couldn’t kill Lin Ming and obtain his Divine Phoenix bloodline, then within half a year, the bloodstain contract would cause him to lose all of his martial arts cultivation, and he would become a cripple!

At that time, what point was there in obtaining the first eight layers of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ or becoming the Island Master of Divine Phoenix Island. There was simply no meaning to any of that!

“Brother Chihuo… what… what should we do?” Mu Yanzhuo’s voice trembled. This was not a laughing matter. It was possible that Mu Fengxian would soon emerge from the Demon God Imperial Palace. If they were unable to kill Lin Ming before that old woman came back, then they would absolutely lose everything they had!

Although he had already prepared for the worst before he made this desperate gamble, now that he finally arrived at this step, he was unable to accept the reality of the situation.

“Stop panicking!” Mu Chihuo coldly said. However, there was a cold sweat dripping down his forehead. “Calm down. As long as we can find him within the next few days, it’s not too late…”

Mu Chihuo grit his teeth as he spoke. As he turned around he saw Mu Qingyi’s sneering face, and a fire suddenly blazed in his heart.

“You dead old woman!”

Ca!

Mu Chihuo’s sword violently thrust forwards. The blade was like a striking snake, stabbing towards Mu Qingyi’s throat.

As Mu Qingyi saw this, she coldly snorted and remained unmoved. She didn’t even blink her eyes, only waiting for this sword to pierce her.

From the beginning, Mu Qingyi had never been afraid of death.

“You damn old woman, you really want to die? It won’t be that easy!” Mu Chihuo’s sword stopped only an inch away from Mu Qingyi’s throat.

At this time, killing Mu Qingyi was useless. First, he had to find Lin Ming.

Mu Chihuo’s expression changed countless times. Finally, a plan formed in his heart, and he cruelly smiled.

If he couldn’t find Lin Ming, then he would use whatever ways possible to force him to come out.

Chapter 509 – Disenchanting Dream Light

Lin Ming took off Lei Jingtian’s spatial ring and then flicked a fireball at the corpse, turning it into ashes. Like this, a fierce and ambitious Sect Master of his generation, a late Revolving Core powerhouse, perished in a breeze of floating ashes.

Lei Jingtian… had died!

All of the Divine Phoenix disciples fell into utter silence. A harrowing fight had concluded in an equally harrowing manner. Lin Ming’s entire body was soaked in blood, and Lei Jingtian didn’t even have a single bone remaining. In just two breaths of time, a late Revolving Core Supreme Elder was forced into a dead end by Lin Ming, and was finally abruptly and brutally killed!

Mu Qingyi let out cold breath, and even Mu Bingyun’s expression was complex. Killing and defeating someone were two entirely different concepts. Even if Lin Ming had borrowed the power of this world’s laws in order to do so, it was still an incredible feat.

In time, if Lin Ming were given space to grow, it was unimaginable just what realm he would be able to reach.

In the time that Lei Jingtian turned into ashes, Mu Yanzhuo felt a tilting dizziness, and his vision almost went black, almost falling to the ground. As for Mu Qingshu, he felt as if the sky had collapsed atop of him. He looked at Lin Ming in the distance and his lips paled, a chill crawling up his entire body.

From the beginning of their betrayal, they no longer had any way to return to how things once were. As for the bloodstain contract in their bodies, it was a guillotine that constantly hung over their heads.

“Let’s go!”

Mu Chihuo’s voice suddenly resounded in Mu Yanzhuo and Mu Qingshu’s ears.

Go? Go where?

Mu Yanzhuo stared off in the distance, as if he hadn’t heard a single word.

“Useless!” Mu Chihuo was also seeped in a cold sweat at this moment. He had originally planned for the three of them to escape in different directions. If it were like this, then he might have a chance to escape. But looking at Mu Yanzhuo’s current listless expression, if he tried to run away by himself, then Lin Ming would most likely use that strange space locking martial skill on him. Thinking about this, Mu Chihuo felt a cold chill sneak up his spine.

The bloodstain contract only gave him half a year. Could he find a backer in this short period of time and kill Lin Ming?

“You two idiots!” Mu Chihuo’s expression was fierce, “This is our last chance to escape. If you want to wait to be capture and for all your skills to be crippled and be sentenced to death and die, then this old man will not follow you along!”

Mu Chihuo’s words were like a bolt of thunder that sounded in Mu Qingshu’s ears. Mu Qingshu grabbed onto that final straw of hope, “Senior Master Mu, please save me. What can we do? I don’t want to die!”

“If you don’t want to die then burn your blood essence and run away with me. This is our only chance!”

A cold wind blew, scattering Lei Jingtian’s ashes in the air.

Zi zi zi!

A faint lightning light flashed in the ashes. A purple ball of light suddenly flew out from the ashes, flying straight up into the sky!

As soon as Lin Ming saw this, he coldly snorted and thrust out his hand. A purple net of thunder fell down from the sky, covering the purple ball of light.

The purple ball of light violently thrashed about, but no matter what it did it could not break through the shackles of the electric net; it could only obediently stay trapped.

“This is the Disenchanting Dream Light!”

Lin Ming waved his hand and grasped the ball of light. This thunder ball was only the size of a fist. On the surface, there was a fierce face, as if it were the visage of some ancient beast.

The legends said that the Disenchanting Dream Light was a special Thunder Soul bred from ancient thunder-attribute sea beasts. 10,000 years after the thunder-attribute sea beast died, the Thunder Soul would form if there was a series of coincidences that came together. This Thunder Soul had the inborn ability to extinguish and devour souls. It could cause a human to instantly lose consciousness or turn them into idiots. With some special techniques, it could even be used to erase or search memories.

“Maybe the face on this ball of light is the so-called ancient thunder-attribute sea beast. But, I have no idea just what sort of vicious beast it could be. This Lei Jingtian must have had some great lucky chances if he was able to obtain a Thunder Soul like this.

Lin Ming was just about to draw up some symbols in order to seal away the Thunder Soul, but at this time he suddenly felt a thick murderous intent break out from Mu Chihuo’s body.

Lin Ming sneered, “You are seeking death!”

“Do it!”

Mu Chihuo cried out and grabbed his longsword. Together with Mu Yanzhuo, he dashed towards Mu Qianyu. At the same time, Mu Qingshu shot towards Zhang Zhen.

The three of them burnt their blood essence in unison!

Within the Divine Phoenix Island forces, Mu Qianyu and Zhang Zhen were the two closest to Lin Ming. Especially Mu Qianyu – she was extremely important to Lin Ming. If they could capture her, they would have a last hope of living.

“Dream on!”

Mu Qingyi stepped up, wanting to help defend Mu Qianyu, but she was forced back by Mu Yanzhuo’s sword light.

Mu Chihuo was extremely quick. He arrived in front of Mu Qianyu in an instant, his sword slashing down!

After all, Mu Chihuo was still a middle Revolving Core master who also burnt his blood essence. He was naturally much stronger than Mu Qianyu.

Seeing Mu Chihuo’s strike, Mu Qianyu didn’t miss a single beat as she stepped back and twirled the Vermillion Bird Sword in her hand, revolving the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ to its limits. Her sword pierced forth, brilliant flames shooting out.

Meanwhile, at her side, Mu Bingyun quietly appeared. The Blue Luan Sword appeared, bone-chilling ice spreading out in all directions.

Ice and fire combined, the Luan and Phoenix battled!

Peng!

True essence shockwaves ruthlessly swept out. Mu Chihuo’s strike which was backed by his combusted blood essence was actually blocked by Mu Qianyu and Mu Bingyun’s combined move. The two of them were only sent flying backwards. Although the two of them had consumed a great deal of energy, neither of them were injured.

Mu Chihuo’s heart raced with nervousness. He wanted to follow up on them, but at this moment, an icy voice sounded in his ear, “Go die!”’

Primeval Halberd Strike!

With the swirling of the Blood Drinking Seals, a powerful suction forced acted on Mu Chihuo’s body, causing his speed to immediately drop a great deal.

Mu Chihuo issued a deep roar. However, no matter how he struggled, he couldn’t break through the bindings of the Blood Drinking Seals.

Mu Chihuo’s complexion changed, “Lin Ming, wait, I have words I want to say…”

“Go speak to them in hell!” Lin Ming’s expression was cold and decisive. His halberd pierced forth. The Great Desolate Halberd seemed to pass through space, instantly appearing in front of Mu Chihuo.

“Ahhhh!” Mu Chihuo’s eyes flashed with a crazed and desperate light. With all of his strength, he cut his sword down at the Great Desolate Blood Halberd!

Kacha!

The sword energy collapsed, and the swirling waves of fire true essence were swept away by the powerful vortex. Lin Ming’s halberd thrust towards Mu Chihuo’s dantian.

At this critical moment, Mu Chihuo bit down on his tongue. True essence wrapped round his palm, and he slapped down onto the shaft of the Great Desolate Blood Halberd.

Blood flew out. In Mu Chihuo’s desperate strike, he had managed to change the trajectory of Lin Ming’s strike. It barely missed his dantian, but it still stabbed into his stomach all the same, passing straight through!

Mu Chihuo’s mouth filled with blood. Despair appeared in his eyes, “You…”

“Die!”

Lin Ming’s expression didn’t change. He twisted the Great Desolate Blood Halberd within Mu Chihuo, breaking apart all of his organs. A massive amount of blood and bits of flesh poured out.

“Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist!”

True essence gathered onto Lin Ming’s right hand, and 10,000 vibrating true essence threads burst forth. Lin Ming punched Mu Chihuo’s chest, directly causing it to cave in and shattering all of his ribs!

With Lin Ming’s punch, Mu Chihuo was sent flying back like a broken kite. He crashed into the floor, on the verge of death.

“Brother Chihuo!” As Mu Yanzhuo saw this, he was startled. His eyes glazed over, and he lost the last remnants of his courage to fight.

On the other side, Mu Qingshu also had a grim and dark expression. His heart was filled with despair. When he battled with the other juniors, in a single exchange of moves, four or five sword lights had pierced him. His clothes had been ripped apart, and he fell to the ground, covered in blood.

“Ku ku ku!” Mu Qingshu coughed out mouthfuls of blood as he propped himself up. As he looked at Lin Ming, his eyes were full of resentment and unwillingness.

“Lin Ming!” Mu Qingshu bit his lips until they bled. After reaching this point, he had lost all hope. Because of Lin Ming, he had lost everything.  He had lost Mu Qianyu, he had lost the title and status of being the number one male disciple of the Vermillion Bird Faction juniors. And even now, he would lose his cultivation and cultivation methods.

Lin Ming bent down to glance at Mu Qingshu. There was no hate in his eyes, only a sad pity. A person like Mu Qingshu didn’t have the qualifications for Lin Ming to hate him.

“You hate that I took everything from you?” Lin Ming sneered. He had already seen through all of Mu Qingshu’s thoughts. “You are weaker than others, and yet your jealousy forced you into a dead end. Truly, it is pitiful.”

Mu Qingshu didn’t speak, only glaring at Lin Ming with naked hate in his eyes as he revolved his true essence to the limit. The deep enmity in Mu Qingshu’s vision was to the point where he wished he could flay Lin Ming alive.

“You want to kill me? You won’t have the chance!” Lin Ming suddenly drew out his palm and slammed down on Mu Qingshu’s chest. A savage true essence sunk into Mu Qingshu’s body, ripping apart all of his meridians!

Pulse Cutting Palm!

Pah!

Mu Qingshu spat out an arrow of blood. All of the true essence he had gathered was cleanly scattered. He lay on the ground like a dead dog, his lips trembling and his eyes popped wide in anger.

Lin Ming didn’t give his opponent a single chance to make a comeback. Being ruthless was the safest method to rid himself of troubles in the future.

This was the profound lesson that Ouyang Boyan had taught Lin Ming.

If it wasn’t for Lin Ming’s prompt rescue, then Qin Xingxuan would have already long since perished.

“Qingshu!”

As Mu Yanzhuo saw Mu Qingshu crippled by Lin Ming’s palm, he felt a deep pain. At the very start of this gamble, he had expected that he might experience this miserable fate. But, he didn’t think that it would be sad to this degree.

“The winner is the king, and the losers are villains. I, Mu Yanzhuo, am sorry to my ancestors.” Mu Yanzhuo said with despair. Then, all of the true essence in his body exploded. There was a series of ‘peng peng peng’ sounds as clouds of blood burst out from all over his body. He had destroyed all of his own meridians and killed himself!

Mu Yanzhuo plopped face down onto the floor, rivers of blood streaming from his body.

“He’s dead.”

Mu Qingyi sighed. The traitors had all died. But, she wasn’t the least bit happy. They won this fight, but Divine Phoenix Island had suffered a great blow. A middle Revolving Core Elder and an early Revolving Core Elder had died. Not just that, but the future Revolving Core Mu Qingshu had also perished. And all of this was because of human nature. They fought because of power, and bled because of greed.

Lin Ming glanced at Mu Yanzhuo and then took out the Disenchanting Dream Light that Lei Jingtian had left behind. He drew up dozens of symbols and wrapped the Thunder Soul in layers of seals. Them, he took out a jade box and placed it inside.

As for Mu Yanzhuo’s left over possessions, Lin Ming didn’t bother with them. These were originally Divine Phoenix Island’s things. He shouldn’t take them, nor did he lack these things.

Chapter 511 – Departing

The exit of the ancient battlefield hung tens of thousands of feet in the air. This connecting path to the ancient battlefield was formed when 30 Life Destruction powerhouses joined forces to create it.

This exit way was a smooth spatial barrier a few dozen feet wide. If one couldn’t fly because of the suppressive laws that governed this broken world, then one wouldn’t even be able to leave.

At this time, tens of thousands of feet into the air, a young man was holding onto a red-clothed woman, slowly flying towards the spatial exit. The young man was naturally Lin Ming. As for the red clothed woman, that was Mu Qianyu.

After Lin Ming reached the Xiantian realm and achieved 100% Tempering Marrow, he had already surpassed Lei Jingtian with the suppressive laws of this world supporting him. Like so, he was able to fly high into the air. But as for Mu Qianyu, she didn’t have this ability; she could only fly with Lin Ming’s support.

The cool breeze slowly passed by. Neither one of them spoke to each other. Mu Qianyu only silently embraced Lin Ming’s back, as if she wanted to remember this feeling forever.

As they silently passed through the spatial exit, Lin Ming and Mu Qianyu arrived at the fragmented world that they had originally started at.

As soon as they entered this small world fragment, they immediately encountered a torrential rainstorm. This fragmented world was very small; the skies could not support too much seawater, so the rain was almost non-stop.

The rainwater was dozens of feet deep. Because of the existence of space cracks littered throughout the fragmented world, the vast expanse of water was turbulent, with whirlpools everywhere.

Lin Ming took out a charm and placed it on his body. Around Lin Ming and Mu Qianyu, a 50 foot globe of sparkling dust appeared, completely surrounding them. From a distance, they looked like a beacon of light in the rainy night.

In this small fragmented world, there were space cracks everywhere. With this sort of symbol charm, once one approached a space crack, the sparkling dust would be disturbed by the space cracks so one could discover them ahead of time.

Also, this small fragmented world no longer suppressed the ability to fly. However, Mu Qianyu seemed to have forgotten this. She held onto Lin Ming as before, quietly resting on Lin Ming’s shoulders, not saying a word.

The twisting gales swept up the deep black ocean waves. The thick bolts of lightning that cut through the sky were like blood-red halberds thrown from a war god. In this vast and endless world, there was only Lin Ming and Mu Qianyu left, the two of them tightly snuggled together.

“We’re here, this is it.” Lin Ming suddenly stopped atop the water; he had already investigated the scene below the water.

A halberd cut out. 15 Blood Drinking Seals twisted into a spiral, forcibly separating the water and creating a black channel. Lin Ming held onto Mu Qianyu and entered the water.

Below this area was a giant altar. The altar was almost 1000 feet high, and was built with dark gray rock. On the altar, there were all sorts of complex and exquisite symbols. These simple and mysterious symbols were the runes of an array formation.

“This is….” Mu Qianyu was shocked. She didn’t think there would be such a great altar hidden in this tiny fragmented world.

“This is an ancient array formation.” Lin Ming calmly said. When he had first been sucked into the space fragment at South Aurora Island, he hadn’t managed to obtain any lucky chances. But, he did manage to find this ancient transmission array.

This transmission array altar was the largest one that Lin Ming had seen until now. Around the altar, there were 108 spaces for true essence stones. This transmission array required 72 medium-grade true essence stones as well as 36 high-grade true essence stones to start.

“A transmission array?” Mu Qianyu was startled. In Divine Phoenix Island, the largest transmission array there could bring one 100,000 miles away. But, that transmission array was several dozen times smaller than this one.

In particular, this transmission array was an ancient array formation. Ever since entering the broken world, Mu Qianyu had come to a deep realization of just how powerful ancient array formations were. It was hard to imagine just how far this transmission array would be able to send someone. Could it go 10 million miles? Or even 100 million miles?

Lin Ming took out true essence stones from his spatial ring and began to place them around the transmission array. These true essence stones had to be placed in a specific order, otherwise, if there was even a single mistake the array formation would be unable to start.

“Lin Ming, you’ve really decided that there isn’t a problem with this transmission array? If you go, what happens if it sends you to someplace dangerous? Or what happens if you can’t return?” Mu Qianyu felt fear as soon as she saw this transmission array. Who knew just what lay on the other side of this transmission array? Also, what would happen if there was a mistake with the transmission array and one got lost in the turbulent flow of space?

“Senior-apprentice Sister Mu, I already studied this transmission array the last time I saw it. There shouldn’t be any problems. There was a similar array formation in the Demon God Imperial Palace that didn’t have a problem, so this one shouldn’t either. Senior-apprentice Sister Mu, If I can ask you, please take good care of my parents and take them safely away to some hiding place. Since I’m in a hurry to leave, the fewer people that see me the better. It’s impossible for me to go back and see my parents.”

Lin Ming felt a bit guilty and regretful that he wasn’t able to visit his parents before he left. Normally speaking, the trials of martial artists wouldn’t bring disasters onto their families. It wasn’t a moral issue, but rather for a martial artist the concept of family was very weak and vague. For instance, taking someone like Nanyun Wang, his parents had already died many, many years ago. But Lin Ming was different. He had just stepped onto the road of martial arts a few years ago. To him, his family was very important.

“I swear I will take good care of Uncle and Aunty.”

“There’s also another matter. Xuan Wuji had obtained the Demon Emperor’s letter. There might be other secrets of the Demon God Imperial Palace that are listed within. For instance, in the ancient battlefield, there is a catastrophic Giant Leviathan Saint Beast that is slumbering within. If I’m not wrong, then Xuan Wuji has the method to summon this Giant Leviathan…”

Lin Ming was helpless to prevent Xuan Wuji from summoning the Giant Leviathan. Although he knew the method to take control of it, his strength was lacking. Not only was he unable to summon it, he didn’t have the time to do so either.

He could only tell Mu Qianyu of this matter and hope that it would be helpful.

“Mm, I understand.”

“Alright. Then, it’s time for me to go. Within ten years, I will definitely return!” After Lin Ming made this pledge again, he flew to the center of the transmission array.

At this time, a voice spread in Lin Ming’s mind, “Boy, so this was what you were playing for…”

As soon as Lin Ming heard Demonshine’s voice, his mind stirred, “You know about this transmission array?”

“I have a slight impression of it. But, this Saint’s divine consciousness is injured, so I can’t clearly remember what this transmission array is. If I’m not mistaken, this transmission array will send you a great distance; it is an ultra-long transmission array! If you want to use this kind of transmission array, you’ll barely be able to do it!” Demonshine nodded his head as he spoke.

“Barely?” Lin Ming’s heart went cold.

“This sort of ultra-long distance transmission array will allow you to travel across space. You will inevitably encounter numerous spatial turbulences. At the speed of which you travel through that space, your body must be strong enough to withstand the squeezing intrusion of space onto you. If your cultivation is weak and you travel through this transmission array, then you’ll just end up a lump of flesh at the end.”

“That can happen too?” Lin Ming’s heart sank. It seems that this long distance transmission array wasn’t as simple as he had assumed, “Do you think my cultivation isn’t enough?”

“It’s enough!” Demonshine pinched his doggy chin with his paw as he spoke. He seemed to ponder for a moment before lifting his eyes and saying, “You have 100% Tempering Marrow and your foundation is also stable. If you go through this transmission array, you’ll be able to just survive.”

Listening to Demonshine’s words, Lin Ming sharply said, “Don’t play with me.”

“What are you saying? Of course what this Saint says will be true.”

“In ancient times, how would a lower level martial artist use a long distance transmission array?”

“It’s not like it was impossible. If you had some strong enough tool you could use it to resist the squeezing of space. For instance, the Cosmic Melting Furnace that you have right now is a relatively strong spatial resistance tool. Unfortunately, with your cultivation you cannot enter the world within the Cosmic Melting Furnace no matter how hard you try. But, you can also temporarily place your important possessions inside. If you do so, then your things will be much safer than in your inferior spatial rings once they are crushed by the space storms!”

“That can happen too?” Lin Ming let out a cold breath. For a spatial storm to be able to crush the world within a spatial ring, that proved just how terrifying it truly was.

There was no other way. Lin Ming could only take out the Cosmic Melting Furnace from within his body. The Cosmic Melting Furnace had a limited space to hold things. Lin Ming placed the Great Desolate Blood Halberd, Purple Comet Spear, as well as all his top quality pills, medium-grade and high-grade true essence stones, and also some cultivation method jade slips inside. All of this was placed within the separate world of the Cosmic Melting Furnace before Lin Ming placed the Cosmic Melting Furnace back within himself. As for the other things that weren’t as valuable, Lin Ming put them into his highest grade spatial ring.

“I have to use this transmission array even if there are dangers.” Lin Ming stimulated his protective true essence to the limit, and then decisively opened the transmission array.

In the instant that the transmission array opened, a purple beam of light fell down from the heavens, directly impacting the center of the transmission array. Lin Ming was completely enveloped by this purple light.

1000 feet away, Mu Qianyu stood in the air as the howling gales swirled around her, her features blurred by the endless purple light.

Lin Ming could see Mu Qianyu’s lips slightly move. A faint voice traveled through the horizon and entered his mind, “I’ll wait for you here… until you return…”

As the voice ended, all of it seemed to be blown away by the wind; it was unclear just what the following words were. After Lin Ming heard these final words, he had already stepped into the vast and mysterious space channel…

………….

Besides Mu Qianyu and a few others, no one else knew about Lin Ming leaving. As for the disciples that had seen Lin Ming depart, they had been given the command to not utter a single word; there were even some that were locked away.

This truth was of great importance. If it was ever leaked out, Divine Phoenix Island would be placed in a situation beyond redemption. Mu Qingyi was extremely careful, she had already learnt a lesson from Mu Chihuo. This time, she would ensure Divine Phoenix Island would keep this secret completely safe.

When the 20 some Life Destruction masters finally exited the Demon God Imperial Palace, they launched a crazy, all-encompassing search for Lin Ming, the Nirvana Dragon Root, and the Cosmic Melting Furnace. All of the large sects exercised their spy networks and connections, but their searches were fruitless. It really did seem as if Lin Ming had died.

A few years later, these greater powers would slowly forget this matter. Lin Ming was just a rare talent that fell from the sky, like a falling meteor. When people mentioned this number one talent of the South Horizon Region, there would be those that sighed as well as those that envied. There were even some that couldn’t help but gloat at this fact.

A genius that died was no longer a genius.

In the absence of Lin Ming, the South Horizon Region still remained in chaos. The South Sea war continued as it had before. Although Xuan Wuji had failed in his search for the Nirvana Dragon Root, in the end, the Giant Leviathan Saint Beast fell into his hand. With the involvement of the Black Flood Dragon Clan, the flames of war burnt through the entire South Horizon Region…

Chapter 519 – Blooming Blood

Lin Ming’s tent was located in a very obscure corner of the Silent Green Tribe. After the two Giant Demons were killed, it wasn’t immediately discovered. Lin Ming was extremely fast. In just a few breaths of time, he was able to rush to the slave registration office.

It was exactly here that the scar-faced Giant Demon who had taken Lin Ming’s spatial ring worked. With his character, how could he possibly swallow such a humiliating insult? Not to mention that the spatial ring had been a gift to him from Mu Qianyu.

Within the slave registration office, the scar-faced Giant Demon was leaning back in his chair, still unaware of anything that had happened. He was looking at the body of a female martial artist slave with lidded eyes.

This female martial artist slave looked around 24 or 25 years old and was exquisitely beautiful. Facing this fearful looking scar-faced Giant Demon, her face was wan. She was only at the late Pulse Condensation period. Compared to the scar-faced Giant Demon, her strength was lacking by far.

“You… don’t go too far!” The woman said.

“Humph! You had better be careful about what you say. I’m not afraid to tell you that in the future, you’ll be going to mine ancient Blood Demon Crystal ore with your little brother. In the mines, there are countless dangers. There are some places where you will be knocking on death’s door! I am the one who will decide your work plans. If you don’t want you and your little brother to be sent to your deaths, then you’d best be a good little girl!”

The woman’s face flushed red with humiliation. She clenched her teeth and took off her spatial ring, tossing it over to the scar-faced Giant Demon.

“That’s right.” The scar-faced Giant Demon licked his lips. In truth, he didn’t really care about the spatial ring of a mere Pulse Condensation period martial artist. He just took pleasure in the feeling of playing with others.

The scar-faced Giant Demon took the spatial ring and swept through it with his mind; it really was lacking. Nothing inside entered into the scar-faced Giant Demon’s eyes.

“There’s nothing good in here!”

The woman’s face turned a shade of blue. She bit her lips, forcing back the swelling anger in her heart. “Since you haven’t taken a liking to anything inside, give it back to me!”

“Haha, wait a little. This isn’t too bad…”

The scar-faced Giant Demon obscenely smiled. He traced the spatial ring and actually took out a pink colored bellyband. He played with it in his hands, “This is great!”

“You! You scum!” The woman couldn’t bear the anger in her heart anymore. She took out a low-grade human-step longsword and stabbed towards the scar-faced Giant Demon.

The scar-faced Giant Demon’s expression turned cold. “You really don’t care for face. Just who do you think you are!?”

The scar-faced Giant Demon reached out his hand and directly caught the woman’s long sword in his hand. He forcefully gripped down and with a ‘kakaka’ sound, the low-grade human-step treasure sword was slowly twisted like an iron bar. Then, he grinned demonically and grabbed the collar of the woman, tossing her to the ground.

“Humph! You have nothing that interests me, but, I am a little bit interested in you. If you’re smart, then follow me for a few nights. If you make me happy, then I might give you and your little brother a good job! Hehe!”

The scar-faced Giant Demon greedily stared at the woman’s beautiful and buxom body. The Giant Demon race practiced a variety of devil arts. They liked to slaughter, and they liked the obscene. Their desire towards beautiful human women even surpassed their desire towards the women of their own Giant Demon race. This was one of the reasons so many humans had been born with the Giant Demon bloodline.

The woman glared at the scar-faced Giant Demon with loathing in her eyes. She spat out a glob of blood.

Peh!

“F*ck! You don’t know what’s good for you. This father will….mm?” The scar-faced Giant Demon was just about to punish her when he suddenly stiffened. He looked up. Around 50 feet away, there was a youth looking at him with cold indifference.

“You?” The scar-faced Giant Demon had a very deep impression of Lin Ming. He wasn’t happy that his good fun had been spoiled. “What the f*ck are you here for? Get out of here!”

“I’m here to take back my spatial ring. My low-grade earth-step spatial ring…” Lin Ming slowly said. His eyes were like sharp daggers that pierced through the scar-faced Giant Demon.

As soon as the scar-faced Giant Demon heard this, his complexion changed. This boy! He clearly knew what rank his spatial ring was, but yet he had been playing the fool! A dark uneasy feeling inexplicably rose in his mind. He instantly thought to murder Lin Ming and cover his steps. The scar-faced giant Demon growled, “I don’t know what you’re talking about. I think you want to die!”

“The one dying will be you, not me. Not only am I going to take back my spatial ring, but I’ll also take a bit of interest. That interest is… your life!”

“F*ck! I will flay you alive!”

The scar-faced Giant Demon took out a long-handled axe from his spatial ring. He stepped forwards, rushing towards Lin Ming!

Facing this scar-faced Giant Demon, Lin Ming only punched out.

Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist!

His bare fist collided with the low-grade earth-step treasure axe!

The scar-faced Giant Demon grinned as his saw this. As for the girl that had fallen to the ground, she covered her mouth and cried out in alarm! She could already see the fate of Lin Ming’s fist. His hand would be split apart and smashed in half!

Peng!

Lin Ming’s solid fist struck the axe. The axe had a three foot long blade edge, and was several thousand jins heavy. However, after Lin Ming punched it, an unimaginable sight happened. There was a loud crashing noise, and the long-handled axe directly burst apart, turning into countless fragments of metal that flew out!

As for Lin Ming’s fist, it remained unchanged after breaking apart the axe. His fist impacted the scar-faced Giant Demon’s chest!

Peng!

Muscles burst. Ribs collapsed. Lin Ming’s fist penetrated through the scar-faced Giant Demon’s chest, piercing all the way through his lungs!

“You… you…” The scar-faced Giant Demon’s blue face was twisted in agony. He looked at the broken axe in his hand with disbelief. He couldn’t believe what had just happened. A single punch had broken apart his low-grade earth-step treasure… was this even the power of mankind?

Plop! Plop!

Blood trickled down Lin Ming’s elbow, dripping to the floor. It was especially loud in the near-silence. The scar-faced Giant Demon’s lips twitched. His face twisted as he tried to clutch Lin Ming’s shoulder with a trembling hand.

As he looked at Lin Ming, his expression slowly turned from shock to fear. It was as if some demon from hell had appeared before him.

“No… no…” The scar-faced Giant Demon was terrified. He could feel that Lin Ming’s hand had passed through his lung, and was now gripping onto his beating heart!

“No… don’t kill me, I was wrong… I beg you… I will give you all my belongings. I’ve hidden them away. If you kill me then you can’t obtain them…” Sweat rolled down the scar-faced Giant Demon’s forehead. His voice shook. As he spoke, blood constantly flowed down the edges of his lips.

Lin Ming sneered. His eyes and voice were merciless as he said, “I have no interest in your things.”

Peng!

Lin Ming clenched his fist. The scar-faced Giant Demon’s heart exploded in a pile of broken meat.

“Ahhhh!”

The scar-faced Giant Demon howled miserably. A massive amount of blood gushed out from his chest, spraying onto Lin Ming and completely dyeing him in a deep blood-red.

The Giant Demon fell to the floor. As for Lin Ming, he took back his hand, his expression unchanged. His hand was covered in crushed meat and blood; it was dazzlingly red.

As the woman saw this, she was stunned dizzy. What she had just seen was like a dream. This boy had destroyed an earth-step weapon unarmed, and had also used a single fist to kill the scar-faced Giant Demon! But, this youth only looked to be around 20 years old. From his appearance, he was likely younger than her!

Who was he? Why did he come here?

At this moment, the woman no longer had time to think. Outside of the tent, there was a series of loud noises and footsteps. A group of Demon Generals and Demon Soldier rank Giant Demons rushed in. “Who is causing all this trouble!?”

The head of these guards was a four star Demon General. After he rushed, he saw the scar-faced Giant Demon on the ground who had died pitifully from having his heart crushed. His anger surged. Someone had actually dared to come in here and kill the Giant Demon who managed this place!

The guard leader’s eyes were red with rage as he looked at Lin Ming. He released his perception and looked at Lin Ming’s dantian, immediately investigating his cultivation. An early Xiantian martial artist. He was surprised that an early Xiantian martial artist could instantly kill the scar-faced Giant Demon, but he didn’t think that this man had even the slightest chance of surviving any longer.

Because this guard leader could easily kill a middle Xiantian realm human martial artist.

He looked at Lin Ming as if he were watching a dead man. But once Lin Ming fell in his hands, his death wouldn’t come so easily.

“Hold him down! Slice apart his tendons but do not kill him! We must bring him back for his death sentence!”

Five one star Demon Generals rushed at Lin Ming, surrounding him. Lin Ming didn’t take out a weapon. He only reached out a hand towards the scar-faced Giant Demon’s corpse.

Peng!

The corpse exploded, and a thick cloud of bloody mist burst out, immediately condensing into a Blood Drinking Seal. With a swishing sound, the Blood Drinking Seal instantly pierced through the five Giant Demons’ bodies. These Giant Demons exploded in a cloud of blood all at once!

Blood essence filled the air, gathering into new Blood Drinking Seals!

In the blink of an eye, five Blood Drinking Seals appeared in Lin Ming’s palm. These Five Blood Drinking Seals were like beautiful flower petals that danced in his hand, slowly and silently revolving. Five Giant Demons had just died. But as for Lin Ming, he hadn’t moved a single step. It was as if the one who had killed them wasn’t him.

The guard leader was completely shocked at this startling scene. He froze up in a cold sweat. He firmly grasped the handle of his saber, but didn’t dare to make a move. He felt as if this wasn’t a youth in front of him, but rather a god of death. Fear filled the guard leader’s heart.

“You… just who… who are you?”

Lin Ming remained expressionless. The five fingers of his right hand suddenly sprung wide open!

Pu pu pu!

The Blood Drinking Seals shot off in all directions, creating a bloody tornado!

“Ahhhhh!!”

Heart-piercing screams filled the entire slave registration hall. The hall filled with blood, and thick drops of blood rained down everywhere. The several dozen foot high tent had been ripped apart by the bloody storm!

Over ten guards died on the spot. Their corpses flew out, leaving only the four star Demon General guard leader by himself. The guard leader kneeled on the ground as he grabbed his saber. Several holes had been drilled into his body. As he looked at Lin Ming, his eyes were filled with fear and despair. “You…”

Peng!

The guard leader’s body exploded, and a new Blood Drinking Seal slowly drifted up from the pool of blood…

Chapter 522 – Polaris, Blood Slaughter Steppes

“You are begging to die!”

Because of Lin Ming’s arrogant answer, the Silent Green Tribe Elders’ complexions had turned somber and bleak. “You refuse our offer only to end up suffering yourself! Let’s attack him together! Kill him!”

Facing Lin Ming, none of these six Great Elders dared to underestimate him. After all, Lin Ming was able to instantly kill Mo Da, and Mo Da was a master who was only inferior to these six Great Elders. This proved that Lin Ming might be stronger than any one of them.

“This boy’s background is too deep. Do not keep any witnesses, kill every human present!”

The six of them attacked together. Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a cold light and he extracted the Purple Comet Spear from his spatial ring. This was the first time in this melee that he had used a weapon.

These six individuals were the final trump card of the Silent Green Tribe. Lin Ming didn’t plan on holding back, he directly opened the Heretical God Force.

Compressed true essence erupted. Lin Ming’s formidable aura instantly rose to the pinnacle. He flicked his finger, and the Divine Demon Thunder Soul which was fused from three Thunder Souls shot out. On the three inch long needle, there was a Purple Flood Dragon and a crimson snake curled around the base. On the crown of the needle, there was a fierce image of a thunder beast.

The Divine Demon Steel Needle howled. It pierced towards the first Elder on the right. At the same time, dozens of Blood Drinking Seals swirled around the Purple Comet Spear, forming a spinning red storm.

“Primeval Spear!”

A spear thrust out and it seemed to swallow all sound. The powerful suction force caused all six Elders to pause. At this time, the triple Thunder Soul fusion Divine Demon Steel Needle arrived.

“Demon Essence Palm!”

An Elder struck down at the Thunder Soul with his palm. His billowing demon essence was like a rolling tide of clouds. But as these demonic clouds met the Divine Demon Thunder Soul, they instantly melted away like snow in the hot summer sun!

“Damn!”

The old Giant Demon’s face turned grim. Although he expected Lin Ming to be strong, he didn’t think that his own Demon Essence Palm would be broken so easily.

“Old Six, help me!”

Seeing the Divine Demon Thunder Soul howl towards him, the old Giant Demon couldn’t help but cry for help.

Ping!

A ghostly knife cut down on the Divine Demon Thunder Soul; this was the rescue from the Giant Demon known as Old Six. The two Great Elders combined their forces, but they were still unable to break apart the Divine Demon Thunder Soul.

“Explode!”

Lin Ming suddenly clenched his hand, and the Divine Demon Thunder Soul exploded. The three-colored light of the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder, Disenchanting Dream Light, and Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder burst out, causing the six Great Elders to struggle.

Meanwhile, he grasped the Purple Comet Spear. He thrust out – slaughter!

All of his potential and will was fused into this Purple Comet Spear strike. The spear light cut through though the void!

“This boy!”

Two Elders cried out as they resisted the arcs of lightning. With a staff and halberd, they struck out at Lin Ming.

Bang!

The ground fissured. The cracks spread through the earth like an ever-growing spider web. With the sound of torn silk, the several dozen feet high headquarters of the Silent Green Tribe, which was made with Sky Worm Silk, was completely ripped to shreds!

Blood Drinking Seals danced in the air. Two Elders screamed. Blood Drinking Seals had pierced through their bodies, causing blossoms of blood to bloom!

“Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder!”

The Divine Demon Thunder Soul roared as it felt the energy of blood essence. As soon as it touched blood essence, it completely sucked it dry. The Giant Demon Elders felt a great deal of their blood essence being absorbed and they suddenly paled.

Just several breaths of time had passed. In just the flash of an eye, Lin Ming had battled against six enemies and had taken the upper hand.

Lin Ming didn’t relent in his attacks. The Purple Come Spear shot out like a snake!

The cold spearpoint was directed towards an injured Elder’s heart. At this critical moment, a ghostly blade blocked Lin Ming’s spear, saving the injured Elder from the maw of death. But as this blade touched Lin Ming’s spear, it became stuck.

The blade-wielding Giant Demon Elder’s complexion changed. “We have to use everything we have together! Otherwise we will die!”

Lin Ming’s vast strength had far outstripped their imagination.

As the six Great Elders heard this, all of them used their special skills. For a time, the billowing demon essence was like a titanic pillar that shot into the sky. It penetrated into the clouds, as if it were connecting the heavens and earth!

The six Great Elders attacked together. Their momentum was like a heaven-breaking spear. All of the surrounding martial artists were horrified. In the Silent Green Tribe, these six Great Elders were god-like existences. The six Great Elders combining their attacks caused everyone to flee backwards, lest they be caught up in the swirling storm of demon essence!

Against this strike that could change the heavens and earth, Lin Ming’s Tempering Marrow true essence completely erupted. At the same time, he combusted the blood of the Ancient Phoenix. Lin Ming’s skeleton emitted explosive crackling noises. Behind him, the phantom of an Azure Dragon appeared. A resounding dragon roar impacted through the horizon!

A spear thrust out. On the Purple Comet Spear, thunder and flame howled, twining together at a single point. A violent energy burst out…

Thunderfire Annihilation!

Lin Ming consumed 60% of his inner true essence to display the full and complete might of Thunderfire Annihilation. This was Lin Ming’s strongest ability. Especially after absorbing the Disenchanting Dream Light, the power of Thunderfire Annihilation was even more terrifying than before. Within the ancient battlefield, he hadn’t been able to use Thunderfire Annihilation because of the suppressive laws of that broken world. But, he could use it in this one. Thunderfire Annihilation immediately formed a black hole of origin energy. All of the power of thunder and fire between the heavens and earth howled out!

Bang!

Thunder and fire wove together, exploding against the billowing clouds of demon energy. The horrible shock wave rolled out in all directions, breaking through all of the walls, causing sand to fly and completely shattering all of the floor tiles. The detonation had caused a 100 foot deep pit to appear in the ground. As for the great Sky Worm Silk tent which had been torn apart by the Blood Drinking Seals, it was disintegrated by the great currents of energy, vanishing into ash.

In just a moment, the entire Silent Green Tribe headquarters had been razed to the ground.

Of the six Giant Demon Elders, three of them were lying down in a pool of their own blood, barely hanging onto their lives. As for the other three, they had been severely injured. Their bodies dripped with blood. They stood among the ruins, their faces filled with fear and disbelief.

As for Lin Ming, his clothes were torn, his forehead was stained with blood, and his face was pale. He only had around 30% of his true essence remaining.

“You…” A Giant Demon Elder stretched out a trembling, bloody finger at Lin Ming, as if he wanted to say something.

“Die.”

Lin Ming didn’t wait for this Giant Demon Elder to spout his nonsense. The Purple Comet Spear thrust out. Blood Drinking Seals flew in the air. Slaughter!

Facing this ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’ spear skill, the severely wounded Elders were unable to resist any longer. Lin Ming’s spear directly pierced through the front Elder’s heart.

Blood spurted out into the wind. The Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder flashed as it sunk into the Giant Demon Elder’s body.

Pu!

A mass of blood fog burst out from the Elder’s corpse, slowly condensing into a Blood Drinking Seal. This Blood Drinking Seal was several times larger than the last Blood Drinking Seals, and the light that shined from it was an even deeper red.

“Third Brother!”

As a Giant Demon Elder saw his brother’s death occur right in front of him, his eyes turned red with rage.

Knowing that living through this was hopeless, the Giant Demon went crazy. He grasped his saber and cut down at Lin Ming!

To this, Lin Ming only gathered his hands together.

Pu pu pu!

Blood Drinking Seals pierced through the Giant Demon Elder like a honeycomb.

The second Giant Demon Elder died, and the Blood Drinking Seals continued their flight of death. Blood burst out from the other four Giant Demon Elders’ bodies, turning into streams of blood.

Finally, all six Giant Demon Elders had been utterly struck down by Lin Ming!

The entire area fell into silence. All of the surrounding martial artists were speechless as they stared at the blood-drenched Lin Ming. None of them knew what to say in their current states of shock.

From the very start, all of those that rose up to rebel against the Silent Green Tribe and had rushed their way to the headquarters had come with the bitter determination that their lives could be ended at any moment, like the frailest of jade. After all, the disparity of strength was just too great. But, none of them expected that as they killed their way over, over 70%of the enemy, including every Demon General at three-stars or above, would be all killed by Lin Ming. Just a single touch was all it took for them to die. And in the end, even the six Great Elders of the Silent Green Tribe had been swept away by him!

Those that followed on Lin Ming’s heels hadn’t experienced any bitterly dangerous battle. It could be said that the Silent Green Tribe was completely destroyed by Lin Ming alone!

Fresh streams of blood flowed over the ground. Corpses were everywhere. Lin Ming put out his hand, and masses of blood blossomed on the ground. One, two, three… until the sixth Blood Drinking Seal.

“This Giant Demon blood essence is truly suitable for the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’.” Lin Ming mumbled as he glanced at these Blood Drinking Seals. Their quality was nearly as good as those formed from a human middle Revolving Core powerhouse.

After Lin Ming formed these Blood Drinking Seals, he also took the spatial rings of all six Giant Demon Elders.

The six spatial rings were all low-grade earth-step. Their quality wasn’t much worse than Lin Ming’s own. As he used his sense to scan through these six spatial rings, he sucked in a deep breath. There were thousands of Blood Demon Crystals within these six spatial rings.

“These six Giant Demon Elders were quite rich. It seems that most of the accumulated wealth of the many years of the Silent Green Tribe had fallen into their hands!”

When Lin Ming had killed his way over to the headquarters, he had also taken the spatial rings of those he had slain. But, the combined wealth from all of those spatial rings couldn’t compare to a single one of the six Elders.

The use of Blood Demon Crystals to Giant Demons were like true essence stones to humans. But since the Blood Demon Crystals also contained a very strong vitality power, they were also useful for humans. A single Blood Demon Crystal was worth dozens of medium-grade true essence stones.

Besides the Blood Demon Crystals, the spatial rings also held many pills and treasures. However, Lin Ming didn’t care much for these things.

“Mm… this is…”

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. He took out a red token from a spatial ring. The token was the size of palm. It was heavy, thick, and a crimson-colored ‘kill’ word had been carved into the front. On the back, there was an engraving of an ancient Giant Demon’s head. It had curved horns and sharp teeth, making it seem hideously fierce.

As Lin Ming took the token in his hand, he could feel a faint murderous aura coming from it. This token seemed to have some sort of charm within it. Just by looking at it, one’s consciousness seemed to fall inside.

“What is this?”

Lin Ming could vaguely feel that this token wasn’t ordinary. Suddenly, he poured his true essence into the token. Then red light shined, forming a line of Giant Demon words in the air.

It read, ‘Polaris, Blood Slaughter Steppes’.

Lin Ming furrowed his eyebrows; what was this?

He subconsciously glanced at the surrounding martial artists to see if any of them knew what this was. But, almost all of them were surprised. Only Huo Yuan was steadily staring at the token in Lin Ming’s hands.

“Huo Yuan, do you know what this is?” Lin Ming asked.

Huo Yuan was startled. Then, he hastily nodded. “My Lord, I haven’t seen this token before, but I can guess a bit of the origins of this token…”

Chapter 524 – Muk Gu

Huo Yuan’s human tribe was called the Skyrise Tribe. Currently, they were being led by an extreme Xiantian senior.

This person was already over 100 years old. For a Xiantian martial artist, a hundred years was only the middle years of their life. But if it took them 100 years to reach the extreme Xiantian realm, then without a stroke of luck, they would never step into the Revolving Core realm.

Prior to this, Huo Yuan had relayed the situation to the leading general. As the general saw Lin Ming and how young he was, he was filled with disbelief. But as he looked at the corpses that were strewn behind Lin Ming, as well as the thick murderous intent that flowed from him, he couldn’t help but believe.

“This is the genius from a great sect who came out to adventure?” The old man whispered to himself. In a sense, the martial artists of Bewitching Cloud Prairie weren’t much stronger than common martial artists. Their legacies were lacking and many of their martial artists at the Houtian realm had very shaky foundations. Only a few of them were able to stumble their way into the Xiantian realm, and this was completely because of the massive amounts of battle and fighting that occurred year-round. A cultivation that came from only fighting could not compare to those talents from large sects.

To meet this sort of genius coming out to the Bewitching Cloud Prairie for adventure, and not only that, but to have him smoothly eliminate the Silent Green Tribe… well, it could only be said that they struck gold.

This youth was indeed nonsensically strong. The general had seen some sect talents before, but compared to Lin Ming, they were nothing more than mud to the clouds.

If they could involve themselves with the sect that stood behind Lin Ming, then their benefits would be endless.

“That… Lord Lin…” The general was forming a humble greeting when at this time, a young little girl in black clothes came running over. She was crying as she shouted out, “Big Brother Lin Ming!”

This little girl was Qing He. She had heard the news that the Silent Green Tribe had been overthrown. She was excited, nervous, and also worried about Lin Ming. All of these feelings mixed together within her, causing tears to fall down her cheeks.

“Everything’s okay, Qing He.” Lin Ming patted Qing He’s head.

“Excuse me, Elder, but I’ll have to trouble you with looking after Qing He.” Lin Ming said to the general that was leading the Skyrise Tribe troops.

“Of course, of course.” The general struck his chest in a promising gesture as he saw that he was able to help Lin Ming with a matter.

“Big Brother Lin Ming, are you leaving?” Although Qing He was still a child, she was quite intelligent. She immediately realized the meaning behind Lin Ming’s words.

“Mm, I have to go…” Lin Ming looked at Qing He and smiled. He was aware that ever since Qing He had been born, there had never been anyone besides her grandmother who treated her kindly. She had lived in poverty and hunger.

In such a situation, especially for young girls like Qing He who were incomparably pure and innocent, it was easy for them to be moved by those who treated them well. After meeting him, she had no longer been starving or afraid. He had helped her drive out the bad guys, and he had treated her kindly. Naturally, it was easy for her to form a sense of dependence on him and to wholeheartedly consider him as her big brother.

Unfortunately, Qing He was only a mortal. She might have some martial arts talent, but in the end this was limited. It was unlikely that their paths would cross again in the future.

“I… I know.” Qing He kindly didn’t say anything further. She only deeply looked at Lin Ming, a trace of reluctance and sentimentality in her eyes.

Qing He was also aware that Lin Ming was only passing by here. He was just like the birds in the sky. Although he might stop by for a rest, he would fly away eventually.

In this way, Lin Ming embarked on the next step of his journey. Under the gaze from the numerous martial artists around him, he slowly walked away…

………

Ten days later…

The high skies were clear and cloudless. But, what was strange was that the sky seemed to be stained with blood. It wasn’t a bright sky blue, but rather the color of flowing crimson blood.

Underneath the skies, the land was barren, vast, and endless. At the ends of these barren plains were several towering mountain peaks.

Woosh!

Two streaks of light cut between two mountains at an extreme velocity. From afar, they were like streams of prismatic light; it was incomparably beautiful.

“Junior-apprentice Sister, the Blood Slaughter Steppes are in front of us. Let me ask you again, are you sure you want to go with me?”

This blue rainbow was actually a giant blue bird. It was unknown what species it was, but it was at least 10 times faster than Lin Ming’s Winged Flood Dragon.

The one who just spoke was a black-clothed youth who stood atop the back of the blue bird. He was tall, stately, and had an imposing appearance. Between his eyebrows, there was a faint infernal energy emanating. Although this youth was suppressing it, it was still unwittingly being sent out.

“Senior-apprentice Brother, I’ve already made my decision. There’s nothing more to say.” A black-clothed girl said. She was standing atop another blue bird that that was beside the black-clothed youth. She had a gauzy mask on. Her shapely body emitted a supremely charming aura. A faint infernal energy also emanated from her. She gave off an aloof and haughty feeling.

These two fellow apprentices were humans. But, they practiced demonic cultivation methods. What they walked was the killing path.

Within the Holy Demon Continent, this was a very common phenomenon. Humans that practiced demonic cultivation methods would naturally be inferior in talent to a Giant Demon. But on the other hand, even if they practiced honest and righteous cultivation methods, they would also be inferior to Giant Demons.

With this being the case, good and evil did not matter. Not to mention that there was rich and thick demonic energy that permeated through the Holy Demon Continent. Cultivating demonic arts was much smoother than in the Sky Spill Continent.

Thus, there were large numbers of those from demonic sects that were here. At this moment, this man and woman were two outstanding talents that came from a large demonic sect.

“Junior-apprentice Sister, as soon as we walk upon the path of slaughter then there is no turning back. We will either kill or be killed. There are very few that are able to cross this sea of blood. You should think carefully about what you want to do!”

“Senior-apprentice Brother, I am naturally clear about all of this!” The black-clothed woman calmly said.

The young man sighed and then didn’t speak again. Suddenly, at this moment, there was someone flitting past below him. It was a blue-clothed youth. Although this young man didn’t have a mount, he was quickly flying by himself.

It had to be known that within the Holy Demon Continent, even if one took transmission arrays to hurry along, there were still great distances that were calculated in 100,000 mile units. Without a mount to ride, flying would consume a great deal of true essence. The average person wouldn’t do something like this.

“Mm? He’s comprehended the Concept of Wind? If he coordinates the Concept of Wind with his flying ability, then it would truly be effortless to fly. No wonder he’s so fast. He must be a talent from some sect.”

The black-clothed youth turned his bird mount to catch up to the young man, “Fellow martial cultivator, I am Muk Gu of Sky Pavilion City!”

“What do you want?” Lin Ming responded. He didn’t give his name. The more he closed in on the Blood Slaughter Steppes, the more cautious he became. Here, murdering and robbing someone was a completely natural and common occurrence.

“Just a greeting from a chance meeting. I assume that you are a talent from some large sect too, huh?” As Muk Gu spoke, he was stunned. He had discovered that Lin Ming’s cultivation was only at the early Xiantian realm. Was it possible that he was headed to the Blood Slaughter Steppes? For an early Xiantian realm youth to head for the Blood Slaughter Steppes, that was truly the height of confidence!

“Friend, I don’t know whether or not you’re going to the Blood Slaughter Steppes, but I would like to advise you that the Blood Slaughter Steppes is not a peaceful place. There, the people can murder you without batting an eye. I see that your cultivation is only at the early Xiantian realm. I wonder whether you are going to the Blood Slaughter Steppes for adventure, or whether you have some matter to attend to? It looks like you have a Blood Slaughter Token on you from the faint infernal energy aura that you’re emitting. Would you be willing to sell it to me? I believe I can provide you with an adequate reward that will satisfy you.”

“My apologies, this Blood Slaughter Token is useful to me, I will have to decline your offer.” Lin Ming flatly refused. He remained calm on the surface even as he went on alert. From his experiences, it wouldn’t be strange if this man tried to rob him or some other strange thing.

Muk Gu smiled after being refused. He said, “Since friend doesn’t wish to, then I will not force you. But, let me give you some last advice. Not everyone in the Blood Slaughter Steppes will be as easy-speaking and reasonable as me, especially those from the Giant Demon race. They won’t even talk with you before killing you. Frankly, if you weren’t a human and rather a Giant Demon, then I might have done the same.”

Muk Gu heartily laughed and then spurred the blue bird to return back to his junior-apprentice sister’s side.

“Senior-apprentice Brother, what is it?” The black-clothed woman asked afar.

“Nothing much. It was just that the young man had a Blood Slaughter Token. I was hoping to purchase it so our fellow disciples could use it too, but it looks like I was rejected. It doesn’t matter anyways. I believe he is from some large sect, and his sect might not be much different from our own. I didn’t know who that heroic youth was, so I was just hoping to get his name.”

…………………….

Lin Ming didn’t continue flying until he saw Muk Gu leave his range of sight. From a moment ago, he could feel Muk Gu’s formidable aura; he could tell he was an extremely self-confident individual. Although his words were respectful, the truth was that he was arrogant, and he also had the strength to match his arrogance. His inner true essence was very thick, and although his cultivation was only at the half-step Revolving Core realm, his strength might not be any weaker than a Revolving Core powerhouse. He didn’t even look over 30 years old! Such an age and strength meant that he wasn’t much inferior to Mu Qianyu!

“I haven’t even reached the Blood Slaughter Steppes and I’ve met a talent like this. It seems that the Blood Slaughter Steppes is truly not a quiet place.” After Lin Ming arrived at the Holy Demon Continent, he felt that the average quality of the martial artists here was much higher than those from the South Horizon Region and Five Element Region.

This was because Giant Demons had outstanding talents, and they were naturally born warriors. The second reason was that war and fighting constantly occurred within the Holy Demon Continent. This was the ideal condition for a martial artist to grow. Therefore, even a human martial artist was much more formidable than those from the South Horizon Region.

For instance, take the Bewitching Cloud Prairie. If the Bewitching Cloud Prairie were placed within the South Horizon Region, it would at best be equal to the Seven Profound Territory. However, the entire Seven Profound Territory of the South Horizon Region only had a single Revolving Core master. But here, in the Bewitching Cloud Prairie, there were 20 to 30 Revolving Core realm powerhouses. Although the majority of them were Giant Demons, there were still seven or eight human Revolving Core masters.

After several days passed, Lin Ming fully entered the Blood Slaughter Steppes. To his surprise, not only did he see humans and Giant Demons, but also many other races.

Among them, one of the races was exceptionally beautiful. The men were handsome and eye-catching, and the women were beautiful. They had alluring jade eyes, long and sharp ears, and ocean-green hair. Besides their eyes, ears, and coloring, they were very similar to humans. Some had radiant patches of scales on their faces, and some even had charming tails.

Afterwards, Lin Ming learned that this was the Fey race of the Holy Demon Continent.

Chapter 530 – First Victory

“Kill! Kill! Kill!”

Skysplit Tower echoed with this thunderous cry. It was easy for the major races to form opposing factions, especially since humans and Giant Demons were mortal enemies; it was normal for them to target each other in the arena. However, in most cases, it was the human side that was defeated.

This was because the humans in the Heavenly Demon Cities were weak on an individual level, and there were also far fewer of them than the Giant Demons.

It was true that the population of humans far surpassed all others on the Holy Demon Continent. But among the humans, there were fewer that walked the killing path, and their talent was also relatively lower. Thus, there weren’t too many human martial artists that ventured to Polaris City.

On the other hand, not only was the Giant Demon race filled with geniuses, but the vast majority of them chose the killing path. Thus, a massive amount of outstanding Giant Demon youths existed in Polaris City.

Because of these reasons, humans in Polaris City were in a naturally weaker position with no status at all.

As for the Ferals, they weren’t much better than the humans. They were naturally slow and lacking in perception, so no matter what cultivation method they practiced it was less effective. So, there were fewer Feral talents, and less that walked the killing path.

It could be said that beside Polaris City, the other Heavenly Demon Cities were all the worlds of the Giant Demons. Besides the Giant Demons, Imps also accounted for a small role. As for the Fey, there were few of them, but by virtue of their formidable individual strength, no one dared to provoke them. Even the arrogant and mouthy Giant Demons didn’t dare to spout nonsense in front of the Fey. A truly powerful Fey was ruthless to the point of eating others without spitting bones.

“Just too weak.” At this time, several beautiful Fey women were merrily laughing in the stands. It seemed as if they enjoyed this blood and slaughter filled Skysplit Tower.

Now, even the usually impulsive and hot-tempered Feral martial artists could only patiently endure this insult. None of them jumped onstage to confront Zha Na. Zha Na was among the strongest of the strong of Skysplit Tower’s first level. Although these Ferals had inferior perception, they weren’t stupid. They knew when they could fight and when they couldn’t, otherwise they wouldn’t have lived up to now.

“Let’s go.” Several human martial artists couldn’t withstand the pressure and wanted to leave the arena.

“Ugh, they really are useless. They can’t even withstand this sort of pressure, and yet they still say they want to walk the killing path? F*ck off and scurry home!” Zha Na loudly ridiculed.

The group of human martial artists turned red, and they all clenched their fists. A smaller human martial artist in his twenties almost couldn’t stand the repeated insults and was about to jump up onstage himself.

“Don’t be reckless!” An older, black-clothed martial artist pushed down that smaller martial artist’s hands.

“Hey, boy, do you have the balls to come up?” Zha Na gloated.

At this moment, Lin Ming calmly stood up. He said, “I’ll come.”

The first floor of Skysplit Tower was very ordinary in terms of strength. Lin Ming wanted to pass it quickly, he didn’t want to get caught up here for any longer than he needed. His figure flashed and he flew onstage.

As the several human martial artists finally saw their fellow comrade enter the stage, they were happy. But, as they discovered Lin Ming’s cultivation, all of them were stunned. That excitement and happiness also sunk into a deep gloominess.

“Early Xiantian realm…”

Although they could see that Lin Ming’s true essence was pure and thick, far exceeding that of any other early Xiantian realm martial artist, the fact was that his cultivation was too low. Between humans and Giant Demons, even when humans were at the same realm or a bit higher than a Giant Demon, they would still be weaker. Much less, Lin Ming’s cultivation was lower than his opponent’s.

“This…” A human martial artist’s complexion turned ugly, he didn’t know what to say. Lin Ming had a good future, but now that he acted this time, he had presented himself to the slaughter. This meaningless death would only allow the Giant Demons to laugh at them more.

As they expected, as the Giant Demons and Imps saw Lin Ming jump onstage, they were stunned at first and then they all immediately burst into laughter.

“There aren’t any humans left? They actually let a little baby come up?”

“Haha, early Xiantian realm, I’m not wrong! He isn’t even enough to use as a toothpick!”

“Yo! That boy is a sexy little looker! It would be such a pity if he died. Come to big sister here, this big sister will take great care of you.” A curved and charming Fey woman giggled. In Polaris City, even if one were a human martial artist, they would usually be bloodthirsty and vicious; there were very few that were handsome.

On the stage, Lin Ming turned a deaf ear to these comments.

Zha Na crossed his arms across his chest and looked at Lin Ming with relish in his eyes. “Hehe, in Polaris City, there are plenty of idiots that bite off more than they can chew, but I haven’t seen someone as stupid as you. An early Xiantian boy thinks that he can challenge me? Is this your first time out of your sect? Do you think that all the other martial artists here are the same as the garbage in your sect, the type that you can jump realms to defeat?”

Lin Ming impatiently looked at Zha Na and asked, “Are you here to fight or are you going to continue blabbering?”

As soon as Zha Na heard Lin Ming’s words, he scowled. His eyes flashed with killing intent as he said to Lin Ming, “Arrogant little boy, you don’t know what it means to die! I’ll deliver you to hell!”

Zha Na suddenly flourished a large axe and chopped down on Lin Ming.

The majesty of the axe combined with the roiling demon essence behind it. It was similar to a roaring ancient vicious beast, blowing in the wind. As Lin Ming stood there, he could faintly hear the screeching of countless souls within the demon essence.

Lin Ming traced his spatial ring, and the Purple Comet Spear appeared. A flashing red thunder crackled atop the spearpoint.

“Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder!”

Kacha!

The red thunder light was like a crimson python that shot towards Zha Na. The power of thunder was particularly potent at annihilating ghosts and demons. After the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder collided with the dark clouds of demon essence, it was like a red-hot iron rod that was inserted into snow. There was a ‘chi chi chi’ sound as the clouds of demon essence rapidly melted away.

“Mm!?”

Zha Na was shocked. He thought that he would be able to split Lin Ming in two with a single strike, but he never imagined that he would be the one that was suppressed.

“Ghost Shadow Cut!”

As Zha Na saw the massive crimson python rush towards him, his eyes flashed with a grim light. He chopped his axe down at the python’s head.

Peng!

Zha Na’s arms were shocked numb. He instantly drew back, the blood in his body swelling. He had barely managed to force back the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder, and at this moment, his mind filled with panic and fear.

How could this boy possibly be so strong!?

In that split second, Lin Ming didn’t give Zha Na the chance to recover. He instantly stepped forwards, his momentum exploding. He attacked with the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder again!

He wanted to stay at the top of Skysplit Tower for a long time. In the future, he would face all sorts of opponents. If his moves were all revealed, then he would naturally be in a much more dangerous situation. Thus, he repeatedly used the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder. The Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder was originally a power of thunder biased towards the demonic path; it was good for supplementing demonic cultivation methods. At this time, it was especially suitable.

“F*ck off!”

Zha Na roared. Both of his eyes were red and crazed. He grabbed his axe with two hands, and chopped down at Lin Ming.

But at this time, Lin Ming’s form trembled and faded away. ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’ was displayed, and he dodged this attack with a speed like ghosts and demons.

Bang!

Behind Lin Ming, the gray stone tiles burst apart. Underneath these tiles was a layer of thick darksteel that was supported by an array formation. As this axe attack cut down, it left shallow marks on the surface.

“This boy is tough to deal with!”

After his attack failed, Zha Na’s figure also flashed away. But, he wasn’t able to dodge Lin Ming’s spear.

The spear light swept out. The Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder chased after Zha Na, shooting towards him.

Zha Na roared and punched at the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder. There was an explosion as the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder burst apart. But Zha Na’s entire body was paralyzed, and his fist was charred black.

“Die!”

Lin Ming’s spear sunk in, directly piercing towards Zha Na’s heart. The Giant Demon race’s demon crystal was located exactly in their heart!

“Ahhhh!” Zha Na’s eyes were bloodshot. Facing the imminent threat of death, he erupted with 120% of his strength. He savagely bit down on his tongue, using the pain to rid himself of his paralysis. Then, he grabbed onto the Purple Comet Spear, wanting to lock it between his hands.

But just as he touched the Purple Comet Spear, an azure true essence burst out. The power of vibration was like a tidal wave as it crashed into Zha Na’s arm, directly shattering it!

Puu!

The Purple Comet Spear easily pierced through Zha Na’s heart. The spear passed through his body, and blood shot out from his back into the wind!

As soon as the spear thrust through Zha Na’s vital point, Lin Ming mercilessly finished the job. He twisted the long spear, shattering Zha Na’s demon crystal to pieces!

Zha Na’s body shook and he glared at Lin Ming. As he looked at Lin Ming with disbelief, the life faded from his bloodshot eyes.

From the start of the battle until Zha Na’s death, only four or five breaths of time had passed. Currently, all of the Giant Demons and Fey that had been laughing and mocking had frozen in place.

Zha Na died!?

Zha Na, whose strength was among the highest of the high within the entire first floor of Skysplit Tower, had died, and he had also died at the hands of an early Xiantian realm human martial artist…

The entire arena was utterly silent. All of those human martial artists that felt pity and regret for Lin Ming had their mouths fall wide open, to the point where an egg could fit inside. This 20 some year old youth had actually defeated Zha Na?

The vast gap that existed between martial artists of humans and Giant Demons had long since been deeply ingrained in these people’s hearts. Although they didn’t want to admit it, they had no choice but to acknowledge the truth.

They stared at Zha Na’s corpse as it hung on Lin Ming’s spear. From Zha Na’s back, blood still bubbled out…

Peng!

A misty fog burst out from Zha Na’s corpse, flying into Lin Ming’s hand where it rapidly condensed into a Blood Drinking Seal, and then immediately vanished.

As for Zha Na’s corpse, it quickly withered away until it became a desiccated mummy. Then Lin Ming tossed it away like a broken sack.

‘This Zha Na was truly an outstanding youth amongst the Giant Demons. His blood vitality is incomparably strong, it’s perfect to create a Blood Drinking Seal from.’

After killing someone and sucking away their blood, there was no change of expression on Lin Ming’s face. He turned, his eyes sweeping the arena as he clearly said, “Who’s next?”

‘This boy!’

All of the Giant Demon martial artists’ expressions towards Lin Ming had changed. He had used just four or five breaths of time to defeat Zha Na. Now no one dared to underestimate him anymore.

The Fey woman that had teased Lin Ming suppressed her stunning smile. “He actually practices a blood absorbing cultivation method. It could be considered the demonic path within demonic paths, the true killing road amongst killing roads. This little fellow looks like a cute harmless animal, but I never imagined he would practice a cruel cultivation method like this! I was almost fooled by his appearance.”

The Fey woman was a bit scared. If she really did try to tempt Lin Ming so she could suck up his yang essence, then she might have been the one to be eaten without a single bone left.

Chapter 531 – Battle

Lin Ming suddenly felt a burning hot energy surge through his feet, sending his spirit soaring into the heavens.

After this energy charged into his body, it recklessly rushed through his meridians, spreading in all directions. All sorts of illusions presented themselves in Lin Ming’s mind. It was like a manic power that had long been repressed in his heart began to wildly gallop around. It crashed through his body, causing his blood to boil…

“This is infernal energy?”

Lin Ming looked at Zha Na’s corpse; this really was the energy that was dissipating from his body. Before, Lin Ming had been relying on the Blood Slaughter Token to absorb a small amount of infernal energy so he hadn’t noticed it, but now that such a massive amount of infernal energy had entered him, Lin Ming suddenly felt his deepest and most primitive desires aroused. It was as if the darkness lurking in his soul was rising to the surface!

He wanted blood, he wanted to kill, he wanted to indulge in and ravage beauties!

At this time, Lin Ming’s mind throbbed with an inexplicable desire and pleasure. He wanted to vent these feelings and lash out like a beast.

This sudden change caused Lin Ming’s heart to go cold. He quickly calmed his mind and entered the ethereal martial intent, allowing his mood to settle.

Lin Ming had practiced the ‘Overbearing Soul Tactic’ for a very long time. In addition to the great power of his spiritual sea, the frantic infernal energy only erupted for an instant before it was suppressed.

“This infernal energy can really disturb a person’s mind. No wonder the people of Polaris City are so crazy and strange. It’s probably because the infernal energy has seeped into their souls over a long time.”

As Lin Ming remembered the ecstatic expression that Zha Na had when he absorbed infernal energy, as well his disturbed green eyes, he couldn’t help but let out a loose breath. If he couldn’t manage to suppress the infernal energy, it was possible that he would be controlled by it. In the end, he might even become a zombie that only knew to kill.

Lin Ming silently closed his eyes. After a few breaths of time, he opened them again. This time, his eyes once again shined with a clear and pure brilliance.

Atop his arm, the blurry Heavenly Demon Tattoo became a bit more solid, and that hideous demonic face also became fiercer.

“This boy’s mental strength is really stable.” A Giant Demon said as he stared at Lin Ming, his expression solemn. “This is his first time at the killing arena. When an average person absorbs infernal energy for the first time, they will become irrational and rabid due to the influx of infernal energy. But, this fellow actually just closed his eyes for a moment to recover. He’s not simple at all!”

“Mm. Zha Na was originally one of the strongest of the strong in Skysplit Tower’s first level. He had accumulated a great deal of infernal energy and that fellow sucked up over half of it. Yet he was still able to maintain his calm. This sort of turbulent infernal energy can cause the desires and impulses of even geniuses to spiral out of control!”

“Heh… how interesting.” Beside the two Giant Demons that spoke, a Fey woman said. She exuded a thick sexual appeal. She drained the red liquid in her glass, her eyes flashing with excitement as she licked her lips.

Seeing the Fey woman’s response, the Giant Demon laughed. “Bloodrose, are you thinking of seducing him? Don’t be too confident, or your plan might fail and he’ll be the one to use you.”

“Haha! I don’t need you to worry about me. As long as they are a man, there is no way they can control their inner desires.” The Fey woman said, her giggle like the tinkling of bells.

On the arena stage, several male slaves quickly rushed up and dragged away Zha Na’s corpse. But, they left behind Zha Na’s spatial ring. According to the customs of the arena battlefield, all of the deceased’s belongings, including spatial rings, went to the victor. The only thing that Skysplit Tower kept after the death of a participant was the Blood Slaughter Token.

“Sir, this is yours.” A male slave brought Zha Na’s spatial ring and cautiously handed it to Lin Ming.

“I have a question for you.” Lin Ming stopped the slave who was putting away the corpse.

The slave was shocked scared. He quickly said, “What question does sir have?”

“What are the conditions for entering the second level?”

The slave respectfully said, “Sir, according to the rules of Skysplit Tower, in order to enter the second level, a contestant must obtain a 12 win streak at the first level, or obtain victory to the point that no one dares to challenge them.”

“I understand.”

Lin Ming casually tossed a low-grade Blood Demon Crystal at the slave. A 12 win streak wasn’t too difficult. Presumably, all of the geniuses with higher cultivations directly went to the second level of Skysplit Tower or even higher. Within the first level of Skysplit Tower, there was no one here that made him feel threatened.

“Will anyone else come up?” Lin Ming asked. His eyes swept over the area where the Giant Demons were.

The tide could turn at any moment. Before, it was the humans that were being forced back by the Giant Demons. But now it was the Giant Demons that were being forced back by the humans.

“This boy, he must really think he’s invincible.” In a corner of the arena, a large Giant Demon fellow crushed the glass in his hands. This Giant Demon wore black clothes and carried a nine foot long claymore on his back. His strength was also amongst the elites of Skysplit Tower’s first floor.

Within the first elite group, there were also those that were weaker and stronger. This large Giant Demon fellow was stronger than Zha Na.

“You want to go up? That boy’s thunder is quite tricky, it has the ability to restrain our cultivation methods. If I’m not wrong, then that thunder should come from a medium-grade earth-step Thunder Soul.”

“As if I would place a medium-grade earth-step Thunder Soul in my eyes. I just don’t know whether or not that fellow has any other abilities.”

“Heh, so what if he does? Don’t you also have final resort abilities?”

“That’s right.” The black-clothe Giant Demon laughed and then stood up. “I’ll fight you!’

The black-clothed Giant Demon jumped up. He directly leapt over the audience. His ten foot tall body carried the weight of a several thousand jin claymore. As he landed onstage, it was like a massive hammer struck the ground, directly breaking apart the tiles where he landed.

“Ho!” After the black-clothed Giant Demon landed, he let out a savage roar like a wild beast. His shout was deafening. His naked upper body was wrapped with thick steel chains. As he moved, these thick chains struck each other; this Giant Demon looked like he was a massive gorilla.

Lin Ming looked at the black-clothed Giant Demon. Just from the strength of his aura, he could tell that his opponent far surpassed Zha Na.

“That is the Carnage Demon Sect’s Claymore King, Gu Yue.” Several people in the stands instantly recognized this black-clothed Giant Demon.

“The Carnage Demon Sect is a fifth-grade sect, and Gu Yue is a direct disciple. His strength can be ranked in the top ten. This time, that boy is shit out of luck.”

“Gu Yue, kill him! Kill that boy!”

All of the Giant Demons in the arena raucously shouted. There were even several Fey women screaming as they took out their bellybands and wildly waved them in the air.

Gu Yue took out the claymore from his back. He flourished the blade, struck the floor with the tip and caused the tiles to shatter. He crudely smiled and said, “Boy, if that last battle was everything you had, then just sit there and die.”

“Black Sun Shining Sky!”

The claymore chopped down, and a black light appeared in front of Gu Yue’s blade. At this time, a billowing demon essence formed a massive black sun around Gu Yue’s body. Black flames burned around him, turning the ground into molten lava.

Lin Ming’s spear thrust out. Thick arcs of Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder drilled through that black flames, directly piercing through the black sun. However, when crimson lightning wanted to break through the black flames, it was actually caught by the demonic essence.

“Heh! All you can do is repeat this move? Then go die!” Gu Yue grinned fiendishly. His Black Sun Shining Sky wasn’t suppressed by this power of thunder, it was extremely resilient. With the black sun binding the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder, he rushed at Lin Ming.

Bang!

A terrifying shockwave surged outwards, lifting all of the tiles of the floor. All of the tiles on the floor melted, and even a shallow section of the darksteel floor underneath was melted.

During this explosion, Lin Ming’s figure flew backward. Only his clothes had been slightly burnt.

“Humph, you’re quite good at running. But, just because you can escape for a moment doesn’t mean you can do it forever!”

Gu Yue unfolded his arms and thick beams of demonic essence shot out from his body. They rapidly spread all around him, completely surrounding him and Lin Ming. In just several breaths of time, hundreds of beams formed from demonic essence wove together in a tight net that completely enveloped the two.

Lin Ming calmly looked around. All he saw were countless thick beams of demonic essence wildly waving around, as if they were black pythons dancing in the air.

“Hehe, Gu Yue has even used his Blacksnake Prison. This fight should be finished soon. It’s said that the Blacksnake Prison is an inescapable net that covers the heavens and earth. Now, this boy can only meet Gu Yue in a frontal collision, and this is what Gu Yue specializes in the most!”

All of the Giant Demons in the arena grew excited as they saw this. The talent of the Giant Demon race was mostly represented by their strength as well as their defensive and offensive capabilities. But, they were inferior to humans in speed. If Lin Ming’s speed was limited by the Blacksnake Prison, then he could only confront Gu Yue head on. If a human were to attack a Giant Demon in a vicious melee, then that was simply asking to die.

“Let’s see where you can run now!” Gu Yue howled, “Black Sun Shining Sky!”

Bang!

A black sun appeared once more around Gu Yue’s claymore. This one was larger than before, and blazed with an even hotter energy. Although Gu Yue was rampant and cruel, he still didn’t underestimate Lin Ming. This strike contained a full 30% of his true essence. He grasped his claymore with both hands and cut down. The black sun was like a flaming black meteor that crashed towards Lin Ming!

With the Blacksnake Prison all around, there was simply nowhere to run. In this face of this blazing black sun, Lin Ming chuckled as he said. “It looks like all you can do is repeat this move too?”

“Humph! You’re at death’s door and you’re still acting glib! Go die!”

The nine foot long claymore cut down!

Just as the blazing black sun approached, Lin Ming lightly flicked his finger. Three Thunder Souls gathered as one; the Divine Demon Thunder Soul roared out!

Pu!

With a barely audible piercing sound, the Divine Demon Thunder Soul sunk into the blazing black sun and broke out from the other side. With a speed that was almost invisible to the naked eye, it approached Gu Yue’s throat.

“Screw off!”

Because of the incredibly compressed energy of the Divine Demon Thunder Soul, Gu Yue thought that this was an ordinary hidden weapon. Without a second thought, he punched out at it. In truth, this weapon was too fast so he couldn’t send out a stronger attack.

However, even if Gu Yue’s fist had been tempered, or even if it were wrapped in demonic essence, how could it possibly compare with the incomparably sharp Divine Demon Steel Needle?

Gu Yue’s protective true essence was pierced through by the Divine Demon Steel Needle like it was thin paper, directly slicing through. The Divine Demon Steel Needle didn’t slow at all nor did it change trajectory. Without the least bit of difficulty, it drilled through Gu Yue’s throat!

Puff!

Gu Yue’s throat was pierced through, and his neck exploded in a bloody mess. He stared with wide eyes filled with shock. The Divine Demon Steel Needle had been too fast, he hadn’t even been able to properly react in time…

Chapter 537 – Shattered Soul Domain

“Lan Xing wins, who will be the next challenger?” On the stage of the martial arena, a black-clothed referee announced after a blue-haired Fey defeated a Goliath youth.

The black-clothed referee was similar to the blue-skinned man that Lin Ming had met earlier. They had the characteristics of several races; this was typical of hybrid races.

Within Polaris City, because of the constant number of people being born, there were often many individuals that had the blood of other races within them. Using someone who was a hybrid to be a referee was much fairer to everyone involved.

“This Lan Xing fellow has already won two in a row. If he wins again, then it will be his third win in a row. How come I’ve never heard of him before?”

“It’s normal if you haven’t heard of him. In fact, this fellow is new here. I heard that he had a complete blowout just a year ago and gained ten whole slaughter points. After he came up to the second level he chose not to fight. Instead, he holed himself up and cultivated for an entire year. This is the first battle that he’s had since he came out!”

“He went into seclusion for an entire year? This fellow is quite terrifying, he actually has the patience to wait. Even a two winged Heavenly Demon master lasted less than 10 breaths of time under his hand. He’s most likely still hiding part of his strength. I guess that his true ability should be near that of a four Winged Heavenly Demon!”

As the audience discussed the match, Lin Ming was closely listening in. He couldn’t help but pay attention to this Lan Xing a bit more.

The truth was that ever since he came to Skysplit Tower, he found that because all the different races here had different cultivation systems, it was very inaccurate to compare cultivation realms to find relative strengths. This wasn’t even considering that everyone here was a genius that could jump ranks to fight. A five-star Demon General of Skysplit Tower could probably defeat a one-star Demon King from the outside.

Because of this, it was much more accurate to differentiate the strength one had with the winged Heavenly Demon Tattoos.

The stronger a martial artist was, the more wings they would have on their Heavenly Demon Tattoo.

From two wings, four wings, all the way to ten wings and twelve wings.

Lin Ming’s own Heavenly Demon Tattoo had quickly condensed two wings. In the future, as he fought in more battles in the arena, his Heavenly Demon Tattoo would also grow.

“Lan Xing! You’ve only won two games, do you really think you’re invincible with just that?”

A red-haired big fellow leapt onstage; he was also a Goliath race martial artist. Obviously, he had stepped up with the intention of regaining some honor for his companion. In Skysplit Tower, the races were very conscious about their own groups. When individuals of the same race fought, they wouldn’t kill each other often. But, if individuals of different races fought, then their every move would be ruthless. It was common for someone to die during these situations.

“With just you? It looks as if I’ll easily obtain my three win streak!” Lan Xing contemptuously glanced at the red-haired Goliath youth and flourished his sword.

“This Lan Xing is too arrogant, he’s not even placing Hong Mao in his eyes.”

“For better or worse, Hong Mao has been on the second floor for less than half a year but his strength is near that of a four winged Heavenly Demon. It would be unwise for Lan Xing to underestimate his opponent.”

As everyone saw Lan Xing being so arrogant, public opinion began to turn towards the red-haired Goliath youth.

As the red-haired big fellow heard Lan Xing’s words, he laughed loudly and extracted a heavy sword  from his back. “Easily obtain? It’s already a miracle that someone like you could live in Skysplit Tower until now. But your good luck stops here. Now die!”

As Hong Mao spoke, his heavy sword cut down at Lan Xing!

Kacha!

The floor tiles exploded into pieces as Lan Xing’s figure faded away like an illusion.

“Great movement technique. What a profound Concept of Wind.”

Lin Ming could see that Lan Xing had an extremely high understanding of the Concept of Wind; it was even far beyond his own.

It could be said that the entire Fey race was the beloved of all natural Laws.

The talent of the Fey far exceeded that of everyone else in the Holy Demon Continent. In terms of physical strength, they were inferior to the Giant Demons. But they had inborn physiques that  placed them in tune with the natural Laws. This allowed them to easily comprehend the power of Concepts and Laws.

This also caused the cultivation methods of the Fey to be infinitely varied; they were impossible for one to guard against.

“Sacred Edge – Blade of Wind!”

In that instant, Lan Xing’s sword disappeared, vanishing into the wind. In that instant, the endless wind of the world had become Lan Xing’s sword. It was everywhere, and impossible to defend against.

Ding ding ding!

For a time, it was unknown just how many sword strokes struck the Goliath fellow’s heavy sword. It caused him to nearly drop his weapon.

True essence recklessly shot out. Hong Mao was startled, his large figure instantly drew back.

However, Lan Xing’s sword followed him closely; there was no escaping it.

Hong Mao loudly shouted, about to resort to his master move. But at this time, three sword lights stabbed out.

Pu pu pu!

Hong Mao gave a miserable shout and flew backwards. Three bloody holes appeared in his body. As he fell to the ground, a large pool of thick blood formed beneath him.

“You didn’t die? Then consider yourself lucky!” Lan Xing didn’t even spare a glance at the half-dead Hong Mao before he stepped offstage.

The entire audience was stupefied. Victory and defeat had been decided in a mere five breaths of time!

Under the stage, several Goliath youths rushed up, quickly lifting away Hong Mao.

“Lan Xing, three win streak!” The black-clothed referee announced.

“Three win streak. He went into seclusion for one year, and as soon as he comes out he gains a three win streak. This Lan Xing absolutely has the strength of a four-winged Heavenly Demon. Looking at him, he only seems to be around 20 some years old. If he doesn’t die, then with enough time he will definitely have the ability to step onto the third floor!

“It seems another rising star came out. But to put it in perspective, there have been countless rising stars in Skysplit Tower these past years. Yet, there are only a few people with the ability to become ten-winged Heavenly Demons.

“Mm. The higher you go the more difficult it becomes.”

People began to discuss just what would happen to Lan Xing after his three win streak.

Normally, in Skysplit Tower, a martial artist wouldn’t continue past a three win streak in a single round. In a high level fight, one would greatly consume strength and true essence. The only exceptions were if one was too strong. At these times, a five or ten win streak would appear.

“Is there anyone willing to come onstage next?” The black-clothed referee loudly announced from the stage.

As the referee’s voice fell, the black-caped Imp smiled and stood up. He looked at Lin Ming, his eyes narrowing.

“Little Brother, let’s go up together.”

The black-caped Imp’s true essence sound transmission sounded in Lin Ming’s ear.

“This fellow is such a coward.” Lin Ming thought with disdain. This fellow obviously feared that he wouldn’t follow him up onstage, and that someone else would challenge him. This black-caped Imp didn’t have a single ounce of confidence.

Lin Ming leapt onstage.

The black caped Imp closely followed.

“That’s Blackrat. That fellow is really sad, he’s still bullying the newbies.” Some of the people in the audience recognized the black-caped Imp. He truly was worthy of the name ‘Blackrat’.

“Heh, you don’t need to say it. That Blackrat’s trick is quite useful. He’s almost a four-winged Heavenly Demon, and he’s about to earn his 20 win streak.”

“Haha, he might become the weakest four-winged Heavenly Demon!”

“Don’t look down on that Blackrat fellow, he has quite the ability. It’s just that he is far too cowardly for his own good. These newcomers are just too stupid and naïve. I know that the new boy onstage just had a complete blowout half a month or so ago. These young newcomers are usually arrogant and full of fighting spirit and boiling blood. They have no idea how strong they are or just how deep the waters of Skysplit Tower can be. Sooner or later, they will suffer for it.”

“Mm. I mean, just look at Lan Xing. He also had a complete blowout, but then he went into seclusion on the second floor for an entire year. Lan Xing’s arrogance isn’t misplaced, he indeed has the qualifications to act like that. Compared to Lan Xing, that boy onstage is just too impulsive…”

Very few people were optimistic about Lin Ming’s chances. Although it was true that he was very talented, a newbie was still a newbie. Both his age and cultivation were simply not enough; he had to be tempered in the forge of battle. In Skysplit Tower, those that were too bold and careless were also the most likely to die.

“Hehe, little boy, don’t be so nervous. I’ll go easy on you.” The black-caped Imp rubbed his hands together as he looked Lin Ming up and down. His black and beady eyes were narrowed. With his wrinkly black skin, he really did look like a sad black rat.

Lin Ming calmly took out the Purple Comet Spear. Thunder flashed on the spear tip.

Lin Ming’s eyes locked onto the shoulder of the black-caped Imp. He could clearly see the Heavenly Demon Tattoo there. This tattoo had two pairs of wings. The second pair was much blurrier than the first.

“Four-winged Heavenly Demon Tattoo… he has over ten times the infernal energy that I do right now. If I can take his, then it will save me a great deal of effort.”

As Blackrat thought Lin Ming was his prey, Lin Ming also thought the same of Blackrat.

“Match, start!” The referee shouted.

Blackrat took out two curved short sabers from his spatial ring. “Little boy, relax; my attacks won’t be too painful.”

Blackrat giggled. Suddenly, his beady eyes flashed with a thick killing intent – Shattered Soul Domain!

Hoo!

The surrounding environment suddenly changed. On the arena stage, thick infernal energy filled the air. It was as if the arena itself had turned into an Ashura battlefield that surrounded the audience. For a time, everyone heard the endless howls of shrieks of the abyss; they had all entered the illusion.

“The Shattered Soul Domain is Blackrat’s killing move. Once he uses it, it will void the souls of everyone within a hundred feet. If the damage is light, then the one struck will turn into an idiot. If it’s heavy, then that person will die. This fellow, he really wants to take that newcomer’s life.”

“Mm, although that newcomer’s cultivation isn’t too high, his talent is just too terrifying. He could actually create a complete blowout at the early Xiantian realm. Blackrat does not want any troubles to appear in the future.”

“Haha, a human genius is about to die! Great! Awesome!”

There were countless geniuses that perished in Skysplit Tower, it wasn’t just Lin Ming. Perhaps as soon as tomorrow, everyone here would have forgotten Lin Ming’s face.

In the stands, as everyone was talking, Lin Ming was standing motionless on the stage without any response.

“Little boy, if you want to blame someone then blame yourself for having too great a talent. I’m also forced to do this, so don’t blame me when you’re a ghost.” Blackrat giggled. His body was like a ghost as he dashed towards Lin Ming, his curved short sabers aimed towards Lin Ming’s throat.

But at this time, Lin Ming’s eyes suddenly flashed with a radiant light. The Purple Comet Spear in his hand struck out like a whip!

Woosh!

“What!?”

Blackrat was shocked. He thought that even if Lin Ming’s soul wasn’t destroyed, he still should have fallen into a deep illusion without any ability to resist. He never thought that Lin Ming would be able to counterattack.

“Shattered Soul Saber!”

Blackrat’s saber changed angles and shot up. He placed the entire strength of his soul attack in his blade, cutting down on the Purple Comet Spear’s shaft.

Pa!

The curved saber was struck out of Blackrat’s hand; Blackrat was sent flying back like a ball by Lin Ming’s spear!

At the same time, Blackrat’s soul attack spread into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea via the Purple Comet Spear. It rushed into him like a thunderstorm, menacing and dangerous!

But in the next instant, this soul attack was completely buried with the vast swirling vortex of the Samsara martial intent. Not even the slightest ripple was stirred up.

Lin Ming already knew that Blackrat excelled at soul attacks. When Blackrat had caused everyone at the martial artist service lodge to faint, this was all due to his soul attack.

Chapter 540 – Top Grade Practice Area

When Lan Xing looked at Lin Ming, although there wasn’t any hostility, there was a slight hint of haughty superiority.

The middle aged man opened up the small box. It was stacked to the brim with medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals. The light of the crystals was very pressing on the eye.

As the young Fey girl beside Lin Ming saw this scene, her beautiful large eyes shined. Her own cultivation wasn’t too high, so this box of pure Blood Demon Crystals left a really large impact on her.

“500 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals, no more and no less.” The middle aged man nodded, satisfied.

Lan Xing said, “Administration deacon, I would also like to trade in a few new battle array discs.”

As Lan Xing spoke, he took out four or five array discs from his spatial ring. Lin Ming had seen Blackrat use these array discs before. These were phantom array discs. They could display light images on top and also record scenes.

The middle aged man glanced over these array discs and said, “Five array discs, 500 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals.”

“Okay!”

Lan Xing took out another small box that was filled with medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals. Now he had spent a total of 1000 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals.

The young Fey girl gulped. These past years she had experienced a number of fantastic scenes. But, she still couldn’t help but be dazed in wonder at such a large transaction.

“What is that battle array disc?” Lin Ming couldn’t help but ask. A battle array disc cost 100 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals and it was only a rental? What was recorded in that array disc that could be so valuable?

The young Fey girl said, “This is a recording of masters fighting. There are battles between Demon Generals and Fey Generals, there are battles between Demon Kings and Fey Kings, and there are even battles between Demon Emperors and Fey Emperors. This is the wealth of Skysplit Tower, so fees are collected to view them.”

“Fights of Demon Emperors?” Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath. Until now, although he had frequently heard of Demon Emperors, Fey Emperors, and all sorts of Divine Sea Supreme Elders, he still hadn’t actually seen these honorable figures before. To him, these characters were legendary existences. What sort of scene would a battle between Demon Emperors be like? Lin Ming was truly looking forwards to this.

“Are there authority requirements to watch the Demon Emperor battle scenes?”

“Mm…not just that, but it requires slaughter points. I’m not too sure of the exact price and authority requirements, but Lan Xing should be wanting to see battles of four-star Fey Kings and above.”

A four-star to six-star Fey King was equal to a human Life Destruction powerhouse.

Normally speaking, a human single stage Life Destruction powerhouse was much weaker than a four-star Fey King. But, there were many stages of human Life Destruction. Could every single layer after layer after layer still be weaker than a four-star Fey King? What about a master at five to six stages of Life Destruction?

And what’s more, once a master crossed seven or eight stages of Life Destruction, this sort of monstrous genius’ strength would have already reached that of a Divine Sea Supreme Elder. To them, defeating a six-star Fey King would be simple.

“Four-star to six-star Fey King battles cost 100 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals to rent one time. This price is expensive enough!”

In summary, a four to five-star Fey King, was also Xuan Wuji’s level.

“This is Skysplit Tower, everything here is expensive. All of the food and water here is transported from other lands by Xiantian martial artists with spatial rings. Not just that, but there are many heroic youths here. Not a single one of them can be considered poor, and all of them have great wealth. Where there is a great deal of wealth, prices of resources will naturally rise.” The young Fey girl said with a obvious look.

In Skysplit Tower, even mortals would have Blood Demon Crystals on them. After all, as long as one encountered a swanky martial artist and served them well, gaining some rewards would also be normal.

Lan Xing examined these five new battle array discs and placed them in his spatial ring after a nod of satisfaction. His eyes floated onto Lin Ming. He casually glanced at him and said, “I’m quite interested in fighting with you. I hope that in the upcoming days you will appear in the arena, and not try to avoid fighting.”

Lan Xing’s declaration of war wasn’t out of Lin Ming’s expectations. He had noticed that Lan Xing’s eyes filled with thick fighting intent whenever he saw him. It was just that this Fey youth’s imperious tone made him feel a bit unhappy.

“Whether I enter the arena or not will all be my own choice. I will not deliberately avoid anyone, but even if I did, it wouldn’t be the likes of you. If you wish to challenge me in the arena, then I will welcome you anytime.” Lin Ming indifferently said as he straightened his sleeves.

“Ho! Those are some pretty confident words. You should hurry up and choose your practice area. I also want to advise you not to rent a place for too long, otherwise you might find that you’ll have wasted all that extra time.”

“Oh? So you want this to be a battle to the death?”

“Swords are blind. In a battle with life and death on the line, death is par for the course.”

The words exchanged between the two were edged and barbed. At this time, the administration deacon impatiently said, “If you two want to get all spicy with each other then you can go to the arena. This building is for registration of practice areas. If you want to register then do so now. If you don’t then go outside.”

The middle aged man angrily waved his hand.

“I will register.”

Lin Ming calmly walked in front of the deacon’s desk and handed over his pass. His information was listed within it.

The administration deacon looked over Lin Ming’s pass and wrote down some numbers on a piece of paper. He lackadaisically said, “The practice areas of the second floor are separated into five grades. The lowest is the fourth-grade. This area requires 20 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals per year. The third-grade takes 80 Blood Demon Crystals, the second-grade takes 200 Blood Demon Crystals, and the first-grade takes 500 Blood Demon Crystals as well as a single slaughter point…”

The practice area Lan Xing had chosen a moment ago was a first-grade practice area. It required 500 Blood Demon Crystals as well as a single slaughter point every year.

“You said the practice areas are divided into five grades. There is also a top-grade area?” Lin Ming asked after he mulled over it.

“Yes, but… there are only two top-grade practice areas on the entire second floor. It requires 200 Blood Demon Crystals every 10 day as well as a slaughter point.

The administration deacon glared at Lin Ming, a bit impatient. This top-grade practice area was empty most of the time. After all, the fees were simply too high. He would normally introduce it to famous individuals; otherwise, he wouldn’t bother at all.

For one year in this top-grade practice area, it would cost 7200 Blood Demon Crystals and 36 slaughter points. There was simply no one who would pay such an extravagant price. When they did, they would rent for 10 days. Even so, there were still very few people that did. It hurt the heart to have to pay such an extravagant price. It was just like a common poor person that couldn’t afford silk. They would rather take the money and buy ten times the amount of cotton instead.

However, this top-grade practice place was very useful. Cultivating in there for a single day was the same as cultivating in other places for four to five days. Some great figures of the second floor would sometimes pay the price if they were stuck at a bottleneck in their cultivation. They would enter the top-grade practice area for ten days or maybe even twenty, in the hopes that they could make a breakthrough to the next realm.

Lin Ming had heard of the effectiveness of this top-grade practice place before. He thought for a moment and then said, “I’ll rent it for 50 days.”

“50 days?” The administration deacon looked at Lin Ming with bewildered eyes. It had to be known that even the famous figures of the second floor would only rent out a top-grade practice area for 10 or 20 days at a time.

Renting one for 50 days meant it would cost a total of 1000 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals as well as five slaughter points. 1000 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals was already a big deal, but those five slaughter points were especially heartbreaking.

This was because slaughter points were that difficult to earn! Not just that, but slaughter points had too many uses. At auctions and trade fairs, there were many precious and rare things that required slaughter points to buy. Even a top rank powerhouse would be frugal with their slaughter points.

“Are you sure?”

“I’m sure.” Lin Ming nodded. The truth was that he had planned on staying on Skysplit Tower’s second floor for 50 days or so. Afterwards, he planned on attacking the third floor. That was where Lin Ming might stay for a few more years.

Hearing Lin Ming’s assured tone, the administration deacon clearly warmed up to Lin Ming’s cavalier attitude. If he could rent out this top-grade practice area for 50 whole days, then as the steward of the area, he too would have some benefits. “50 days, great! I’ll register you!”

The administration deacon had completely wiped away his previously languid manner. He flourished his pen and began to write with great strokes.

As for that young Fey girl who had come with Lin Ming, she was feeling ill.

1000 medium-grade blood Demon Crystals and five slaughter points for a mere 50 days of rent…

Even if one’s practice efficiency was five times higher, so what? That was equal to 250 days at a first-grade practice area. To save a mere 200 days… the cost was unbelievable!

This was simply a waste, an absolutely self-destructive waste.

Lin Ming naturally knew what function slaughter points had. But, he didn’t lack when it came to treasures, pills, or cultivation methods, so he had no need to go to a trade fair or an auction. Secondly, he had complete confidence that he would be able to earn more slaughter points a short time later. As a result, he happily spent as many slaughter points as he needed to.

As for those 1000 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals, they meant nothing to him. He never cared too much for something as vague as wealth to begin with. As for practice, he only used high-grade Blood Demon Crystals. Medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals were for spending.

Lin Ming took out two boxes that held a total of 1000 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals. These were the wealth that Blackrat had left behind after his death.

Lan Xing grimaced at the side.

This boy!

He was actually showing off his wealth in front of him?

Lan Xing was naturally proud. He felt uncomfortable that there was someone trying to push him down. He already thought that his own spending was lavish, but as he watched Lin Ming in front of him, even he felt pained by his actions. He didn’t care much about Blood Demon Crystals, but slaughter points were a completely different matter.

‘This fool, he’ll rue the day he indiscriminately wasted so many slaughter points!’

Lan Xing darkly thought in his heart.

“Young Hero, would you like to rent some battle array discs?” The administration deacon’s voice was filled with hospitality. If he managed to rent out a high-level battle array disc, then he would also have some benefits from that.

Lin Ming hesitated for a moment before slowly asked, “Do I have the authority to rent out an array disc of Emperor level masters?”

“This… no, it’s not possible. Also, the second floor does not have any. The highest recorded battles we have here are battle array discs with quasi Emperors. They cost 1000 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals and a slaughter point for one month of rental time.

A quasi Emperor was the realm between a six-star Demon King and Demon Emperor. It was equal to a fifth or sixth stage Life Destruction Supreme Elder, and was at a much higher level than Xuan Wuji.

“Mm. Then I’ll take one.” Lin Ming had just obtained a Glory Emblem, so he had a two-star authority now. As for Blood Demon Crystals and slaughter points, he didn’t care too much about that. Once he entered the third floor, it would naturally be much easier to obtain slaughter points than on the second.

As the young Fey girl heard the tone of this conversation that was like Lin Ming was buying cabbage from a street market, she was stunned speechless.

As for Lan Xing, his eyes flashed and he sneered, “In order to push me down, you still have do such pathetic things? Is your head really that swollen? You really are childish. As far as I know, you don’t have any more slaughter points than I do, and yet you’re wasting them like this to get to me. You are such a stupid idiot!”

Chapter 541 – Enlightenment Once More

Lan Xing finished his rant, and without any intention of staying at this place any longer, turned around and stomped out.

Lin Ming didn’t think that Lan Xing would have such an explosive reaction. As he watched Lan Xing stride away, Lin Ming shook his head and said, “How ridiculous.”

He calmly took out another box of Blood Demon Crystals and set it on the table. “There are 1000 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals here, you can count them.”

“Mm, alright.” The administration deacon happily smiled and swept over the box with his divine sense. Then, he kindly placed it away. The more this type of guest came back, the greater his profits would be.

“Do you need any other battle array discs?” The administration deacon enthusiastically asked.

Lin Ming thought about it for a moment. He said, “I’ll take three battle array discs with three-star Fey Kings and Demon Kings. I don’t need any others.”

Lin Ming’s interest in Life Destruction level powerhouses was much lower than his interest in Emperor level characters. But, it was also helpful if he understood the different sorts of combat techniques of the Fey and Giant Demon races.

“Alright. That will be a total of 600 medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals.”

So far, Lin Ming had already used up all the medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals that he obtained from Blackrat. But if he combined the Blood Demon Crystals of Zha Na and Gu Yue, then he had more than enough.

Lin Ming received the key to the practice area as well as seven array discs. He turned to the young Fey girl and said, “Miss, please take me to the practice area.”

“Okay, great!” The young Fey girl’s eyes filled with eager passion as she looked at Lin Ming. It was rare for anyone to see such a rich master. And even if she did, it might not even be her turn to serve him. That Lan Xing was already extremely opulent.

The space within Skysplit Tower was immense. Since Lin Ming’s practice area was thousands of feet deep, it was an extremely long walk. Along the entire way the young Fey girl endlessly chattered about the going-ons of Skysplit Tower, whether that information was useful or useless. She even completely informed Lin Ming about everything she knew about the powerhouses of the second level.

The more the young Fey girl spoke, the closer she approached to Lin Ming. Finally, she was close enough that she was nearly hanging off Lin Ming. Her curvaceous and luscious body melted onto his, and she constantly traced his arms.

Lin Ming ignored the girl’s advances several times, but this young Fey girl was abnormally blind in her flirting. Lin Ming finally grew impatient. A cold light flashed in his eyes and infernal energy emitted from his body. The young Fey girl shook and scurried away, her eyes filling with fear and worry.

Within Skysplit Tower, as the lowest level of all martial artists, the young Fey girl was considered slightly better than a senior slave. Those like her could not even dare to provoke the challengers, which was why the young Fey girl was so terrified.

As Lin Ming saw this, he couldn’t help but think of little Qing He. As he thought about the fate of these pitiful slaves, his heart softened. He said, “Continue speaking. This is for you.”

As Lin Ming spoke, he tossed over a small bag of Blood Demon Crystals.

The young Fey girl hesitated for a moment. Then, she bit her lips and slowly took the bag.  As she weighed it in her hand, she feared that there were more than a dozen Blood Demon Crystals inside.

The young Fey girl continued to warily inform Lin Ming on the situation at Skysplit Tower, but this time she didn’t dare to approach Lin Ming even a bit.

As the two reached the practice area, they opened the door, and within was a single transmission array.

The young Fey girl said, “Young Hero Lin, I can only bring you here. You can use the key to activate the transmission array. Then, you can enter your room. The room has layers upon layers of spells and array formations covering it; you do not need to worry that others will spy on you, so please rest assured.”

“Good.” Lin Ming nodded. He placed his key into the array formation, and with a white flash of light, he was suddenly in a dark room.

As he entered this room, the first feeling he felt was cold. There was extreme chilling energy here that made him feel incredibly creeped out.

The room was filled with a layer of misty black fog that wafted around. This was a rich infernal energy that had condensed into essence.

“To think that the infernal energy in this room is rich to this degree. If a lower level martial artist were to come here, they would lose their mind. Even a Xiantian realm powerhouse would find their heart affected if they stayed here for too long!”

The room was only 30 feet by 30 feet. There was a bed made from black rock and the only thing on it was a hard pillow. There weren’t even any bedsheets; it was extremely depressing to see.

If an average person had to live in this environment for an entire month, they would probably descend into madness.

However, this couldn’t be considered much to Lin Ming. A martial artist’s seclusion was originally a lonely and devout path.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and then sat down on the bed. He pulled out the quasi Emperor battle array disc that recorded their battle.

He placed a Blood Demon Crystal in the array disc, and a series of phantom illusions beamed into the air.

Above the boundless jet black sea, the waves rolled and storms surged in the air. Two silhouettes were suspended high above the sea.

One wore a black cloak, and he held a long spear in his hand. This man was a Giant Demon.

As for his opponent, she was an ice cold beauty. She wore a black veil, and her two pointed ears peeked out from the sides. Her inky hair fell down like a waterfall, and shiny scales glimmered at the edges of her eyes. She was a Fey beauty.

“Two great quasi Emperor masters!”

Although Lin Ming couldn’t see their cultivation in these phantom images, for some unknown reason, he actually felt somewhat scared. This was a fear that swelled up from the depths of his being!

“A mere illusion can still retain such an aura, what would happen if it was the real person? This is also only at the quasi Emperor level. If it was the true Emperor level, a Divine Sea Supreme Elder that had crossed Life Destruction seven or eight times, then what would that be like?”

As Lin Ming thought out loud, he felt his blood boil with passion.

Woosh!

The Giant Demon was the first to make a move. He stabbed his spear out at the icy Fey beauty. The fierce combat had begun!

With Lin Ming’s eyes, he was completely unable to track the movement of the battle. He could only see the sea’s waves crash in massive tides, and the sky permeated with intense demonic essence. Sword and spear energies cut through the heavens and earth, and dark clouds roiled in the skies.

The space was disturbed. Visible ripples radiated out in the sky. From high above, it was like black flowers blooming in the air.

“Mm? This is…”

As Lin Ming glanced at the sea, he saw that the ripples had created a small vortex in the water. A massive amount of seawater was being swallowed up into this vortex and completely disappearing.

Was this… a space crack?

When Lin Ming had journeyed through the broken world, that entire world had decayed into fragments. That broken world had been flooded by a massive amount of seawater that came from the South Sea, and Lin Ming had also seen a number of similar vortexes there. If a martial artist ran into them, they would be directly ripped in half!

These space cracks hadn’t been here before the two quasi Emperor level masters battled. If he wasn’t wrong, then these space cracks were the result of intense true essence shockwaves and energy vortexes that tore apart space.

“Just a fight between quasi Emperor level masters can create tears in space? What would happen in a battle between Emperor level masters?”

Lin Ming exclaimed out. Over time, he found that these small vortexes in the ocean slowly shrunk until they finally disappeared.

“Torn space cracks in a fight of quasi Emperors are only temporary. It seems like stable space has the ability to independently regenerate, unless it was like the disintegrating broken world in which the Demon God Imperial Palace was located. Otherwise, it wouldn’t have been so easy for those Life Destruction Supreme Elders to create a space channel.”

Lin Ming fully concentrated on the fight again, watching it over and over. No matter how many times he saw it, his current eye speed wasn’t able to keep up with the speed of the two quasi Emperors’ moves. However, these moves and martial skills weren’t important to Lin Ming; what he wanted to experience were the Concepts and Laws!

“The quasi Emperor Giant Demon’s Concept seems to contain a desperate and frenetic strength. Just from looking at his spear moves, it feels like my own soul is breaking apart…  maybe… is this the Concept of Annihilation?”

Lin Ming was secretly surprised. These were just phantoms from a recording, and yet there was such a preeminent aura. If he was actually watching them fight, then he didn’t know what sort of situation he would be in. This Concept of Annihilation was too terrifying. From just a glance, a martial artist with an infirm will would have their very souls destroyed.

“The Fey woman seems to be using the Concept of Water and the Concept of Wind. Her moves are too fast; they leave one feeling as if space and time are in upheaval. I fear that her moves also contain the Concept of Time and the Concept of Space. The Fey are truly beloved by the natural Laws. This Fey woman understands too many Concepts. And, what is most terrifying Is that her mastery of these Concepts has reached a degree where she can freely use them and fuse them into her attacks. This is simply unbelievable!”

This battle did not have an end. As the phantoms reached the white hot stage, they finally vanished, without showing who won or lost. Lin Ming thought this was a pity, but he had still gained a great deal of benefits from watching this. In particular, that Fey woman. Her understandings of wind, time and space seemed to raise a certain awareness in his heart.

This awareness combined with what Lin Ming had experienced as he traveled through the space channel to the Holy Demon Continent. He had a faint sense as if something was almost within reach, but he still couldn’t touch it.

The power of space and time within that space channel echoed within Lin Ming’s mind. At this time, time seemed to bend, and even Lin Ming’s thoughts seemed to slow down. It was like a film was slowly playing in his mind.

Like this, Lin Ming became lost in thought as he unknowingly entered the ethereal martial intent state.

With the support of the ethereal martial intent, spiritual sense’s concentration increased ten times over. Even his breathing seemed to fall into a vague state; there wasn’t even a single sense of perception or leftover thought in his body.

A circle of black infernal energy gathered around Lin Ming, forming into a faint black fog. It quietly floated into Lin Ming’s body. Without any external guidance, the infernal energy instinctively revolved in a nearly perfect route through Lin Ming.

Lin Ming had unconsciously reentered into a state of enlightenment. As he maintained this state, time seemed to pass by him. Unknown to him, several days passed…

……….

Days later, at the second floor’s arena –

“Lan Xing, victory!” The black-clothed referee held up Lan Xing’s hand. “This is a seven win streak as well as Lan Xing’s seventh victory! If he continues winning and reaches a ten win streak, will these be the first slaughter points that he wins from the second floor? Does anyone else here dare to challenge Lan Xing?”

The black-clothed referee’s voice was filled with crazed passion.

“This Lan Xing is too fierce. I said that he had the strength of a four-winged Heavenly Demon before, but it seems I’ve underestimated him. He might even have the strength of a four-winged back section Heavenly Demon!”

There was an extremely long path from a four-winged Heavenly Demon to a six-winged Heavenly Demon. Thus, as the sixth set of wings of the Heavenly Demon Tattoo was being formed it would be divided into the front section, middle section, and back section.

“It looks like Lan Xing will reach a ten win streak. The masters of the second floor won’t stop him until he reaches that point.”

“Yes, this is what usually happens. It’s rare to be able to raise such a fat sheep. Lan Xing will only be of value to those masters once he earns a ten win streak and some slaughter points.”

Chapter 544 – Measure for Measure

Ka ka ka…

The amethyst armor that covered Lan Xing’s body began to gradually sink back into his body, and the arcane runes on his face began to fade away until he appeared like the unbearably handsome Fey youth from before. But, blood still stained his face, giving him a fierce look.

As Lan Xing looked at Lin Ming, his eyes were filled with pride and an intention to fight.

“Young Hero Lan has obtained an 11 win streak. He has officially gained one slaughter point as well as two slaughter points from his gamble with Huyan Luo. Would Young Hero Lan like to continue battling?”

“No,” Lan Xing shook his head, “I will rest for two hours before I begin my 12th match.”

Everyone had thought that Lan Xing would continue and try for a 12 win streak in a single go. But his words had surprised them.

“This boy! From his gamble with Huyan Luo, I had the sense that he was incredibly brazen, but now it seems that he is actually quite calm. He has consumed just a bit of energy but hasn’t gotten carried away by his victories. He actually decided to take a rest for two hours before continuing.”

“Mm. It looks like it wasn’t a moment of impulse that caused him to make a bet with Huyan Luo. It’s likely that he investigated Huyan Luo ahead of time and believed he had a high chance of winning.”

“Hehe, did you notice that Lin Ming also arrived? Do you think that Lin Ming will dare to stay here for two hours?”

“This isn’t a question of whether he dares to but rather if he’s an idiot and will be swayed by his mood. Lin Ming arrived just in time to see Lan Xing’s last fight; that Fey King Battle Body is no joke. Lan Xing’s combat prowess has already reached the first tier of Skysplit Tower’s second floor, and not just that, but he can’t be considered too weak amongst the first tier!”

As the audience spoke, many of those present were looking at Lin Ming. They were looking forward to seeing how Lin Ming would respond to this.

Under the watchful eyes of the audience, Lin Ming didn’t have much of an expression. Instead, he calmly walked onstage.

‘Mm? Lin Ming is stepping onstage?’

People had just had this thought when Lin Ming leapt up. Slowly, he fell onto the arena like a dragonfly on a still lake.

Lin Ming glanced at the black-clothed referee and calmly said, “I would like to fight.”

“Ah!”

Many of the audience gasped in surprise and excitement. Lin Ming hadn’t left nor did he meditate to rest. Instead, he had entered the arena stage to fight. Was he trying to prove a point here?

Lan Xing was also a bit stunned. He immediately smirked and then closed his eyes, returning to meditation to restore his mind.

He didn’t need to look before realizing that Lin Ming wouldn’t encounter any decent opponents. Although there was a great deal of masters that were present today, none of them would make a move against Lin Ming, and this was simply because there was no advantage in doing so.

At most, some of the weaker second tier human martial artists would come to challenge Lin Ming. These individuals came to gain experience as well as to challenge the gap between them and others. The martial arena of the second floor was never lacking in these types of martial artists, thus it was never difficult for one to gain a ten win streak. But, for those above a ten win streak, there were mighty masters everywhere. This was because they could gain slaughter points by ending someone else’s winning streak.

And because the strength of these individuals might be too close, when a heated battle occurred, oftentimes death would accompany it.

“White Wind Sect’s Zhou Tianyu kindly requests Sir Lin’s guidance!”

A human martial artist jumped onstage. He wasn’t some random nobody. In fact, he had condensed a two-winged Heavenly Demon Tattoo; his strength could be considered decent.

There were many martial artists on the second floor that would condense a Heavenly Demon Tattoo and then lose a round. They would then have to spend another period of time condensing it again, and repeat this process many times. But as long as they kept their life then failure wasn’t much at all.

As the referee announced the start of the match, Zhou Tianyu’s sword flashed towards Lin Ming’s chest like a serpent. His sword strike contained a vague hint of the Concept of Water. His sword energy was long, liquid, and couldn’t be cut.

However, this was completely nothing to Lin Ming. As soon as his spear power was displayed, a vibrating wave of true essence erupted. That wave of endless true essence smashed into the sword energy, shattering it into nothing.

A spear thrust out, the tip like a bolt of lightning. It seemed to disappear into the void and instantly appeared between Zhou Tianyu’s eyebrows.

Chi!

Infernal energy suddenly converged on him. Zhou Tianyu felt a chilling cold between his eyebrows, and the hairs on his back began to stand on end. In that moment, he felt as if Lin Ming’s spear would cut through his head.

“I… I’ve lost.”

Zhou Tianyu was secretly relieved, but he discovered that his back was wet with sweat. Just then, he almost thought that he would die.

“Well fought.”

Lin Ming withdrew the Purple Comet Spear, and a surge of infernal energy within Zhou Tianyu rolled out and into Lin Ming’s body. Although it wasn’t much, it was still able to make Lin Ming’s Heavenly Demon Tattoo a bit more solid.

“Lin Ming, victory!” The referee loudly announced.

“What a powerful spear. Whether it’s his spear power or infernal energy, he can freely use them with skill and ease. I wonder if Lin Ming is hiding any more strength.”

“Mm. Lin Ming is indeed powerful, but his opponents are too weak. Even if he wins beautifully it doesn’t mean much. If Lin Ming wants to defeat Lan Xing… the chances aren’t too high.”

Zhou Tianyu wasn’t even at the same level as Huyan Luo. There were very few people that believed Lin Ming would win.

However, in a corner of the martial arena, a white-haired middle-aged man was deep in thought. In that split-second, his sense of space and time seemed to have been mixed up. “Was that an illusion? That seemed like just a casual strike from that boy, but if I were to face it, even I would find it difficult to avoid…”

Four win streak, five win streak, six win streak…

Lin Ming obtained an eight win streak in a single go. Every match didn’t exceed three moves. He was like an unstoppable juggernaut that mowed down everyone before him.

Although none of Lin Ming’s opponents were masters, every battle was easily won. In all these rounds, Lin Ming’s breathing hadn’t even quickened. This secretly startled some people present.

“Eight matches, eight victories. This is Young Hero Lin’s fifth match today. Do you wish to continue with a sixth match?” The black-clothed referee asked.

Within Skysplit Tower, a martial artist normally wouldn’t fight more than three battles a day. The truth was that this was for the sake of caution. They wanted to avoid seeming too arrogant and cocky, thus drawing out some masters to suppress them.

As Lin Ming was now, he could breeze through these past five matches like nothing.

“Perhaps.” Lin Ming glanced over at Lan Xing, thinking about how much time was left. He, like Lan Xing, wouldn’t underestimate his opponent. Lin Ming was looking forwards to seeing just what this Fey King Battle Body was all about.

After Lin Ming stepped offstage, everyone’s eyes were on him. They wanted to see whether he would leave or stay in the martial arena.

Lin Ming was a pure newcomer, much newer than Lan Xing. Lan Xing had already practiced on the second floor for an entire year. At this time, facing this sort of opponent, it wouldn’t be a shame if Lin Ming avoided battle.

However, Lin Ming only silently walked over to a seat and sat down. These several matches hadn’t really tired him, he was only sitting to adjust his mentality.

“He sat down! Heh, the newborn calf really doesn’t fear the tiger!”

“He’s only treating him equally. He’s already aware that Lan Xing will challenge him yet he doesn’t care. Instead, he calmly welcomes Lan Xing’s challenge.”

“This is quite fun to watch!”

When masters fought, especially two rising star talents, it often drew a great crowd. The news of the potential battle spread out, and more and more people crowded into the arena. There was constantly people streaming through the entrance of the martial arena. Soon, there were 4000 to 5000 people in the stands. Besides some martial artists that had gone into closed-door seclusion, most of the other martial artists had come. There were even some lower level martial artists that mainly did business on the second floor who also came, hoping to see the fun.

The entire martial arena was filled with people. As for the center stage of the martial arena, there actually wasn’t anybody fighting. They were all waiting for Lin Ming and Lan Xing to fight.

Time slowly passed. Lin Ming was like a monk as he sat in meditation, and Lan Xing wasn’t in an hurry either.

The crowd around the two began to loudly shout in their discussions.

In truth, Lan Xing didn’t even need an hour to restore his peak condition. But even so, he still stayed in meditation without any desire to stand up. In this situation, a normal person would inevitably become patient and jump onstage for the waiting audience. But, Lan Xing completely disregarded all of this. Since he said he would rest for two hours, he would rest for two hours.

The mental stability was startling.

“It’s time.” Two full hours later, Lan Xing opened his eyes from his quiet meditative state. His voice was calm like a placid lake.

“What a strong mentality!”

Some people in the audience couldn’t help but cry out in acclaim. People with this sort of disposition could maintain their peak battle condition at all times. There were very few external factors that would be able to affect their state of mind.

“This fellow is quite scary. Not only is his strength heaven-defying, but he also has a calm personality.”

Lan Xing looked over to Lin Ming, the corners of his lips rising in a grin, “Since you’ve been waiting here for me, it looks like you’ve already decided to fight me. Since that’s the case, let’s go onstage!”

Lan Xing’s figure blurred and he appeared on the arena stage. Lin Ming followed, lightly falling onto the stage.

“Lin Ming, during my match with Huyan Luo, I made a bet with slaughter points. Do you dare to follow my gamble?” Lan Xing taunted.

“How many do you want to bet?” Lin Ming asked.

“The same, two. If you can defeat me, not only will you obtain slaughter points from stopping my winning streak, but you can also win two slaughter points from a bet. Of course, this all depends on whether or not you can win.”

“Then let’s do it!” Lin Ming readily agreed.

“Haha, great! Wonderful! Then I won’t be polite!” As Lan Xing spoke, he extracted a longsword from his spatial ring. The blade began to hum in the wind.

This was the achievement of integrating the Concept of Wind into one’s sword skill.

In terms of the Concept of Wind, Lan Xing’s understand far surpassed that of Lin Ming.

Lin Ming also took out the Purple Comet Spear. A tranquil yet indomitable aura suddenly burst out from him. He was like a towering mountain, unreachable and unattainable.

Chi chi chi!

The two hadn’t even fought but their auras were already colliding with each other. Compared to Lin Ming’s steady aura, Lan Xing’s aura was like flying arrows, both sharp and penetrating.

“Heh! You are truly extraordinary. Then I will see just how much of my strength you will be able to pull out!” As Lan Xing spoke, his expression changed. His eyes flashed like cold stars in the sky, a chilling light emanating from them.

“Sword of Wind!”

As Lan Xing finished speaking, the sword in his hand disappeared. His sword had fused into the wind. One could only see the wind, but not the sword.

In that instant, countless sword lights wove into a net that covered the sky, falling down onto Lin Ming.

“Golden Roc Shattering the Void!”

Lin Ming instantly vanished. The tiles that were underneath his feet were sliced into pieces by that the sword energy!

Chapter 546 – Great Harvest

“You…”

The sword energy on Lan Xing’s palm had already faded away. His blood-red eyes were wide as he stared at Lin Ming. He never imagined that he would be defeated so quickly. He still had finishing moves that he hadn’t used yet, but… he no longer had the chance!

What a fantastical Concept of Space. Before Lan Xing had even brought down his palm sword, the Purple Comet Spear had already seemingly teleported in front of Lan Xing and pierced his heart.

“I… never thought… I would lose to a human in Concepts…”

Lan Xing clutched the shaft of the Purple Comet Spear and ruefully smiled. As he opened his mouth, he coughed up great mouthfuls of blood. His heart and lungs had shattered, and blood filled his chest, pouring out of his throat.

Lin Ming withdrew his spear. Vibrating true essence had already broken apart every single meridian in Lan Xing’s body. With his heart burst apart too, there was absolutely no way for him to leave alive.

Ever since he had suffered under Mu Qingshu, Mu Chihuo, and Ouyang Boyan, almost causing those close to him to pay with their lives, Lin Ming had become increasingly decisive and ruthless. He would stamp out the trouble at the source before it was allowed to bloom.

A massive amount of blood sprayed out. The tiles under Lan Xing’s feet were stained red. This shocking scene completely silenced every martial artist present.

Before now, there was almost no one that believed Lin Ming would win. But not only had he won, he had won so quickly!

During the entire fight onstage there had only been several moves exchanged. Lin Ming defeated Lan Xing with overwhelming strength and speed!

It could be said that Lan Xing couldn’t dodge the last strike because Lin Ming had a touch of the Concept of Space within his spear. But without a doubt, even if Lan Xing was able to dodge this attack, he would still have been defeated in the end!

This was because after they had used all their hidden cards, Lin Ming’s aura had already suppressed Lan Xing’s. This was illustrated by Lin Ming breaking apart Lan Xing’s curtain of sword light with his spear potential.

“Lan Xing was defeated! This boy!” In the audience, a pale Giant Demon who had been waiting for Lin Ming to lose now had an extremely ugly expression on his face. Over the years, he had already formed an inborn sense of arrogance and racial superiority. There was no way he could accept that a mere human had surpassed all of the heroic youths of his Giant Demon race.

“I fear he might have the strength of a peak four-winged Heavenly Demon. This strength could be ranked in the top 10 of the entire second floor of Skysplit Tower.

“Unbelievable. A genius like Lan Xing already had the qualifications to become a Fey Emperor in the future. But, this boy actually defeated Lan Xing. Could it be that…”

“Humph, one’s aspirations aren’t equal to their own prominence. Lan Xing had the qualifications to ascend to a Fey Emperor, but that is only the qualifications. Above a Saint level talent is an Emperor level talent, but how many Emperor level talents appear every year, and how many of those are truly able to become a Fey Emperor or Demon Emperor? They die halfway, buried, with all their potential gone. Everything they once grasped they will lose. It’s far too early to call this boy Lin Ming a Peerless Emperor!”

A Fey martial artist bitterly said. Within the Holy Demon Continent, the humans and Ferals had the lowest number of Emperor level powerhouses. Lin Ming had just killed a Fey genius, and others had said he could become a Peerless Emperor in the future, so he naturally wasn’t feeling too happy about matters.

Lin Ming ignored the discussion of the surrounding martial artists. At this moment, he was quietly baptizing himself within a rich infernal energy. Lan Xing had accumulated a great deal of infernal energy, and now over half of it was Lin Ming’s. This flow of energy was extremely suppressing.

The dark desires of his heart and his obsessions were rapidly stirred up by the thick infernal energy. They percolated with Lan Xing’s own ambitions…

Power, beautiful women, glory, the martial arts boundary of a Fey Emperor… all of this poured into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea.

These sudden and intensely strong desires and passions were like demons that rapidly multiplied in Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, trying to take root there.

“This Skysplit Tower is truly a paradise of corruption!”

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a cold light. The black vortex of the Samsara martial intent suddenly appeared, directly sucking up all those desires and obsessions and tearing them to shreds.

As Lin Ming’s heart calmed down, he quickly recovered his thinking.

‘I already have a strong soul force, but I was still affected by these desires. There are many martial artists present whose soul force is far inferior to mine, and they probably can’t resist this invasion of desires. Although they might not be dominated by these thoughts and turned into slaves of them, their hearts would still be affected. But, the cultivation methods of the demonic path already veer one into doing whatever they please, so losing a bit of their thinking isn’t much at all.’

One could look at the fate of the slaves of Skysplit Tower to see just how distorted the personalities of the Skysplit Tower challengers became. Being cruelly ravaged, humiliated, mistreated, or even killed… these slaves suffered everywhere and at all times.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and the infernal energy within his body began to revolve within him. On his arm, the Heavenly Demon Tattoo began to condense. After the first pair of wings was completed, the second pair was nourished by the infernal energy, and began to slowly form…

Four-winged Heavenly Demon!

After killing Lan Xing, Lin Ming had finally reached the realm of a four-winged Heavenly Demon.

The realm itself was unimportant to Lin Ming. But, the accumulated infernal energy was greatly advantageous to the cultivation of the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’.

Lin Ming took Lan Xing’s spatial ring and glanced at it. Impressively, it was a medium-grade earth-step spatial ring.

This was truly the background of a genius from a large sect. The spatial ring was a medium-grade earth-step treasure, and not just that, but a very good one amongst its rank.

As for the Blood Drinking Seal, Lin Ming naturally wouldn’t forget about it. But for better or worse, Lan Xing still had an extremely high status within the Fey race. He didn’t cause Lan Xing’s corpse to explode and embarrass the Fey. Instead, he let the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder make a circle within Lan Xing’s corpse, directly sucking up all of his blood essence.

After this was all finished, several of Skysplit Tower’s staff came up and carried away Lan Xing’s corpse.

Those who killed could end up being killed. Lan Xing, who had been overweeningly arrogant and swollen with self-importance, also perished here. Every martial artist present knew that they could suffer the same fate someday.

“Well… Young Hero Lin, would you like to continue?” The referee’s voice was a bit unnatural. This Lin Ming’s talent was just too terrifying. As long as he didn’t die here, he would inevitably become a high ranking figure within Skysplit Tower. He might even become his superior.

“No, I’ll stop here for today.” Lin Ming refused to continue. After this battle, he had obtained some more insights into the Concept of Wind. He wanted to head back to his room and contemplate on them.

“Great. Young Hero Lin, if you will.” The referee’s attitude was exceptionally respectful.

Lin Ming turned and stepped off the stage. The martial artists in the audience had a touch of awe and wonder in their eyes as they watched him leave.

Lin Ming arrived the martial arena’s exit. The young Fey girl was waiting there. She blankly looked at Lin Ming, unsure what to say.

“Sir Lin, you…”

Lin Ming tossed the young Fey girl a small box of Blood Demon Crystals and said, “Five days from now, wait for me at Morningdew Inn.”

Morningdew Inn was an inn that was near the transmission array that led to Lin Ming’s practice area. Normally speaking, there wasn’t anything inside a martial artist’s practice area. Thus, most martial artists would choose to stay at inns. They would return to their practice area to cultivate.

“Ehm… okay… alright…” The young Fey girl quickly replied. If another martial artist wanted to meet her inside an inn, then she would understand what they wanted her to do. But Lin Ming wasn’t someone who was interested in those things, otherwise he would have already done so.

“What would Sir Lin like to do?”

“I want you to bring me somewhere where I can rent out battle array discs. They only need to be at the quasi Emperor level or above.”

Renting out high level quasi Emperor battle array discs required a slaughter point. Even the top geniuses of large sects weren’t willing to watch these more than a few times. But listening to Lin Ming’s meaning, it seemed that he wanted to rent out a great number of these.

The young Fey girl gulped and blankly nodded.

“Then… I’ll see you five days from now.” Lin Ming left after he finished speaking. He didn’t seem as if he was moving quickly, but the ground beneath his feet seemed to shrink. He only took a few steps, but he had already disappeared around the corner…

……………..

Lin Ming sat atop the bed in his practice area. He had completely taken out all of Lan Xing’s possessions from his spatial ring and had looked over them. He was secretly shocked. Killing others and taking their wealth was truly the fastest way to become rich. Lan Xing’s total wealth was several times greater than that of Blackrat.

There were tens of thousands of medium-grade true essence stones, and also several dozen high-grade true essence stones.

In addition to that, there were countless large and small bottles, jade slips, and treasures.

There was no need to look at the medium-grade Blood Demon Crystals, they were all for spending.

As for the high-grade Blood Demon Crystals, they were for cultivating. Lin Ming put those away.

After carefully inspecting the pills, Lin Ming separated them by different general classifications.

All that was left over were the jade slips.

Lin Ming was looking forward to the jade slips in Lan Xing’s spatial ring. He immediately immersed his perception in the jade slips, slowly sweeping through them. He patiently took over an entire hour to scan them. Suddenly, Lin Ming’s eyes brightened.

This was it!

Lin Ming had picked up a common-looking jade slip from among the pile. This jade slip didn’t record cultivation methods or martial skills. Instead, it was the accumulated experiences of Fey masters about the Concept of Wind.

Looking at the soul imprints on the jade slip, it obviously didn’t come from a single person. Rather, it was the collected attainments and experiences of a great number of Fey masters. This was absolutely a priceless treasure!

This sort of Concept comprehension jade slip was similar to a cultivation method jade slip: the contents could not be duplicated. One could only write down the contents if they had a deep understanding of it. This only served to raise its value. The reason that Lan Xing brought this with him was likely so that he could meditate on it at any time.

“The Fey are born beloved by the natural Laws. They have countless masters who have reached Large Success in Concepts. These masters leave behind their legacies, and this continues onwards. As these experiences accumulate, the Fey race’s superiority in Laws and Concepts will also widen.

Several generations, dozens of generations, the total accumulation of these people was terrifying. This was also the reason why the more ancient clans had a more profound heritage.

“With this jade slip and my original understanding of the Concept of Wind, my own Concept of Wind will inevitably rise to a higher level!”

Speed had never been Lin Ming’s strength. If he could further his Concept of Wind, then in addition to a basic understanding of the Concept of Space, Lin Ming was confident he could break through to the second layer of ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’. At that time, his strength would rise.

Chapter 575 – Termination Emblem

One month later, it had been a total of half a year since Lin Ming entered the third floor of Skysplit Tower.

Within the open space of the Concept of Thunder practice area, a young man stood there. His upper chest was naked, and his long hair hung down to his waist. A faint imposing aura emanated from between his eyebrows, but as he opened his eyes, a burst of light flashed within them like a bolt of thunder.

Between his eyebrows was a faint fire mark. It seemed like a scar, but as one stared at it, it made one feel apprehensive, as if some mysterious force was gripping them.

As soon as the middle-aged man in charge of the registration office saw Lin Ming come in, his heart inexplicably jumped.

“My practice has ended. Please register it.” Lin Ming said.

“Oh… okay, good.” The middle-aged man responded as he quickly took out a jade slip. He verified the registration and then refunded Lin Ming’s deposit. As one of the deacons of Skysplit Tower, this middle-aged man’s cultivation was at the late Houtian realm. But, as he came into contact with Lin Ming, he strangely felt a great pressure envelop him.

“This is a return of 40 high-grade Blood Demon Crystals.”

Lin Ming glanced over and received them.

“Well… there’s also another matter… about your recent match schedule.” The middle-aged man took out another jade slip and carefully handed it to Lin Ming.

Lin Ming sunk his sense inside. Inside this jade slip was material on his opponents. One was arranged two months ago, and another was more recent.

Of the two people, one’s strength was ranked 17, and another was ranked 12.

“Yan Hu, peak six-winged Heavenly Demon, 122 win winning streak.”

“Ming Sun, peak six-winged Heavenly Demon, 133 win winning streak.”

Lin Ming thought about these two. According to the rules of Skysplit Tower, he would have to accept these two matches continuously.

Both of them were martial artists that had managed to accumulate a win streak over 100. Of course, in Skysplit Tower, when one killed another person they gained at least a 10 win winning streak, otherwise it would be impossible to win 100 victories on the field.

The middle-aged man looked at Lin Ming and said in a low voice, “Lord Lin, if you can kill a martial artist with a 100 win winning streak, you will obtain the Termination Emblem.”

Because of the change in Lin Ming’s temperament and aura, this middle-aged man had unconsciously become respectful of Lin Ming. Compared to the first time he had seen Lin Ming, it was as if he were a completely different person.

“Oh? Is this how one earns the Termination Emblem?”

When Lin Ming was on the first floor, he had already heard about the Termination Emblem. Among the possible emblems one could obtain, it gave one of the higher rewards.

Lin Ming’s heart stirred. At this time, he really did need slaughter points. “How many slaughter points will I receive for the Termination Emblem?”

“50 slaughter points. In addition, after obtaining the Termination Emblem you will receive a higher authority, allowing you to access more practice areas within Skysplit Tower.”

“Mm?” Lin Ming’s eyes brightened. “What other practice areas are there in Skysplit Tower?”

“This… when Lord Lin obtains the Termination Emblem then you will be made known. As for now, it’s inconvenient for me to tell you, so I’ll have to excuse myself.”

“Mm, I understand.” Lin Ming nodded. As for obtaining this Termination Emblem, he never doubted himself. “What time are my matches?”

“Tomorrow. They will both be in the same area. I wish Lord Lin good luck.”

……………….

From the first floor to the third, every floor became increasingly lonely and deserted the further up one went.

On the first floor, the arena that could hold tens of thousands of people was nearly full every day. There were cheers, endless clamoring, shouts, cries, and people acting crazy everywhere.

As long as one paid a medium-grade Blood Demon Crystal then they would be able to enter the first floor. Many of these individuals were not challengers or even young elites. They had gathered there purely because they loved to see these killing games.

Thus, it could be said that the martial arena of the first floor was a never ending slaughter fest.

As for the second floor’s martial arena, it could only hold around 8000 people. The audience was nearly all challengers and they were much more restrained than those people on the first floor. Often they would peacefully watch the match – they wouldn’t be crazily shouting.

As for the third floor, it was even lonelier. The martial arena could only hold a mere few thousand people. The audience every day amounted to several dozen individuals. In a single day there would often only be a few matches, so most of the time the martial arena of the third floor was unoccupied.

Today however, the martial arena of the third floor had a rare surprise breakout of just over 100 people. It had to be known that the third floor only had around 300 to 400 challengers. This meant that nearly a third of the martial artists of the third floor had arrived at the martial arena. There were many among them that had even ended their closed-door cultivation early in order to hurry here.

Normally, only someone as famous as the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars or an equally renowned figure would arouse such interest in a match.

But, the one who walked onstage today was only a single human, Lin Ming.

Although Lin Ming was a remarkably outstanding talent, he was still a newcomer; there weren’t many people that cared much for him. But during his first match he had reversed everyone’s expectations and killed Hong Zhong, someone who was ranked around 30th to 40th on the third floor. The talent he revealed had startled and frightened everyone present.

For a newcomer to achieve this degree of success was truly abnormal. Thus, Lin Ming had naturally come under everyone’s attention. Especially today! He would continuously fight in two matches without a break!

But Lin Ming’s two opponents, Yan Hu and Ming Sun, were not average challengers. They were both ranked in the top 20 of Skysplit Tower’s third floor.

Today, there were even many top 10 masters of the third floor that had come. Without doubt, Lin Ming would inevitably become a powerful rival of theirs. They naturally had to be cautious and observe him.

Muk Gu was also among the group. The humans on the third floor did not surpass two digits in number. Muk Gu seemed very ordinary and plain as he mixed in the crowd.

As Muk Gu saw Lin Ming calmly appear on the edge of the arena stage, he didn’t know why but he felt his mind jump. He felt that he understood Lin Ming less and less. Looking back to the first time that he met Lin Ming on the outer borders of the Blood Slaughter Steppes and had even threatened him somewhat, he felt that his actions were simply laughable.

But at that time, Lin Ming absolutely hadn’t been as strong as he was right now. The speed of his progress was terrifying. Muk Gu could not help but marvel at this fact.

“First match, Lin Ming against Yan Hu!”

The referee loudly announced on the arena stage.

Yan Hu was a Goliath; he was even a head higher than Xue Man. To everyone, he was simply like a giant iron tower.

His weapon was a great sledgehammer. Its weight was almost 100,000 jins.

With a loud roar, Yan Hu leapt onto the arena stage. The entire floor shook from the impact!

Yan Hu did not have even the slightest bit of contempt for Lin Ming. Such a roar seemed like the rude behavior of a barbarian, but it was in fact a type of Goliath war roar martial skill. It was used to enhance one’s own aura and combat strength.

“Yan Hu is completely serious. He has taken Lin Ming as a great enemy.”

“This is normal. Lin Ming displayed a strength equal to that of a top 30 ranked challenger, but who knows how much strength he’s still hiding. Perhaps Yan Hu will lose!” A challenger said, very sure of himself. Of the challengers on the third floor, none of them dared to look down on Lin Ming anymore. Lin Ming was probably in his early twenties and yet he already had this degree of strength. In a few more decades, he would be even more terrifying.

“Don’t underestimate Yan Hu either. Yan Hu isn’t too bad; his strength can probably be ranked 17th or 18th. Those martial artists that can enter the third floor of Skysplit Tower and reach the top 20 are not ordinary geniuses of their generation. Not just that, but Yan Hu excels most at understanding the esoteric strength of the earth. His strong points lay in his defensive ability. Lin Ming’s final move is probably that Chasing Thunder. It’s an attack with a speed and striking force that reach the limit. Here, it will be the sharpest lance against the hardest shield. It’s still too early to judge just who will win. This will be a fierce match between two equal opponents!”

…………….

Lin Ming held his spear, the tip pointed towards where Yan Hu stood. Even though he merely stood there, the aura he gave off was like that of a peerless treasure spear. This spear could pierce through all, unstoppable and invincible!

As Lin Ming reached this degree, his imposing aura was no longer a field of pressure. Instead, it could manifest into essence. Lin Ming’s aura was like that of a spear piercing through your chest, incomparably sharp!

As for Yan Hu’s aura, it was like a heavy and solemn mountain. As their auras clashed, one could clearly hear the sound of Yan Hu’s aura nearly being pierced through. An invisible pressure pushed down on Yan Hu’s body. His face was grim and dignified; he had come into a fatal situation.

“I will admit that you are very strong, but these years, the number of powerhouses of the third floor that have died by my hands has reached the double digits! Let me show you my ultimate combat strength!”

As Yan Hu spoke here he exploded in a roar. All of the muscles on his body began to suddenly rise, his veins twisting like blue worms. Just like the Fey had their Fey King Battle Body, the Goliaths could also draw strength from their bloodline and use this to their advantage, a unique form of fighting that only they had.

As Yan Hu entered into his battle form, his aura soared into the sky, directly pushing back Lin Ming’s sharp and imposing aura.

“The Meaning of Earth – Absolute Defense!”

Earth-attribute demon essence gathered around Yan Hu, turning into thick waves of soil, constantly rolling and sliding, giving off an oppressive sense.

“Hehe, in terms of strength, I can only be ranked 17th or 18th on the third floor. But in terms of defensive power, I am confident I will not lose to anyone! While you spent your time closed up comprehending your Concepts, I did not idle around. I too spent an entire three months perceiving the Concept of Earth and spent a total of nine slaughter points! With this price, my comprehension of the Concept of Earth went up yet another step, and my defensive abilities have absolutely reached the stage of Large Success! With my speed and response time, I know that it’s impossible for me to dodge that move of yours. But if I can’t then I’ll just block it, how hard could that be?”

Yan Hu already knew of Lin Ming’s killer move – Chasing Thunder. With that advantage, he had planned from the very start to not attack. Instead, he would spend everything on his defense. In terms of defensive ability, the Concept of Earth was the absolute mightiest amongst the five elements.

“Mm? This so-called absolute defense seems to be…” In the arena, a top 10 rankings martial artist’s eyes brightened. Yan Hu’s defense was not merely an accumulation of earth origin energy, but rather it contained very calm and steady fluctuations; this was definitely the application of the Law of Earth. If he wasn’t wrong, then these fluctuations had the ability to mollify attacks.

“It seems that Yan Hu has really been working hard on the Concept of Earth these past months to prepare! He is quite smart! He knows well enough that his speed cannot compare with Lin Ming’s, so he isn’t even thinking of dodging. Instead, with his several month-long practice, he plans to use his absolute defensive ability to meet Lin Ming in a head-on attack.”

“Mm. Yan Hu’s defensive ability can’t be disregarded. I don’t know whether or not Lin Ming’s Chasing Thunder can break apart this defense, but if he can’t then he’ll be in a dangerous situation. It’s true that Lin Ming’s Chasing Thunder is powerful, but this sort of mighty killing move has to consume a great deal of strength. On the other hand, Han Yu’s absolute defense doesn’t use much at all. If Lin Ming continuously uses Chasing Thunder but can’t break open this defense, then he will fall into a passive position because of his overconsumption of true essence. Finally, Yan Hu will be the one to counterattack!”

The martial artists in the arena were able to quickly guess just what Yan Hu’s plan was. This tactic was indeed intelligent. Most people hadn’t thought Yan Hu would win, but they also didn’t think he would make such a significant breakthrough in his absolute defense. Now, it seemed as if it would be hard to judge just who would win this fight.

Chapter 576 – Crush

On the martial arena, facing these roiling brown waves of earth in the air, Lin Ming shook his hand, the Purple Comet Spear’s point trembling. “You want to use your defense to block my attack? How interesting! You seem to have confidence in your defensive ability. Is it known as the absolute defense?”

“Humph! Why don’t you test whether or not it is an absolute defense? Stop trying to play mind tricks and take my move – Beast Trapping Cage!”

Yan Hu pounded down the sledgehammer in his hands. A wave of earth-attribute true essence rose up in all directions, trapping Lin Ming within and limiting his ability to dodge.

“Say hi to my hammer!”

Yan Hu was like a massive bear as he jumped up. With both his hands gripped on his sledgehammer, he smashed down with all his might. Yan Hu did not excel at speed, thus he trapped Lin Ming into this Beast Trapping Cage in order to use his strongest strike. This move also contained the Concept of Earth. Combined with Yan Hu’s terrifying strength and the massive weight of the hammer, even a mountain would be smashed apart by him!

“The Concept of Earth, that’s so rarely seen!” Normally, the Goliaths and Giant Demons’ demon essence did not have this attribute. But, Yan Hu was unexpectedly skilled in the Concept of Earth; this was indeed rare.

Lin Ming flourished the Purple Comet Spear and opened 60% of the Heretical God Force. Above the Purple Comet Spear, thick arcs of electricity violently turned like a dance of purple snakes.

Chasing Thunder!

Woosh!

Lin Ming’s figure instantly vanished. After making significant progress in the Concept of Thunder, Lin Ming’s Chasing Thunder was far different from the time that he had used it to kill Hong Zhong.

With a ‘kacha’, the Beast Trapping Cage instantly exploded from within. Lin Ming attack continued unabated. The spear was like a bolt of lightning as it pierced towards Yan Hu!

This speed was far too extreme. Yan Hu’s sledgehammer was only midway in the air; to use his weapon to block Lin Ming’s attack was naturally impossible.

Yan Hu’s pupils shrank. Absolute Defense!

Browned waves of energy fiercely swept into the air, forming a thick barrier in front of Yan Hu.

Kacha!

Chasing Thunder’s dazzling radiance pierced through the barrier. The sharp spear light passed through layers and layers of earth origin energy, weakening along the way until only a tiny wisp of it pricked Yan Hu’s body.

With an explosive sound, the barrier of earth origin energy shattered in half. Yan Hu was like a massive rubber ball that was kicked backwards!

Bang!

Yan Hu fell onto the ground. His organs were injured, and the blood in his body tumbled, his face flushing red.

“it was just a tiny wisp of spear light yet it’s powerful to this extent?” Yan Hu jumped up from the ground, his heart shaken. After this wisp of spear light entered his body, it began to ruthlessly destroy his meridians and organs. Not just that, but it had an endlessly growing property too it. It was only with great difficulty that he was able to suppress it.

However, he had finally been able to block that strike!

Yan Hu breathed heavily. He reinforced the absolute defense around his body and looked at Lin Ming.

If he could defend against Chasing Thunder, then that meant he had the ability to win this battle.

If Lin Ming could not break his defense, he was in an invulnerable position!

“Yan Hu’s defense is truly fierce. Lin Ming’s strike was even more potent than when he fought against Hong Zhong. But, it was still blocked by Yan Hu. The earth-attribute demon essence fluctuations in that shield are ingeniously done. It used multiple layers in order to weaken Lin Ming’s attack.”

The audience all had extraordinary eyesight. They had seen the mystery behind what just happened.

“Mm. Yan Hu’s utilization of the Concept of Earth is excellent. In defense, it really does need the Concept of Earth. If it were any other Concept, then they would have been defeated by that strike.”

“I don’t know if Lin Ming can use Chasing Thunder multiple times or whether he has other master moves. A technique like Chasing Thunder seems like it is bound to cause a great burden on one’s body and true essence reserves. If Lin Ming uses that skill two or three times but still can’t break through Yan Hu’s defense, then he will be in danger.”

Above the martial stage, Yan Hu had already stood up. Waves upon waves of yellow earth covered him as he confronted Lin Ming from a distance.

“If you have any other moves, then use them. I know that you are still hiding some finishing moves in your hand, and I will follow every one of them! If you keep hiding them, then you won’t have a chance to use any of them!” Yan Hu suddenly yelled at Lin Ming, saying that he could defend against any of Lin Ming’s hidden killer moves. The truth was that he wasn’t too sure, but as long as he could block all of these attacks, then victory was his! If he couldn’t block them, then nothing but death awaited him!

“Other moves?” Lin Ming faintly smiled. “I don’t need to. Dealing with you, just this move is enough!”

His mind touched upon the Heretical God Seed. Lin Ming’s Heretical God Force opened to 80%!

Chasing Thunder!

Before Yan Hu had a chance to respond, Lin Ming became one with his spear, turning into a dazzling beam of light!

A purple flash of light pierced through space. It was like a god throwing down a purple spear!

Kacha!

This strike was even more violent than the one before it. The absolute defense of earth was shattered by this lightning, causing all of the origin energy fluctuations to collapse and be destroyed. Yan Hu gave a pitiful cry as he flew backwards. More spear lights flushed into his body, causing him to shake and spit out a mouthful of blood.

Whilst Yan Hu’s body was still high in the air, Lin Ming had instantly appeared on the other end of the martial arena stage!

This sudden change caused everyone present to widen their eyes. However, they too didn’t have enough time to respond. Lin Ming spun his spear and swiveled around.

Heretical God Force – 100%!

Chasing Thunder!

With this third Chasing Thunder, Lin Ming turned into a bright ray of light again. Spear light spread through the entire martial arena!

Bang!

The absolute defense around Yan Hu broke apart like a disintegrating rock, completely ruptured! Blood rained in the air, and Yan Hu fell onto the ground with a loud plop like bag of rotten meat.

The third spear light had completely penetrated his body. All of Yan Hu’s organs were twisted and destroyed by the power of thunder – he died on the spot.

Coming to Skysplit Tower’s third floor, it was necessary for everyone to be mindful of their own death. People here constantly killed each other. Everyone had chosen the path of death.

Over.

Lin Ming stood in the center of the arena stage. He recovered all of the leftover compressed true essence back into the Heretical God Seed and completely restrained his aura. After the violent battle a moment ago, he was now calm. It didn’t seem as if he had consumed too much energy.

All of the martial artists that were discussing the match were stunned silent. They looked at Lin Ming, dumbfounded, without a single word to say.

He had used a total of three consecutive Chasing Thunders!

Every strike was stronger than the last! Especially the last two. They had chained together without end. The first pierce and then the second, all of that happened in less than the blink of an eye!

“How can it be like this… that’s so… unreasonable. This move reaches the extreme in speed, and yet he can use it whenever he wants. Does it not use true essence?”

A martial artist muttered. In his view, the stronger a move was, the faster a strike was, the more energy it should consume. Accelerating to the limit of speed should definitely place a great burden on one’s muscles and skeletons, as well as requiring a massive amount of true essence. But, Lin Ming seemed as if he could use this move as many times as he wanted too. After he used it, he still remained so calm, as if that fight hadn’t even happened.

“The force is so great yet the energy it requires is so little. He can actually use it continuously… this Chasing Thunder is too terrifying!”

“You’re wrong. It isn’t that this move doesn’t require much energy, but instead that Lin Ming’s bodily strength is high and is able to withstand such an extreme speed. At the same time, his endurance and total true essence quantity is alarming. All of these factors together are why he can use this attack like this. If it were you or me instead of him, then after using that move several times our body wouldn’t be able to withstand it!”

It wasn’t known who spoke this, but the atmosphere of the arena fell silent yet again.

Strength, speed, striking power, all of these were abnormal. Not just that, but his defensive power was also freakish. Combined with his endurance and ability to recover, this person simply didn’t have a weakness!

“His strength is close to, or perhaps it can even enter the top 10 ranks on the third floor. Yan Hu wasn’t even able to force out his full strength!”

On the third floor, after reaching the top 10, the strength of the challengers rose yet another level. Especially the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars, their strength went even further. Each and every one of them was a top master that was looked up at and admired by others.

“If this continues then Lin Ming will easily become one of the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars!” A martial artist said with envy.

On Skysplit Tower’s third floor, a Heavenly Demon Seven Star was the symbol of not only strength, but also wealth.

When one reached the level of a Heavenly Demon Seven Star, they would no longer need to worry about having to fight in a match every two months. Not just that, but they received a fixed amount of slaughter points every month. If they subordinated themselves to a High Lord, not only would they be able to receive more slaughter points, but they could use practice areas at high discounts. Naturally, many martial artists were envious of these benefits, but the standards for being chosen were too high. In order to be chosen, one had to have either high strength or amazing talent. Otherwise, it was too difficult to find a High Lord’s favor.

“Lin Ming, victorious! Congratulations Lord Lin, you have obtained the Termination Emblem!” The black-clothed referee said to Lin Ming in an increasingly respectful tone. “For ending his winning streak, you have obtained 12 slaughter points. From a 65 win streak, you have risen to 92, and the reward for that is another three slaughter points. The Termination Emblem’s reward is 50 slaughter points, for a total of 65 slaughter points!”

Gaining 65 slaughter points through a single match could be called suddenly becoming wealthy overnight. Of course, this was mainly because of the Termination Emblem’s contribution. The slaughter points for this emblem could only be rewarded a single time. Next time, there wouldn’t be any.

“I understand.” Lin Ming nodded, and then took off Yan Hu’s spatial ring. He casually put out a hand and the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder flew into Yan Hu’s corpse, taking a random route before bursting out in a fog of blood where a Blood Drinking Seal slowly condensed.

With Lin Ming’s current level, he no longer needed to use the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’. To Lin Ming, the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’ was now a cultivation method. Of course, he referenced the style of this cultivation method in order to achieve a greater mastery of different skills through it.

Lin Ming looked at the Blood Drinking Seal in front of him and pondered for a moment. “If I can use the fusion of the Concepts of Thunder and Fire as a basis and then combine it with the Blood Drinking Seals, and further fuse that into my spear, just what would that be like…”

This idea instantly crossed Lin Ming’s mind. But in his current state, it was far too difficult to do this. Lin Ming was already barely able to fuse the Concepts of Thunder and Fire.

At this moment, a massive amount of infernal energy from Yan Hu’s body rushed into Lin Ming.  After passing through multiple baptisms of infernal energy, Lin Ming had already completely adapted, and no longer needed to revolve the Samsara martial intent to resist it. Instead, he could rely solely on his stubborn consciousness.

Hisssss………….

On Lin Ming’s arm, the Heavenly Demon Tattoo seemed to come to life. The vicious-looking demon’s expression became increasingly clear as the fourth pair of wings slowly formed. Lin Ming began to approach the level of an eight-winged Heavenly Demon more and more.

He was now a late six-winged Heavenly Demon, close to the peak. If this continued, then he would only need to complete two or three more matches before becoming an eight-winged Heavenly Demon.

And, eight-winged Heavenly Demons were all top 10 strengths on the third floor.

“Then, onto the second match! Lin Ming against Ming Sun!”

As the referee loudly announced this, everyone’s eyes shifted towards Ming Sun. Ming Sun was a Fey and also a peak six-winged Heavenly Demon. His winning streak was at 133. His strength was ranked twelfth on the entire third floor!

Suddenly, Ming Sun’s expression turned ugly.

Chapter 583 – Give You One Day to Leave

With his original arrogance dashed away, the Imp visibly withered. But one couldn’t blame him for being so scared. A Titled Asura was simply too terrifying. For instance, take the Eightfall Asura Hao Gan. He finally achieved eight stages of Life Destruction and earned the great title of Eightfall War Emperor.

Among Emperors at his same level, no one was his match. Even old monsters born thousands of years ago greatly feared the Eightfall War Emperor and gave him his due respect.

If one wanted to win against the Eightfall War Emperor, they needed to achieve an absolute superiority through their cultivation. Otherwise, they would be ruthlessly oppressed by the Eightfall War Emperor.

Thinking that Lin Ming would become such a person in the future, the Imp felt his scalp tingle.

If he truly offended such a person, then even Skysplit Tower would not be able to protect him. Thus, he nodded and timidly said, “Sir Lin, this little servant will leave first.”

The Imp left like he was fleeing. He didn’t dare to mention the matter of pledging allegiance again to Lin Ming.

What a joke. Of Skysplit Tower’s 12 High Lords, besides the Chief High Lord who was also the Tower Master, the other 11 High Lords weren’t even heaven-step Asuras. There were also many of them who weren’t even earth-step Asuras, so how could they expect a Titled Asura to subordinate himself to them?

There were many names on the King Tablet, but that was the total accumulation of 10,000 years. It was the converging of all the heroic young talents of the entire Holy Demon Continent. Let alone a heaven-step Asura, even an ordinary Asura was a peerless genius of their generation.

The Imp rushed to the transmission array as fast as he could, directly passing to the fourth floor where the High Lord was.

“Sir Heian, there is very bad news!”

The Imp was originally short. Coupled with his fat body, he looked like a round bouncing ball as he rushed up, stumbling and rolling through the corridor.

High Lord Heian frowned as he looked at the panicked Imp. He coldly shouted, “What are you so flustered about?!”

The plump Imp knelt on the ground, out of breath, “Sir, it’s bad, Lin Ming has become a Titled Asura and earned the smelting trial qualifications!”

“I know already!” High Lord Heian coldly replied, his face glowering. In truth, he was among the first to learn that Lin Ming had become a Titled Asura. He had no need for this man to tell him that again.

When he first learned this news he was also alarmed, completely horrified. A Titled Asura… there was too much meaning behind that. This sort of character even surpassed the scope of Skysplit Tower. It involved the race war of the entire Holy Demon Continent!

As the Imp saw High Lord Heian remain silent, he didn’t know what to make of things. He weakly proposed, “Sir… Lin Ming promised a moment ago that he wouldn’t be enemies with us. Perhaps we can take a look at this and… change our strategies. We can remain on good terms with Lin Ming and not provoke him… if we do, then in the future…”

“Humph! Stupid!” High Lord Heian coldly shouted. The Imp was frightened. He instantly prostrated on the floor, no longer daring to say anything more.

“That Eightfall War Emperor is already the best example. If we raise a tiger then that is just drawing disaster back onto us! It will inevitably bite back! If we let another human become a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon and they later become a Divine Sea Supreme Elder, then the foundation of the Blood Slaughter Steppes will be shaken!”

High Lord Heian no longer thought that Lin Ming might sign the soul contract to obey Skysplit Tower. A talent of this level was a dragon in a deep pool; their potential was limitless. How would they be willing to let others put shackles on them? Let alone him, even that heaven-step Asura Feng Shen refused to sign the soul contract. They were individuals whose pride reached the pinnacle. Would they ever be willing to be dogs for other people?

However, Feng Shen’s background was extraordinary. The powerhouse behind him negotiated with the Tower Master and received a personal guarantee. Finally, Skysplit Tower was willing to compromise.

But Lin Ming was different. No one had managed to discover what major power lay behind Lin Ming, supporting him. But even if they did, that power could only be an enemy.

This was because Lin Ming was a human.

Just the Eightfall War Emperor caused Skysplit Tower to have restless nights, so how could they allow another human to rise to the position of a Supreme Elder and threaten the Blood Slaughter Steppes?

High Lord Heian was bleak as he stood up. He strode directly towards the meeting hall…

……………………

Lin Ming looked at the door of light in front of him. Behind this door of light was a minor dimension. This was the King’s Cage for a Titled Asura! This Skysplit Tower simply had too many sealed dimensions within it. It was hard to imagine who was the one that initially created Skysplit Tower.

Behind Lin Ming were many martial artists standing around. They were onlookers.

Two hours ago, Lin Ming became a Titled Asura. This news already spread through the third floor like a blazing tornado. Nearly everyone had heard this unbelievable news.

Prior to this, a Titled Asura was like a fairy tale to them. They never imagined that such a thing would happen near them. This event gave off too fantastical a feeling, as if they were living a dream.

In just a few minutes, a massive number of martial artists had gathered at the special practice area entrance. They all wanted to take a gander at the stone tablet. But, there weren’t actually many that had the authority to enter. Most of them could only join in on the fun by watching through the other side of the door.

After seeing the King Tablet, others couldn’t help but sigh in praise. Some people even used a battle array disc to record a phantom image of the name so that others outside could see.

But more people even went to the entrance of the King’s Cage, waiting for Lin Ming to enter.

At this moment, no one in the room was speaking. Most of them were just curiously looking at the door to the King’s Cage, wanting to know what the difference was with a Titled Asura level King’s Cage.

“Sir Lin, entering the King’s Cage requires 20 slaughter points. In your life, you can only enter the King’s Cage one time, and your skeletal age must be less than 30 years too. There is no time limit inside. Are you ready to enter?” Deacon Bai respectfully asked.

“I am!”

Regardless of what rank King’s Cage one entered, it still cost 20 slaughter points.

By obtaining a high level smelting trial qualification, the benefits were naturally much greater.

If one only obtained normal Saint level qualifications, or even an ordinary qualification, then there wasn’t much meaning in entering.

The qualification one obtained all depended on their own individual ability. A Titled Asura level King’s Cage was a rare experience. It was said that after the Eightfall War Emperor entered the King’s Cage, he was then able to comprehend the Laws of Space and Time. This set down the solid foundation for his future achievement of becoming an unstoppable powerhouse within his level!

However, everyone’s fortunes within the King’s Cage were different. Lin Ming wouldn’t necessarily be the same as the Eightfall War Emperor. Whether he could come across the Concept of Space or something else was unknown.

“Sir Lin, please confirm that you have sufficient food and water. In addition, this is an escape talisman. Upon entering the King’s Cage, it is possible that you will encounter an extremely dangerous or life-threatening situation. If you find that you cannot withstand it, then you can use this escape talisman to exit.”

As Deacon Bai spoke, he gave Lin Ming a transmission talisman.

Although this was a talisman, it was actually carved from jade. It was similar to the escape symbol that Mu Fengxian had given to Lin Ming. The escape symbol could transmit one to a farther distance and also any space, whilst the escape talisman that Deacon Bai gave him could only transmit one to a fixed point within Skysplit Tower, not just that, but it was a very short distance.

“Thank you Deacon Bai.” Lin Ming had a good impression of this Deacon Bai. He didn’t think he would need to use this transmission symbol, but the longer he stayed in the King’s Cage, the greater his harvests would be.

Although he thought that, the truth was that it was impossible to stay in the King’s Cage forever. The longer one stayed in, the more difficult it became. At some point it would become unbearable and thus they he would have to leave.

Generally, a heroic young elite from a top fourth-grade sect or a bottom fifth-grade sect would be able to stay in the King’s Cage for around 10 days of time.

On a higher step, those young outstanding youths that were listed as Asuras on the King Tablet could last 15 days to a month.

For instance, the number one ranked Heavenly Demon Seven Stars and also a heaven-step Asura, Feng Shen, was able to stay inside for 28 days.

As for the worse Yan Chi, who was listed as an earth-step Asura, he stayed within for 21 days.

According to legends, almost 3000 years ago, the person that stayed in the King’s Cage for the longest period of time was the Eightfall War Emperor. He stayed inside for an entire two months!

Beneath the Eightfall War Emperor was the Netherworld Asura Mo Kun, who stayed inside for 45 days.

There were great disparities even between Titled Asura.

As for the first Sky Ghost Asura Shentu Hongxi, because those were events from 8000 years ago, the records were unclear and there were several versions of myths. It was unknown how long the real Shentu Hongxi stayed within the King’s Cage.

After taking several deep breaths and adjusting his condition to its peak, Lin Ming’s eyes burned with a brilliant fighting spirit. He was earnestly awaiting the challenge of the King’s Cage!

As he was about to step forwards, at this moment, a voice called out for him.

“Stop right there!”

Mm?

Lin Ming turned around to see that the representative that High Lord Heian sent out had reappeared. And, in front of him was a Giant Demon wearing a black suit of armor with a cape thrown over his shoulder. His body was solid and tight as if it were sculpted of iron, his muscles nearly bursting from his armor. His eyes seemed to flash like lightning.

From this Giant Demon man’s body, Lin Ming sensed a terrifying aura. This fellow was absolutely a master!

Lin Ming frowned, “What is it?”

Around Lin Ming, many other martial artists saw the caped man and their expressions changed.

“Maha!”

“Maha is the third ranked amongst the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars!”

Some people immediately recognized the caped Giant Demon’s identity. On Skysplit Tower’s third floor, Maha’s strength far surpassed Da Gu’s.

“This fellow is Maha?” As Lin Ming looked at the caped Giant Demon, he was slightly startled. He had already heard of Maha’s name all the way back in Sun Flood City.

“You are Lin Ming!” Maha looked at Lin Ming, his pitch black eyes seemed as if they could see through Lin Ming.

“Why are you looking for me?”

“Hehe.” Maha’s laugh was like gravel. “There are some things that I wish to talk to you about. Come with me.”

“No need. If you need to say something, then say it here. I’m busy with my practice.” Lin Ming’s voice was calm, but it carried a faintly keen aura.

“Humph.” After being directly rejected by Lin Ming, Maha was a bit annoyed. “Your practice can wait!”

“The High Lord has spoken. He gives you one day to leave Skysplit Tower. You’ve already been at Skysplit Tower for over a year and a half. You’ve already gained a great harvest here. You’ve accumulated a great deal of infernal energy, made gains in practice, and also become extremely wealthy. People should know just how far they can reach, and be content with what they have lest they overreach.” Maha used a true essence sound transmission to speak. This sort of implicit threat went against Skysplit Tower’s rules. Naturally, he couldn’t speak publicly.

“You want me to leave? I’ve just obtained the qualifications to enter the Titled Asura King’s Cage, and you want me to leave? Is there anything more ridiculous in this world?” Lin Ming angrily laughed. If he left here, then he’d really be letting others bully him to the extreme.

Chapter 585 – Heavenly Demon Force Field

“Penetrating Rainbow!”

Lin Ming gave a loud shot, opening the Heretical God Force to the limit. On the Purple Comet Spear, the Concepts of Thunder and Fire began to unceasingly blend together. Man and spear became one, turning into a comet that smashed into the black barrier.

Bang!

The black barrier viciously trembled. Under the impact of this unrivaled force, the black barrier completely shattered.

Lin Ming ran out of the King’s Cage once more.

“Third!”

Lin Ming had continuously broken through three cages. To him, this wasn’t too difficult.

At this time, a fluid conscious thought entered into Lin Ming’s mind once again, passing a wordless message to him.

“Mm? After breaking through the first three cages, that completes the basic test for a Titled Asura and I can choose to leave after…”

Lin Ming saw that not too far away, a light appeared out of thin air. After a while, it actually formed into a transmission array. According to what he had just learned, he could leave the King’s Cage as long as he stepped into the transmission array.

“Should I leave the King’s Cage or continue practicing?

“Of course I’ll continue!”

Lin Ming estimated that only four hours or so had passed since he entered. He certainly wouldn’t leave so soon.

Xiu! Xiu! Xiu!

Beams of light fell down like rain, but this time they were no longer black. Instead, they were seven-colored like a bright spring rainbow.

Lin Ming could feel that there was a very big difference between the light from now and before. But how, he actually couldn’t say.

“Interesting!”

As the rainbow light formed into a new King’s Cage around Lin Ming, his true essence constantly revolved within him. The Heretical God Force began to brilliantly burn…

At night, within the special practice area of Skysplit Tower, dozens of golden seals were floating in the air. A caped old Imp was standing there, drawing with a red painted brush as he constantly drew new seals in space. The seals connected to each other, as if they were isolating an entire space.

Behind this old Imp was High Lord Heian. He was expressionlessly watching the old Imp’s actions, silent, until the black caped Imp finished drawing up the first section of seals. High Lord Heian then asked, “Master Suo Ge, how long will the great spatial lock array you’re laying down need to be completed?”

“Around two days.” The old Imp said.

Suo Ge was the greatest array master within the Blood Slaughter Steppes. He was simultaneously skilled in current array formations as well as having deeply studied ancient array formations.

When Suo Ge was young he had suffered a grievous injury, causing the demon crystal within him to break. Although he had been able to maintain his life through liberal use of high quality pills, his injury was too heavy, causing permanent damage that couldn’t be restored. This caused his cultivation to be forever stranded within the Demon King realm.

Since it was hopeless for him to attempt further cultivating, Suo Ge used the remainder of his time to thoroughly research and analyze array formations.

Through coincidence, he found his own lucky chance, obtaining a small portion of a legacy concerning ancient arrays. After studying them through meditation, his understanding of ancient arrays reached a very high level.

“Mm, good. Then for these two days, I’ll temporarily close this area away from the public so you can feel at ease while you lay down the array. There must not be any mistakes.

“Of course.” Suo Ge said as he returned to drawing the array.

The dimension of the King’s Cage led to a transmission array in Skysplit Tower. After finishing with the smelting trial, a martial artist would need to pass through this transmission array in order to leave.

This was an array formation that belonged to Skysplit Tower itself. Suo Ge naturally didn’t have the ability to alter it.

But, what he could do was use a roundabout way and block the surrounding space around the transmission array, trapping Lin Ming within the King’s Cage.

“Master Suo Ge, how long can this great spatial lock array be maintained for?” High Lord Heian asked.

“Probably around four months.”

“Four months is enough.” High Lord Heian’s lips curved up in a sinister smile. If Lin Ming was trapped in the King’s Cage for four months, then he didn’t believe he would be able to return alive.

Once the King’s Cage surpassed the limit that a martial artist could bear, it would turn into a life-threatening situation. Otherwise, martial artists wouldn’t be given escape talismans.

Even so, there had been many martial artists that had perished within the King’s Cage.

For a Titled Asura to die within the King’s Cage… that would certainly be entertaining news.

Although this would arouse the suspicions of many people, High Lord Heian couldn’t manage so many matters.

High Lord Heian thought about it again and said, “Master Suo Ge, could you return sometime within four months and reinforce the array formation again.”

“I can.” Suo Ge said.

“Four months added with another four months, altogether eight months. Even if you are a True Dragon, you will still die trapped within the King’s Cage!”

…………………….

Time passed a day at a time. With Lin Ming being immerse in his practice, the notion of time had become blurred to him.

“Break!”

Lin Ming’s spear thrust into the rainbow wall of light. The wall of light fiercely trembled, but after several breaths of shaking, it stopped without the slightest hint of damage on it.

That one strike just now had contained all of Lin Ming’s strength, but it hadn’t even been able to cause a dent. Still, Lin Ming wasn’t impatient. He began to quietly prepare his next attack.

After such a long time in here, Lin Ming had finally discovered the rules of the King’s Cage.

Breaking the King’s Cage didn’t depend on a single strike to reach the standard that could break the cage. Rather, it looked at the total accumulated strike damage to measure whether it achieved the standard.

It was like the cage itself had an invisible life value. Every attack against this barrier would consume a part of this value. When all of this value was depleted, then the cage would naturally break.

At the critical point right before the peak, even a random punch would shatter the cage.

In other words, as long as one had enough time, they could continuously break through these cages.

Currently, Lin Ming had already been stuck inside these rainbow colored walls of light for two or three days.

However, as time passed, he began to discover that something suspicious was happening. This rainbow colored cage began to be filled with an invisible energy field.

At the beginning, this faint energy field only disturbed Lin Ming’s inner true essence a little. Afterwards, with time, the energy field began to grow increasingly strong, until it reached the point that it affected Lin Ming’s entire body, forming a heavy pressure upon him.

From his flesh to his organs, meridians, dantian, everything was enveloped in this heavy pressure. His heartbeat became heavier, and the blood in his veins seemed to flow like molasses. Even his true essence circulation was no longer smoothly travelling through his meridians. Even a breath took more effort than normal.

After some time, even Lin Ming’s soul came under its effect.

Lin Ming was startled. He felt that this invisible energy field had already penetrated deep into his spiritual sea where it began to intensely collide with the black vortex of the Samsara martial intent.

“What is this?”

Lin Ming had never experienced such a strange energy field like this.

At this moment, a voice appeared in Lin Ming’s mind.

“This is the Heavenly Demon martial intent.”

What?

Heavenly Demon martial intent!

Lin Ming was shocked. After one became a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon, they could obtain the Heavenly Demon martial intent. Once this special martial intent activated, it could form a ‘domain’ around the possessor. This was the so-called ‘force field’.

Every time someone stepped into this domain, they would come under the influence of this force field, only able to use 50 to 60% of their full strength.

The weaker one was, the greater the effects of the Heavenly Demon martial intent would be on them.

“I see. So that’s how it is. The Heavenly Demon martial intent creates pressure on a person’s body and soul. Thus, this would influences a martial artist’s strength. If a martial artist was particularly weak, then they wouldn’t be able to withstand entering this energy field, and would vomit blood or even die.

“If someone was enveloped by this energy field and had to constantly attack with all of their effort, then the load on their muscles, meridians, and organs could be imagined. No wonder some martial artists can only last for several days.”

Lin Ming was suddenly enlightened. In this case, if a martial artist had to squeeze out all of their potential to the limit, their harvests would be great if they could withstand it. But, if they couldn’t then it wasn’t a surprise if they died.

After withstanding this pressure, Lin Ming attacked the rainbow colored cage again and again.

Because the flow of his true essence was hindered, every attack consumed much more energy than before.

With the constant increasing of the energy field’s pressure, he felt his body becoming notably heavy, and from his head to his toes, every place felt uncomfortable.

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

On the rainbow colored barrier, the light of thunder and fire coalescing together blazed brilliantly.

But in this non-stop attack, Lin Ming discovered that under this great pressure, the benefits he received were much greater than what he imagined they would be.

If a martial artist’s meridians were a canal and the dantian was the source of water, then the muscles, skeletons, and organs were the farmland that needed to be irrigated.

After reaching the Xiantian realm, whether a martial artist was cultivating or attacking, the acupoints throughout their body would be constantly absorbing heaven and earth origin energy, gathering it into the dantian before releasing it into the meridians where it spread throughout the body.

This sort of passive method of transportation had a considerable limitation, and that was no matter what happened, it was difficult for the heaven and earth origin energy to penetrate deep into every part of the body.

Normally, whether it was combat or practice, even if the body’s energy was consumed to the limit and one was incomparably exhausted, there would always be some acupoints and meridians that weren’t used.

If the body didn’t thoroughly experience this, then it would affect one’s foundation, interfering with the growth of their strength.

But this Heavenly Demon martial intent energy field was different. This force field was a wondrous state. Not only was it formless and invisible, but it could easily penetrate into every tiny cell within the body; not even hair would be left out.

Heartbeat, blood flow, muscles, skeleton, marrow, meridians, every part of the body no matter how small had to overcome the suppression of this energy field. They would need to autonomously absorb true essence and also use that true essence.

This process was an exceedingly good experience.

In this energy field, even if one stood stock still, it would still be a form of practice, much less now when one had to make all sorts of high intensity attacks under extreme conditions.

The benefits to the body were massive.

Not only would the essence gathering system be tempered, but the body transformation system was the same.

As for someone like Lin Ming who had a dual cultivation of energy and body, this was simply a paradisiacal environment.

After realizing this, Lin Ming became thrilled. His attacks became increasingly swift and fierce.

As spear lights kept thrusting towards a single point, Lin Ming opened the Heretical God Force as he combusted the blood of the Ancient Phoenix!

With his entire body having to withstand this massive pressure as well as the crazy amount of true essence absorption, this sudden and intense change caused some of the blood vessels near the surface of his skin to directly burst open!

“No stopping here!”

Bang!

With a thunderous explosion, the entire rainbow colored cage shattered like glass!

Lin Ming gasped, dragging in deep breaths. Some of the muscles on his arms were torn open and dripping with blood.

He had consumed 70 to 80% of his true essence and his body was terribly tired. However, the advantages he obtained were great. He discovered that unconsciously, his late Xiantian realm cultivation was becoming more stabilized. He had begun to take steps towards the extreme Xiantian realm!

Chapter 586 – Chaos Prison

From the late Xiantian to extreme Xiantian, this increase in cultivation wouldn’t cause Lin Ming’s relative strength to rise by much.

But from extreme Xiantian to Revolving Core, that was a massive leap!

Within the Sky Spill Continent, a Xiantian martial artist could be haughty and arrogant within a small mortal country. But, a Revolving Core master could actually dominate their own area, creating their own sect.

After swallowing down some recovery pills, Lin Ming didn’t even have time to heal before a new cage came shrouding down on him, closing him in once more.

But the Heavenly Demon force field hadn’t weakened in the slightest. It still enveloped Lin Ming, making it difficult for him to even regenerate his wounds.

“Once this Heavenly Demon force field comes down, it won’t weaken even if I break apart the cage. As long as I stay in the King’s Cage, every day I do means I will have to withstand the pressure of the Heavenly Demon force field for another day!”

This covered every tiny unit in his body, and even his soul came under heavy pressure. This feeling left one gasping for breath. And what was most frightening was that the Heavenly Demon force field slowly strengthened over time.

This was why even a top talent like Feng Shen could only stay within the King’s Cage for 28 days.

He was too exhausted.

If this was normal practice, then after someone exhausted all of their true essence they could just sit in meditation for several hour and then take a long sleep to recover all their physical strength.

But in the King’s Cage, they had to resist the pressure of the Heavenly Demon force field even when they were sleeping, constantly consuming true essence.

If a martial artist with a poor recovery rate came and his rate of true essence consumption was higher than what he could recover in meditation, how could he persist in the King’s Cage?

However, consumption of energy was not a problem to Lin Ming. In terms of endurance and resilience, he was superior to even those old first stage Life Destruction monsters! Of course, his strength was far weaker than theirs.

Time passed day by day. Lin Ming didn’t know how much time passed, but no matter how prodigious his resilience was, after facing such heavy pressure constantly in this environment, he still felt his mind and body sliding into collapse.

Of his entire body, there was no point that wasn’t distressed. Even his spiritual sea was bearing this tremendous pressure.

This caused Lin Ming to be especially startled. His soul defensive strength was in no way inferior to a  Life Destruction powerhouse’s, but if even he felt such a weight on his soul, then other people’s situations could be inferred.

“This is truly worthy of a Titled Asura smelting trial. If the Eightfall War Emperor could last for two whole months here, then he was certainly a proud son of heaven amongst his generation…”

……………

Skysplit Tower, special practice area.

A light flashed and a white-robed youth left the practice area, silently looking at the King’s Cage. This young man was the first ranked master of Skysplit Tower’s third floor, Feng Shen.

At this time, the door of light leading to the King’s Cage was calmly flowing, like a ocean weave in a gentle breeze.

However, under this seemingly calm appearance, Feng Shen was well aware as to how great the pressure within the King’s Cage would rise to be.

Today was already the 40th day!!!

When Feng Shen entered the King’s Cage, he had only been able to stay within for 28 days.

The duration that one could persist inside had nothing to do with one’s individual cultivation. Rather, it looked at a martial artist’s talent, tenacity, perseverance, will, cultivation, and other factors that affected it.

Thinking back to his experience in the King’s Cage, Feng Shen still had a lingering fear. As he nearly finished the 28th day, the pressure suddenly rose by another level. It was horrible to the point of tearing his meridians and crushing his soul.

As a last resort, Feng Shen had to use the escape talisman to leave.

“40 days… that already approaches the level of the Netherworld Asura. This is a talent that challenges the heavens themselves. Him and I were both born in the same era. I don’t know whether that is luck or misfortune…”

Feng Shen shook his head, turned his eyes and walked away.

Five days passed in a flash.

45 days!

This was a time equal to the Netherworld Asura. The news quickly spread through the third floor like wildfire.

This implication of this was that Lin Ming’s talent already surpassed the Netherworld Asura’s!

This was truly a legendary achievement. Towards Lin Ming, the martial artists of the third floor felt admiration, envy, jealousy, veneration, love, every single viewpoint could be found.

Lately, a great number of martial artists either wittingly or unwittingly passed by the special practice area every day, wanting to see if that was the time that Lin Ming would come out.

The number of days continued to increase.

46 days, 47 days, 48 days… 50 days!

As long as he could stay within for another 10 days, then that was the record of the Eightfall War Emperor!

If so, then that was truly a heaven-piercing achievement!

To this extent, the number of people jealous of Lin Ming actually grew smaller and smaller.

When Lin Ming’s lofty star far surpassed them, their jealous hearts paled. This was because they were simply not on the same level, so there was no point in competing with him. Instead, these individuals would rather witness the birth of a miracle in front of them.

“Humph! What a group of idiots! Do they really think that Lin Ming has lasted until now?” In a luxurious restaurant in the vicinity of the practice area, Yan Chi was drinking wine, sneering at the crowd gathered outside the special practice area.

In front of him were Maha and Kai Yang.

These three people had pledged their allegiance to Skysplit Tower one year ago. Because they signed a soul contract, they were loyal to Skysplit Tower. Naturally, High Lord Heian had no need to hide the truth from them.

They were already aware that Lin Ming would never emerge from the King’s Cage.

“50 days. Lin Ming most likely died inside. Although he was a truly prodigious character, he was still not on the same level as the Eightfall War Emperor. Even if he could compare with the Eightfall War Emperor, it wouldn’t matter anyway. High Lord Heian has already decided to seal the King’s Cage for eight months. Even if Lin Ming was the reincarnation of a demon god, there’s nothing he could do about it.” Maha sneered from the side while throwing some dried fruits into his mouth.

“Hehe, I really want to see these people’s expressions after another three or four months; I will be ecstatic. They all think that Lin Ming can create some sort of miracle, but none of them will know that Lin Ming has already died. A Titled Asura level talent has actually died in Skysplit Tower, how ironic is that!” Kai Yang repulsively grinned as he stroked his wrinkled chin. In his heart, he was thinking it was unfortunate that there was a Demon God Bone in Lin Ming’s spatial ring.

Kai Yang had also seen this Demon God Bone before. It was the size of pigeon’s egg. For it to be left within the King’s Cage without knowing whether or not it would ever come out was simply a great waste.

“Let’s go. The High Lord has made an exception and opened up the Divine Image Hall for us. We will each have 10 days to meditate inside and learn as much as we can. Let’s go back and prepare so that we’re in our best condition for it. We can’t miss this opportunity.”

“Mm, let’s go.”

…………………….

In the King’s Cage, the Heavenly Demon force field’s pressure rose another level. These past days, Lin Ming had discovered another rule, and that was that the Heavenly Demon force field’s pressure would rise another level every 10 days!

During this grueling process, Lin Ming’s body was constantly adapting towards this higher pressure. His body, meridians, all of these were being tempered and unceasingly strengthening.

As the Heavenly Demon force field grew stronger, so did Lin Ming.

“Mm… this is?”

When a new cage came falling down, Lin Ming was startled. This time, the cage was completely different from the usual barriers of light.

Fu—!

Everything in front of him turned pitch-black, chaotic. He couldn’t see anything at all!

A thick darkness manifested into reality, fusing together with the Heavenly Demon force field. An overwhelming force enveloped everything, making Lin Ming feel as if he were suffocating!

This chaotic darkness contained a great resistance. Even moving was extremely difficult.

Lin Ming felt as if he had sunk deep into a quagmire. He couldn’t see anything. Even when he released his perception, it was blocked by this chaotic darkness.

His perception could only extend a single inch outwards from his body!

To a martial artist, this was no different than blinding them.

Lin Ming’s chest ached. He tried to breathe, but the amount of air he inhaled was pathetic.

Could the Eightfall War Emperor have been defeated at this pass?

Lin Ming carefully thought back. When he had first entered the King’s Cage, it had been around 10 days before he encountered the bitter taste of the Heavenly Demon force field.

This could also explain why the worst of all martial artists could only last 10 days in the King’s Cage before they were defeated. This was probably because they couldn’t withstand the beginning of the Heavenly Demon force field.

Then, Lin Ming began to count. The Heavenly Demon force field had strengthened around five times by now. If he wasn’t wrong, then 50 days had passed. In addition to the 10 days at the start, this was his 60th day. This was the same time that the Eightfall War Emperor had forced out!

What kind of amazing character was the Eightfall? He had crossed eight stages of Life Destruction while grasping the Concepts of Space and Time, then becoming a great Emperor that was peerless within his level. As a human, he overcame all odds and earned the title of 12-winged Heavenly Demon within Skysplit Tower!

But he had been defeated at this stage! This proved just how difficult this part of the trial was!

“Senior Eightfall was defeated here. Then, let me see just how far I can go!”

Lin Ming roared out and the Heretical God Seed erupted. His skeletons began to issue popping sounds as the faint cry of a dragon emerged from within his body.

The Purple Comet Spear lay horizontal. On the spear point, the power of thunder and fire wove together.

Penetrating Rainbow!

A spear thrust out. A radiant spear cut through the stick black chaos, a ripple shaped thrust penetrating dozens of feet far away!

However, this strike ended here. The spear light was eventually swallowed by the black chaos. The three foot wide hole and the spiral ripples that extended dozens of feet out slowly vanished.

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed. He took an immediate step forwards and crashed into that spiral shaped tunnel he had formed. In a single step, he jumped a hundred feet forwards. But then, he was suddenly engulfed once more by that black chaos!

The resistance suddenly increased. Every step Lin Ming took was beset with hardship!

Without a doubt, this sticky black chaos was the King’s Cage of this round!

In the last cage, as long as one had enough striking power, they could break through it sooner or later. But now this current cage, no matter how fierce one’s attack was, it would eventually fade away into this regenerating darkness that had manifested into existence.

He could only rely on his own two feet to leave!

Lin Ming took out several dozen high-grade Blood Demon Crystals from his spatial ring. In a single breath he sucked dry all of their heaven and earth origin energy as well as their blood vitality.

Eight Inner Hidden Gates – Gate of Healing, open!

Bang!

Between Lin Ming’s clavicles, a white light began to shine!

Lin Ming had only touched upon the threshold of the Gate of Healing – he hadn’t actually opened it yet. If he forcefully used the Gate of Healing’s strength, then it would instantly place a great burden on his body.

After touching the Gate of Healing, a powerful resiliency and strength came gushing out.

Lin Ming aimed at the direction he started moving in and thrust out his spear!

The spear light pierced through the black chaos. Lin Ming moved forwards, one step at a time.

Lin Ming didn’t know how large this black chaos was, or whether this was the correct method to leave this chaos prison. But he had no choice.

All he could do was move forwards!

Chapter 587 – Perhaps, Him Alone In 10,000 Years

Two months, and Lin Ming still hadn’t come out!

As the time passed 61 days, the news rapidly spread throughout Skysplit Tower. The time that Lin Ming had been in the King’s Cage for had already surpassed the Eightfall War Emperor’s record!

This was the creation of a new legend! The only one to do so in 10,000 years!

Soon, not only did the martial artists of the third level know, but even those of the second floor and first floor. Although these people didn’t know what it meant to stay in the King’s Cage for two months, what they did know was that Lin Ming was the first to do so in the last recorded 10,000 years. Even the mortals in Skysplit Tower were awed by this.

“The first in 10,000 years. I never thought this could happen, ever!”

In a simple teahouse, Muk Gu was sampling tea, listening to the surrounding martial artists speak. He had been on the second floor for the last several days visiting his sister, and now that he learned this, he felt it a bit incredible himself.

“Maybe after a few dozen more years, the Holy Demon Continent will have another Eightfall War Emperor!”

In front of Muk Gu, Muk Qing was eating cake. She thought for a moment and said, “It’s been a year and a half since I first saw him. I never thought that he’d turn out so fierce… Senior-apprentice Brother, do you think that we can win him over?”

“Win him over? With what? We are just an ordinary fifth-grade sect. We don’t even know what sort of background Lin Ming has. It’s impossible for a talent of this degree to just come out of nowhere. He might have some top powerhouse as his master.”

Muk Gu shook his head and continued to stir his tea. He took another sip and said, “A character like this, it’s impossible for us to draw him in; it’s already fortunate enough if we can remain on good terms with him. Although the first time we met was relatively bad, afterwards I think I eliminated any problems. I could consider us as having a bit of friendship.”

Within the Holy Demon Continent, humans had been in a miserably position or a long time. Muk Gu was glad to see a top human powerhouse be born in front of his eyes.

Of course, if he could remain on good terms with Lin Ming then that would also be a great benefit to his sect.

………………………

Time passed slowly. Soon, it had been 70 days!

On the third floor, the news had already passed on. Rumors were spreading crazily. Every day, there would be a massive amount of martial artists rushing towards the special practice area, wanting to see if Lin Ming would come out.

He had actually stayed in the King’s Cage for 10 days longer than the Eightfall War Emperor. Just what sort of monstrous talent was this?

“70 days…”

Feng Shen quietly watched the door of light leading to the King’s Cage, his eyes flashing with a cold light. Before now, he never thought that Lin Ming would be able to reach this degree.

Feng Shen had once been immeasurably proud of his talent. But now, he had been far surpassed by Lin Ming.

“Hehe, Feng Shen, this is the first time seeing such an expression on your face.” A voice suddenly sounded out.

Feng Shen turned to see Kai Yang.

Kai Yang rubbed his chin, smiling as he looked towards the door of light leading to the King’s Cage, a look of indifference on his face. “Feng Shen, this isn’t like you at all. Aren’t you usually so high and mighty? Since when did you have such a startled appearance?”

Feng Shen frowned. With his prideful attitude, he usually never interacted with anyone – he simply disdained speaking to these people.

In Feng Shen’s eyes, Kai Yang was nothing but a dog that worked for resources. Such a person could make a bit of progress, but their will and mind were not strong. It was impossible for someone like this to soar into the sky!

Without a word, Feng Shen turned and left.

Seeing Feng Shen’s response, Kai Yang was a bit displeased. He coldly snorted and said, “Do you think Lin Ming is still practicing inside? Do you really believe he has the talent to surpass the Eightfall War Emperor? Hehe, maybe he’s already died inside.”

In the King’s Cage, there was always the risk of death.

Before the creation of the escape talismans, there was an extremely high chance that a martial artist would perish within the King’s cage. A great number of martial artists believed that they could withstand the pressure from the Heavenly Demon force field. In order to squeeze out all their potential and improve even more, they would break through a cage, getting more and more until finally, the pressure from the Heavenly Demon force field grew too much. At that time, as attacking became more and more difficult, they would finally be unable to break through the cage, resulting in their death within.

After the escape talismans were created, the death rate greatly decreased. But, there were still those who died inside.

It was like a mortal that didn’t sleep for several days while doing high intensity work, this too could cause sudden death. For a martial artist, if they stayed under the massive pressure of the Heavenly Demon force field, their heart, dantian, and soul all came under enormous burden. If this accumulated for a long enough time, then it was possible they could suddenly die!

The heart stopped beating, collapse of the spiritual sea, or even the dantian might explode… in this case, one would die before they had the chance use the escape talisman.

“Die inside?” Feng Shen chuckled, “How could a True Dragon level talent die inside the King’s Cage!?”

“F*ck! What is so great about this Feng Shen! Just because his background is good and his talent is high, he doesn’t keep us in his eyes. If he came from the same background as I did then I wouldn’t need to be so humble in front of him! Shit, I’ll wait and see whether or not you can still say Lin Ming will create a miracle once he’s been inside for 100 days, 120 days! True Dragon level talent, f*ck that!”

Kai Yang muttered to himself, blatantly envious of Lin Ming.

‘Hehe, I wonder what sort of expression you’ll have once you know that Lin Ming died inside the King’s Cage. A pinnacle Emperor level talent actually died in a practice area, hahahaha! Too ironic, too funny, too interesting!’

Thinking of this, Kai Yang viciously smiled, his heart feeling much better. He wanted time to pass faster so that when 100 days passed, he could see whether or not these martial artists were still clamoring for Lin Ming.

75 days…

80 days…

85 days…

………………………

Time passed a day at a time. When the 80th day arrived, some people already suspected that Lin Ming might have died within the King’s Cage. But, this suspicious was not held by the vast majority. After all, he was a peak Emperor level talent. If he died in the King’s Cage, then wouldn’t that be the greatest joke of the world?

However, this rumor began to slowly spread. On the 85th day, more and more people believe that Lin Ming had died!

“What a joke, a Titled Asura whose name is carved into the King Tablet has actually died inside the King’s Cage. Who would believe this if it got out!”

In a restaurant on the third floor, some people were discussing Lin Ming. These days, Lin Ming was the topic of every conversation. He was being talked about in every restaurant and teahouse nearby.

“Even if I don’t want to believe, this is the reality. Maybe Lin Ming was too confident in himself and overestimated his bodily limits, finally doing something stupid.”

“Lin Ming’s most likely dead. Otherwise, 85 days is almost three months. That will almost be a month over the Eightfall War Emperor. Isn’t that just too exaggerated? How could that be possible?”

“Haha! I’m dying from laughter here, it’s too funny, too funny!” A Giant Demon martial artist said as he struck the table. “These past days those human clowns on the third floor have been far too arrogant. They are so proud and happy about someone from their own race having such a great accomplishment, and look, the result is that Lin Ming actually died in the King’s Cage. I’ve never seen something so ridiculously stupid before!”

“His head is damaged. To think that he would die even with an escape talisman. You can’t even make this up, but he’s even a Titled Asura. I can’t stop laughing, this is the funniest joke of the last 1000 years!”

The Giant Demons were mortal enemies with humanity. When Lin Ming was at the height of his power, these Giant Demon martial artists naturally didn’t utter a word. But now that Lin Ming had died, all of the envy and hate they had piled up suddenly exploded out at once.

A human genius was also their competition. If he died, then they were all indescribably happy.

Muk Gu was also in this restaurant. As he heard this conversation, his complexion turned very, very ugly.

He mindlessly took another drink of his wine and then stood to leave.

“Hey, isn’t that the guy? What’s his name?” The Giant Demon martial artist who was speaking saw Muk Gu. On the third floor, Muk Gu’s strength was at the very bottom, so many people didn’t know what his name was.

“I think he’s called Muk Gu.” A nearby Imp reminded.

“Oh. Muk Gu. I remember now, haha. Muk Gu, come and drink some wine with us. Regale us with the glorious stories of Lin Ming, your human race’s top talent!”

The Giant Demon wantonly smiled. After being pressed down by these humans for the last several weeks, he was finally able to release all the stress.

Muk Gu suppressed the simmering anger in his heart and coldly said, “It’s only been 85 days, and you’re already so sure that Lin Ming can’t withstand it anymore? Just because you cannot understand his limits does not mean they exist!”

“I can’t understand his limits? Hahaha! Your words remind me of when I was a child. There was always this other kid that would be beaten up by me. Every time that I knocked his teeth out, he would always say that he would go home and get his father to come out and punch me! How hilarious!”

The Giant Demon martial artist slammed the table as he spoke, ruthlessly taunting Muk Gu.

Muk Gu’s complexion became increasingly ugly but there wasn’t any reason in retorting. In fact, even his own heart was wavering; did Lin Ming really die?

‘Lin Ming, Lin Ming, I’m asking you to hurry… an existence like you is already destined to reach the highest level of this continent in the future… how could you possibly die in the King’s Cage?’

Muk Gu sighed. Was humanity’s destiny really so lacking? Were they truly unable to give birth to a such a glorious and peerless powerhouse?

…………………..

In the King’s Cage, the ground was snow-white and covered by boundless dark clouds.

These dark clouds were very thick and sticky, to the point that one could cut them with a saber. These dark clouds seemed as if they were made of the blackest ink.

The dark clouds quietly undulated. At this time, there was a muffled sound as a small piece of the dark clouds opened, a flash of golden light quickly passing through.

Then, silence. There was nothing again but inky dark clouds.

After another incense stick of time, another golden light flashed. This time, it stayed for a longer time before disappearing again.

The time, the time since the last disappearance was much longer, as if the golden light was condensing in strength. Around an hour later, there was a sound like a dragon crying as a beam of light as thick as a thigh burst through the dark clouds. It was like the sword of a god, directly piercing into the horizon!

In the moment that the dark clouds broke apart, a person’s figure rushed out of the hole created by this beam of light.

This figure tumbled onto the floor like a thunderclap.

“I finally came out!”

Lin Ming lay sprawled on the ground without even the strength to move his fingers. He had been stuck in the chaos prison for nearly an entire month!

This was truly a horrifying and painful experience!

The chaos prison was incomparably thick. Even though Lin Ming used his full force to advance, his speed was still as slow as a crawling turtle.

He had no choice but to use attacks to break open the chaos cage, taking advantage of the moment that the chaos was ripped open to take a few steps forward.

Like this, his speed was quick, but he consumed true essence like he was pouring water away.

It had to be said that even if Lin Ming used his killer move Penetrating Rainbow, he was only able to open a channel a few dozen feet long.

But how big was this chaos cage?

Lin Ming simply didn’t know!

Chapter 589 – Crisis

In the dimensional fragment cage, Lin Ming closed his eyes, moving with Golden Roc Shattering the Void. Under the tremendous pressure, his steps didn’t have any of the usual fleeting vibrancy, instead, it was like they were made of lead.

In this cage of space, his eyes were useless. The space cracks simply couldn’t be seen by the naked eye.

Even his perception was limited.

What Lin Ming could depend on was his understanding towards the Law of Space, and his mastery over the power of space only.

Whenever a space crack quietly approached, Lin Ming could feel the fluctuations emitting from space. The fluctuations were like ripples in the water, appearing out of nowhere.

Every time, Lin Ming would move in advance in order to dodge the space cracks that could cut him open.

With Lin Ming’s strength, even if he had completed Tempering Marrow and his body was comparable to a treasure, or no matter how thick his protective true essence was, in front of these space cracks, it was nothing more than brittle paper.

Woosh!

A purple gold spear light flashed through like a meteor, smashing into the barriers of the space cage!

Kacha!

Spear light erupted. The space barrier trembled just a bit before returning to normal, as if nothing had happened.

These past days, Lin Ming had been constantly attacking the space barrier. Although he hadn’t been able to shake it, Lin Ming, through this nonstop barrage of attacks, was unconsciously deepening his comprehension into the power of space.

But at this moment, Lin Ming’s body trembled. On his shoulder, blood erupted into a crimson rain. The blood was quickly twisted into a red mist by an invisible power before vanishing into an invisible whirlpool.

Lin Ming was shocked; he immediately drew back.

His right shoulder had been completely torn open!

“That was too close!”

Lin Ming’s forehead dripped with a cold sweat. A moment ago, as he was distracted with his attacks, a small space crack the size of a slip of paper had quietly crept towards him. Such a small space crack created extremely small ripples in the void. With Lin Ming’s attention being diverted, his perception wasn’t as sensitive, so he hadn’t been able to sense it.

Such a small space crack, yet such a terrifying destructive power!

“Luckily, it was just my shoulder!”

A chill crept up Lin Ming’s back. When he had entered the ancient ruins of the Demon God Imperial Palace, the space cracks there hadn’t been so horrifying.

At that time, when a second stage Life Destruction Supreme Elder or those stronger flew into the broken world, they didn’t fear those space cracks at all.

Lin Ming felt that although his current strength wasn’t comparable to those old Life Destruction fellows, it shouldn’t have been that far away. But yet, a small space crack the size of a tiny slip of paper had completely torn his shoulder apart!

This showed that in this different world, the power of space cracks was completely different.

In the Demon God Imperial Palace, the broken world that held it was already approaching collapse. The power of space there was too weak.

On the other hand, the world of the King’s Cage was very stable. The more stable a space was, the stronger the power of space was. After space disintegrated and formed space cracks, the dimensional fragments were correspondingly more terrifying!

Who else dared to say that the Concept of Space’s striking power was weak?

If one could truly and completely grasp the Concept of Space, touching upon the source of all space, then with a casual strike, they could tear apart space itself. Who could defend against an attack like this?

If he could soar into the Realm of the Gods, twist the space there and use that incomparably stable space as his weapon, then how powerful would such an ability be?

Although this possibility was fascinating, Lin Ming didn’t have any more time for distractions. He noticed that in the space around him, he found that there were more and more tiny space fragments and space cracks appearing!

The space cracks that had once been 10 feet long had become 3-4 feet long and now, they were only the size of a slip of paper.

If such a space crack pierced his arm or leg, then with Lin Ming’s exceedingly abnormal regenerative ability, he would still be able to live on. But, if it pierced his heart, then Lin Ming suspected that even the Heretical God Seed or the Magic Cube wouldn’t be able to save him.

“There are more and more fragments; these should be because my attacks shattered them.”

The stable space had been torn apart by that strange force field. Now, with Lin Ming’s attacks added on, more and more tiny space fragments started to appear.

“The Heavenly Demon force field’s pressure has increased again!”

This time, the Heavenly Demon force field strengthened yet again. This was undoubtedly one stroke of bad luck after another!

Not only did his body slow down, but his perception was dulled. Lin Ming found it difficult to detect those tiny space fluctuations.

This was like a martial artist being under a rain of arrows and having their vision suddenly blur.

“This is bad!”

Cold sweat rolled down Lin Ming’s back; he had completely lost control of the situation!

Once his time in the King’s Cage surpassed 100 days, Lin Ming was beginning to finally find it hard to persist!

The dimension fragment cage couldn’t be broken and the tiny space fragments were nearly impossible to detect or defend against.

Under this massive pressure, he was even finding it hard to maintain his speed for a long time.

Lin Ming gripped the escape talisman in his hand, hesitating.

In his life, he would only be able to enter the King’s Cage once. During his three months here, he had harvested a great deal. If he left like this, then it would be a bit dismaying.

But in this situation, if he wasn’t careful then he might possibly die inside here. A Titled Asura, perishing in the King’s Cage. Wouldn’t that be just too big of a joke?

However, when four or five space fragments continuously disappeared from Lin Ming’s perception, his complexion finally changed.

He crumpled the escape talisman.

Lin Ming was resolutely determined to leave the King’s Cage.

Ho–!

A transmission array suddenly appeared underneath Lin Ming’s feet. With a flash of light, Lin Ming was covered in the golden light of the escape talisman, his figure blurring.

“Mm?”

Lin Ming’s expression changed. He could clearly feel that he had passed through the space channel and arrived in Skysplit Tower, but the surrounding space had been blocked off!

The transmission channel had been sealed. He had no way to leave!

“What’s going on?”

Peng!

In Lin Ming’s hand, the escape talisman suddenly exploded into dust. The light vanished, and Lin Ming found himself in the space cage once more.

If the space in Skysplit Tower was blocked, then that was the same as eliminating the exit.

Could it be…?

Lin Ming’s mind raced. He wasn’t an idiot. If someone could do this, then there was only one possibility; it was a high level figure of Skysplit Tower!

“A space blocking array formation. Skysplit Tower also seems to have some capable individuals. This sort of array formation is considered complex, even among ancient array formations!” Lin Ming had inherited the memories of a Realm of the Gods’ array master, so he had a great deal of understanding into this sort of array formation. But, to lay it out so that it would forcibly block a transmission array wasn’t an easy task.

“You want me to die in here?” Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a cold light, killing intent blazing in them.

Fuu! Fuu! Fuuu!

Within the space cage, the space fragments flew around. Lin Ming could even hear some of the space fragments colliding with each other, and the sound of space breaking filled the air.

These sounds were clear, but they were actually the sounds of death!

“What should I do!?”

The normally calm Lin Ming was now panicking.

Although he had a good deal of understanding into this sort of space blocking array formation, wanting to break it open was another matter altogether. It would not be easy.

Not mention that Lin Ming couldn’t break it, but even if he believed he could, there was one condition required. This was that he needed a transmission array leading to the center of that blocked space!

To Lin Ming, this was obviously impossible!

Chapter 590 – Betting It All

The transmission array would only appear once this space cage was broken and it would only appear for a short period of time. If Lin Ming wanted to break open the space locking array during that brief period of time, then that was simply unrealistic!

Thinking of this, Lin Ming felt his back go cold.

The tiny space fragments were hidden around him, appearing and disappearing; he simply couldn’t evade them all. If this continued then he would die without a doubt!

Chi!

With a light din, Lin Ming felt a cool touch upon his ear. A space fragment had scraped his ear as it flew by!

Caught up in a space vortex, blood shot out from his ear!

He had been completely unaware of this small fragment. Fortunately, it had brushed past his ear with only a bit of the power of space spreading out. If it had shot into his eyes then the consequences would be have been disastrous!

“What can I do?”

Lin Ming’s mind went into overdrive as he went on full alert.

As he noticed several more tiny space fragments disappear from the field of his perception, a flash of inspiration went off in Lin Ming’s mind – the Cosmic Melting Furnace!

That was it! The Cosmic Melting Furnace had its own world within. He could enter it!

The top treasure of the Demon God Imperial Palace was invaluable; it was at least a heaven-step treasure.

Lin Ming could only open the first layer of the Cosmic Melting Furnace. But… that was enough!

Lin Ming summoned the Cosmic Melting Furnace with the quickest speed possible. He opened the lid and directly rushed in!

Now, this furnace was all he could depend on.

Kacha!

With a snapping sound, the Cosmic Melting Furnace gently quivered. A space fragment struck the side of the Cosmic Melting Furnace, breaking into smaller pieces!

But the Cosmic Melting Furnace only vibrated, not a single mark left on it.

This could be called an artifact treasure. It was naturally not something that a space fragment could break.

Lin Ming let out a cold breath of relief. He was now hidden within the first layer of the Cosmic Melting Furnace. With the lid closed, this was a completely enclosed and separate space. Originally, Lin Ming had also absorbed the Nirvana Dragon Root here.

“Although I can’t use this Cosmic Melting Furnace to attack, it can actually be used to defend in this way.”

Until now, Lin Ming truly hadn’t used the Cosmic Melting Furnace. He didn’t think that it would have uses like this.

“The Heavenly Demon force field’s pressure has also weakened a bit…”

Although Lin Ming was currently within the Cosmic Melting Furnace, he could still clearly feel the pressure from the Heavenly Demon force field, though a majority of it had been isolated.

This pressure was truly pervasive!

Thinking of it, the 12 Skysplit Towers, Blood Slaughter Steppes, and Eternal Demon Abyss were a much more terrible relic of the past than the Demon God Imperial Palace. Otherwise, 12 Emperor level powerhouses wouldn’t have instantly died here. The Six-fingered Sin Fey, who had obtained the title of twelve-winged Heavenly Demon and became the greatest powerhouse of the Holy Demon Continent, had come here on his own volition after experiencing a bottleneck in his 6000 years of cultivation. He had come to the Eternal Demon Abyss to seek his own lucky chances, but had also died inside like everyone else, without even his corpse left.

On the other hand, the Demon God Imperial Palace was much calmer. If a Life Destruction powerhouse went in, then they had a 90% chance of leaving alive.

After all, in the past when the Demon Emperor had founded the Demon God Imperial Palace, he still hadn’t soared up into the Realm of the Gods. No matter how powerful he was, he wouldn’t be more formidable than the mystical force that existed in the Eternal Demon Abyss.

From Da Gu’s description, a massive earth-shattering claw had risen up and instantly killed 12 Emperor level powerhouses, one of them who was a legendary Hallowed Lord. Just thinking about this was horrifying!

Feeling the space fragments strike the Cosmic Melting Furnace, Lin Ming’s eyebrows wrinkled together.

Although he could hide in the Cosmic Melting Furnace for now, he couldn’t do so forever.

If he couldn’t break apart the dimensional fragment cage, then he couldn’t return. Not just that, but the force field pressure in the Cosmic Melting furnace would also be constantly rising. If he retreated into this furnace and wasted his time here, then that was the same as drinking poison to slake his thirst!

When the pressure became stronger, it would be even more difficult to break through the space cage.

What could he do?

Lin Ming was silent for a moment, and then he clenched his teeth. He pulled out a black glass bead from his spatial ring.

This was the Demon God Bone!

According to Da Gu, these were the remnants of Emperor level powerhouses. When an Emperor level Supreme Elder died within the Eternal Demon Abyss, the energy within their body would condense into this essence!

Like pine sap that became amber after being buried in the ground for hundreds of thousands of years, the rich energies in the Eternal Demon Abyss condensed into substantive energy. After an immeasurably long period of time, this energy would naturally crystallize.

This sort of crystal, if he melted it into his life source and used it to nourish the fires of his life, let alone raising his strength, it was even enough for a Demon King powerhouse to break through to become a Demon Emperor. This was a heavenly treasure that a Demon King level martial artist would go crazy over!

Of course, he could also use it to temper his body, but this was an extremely wasteful method. Even a Giant Demon martial artist wouldn’t use it in such an extravagant way.

Tempering the body…

Lin Ming muttered to himself. He had some understandings about the usage of the Demon God Bone from Da Gu, as well as gaining some insights from Maha. This was to integrate the energy of the Demon God Bone into his own life source.

To a human martial artist, this so-called life source was the dantian.

To a Giant Demon martial artist, the life source was their demon crystal.

Lin Ming cultivated humanity’s essence gathering system. Logically, if he absorbed the Demon God Bone then he should absorb it into his dantian.

But Lin Ming didn’t want to do this. He was preparing to use the Demon God Bone to temper his body. This was also called the most wasteful method.

He wanted to take the incomparably rich energy within the Demon God Bone and fuse it into the Gate of Healing, using this to break through the final boundary of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates!

This was the fastest way Lin Ming could think of to make a breakthrough in his strength.

“With my current strength, it shouldn’t be a problem to swallow the Demon God Bone.”

Lin Ming also had some understandings towards the Demon God Bone. Since the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars could use them, he shouldn’t have a problem either.

Of course, swallowing the Demon God Bone was not a problem, but whether he could borrow its power to open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, he was completely unsure. From Tempering Marrow to the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, that was equal to a large increase in realms. There was a gap in the middle of these two that was nearly insurmountable.

From all the brutal requirements Lin Ming needed to complete Tempering Marrow in the past, one could see just how difficult it would be to open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates.

Although he had just barely traced upon the threshold, it was at most equal to being a half-step into the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. It was the same as being a half-step Xiantian or half-step Revolving Core. Even though it was just that minor bit, the difference from truly being at the Xiantian realm or Revolving Core realm was huge.

Success or defeat, all would be bet on this!

With teeth clenched, Lin Ming poured his true essence into the Demon God Bone. As true essence flowed into it, the Demon God Bone gradually softened. It turned into a squishy oblong sphere and then completely turned into liquid.

This black liquid was like ink, but also carried a glassy sheen.

Lin Ming flicked his finger and divided the black liquid in half. Half was swallowed by him, and the other half was placed in the center of his clavicles where the Gate of Healing resided.

When the liquid black Demon God Bone first entered, it was icy cold. But as it entered into his belly, it turned into a blazing fire.

The liquid black Demon God Bone that Lin Ming had placed between his clavicles also felt as if it had caught one fire. With a ‘chi chi’ sound, this black mercurial liquid quickly seeped into his body.

It quickly permeated through his pores and deep into his clavicles where the Gate of Healing was.

The Demon God Bone was originally a supremely tyrannical medicine. With Xing Tian’s strength, he simply wasn’t able to use it.

Lin Ming’s strength naturally far surpassed Xing Tian’s at this moment. By reason, it shouldn’t be a problem for him to use it.

However, what actually happened was beyond Lin Ming’s expectations. He was still under the Heavenly Demon force field, and every cell in his body was resisting this force field. It was impossible for his condition to be at its peak.

While resisting the Heavenly Demon force field, the maddening power of the Demon God Bone manically flowed into his body!

These two forces came from the same source. When the Demon God Bone’s energy merged into Lin Ming’s body, it actually fused together with the force field into one whole. Instantly, Lin Ming felt as if his throat was smoking and there was a demonic fire combusting within his body!

Lin Ming’s cells were originally under a heavy pressure. Now, with the sudden increase in force, some of Lin Ming’s cells directly burst open!

Puff!

Lin Ming coughed up a mouthful of blood. This was blood that was coming from his body bursting apart at the seams!

“Damnit!”

To use the Demon God Bone to open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates was originally a sudden inspiration idea that Lin Ming had. But what would really happen after he swallowed the Demon God Bone was simply unpredictable.

He never thought that the Demon God Bone would actually work so well together with the Heavenly Demon force field. Both of these stemmed from the Eternal Demon Abyss; there simply wasn’t any problem in them fusing together, creating a force that wildly rampaged through Lin Ming’s body.

This was the same as Lin Ming’s body having to withstand double the energy pressure.

Too hot!

This was Lin Ming’s greatest thought. It was like his body had caught on fire. His meridians, dantian, organs, everything surged with a agonizing heat.

It felt like magma was flowing through his body. Lin Ming wanted to use the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ to forcefully suppress this feeling and absorb this manic energy, but he had already consumed over 50% of his true essence and now he was powerless to do any of this.

Puff!

A fog of blood burst out from Lin Ming’s arm. After his blood left the protection of his true essence, it was instantly scorched to ash. Lin Ming’s insides had become a stove.

The energy grew hotter and hotter like a growing inferno. On the other hand, Lin Ming was quickly consuming true essence. Soon, everything would go completely out of control. When this happened, it was possibly that Lin Ming’s body would be completely burnt down by this berserk energy!

Chi chi chi…

That was the sound of the periphery of his meridians being burnt.

“Too hot… too thirsty…”

Clutching his throat, he felt like his clavicles had been incinerated. And this heat had already spread to his throat.

With great effort, he fumbled around his spatial ring hoping to take out some water. But when he reached in, he actually touched something cold.

This is…

Lin Ming took out this object, and was startled to see it was a jade box. Around this jade box there was a faint chill in the air, and a layer of frost was condensing around it.

Opening the jade box, there was a cocoon of electricity. And in this cocoon was the Nameless Divine Pill refined from the Nirvana Dragon Root!

When Lin Ming had first attempted to open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, he had melted a small part of this Nameless Divine Pill’s efficacy and swallowed it. He took what was left over and sealed it away in this jade box.

The smaller Nameless Divine Pill was covered with a blue layer of ice cold frost. Even placed in the jade box one could feel an implicit terrifying ice cold energy. This ancient air that emitted from it seemed to have experienced tens of thousands of years, making one feel suffocated.

Lin Ming could clearly recall that when he had placed this pill into the solar origin spring water, the spring water had directly turned into a lump of ice.

An absolute cold. The piercing cold in that water seemed as if it could freeze his soul.

When he approached it before, his muscles had begun to shiver, and when he touched it, his body was frozen and almost shattered!

Extreme cold! Extreme heat!

Two polar extremes!

Lin Ming suddenly grit his teeth, raised the Nameless Divine Pill and prepared to swallow it!

Chapter 591 – Break Through the Eight Inner Hidden Gates

The Nameless Divine Pill used a Nirvana Dragon Root as a main ingredient, and by combining all sorts of other rare and precious materials, it became a medicine even more brutally tyrannical than the Demon God Bone!

When Lin Min absorbed the Nameless Divine Pill, he had done so by melting its medicinal efficacy into a barrel of solar origin water, and even then he had only dared to absorb less than half of it.

Even so, Lin Ming’s hands had been frozen old, the pain piercing as his skin and muscles cracked open.

But now, Lin Ming had chosen to directly swallow the pill. His current strength was much greater than in the past, but the problem was that his condition was much worse!

Swallowing the Nameless Divine Pill at this time was an act of suicide!

But Lin Ming didn’t have any other method. His true essence would sooner or later deplete, and when that happened, all of his meridians and muscles would inevitably be burnt to cinders by the Demon God Bone’s crazy energy!

To use the extreme yin cold of the Nameless Divine Pill to counter the scorching hot energy of the Demon God Bone, at this critical moment, Lin Ming had chosen this crazy strategy!

He was betting his life on this last desperate gamble!

Lin Ming revolved his true essence to the limit. With a fierce clench of his teeth, he swallowed the Nameless Divine Pill!

In that instant, Lin Ming didn’t feel as if he had swallowed a pill, but a 10,000 year old chunk of absolute zero ice!

From his mouth to his stomach, a cold energy spread out!

His throat instantly lost all feeling, and the cells in his body begin to freeze and crack apart. His blood started to ice over as cold energy invaded his meridians and blood vessels, recklessly spreading throughout!

Soon, this cold energy ran into the boiling hot energy of the Demon God Bone!

The spreading cold energy met the blazing hot flames; a fierce collision began!

Originally, just the Demon God Bone’s sole strength was not a match for the Nameless Divine Pill.

However, the Demon God Bone and the Heavenly Demon force field stemmed from the same source. Both of these fused together, creating a force equal to that of the Nameless Divine Pill.

On the other hand, the Nameless Divine Pill’s energy and the Heavenly Demon force field were incompatible with each other. As both of these forces met, they recklessly struck at each other, each wanting to annihilate the other!

Lin Ming’s body had become a battlefield!

Although because the interweaving hot and cold energy made it so that Lin Ming’s meridians weren’t charred or frozen anymore, the collision of the two intense types of energies released an immense amount of force that directly tore apart Lin Ming’s meridians and blood vessels instead!

Lin Ming fell to his knees. His insides felt like they were twisted together inside of him. This sort of feeling was a pain worse than death.

Unconsciously, Lin Ming’s nose, eyes, and ears all began to ooze blood.

As blood streamed down his nose, it froze into crimson ice. But as blood bled from his ears, it had scorch marks upon it.

If this sort of violent destructive damage occurred to a normal martial artist, they would have died long ago.

But in these past years, Lin Ming’s body had condensed many types of incomparably powerful blood vitalities and life energies. Reverse scale blood, blood of the Ancient Phoenix, numerous kinds of heavenly materials, and in addition to this there was also the azure true essence that endlessly grew, continuously invigorating him. All off these factors had made it so that Lin Ming’s resilience and recovery ability far surpassed even an Emperor level powerhouse!

It was impossible for him to control any of these two different energies. He could only bite his teeth and revolve the last dregs of his true essence with the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, forcing this battlefield towards the Gate of Healing!

As the red and blue energies mixed together, it was like a hysterical flood dragon, madly crashing into the Gate of Healing!

Peng!

Between Lin Ming’s clavicles, a burst of blood sprayed out. The muscles and skin were completely torn open; even the bones underneath were broken!

Lin Ming felt his vision turn black for a moment and his body weaken. He didn’t even have the strength to kneel and instead toppled onto the floor.

Fresh blood flowed out from the wound along Lin Ming’s clavicles. Along the fractured bones, one could even see a faint golden marrow.

Energy surged. Along the Gate of Healing, an earth-shattering change was occurring. However, Lin Ming no longer had any true essence to control these two violent energies. Now, he could only let them freely rampage through his body.

Quickly, a pool of blood formed around him, and Lin Ming felt his head become leaden and his vision blur as he gradually lost consciousness.

………………………….

After an unknown length of time, Lin Ming finally woke up. His eyes popped open, a gentle shimmer reflected in them.

There was not a part in his body that didn’t hurt. Especially the area between his two clavicles; it both hurt and itched. His true essence had been finally depleted. He didn’t even have the strength to crawl on his belly or move his fingers.

Lin Ming strained to gather a bit of his perception. As he examined his body, he was surprised to find that the energies of the Demon God Bone and Nameless Divine Pill had already disappeared from within his body. Between his clavicles, where the Gate of Healing was located, the broken bones were already mending.

The Gate of Healing…

Opened!!!

As Lin Ming realized this, he paused for a while, an unreal feeling passing over him.

Opening the Gate of Healing had been far more difficult than completing 100% of Tempering Marrow.

Lin Ming had used the Nirvana Dragon Root to complete Tempering Marrow. But, when trying to open the Gate of Healing, he had only touched upon the threshold of it even though he had absorbed part of the Nameless Divine Pill that was refined from the Nirvana Dragon Root.

Lin Ming using the Demon God Bone to temper his body and open the Gate of Healing had only been an attempt.

He never imagined that once the power of the Demon God Bone and Heavenly Demon force field combined together, it would clash with the Nameless Divine Pill.

The struggle of ice and fire; this tyrannical energy had finally gathered towards Lin Ming’s Gate of Healing, and in an intense confrontation, the outbreak of energies had managed to break through the shackles of the Gate of Healing in a single go!

This also meant that Lin Ming had finally entered into the Eight Inner Hidden Gates body transformation realm!

Although his injuries hadn’t fully healed yet, Lin Ming could already see heaven and earth origin energy flooding towards his clavicles. It was like a leak had opened within the Gate of Healing, causing a massive whirlpool of true essence!

Not just that, but the Gate of Healing could also independently filter heaven and earth origin energy, making it even purer.

Once the Gate of Healing was opened, a martial artist’s body would gain the ability to constantly and autonomously absorb heaven and earth origin energy. The advantages towards cultivation were obvious!

During a battle, it was possible to restore true essence at an extremely quick pace. This was equivalent to Lin Ming constantly eating medicines. Not just that, but the energy that the Gate of Healing provided was incomparably pure; it wouldn’t have toxins like pills would.

Lin Ming could clearly feel the heaven and earth origin energy converging onto his body, revitalizing his dried up meridians. His bodily strength was also being restored at an astonishing pace.

From the point of not being able to move a finger, only a mere incense stick of time passed before Lin Ming could feel his strength returning.

The smaller wounds on his body regenerated at a visible speed. Even the torn muscles and broken bones began to itch, signs that they were growing back.

After a quarter hour, his true essence had already been restored to a reasonable degree. The small injuries on his body had completely vanished, and the severe wound next to the Gate of Healing had recovered by half.

One hour later, the severe wound next to the Gate of Healing was almost fully repaired and as good as new. Lin Ming’s true essence was also regenerated to its peak condition!

In the past when Lin Ming had such heavy injuries, even when he sat in meditation and also took recovery pills he wouldn’t have healed so fast.

A vast and pure true essence poured into his dantian. Lin Ming felt his dantian suddenly shake as if something inside were fiercely contracting. When he examined his body, he was surprised to find that he had reached the extreme Xiantian realm!

Extreme Xiantian was only a step away from Revolving Core.

Many martial artists were stuck at this step for their entire lives, but to Lin Ming, this was no problem at all.

His foundation was already as solid and stable as it could be. Crossing this last step would be smooth without a gruelingly fatal bottleneck.

In this way, Lin Ming became even closer to the Revolving Core realm. His rising cultivation speed had ever exceeded his own expectations.

Going from the late Xiantian realm to the extreme Xiantian realm didn’t have too much of an effect on Lin Ming’s strength. But, it was different from extreme Xiantian to Revolving Core! The true essence in Lin Ming’s dantian was already incomparably thick. Once he formed his own revolving core, his strength would shoot into the sky!

It had to be known that as of now, Lin Ming was only 19 years old. He had great hopes of reaching the Revolving Core realm before he was 21!

When Mu Qianyu was 22 years old, her great talent had let her enter the Xiantian realm. Up until the point that Lin Ming had been forced to leave, she still hadn’t managed to step into the Revolving Core realm.

Lin Ming’s cultivation speed could simply be called terrifyingly monstrous!

The sooner one broke through to the Revolving Core realm, the more potential they would have in their future. 21 years old, 22 years old – even for mortals that only lived for dozens of years, this was still the best time of their lives!

Lin Ming took a deep breath and gripped his fists in excitement. This disaster had actually been a blessing in disguise. As for how far his strength had increased, even he didn’t know.

If he didn’t fight then he wouldn’t know!

“Right now, I should be able to break through this dimensional fragment cage!”

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a bright light and he suddenly jumped out from the Cosmic Melting Furnace. He felt his entire body brimming with strength.

All those people that had tried to kill him… there would be no mercy for them!

Outside of the Cosmic Melting Furnace, the Heavenly Demon force field pressure naturally increased – there was even more than before. But as it enveloped Lin Ming, it actually felt much lighter than before!

The Heavenly Demon force field was no longer an obstacle he couldn’t withstand. Now that the force field’s suppression on his soul force was reduced, Lin Ming’s perception was sharper. He could clearly feel and capture the locations of all the tiny space fragments.

In his field of perception, it was like he was surrounded by a field of shimmering stars.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and stepped forwards. His steps, after integrating the Concept of Space that he was increasingly skilled at, seemed as if he were drifting erratically about, like ghosts and demons.

Even though it was obviously impossible to pass through the narrow gap between two space cracks, Lin Ming still stepped forwards. At this time, there seemed to be a strange distortion in space before he suddenly slipped through.

A spear thrust forth!

The Heretical God Force completely opened, the blood of the Ancient Phoenix burned, and a vast true essence erupted like an unforgiving volcano!

Bang!

The space barrier violently shook. Because the Heavenly Demon force field’s suppression effect on Lin Ming had reduced, his striking power had naturally risen by a great degree!

“After making a breakthrough in my strength, my strike without fused Concepts is already no worse than my past strikes with fused Concepts. If I add in Concepts now, just what would that be like?”

Lin Ming’s eyes burned with a fighting spirit. The power of thunder and fire merged into the Purple Comet Spear. Thick arcs of electricity violently sparkled, waves of brilliant flames combusting!

Lin Ming poured his complete will and potential into the Purple Comet Spear. True essence erupted from his body!

Penetrating Rainbow!

A spear shot forth. It tore through the void, even ripping apart any space fragments that approached it!

This spear strike smashed into the dimensional fragment barrier.

Bang!

With a loud explosion, the space cage rattled, countless fragments flying out. Atop the space barrier, visible cracks appeared. These fissures appeared for a moment before instantly disappearing, as if they were never there to begin with.

However, even though these fissures only appeared for a brief period of time, it heralded the fact that it was only a matter of time until Lin Ming broke through this dimensional fragment barrier!

Chapter 592 – Breaking Through the Last Cage

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Spear after spear, Lin Ming’s relentless onslaught of attacks didn’t falter.

At the beginning, the space barrier would tremble, cracks would appear and then instantly disappear. Then, these cracks appeared for several breaths of time, and finally, before the old cracks disappeared, new cracks were already forming.

The cracks were becoming increasingly dense!

During such a barrage, Lin Ming’s understandings towards the Concept of Space were becoming increasingly profound!

When the cracks in the space barrier reached a tipping point, there was finally a ringing explosion as the barrier shattered apart like a pane of glass. Under Lin Ming’s attacks, the space cage had finally collapsed!

As the space barrier collapsed, a massive amount of chaotic space power surged out. The broken space fragments didn’t disappear; instead they were swept up into the turbulent flow of space, forming a huge storm containing massive space fragments.

When Lin Ming encountered space storms in the past, they had simply been formations purely made from the power of space. Although it was violent and fierce, if one was strong enough and also had a deep understanding of the Concept of Space, they could live within the space storm.

But now, with the space fragments twisted into the space storm, its destructive power could be imagined!

And not just that, but Lin Ming also felt that there was a faint distortion in time within this space storm. If he wasn’t able to adapt to the power of time and took a single wrong step, this he wouldn’t even have a skeleton remaining!

Facing such a space storm, Lin Ming’s expression turned solemn. But, his eyes actually shined with excitement!

If Lin Ming hadn’t opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates then he wouldn’t have dared to brave this space storm. That would be the same as suicide.

But now that he had unlocked entry into the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and also broken through to the extreme Xiantian realm, his mind blazed with fighting spirit! Breaking through that space cage just now hadn’t felt good enough!

After controlling the changing time, Lin Ming opened the Heretical God Force without hesitation. He grasped the Purple Comet Spear and rushed into the space storm.

This was a space stormed that contained the Law of Time – it was obviously a new cage. If he couldn’t break through it, then there was no possibility of leaving the King’s Cage.

After entering the space storm, Lin Ming felt a terrifying tearing force, as if his entire body was about to be ripped apart. This space storm was the most violent one that he had met up until now!

Woosh! Woosh!

Two space fragments shot out. Lin Ming’s footsteps moved and his body seemed to twist in an incredible manner, passing through a narrow half-foot wide gap between the two space fragments.

Kacha!

The two space fragments smashed into each other, exploding and creating even more smaller fragments!

As Lin Ming saw this his mind went cold. In this space storm, the space fragments would continuously crash into each other. Like this, the fragments would become smaller and smaller as their numbers increased!

When that happened, no matter how great Lin Ming’s understanding of the Concept of Space was or whether he could capture each space fragment in his senses, he wouldn’t have the ability to completely dodge all of them.

He had to leave this cage as soon as possible, before he ran out of time!

Lin Ming didn’t dare to delay a moment further. His feet stepped upon Golden Roc Shattering the Void as he rushed into the very depths of this space storm.

Although this space storm was crazy and brutal, it wasn’t like a barrier that would block Lin Ming from moving forward. Lin Ming could use his comprehension of the Concept of Space to slither his way through this terrifying storm which contained space fragments that could pierce through the hardest defenses.

To him, this space storm was a great impediment, but Lin Ming was still fast. In just an incense stick of time he had ran several miles.

“Mm? It’s like…”

Lin Ming’s heart suddenly chilled. He felt that something was wrong, but he just couldn’t place his finger on it.

He put down these doubts that clouded his heart and continued to move forwards. After another incense stick of time, that sense of unease only grew

He found out that he… had been moving in circles!

The space storm all around him was the same. The only way that Lin Ming could judge he was running in circles was purely through his intuition.

From the start until now, he hadn’t even taken a half-step out of here!

Was this spatial warping?

If space was linear, then a distortion could force it into a closed circle. Although he thought that he would always travel in a straight line, the truth was the he was always revolving around a circle, finally returning to the beginning.

But now, Lin Ming had a very high understanding into the Concept of Space. He could feel that although the power of space surrounding him was violent, there actually wasn’t any sign of distortion.

This… just what was going on?

Could this be…

Lin Ming was suddenly surprised. Could this be time…?

When he entered the space storm, he had felt that something was wrong with the flow of time. After adjusting to it a bit he thought that he had adapted himself to the twisting time within the space storm. But could it have really been so easy?

This cage was ahead of the dimensional fragment cage. Without a doubt, it should be much more difficult to break. Could the Concept of Time here really be so simple?

As Lin Ming thought about it, he could feel a chill crawl up his back. Time was even stranger than space.

This sort of strange and unknown phenomenon had always caused people to feel fear; even Lin Ming was no exception.

For years, Lin Ming’s understandings towards the Concept of Space had been constantly deepening. But, the Concept of Time had always lagged behind this.

“So it turns out that this cage is not a space storm but rather a time cage. The space storm is merely an illusion. The real killer is the time trap inside!

“What is going on? Why do I feel that I’ve already adapted to the time, but yet something so strange is happening? It’s as if…”

Lin Ming’s mind moved. He continued to move forwards in this vortex of space, but every time he did so he would return back to where he started.

Return to where he started…

A light went off in Lin Ming’s mind. He turned around and looked at all the space fragments floating around him. These space fragments were constantly smashing into each other and breaking, but even after such a long time, these space fragments were still at the same size; none of these space fragments had broken!

Was this…

Time was returning to the start?

It wasn’t a distortion of space, but rather that time was returning to a zero point?

“How weird! My thoughts haven’t come under the influence of this rewinding time, but it’s just that my position is returning back to the start…”

Lin Ming felt like his thoughts were in a mess. Without a doubt, he was in a cage, a cage where space and time mixed together. Lin Ming’s understanding of the Concept of Space was enough, but it was his understandings towards the Concept of Time that was lacking.

He no longer moved, completely calming and focusing his mind to perceive the intangible time cage around him.

Time was much more abstract compared to time . One could sense space, but time was completely insubstantial. Regardless of his eyes or his perception, it was impossible to sense.

As Lin Ming was calming his heart and feeling the flow around him, he was also dodging the space fragments.

Like this, a day passed…

At the start, Lin Ming had to use movement techniques to avoid the space fragments.

But afterwards, he was almost completely fused into the space itself.

A space fragment shot towards him like a knife. Lin Ming’s body was like a wisp of flame in the wind, easily avoiding this space fragment as if he wasn’t consciously dodging, but instead using the power of space to push these fragments away.

Lin Ming had already fully fused with the power of space.

Chaotic images constantly flashed through Lin Ming’s mind.

Time was only the change of all things, an illusion of thoughts and consciousness. When the flow of time changed, that was only changing the conscious perception of the change in all things.

‘It wasn’t that I was in a different dimension of time constantly returning to the start, but rather my own mind falling into a maze of time, making me unable to realize what direction I was going in.

‘I thought that I was going forwards, but the truth was that all my efforts were only an illusion. So no matter how I ran… I was only running in the same place!’

Time could flow backwards, it could be confusing, but it could not alter the heart of a martial artist.

‘Ward my heart of martial arts to break this maze of time!’

In that moment, Lin Ming seemed to touch upon the source of time itself. Although it was only for the briefest of moments, it had still been there. Lin Ming opened his eyes, no more confusion clouding them. He still hadn’t moved, and the space storm was twisting around him still, the flow of time in disorder.

Time was originally a conscious illusion of all things towards change. In order to break this maze of time, Lin Ming didn’t need to move a single step. What he needed to do was to remove the illusion and demons in his heart.

Revolving the Samsara martial intent, Lin Ming’s spiritual sea become bright and clear. At that moment, as he stood in the chaotic maze of time, he saw the correct path out.

Without any hesitation, Lin Ming stepped upon Golden Roc Shattering the Void and quickly advanced forwards!

In the space storm as the space fragments danced in the air, Lin Ming rapidly and smoothly passed over them. He was as flexible as a fish, as if all of these fatal dangers in his path were only there to contrast his vibrant grace and splendor!

Lin Ming’s footsteps grew faster and faster, and his mind became more and more clear. After a time, he saw the world brighten with light as the space storm opened up before him. In the next moment, he was suddenly in a pure and tranquil white world.

This time, the space around him was normal.

As the cage of time and space collapsed, the space fragments flew back into the space cracks, patching them up in perfect order.

Like that, all of the space cracks and space fragments vanished, everything returning to serenity.

Lin Ming helplessly watched this scene unfold, horrified to the extreme.

The power of space could actually be used to such a ridiculous level and in such an ingenious way? What sort of understanding towards the Concept of Space did one have to achieve in order to reach this level? It was hard to imagine.

At this time, a voice entered into Lin Ming’s mind. “I congratulate you for breaking through the final cage, the cage of space and time. Thus, you have succeeded in breaking past the 13 cages. There is only one path remaining… the Road of Emperor!”

Lin Ming was surprised to hear this. Was the Road of Emperor a part of the King’s Cage?

Woosh!

A door of light appeared out of thin air, shimmering like mercury. “This is the conclusion to the King’s Cage. The time of your trial was 108 days. You do not yet have the ability to pass the Road of Emperor. Now, I grant you your reward for successfully passing the King’s Cage…”

“Reward?”

Lin Ming was shocked. There was also a reward?

As Lin Ming was lost in thought, he suddenly felt the surrounding Heavenly Demon force field collapse around him, flushing into his body like a tide!

This sort of feeling was like his body was about to suddenly burst. Lin Ming stuffily coughed, nearly spitting out a mouthful of blood!

Previous Chapter

Chapter 594 – Return With A Blood Sacrifice To This Spear

The light barrier array formation within the special practice area was only there to deceive the eyes and ears of others. These days, an old Imp man was actually within the light barrier.

He was array master that High Lord Heian had personally invited over – Suo Ge.

Suo Ge was familiar with ancient array formations. This great space locking array was naturally of his own making.

The great space locking array formation could only last for four months. But just in case, in order to prepare for all possibilities, High Lord Heian had invited Suo Ge to come and reinforce the array formation before it expired.

For the first arrangement and then the following reinforcement, High Lord Heian had given Suo Ge 6000 high-grade Blood Demon Crystals!

This was six large chests brimming with crystals; it was absolutely a great wealth!

Thinking of this, Suo Ge grew excited. An array master was a profitable career, but at the same time it was also a career where one feverishly burnt through money. All of those precious array discs, array flags, materials, ancient array formations jade slips, which one of them wasn’t sold only at astronomical prices?

Because Suo Ge was wounded during his youth, his cultivation wasn’t too high. This was also the reason that it wasn’t easy for him to earn Blood Demon Crystals.

With this wealth, he had enough to keep himself well supplied and happy for a long period of time. As Suo Ge thought of this, he chucked, his wrinkled face scrunching together like a scrunched up pile of black pigskins.

His actions became more and more lively. Array symbols flew from Suo Ge’s hands like golden leaves, floating into the air.

“High Lord Heian is really taking this Lin Ming boy seriously. He isn’t relaxed that my array formation already lasts four months, but even wants it to last for eight months.”

Although High Lord Heian hadn’t clearly stated the reason why he wanted this great space blocking array here, Suo Ge was not an idiot nor was he deaf. He naturally heard the martial artists of the third floor talking about Lin Ming, and he was able to instantly understand the situation. The reason that High Lord Heian had asked him to come and set up this array was in order to seal Lin Ming within the King’s Cage.

This was a truly incredible and serious act. A High Lord had personally handed down this order and had also used such a roundabout method to accomplish it. Obviously, this Lin Ming was not ordinary at all!

As soon as this caught Suo Ge’s attention, he learned that Lin Ming was actually a Titled Asura!

This was only the fourth Titled Asura in 10,000 years! This was truly an existence from legends!

“Boy, don’t blame me. My array formations are based upon the ancient principles. For you to die under them and also have High Lord Heian care so much about you that he is willing to part with 6000 high-grade Blood Demon Crystals, this should be enough to have you die in peace. All I can do is make the coffin you’re in a bit more refined.”

Suo Ge licked his lips. In his life, he had been able to use his array formations to kill a Titled Asura, a person who in the future would become a top human Emperor, a proud son of heaven amongst his generation. Just thinking of this filled Suo Ge with a sense of accomplishment. Perhaps, he might be recorded down in the history of the Imps and array masters.

Because of injuries he hadn’t been able to break through to higher martial arts realms. But, if he could still leave behind such an infamous reputation to go along with his Dao of array formations, then that was enough for him to be proud of.

Filled with satisfaction, he began to draw up the next golden array symbol. As he was about to complete this array symbol, the array formation suddenly trembled. This was followed by the sudden inexplicable collapse of an array symbol!

Peng!

“Mm?”

Suo Ge was surprised. If this array symbol shattered here then there would be problems. This meant that there would be a giant hole in this part of the array formation.

“What happened?”

Suo Ge twisted his eyebrows together. Was it possible that there was some problem with the King’s Cage?

If some violent space turbulence broke out from the King’s Cage, then it wouldn’t be surprising if it affected this space blocking array.

Suo Ge shook his head. He raised his head, about to draw up another array symbol to replace the broken one, but just as he was about to finish, sudden ringing sounds filled the air.

Peng! Peng! Peng!

Three array symbols continuously disintegrated.

Suo Ge stood there, dumbfounded. It seemed that this violent space turbulence was not minor!

He was about to redraw the broken array symbols, when suddenly…

Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng!

The sound was like raindrops hitting a bucket. The array symbols in the formation began to burst one after another. Soon, this entire section of array symbols would completely collapse.

“Unlucky!”

Suo Ge cursed.

He had spent most of the day drawing up this group of array symbols.

Should he redraw it?

This required more materials as well as a massive amount of energy.

As he was growing angry about this matter, he heard a loud series of explosions. Nearby, a second section of array symbols was also breaking apart!

Then, as the sound of explosions still lingered in the air, in just a few breaths of time, Suo Ge’s entire great array completely broke apart. The power of space here that was sealed soon returned to normal. The entire space blocking array had failed!

Suo Ge paused.

The large array had failed?

What the hell…

Was this really caused by chaotic space flows?

Suo Ge didn’t know why, but an ice cold feeling filled him. From the soles of his feet to his thighs to his waist and straight into his spirit, he felt a terrifying and unexplainable chill!

It had been just shy of four months. Even if the large array failed, that Lin Ming… should still have died!

Suo Ge was frightened. He hesitated for a moment about whether he should immediately report this matter to High Lord Heian, when a sudden portal of blazing blue light shimmered into being within the empty void!

Transmission gate!

In that moment, beads of sweat dripped down Suo Ge’s forehead!

Could it be…

“Calm down, calm down, he might not be able to deal with me!”

As Suo Ge thought this, he turned around to run away. He wanted to run out of the special practice area and inform High Lord Heian of this crazy change of events.

But at this moment, he felt like his own speed had slowed down by an infinite amount. He was obviously running forwards with full-throttled desperation, but he couldn’t even manage to move a tiny step forwards!

This strange feeling horrified Suo Ge!

“This is…!”

Suo Ge felt his knees weaken. He felt like a mortal standing in front of a tiger cage, and now, that cage had been opened!

“Bastard!”

Suo Ge’s eyes turned red. He turned around and suddenly waved his arms. An array disc came shooting out from him, heading straight towards the shining door of light!

However, before the array disc could even close in, there was an echoing ‘kacha!’ as the array disc was shattered apart, turning into powder!

Right after, a radiant spear light shot out from the door of light, thrusting straight towards Suo Ge.

“Ahh!”

Suo Ge roared and extracted a keen sword from his spatial ring, wanting to cut that spear light in half.

But… he was too slow.

He had fallen into a whirlpool of time. It was impossible for him to break free.

In that instant, Suo Ge fell into despair. He had just lifted the sword in his hand when the spear light reached him, shooting straight between his eyebrows.

“Ahhhhhhhhhhh!”

In front of Suo Ge’s horrified eyes, the spear light easily pierced through his bodily true essence. It shot through between his eyebrows, smashing apart his spiritual sea and crushing his brain before exiting right through the other side, carrying with it a rain of blood and brain fluids as it directly impacted the light barrier array formation!

Chi-la!

The light barrier was almost torn in half!

Suo Ge’s eyes had glazed over, becoming completely empty. In the last moments of his life he had seen a young man, wearing ripped up blue robes with long hair hanging down to his waist, stepping out of the transmission gate.

His eyes were as sharp as the thunder of the highest heavens!

His aura was as chilling as the nine silent layers of the endless abyss!

Seeing this youth, Suo Ge’s soul froze, like he was a mortal lying naked in a snowstorm, feeling nothing but a bone-freezing cold!

This was also Suo Ge’s last thought…

…………..

…………..

“Haha, the King’s Cage has finally opened! It should be time for this father to go. Heh, just look and see how awesome this invincible father’s might is! I will stay inside for 20 to 30 days in a single breath!” Outside of the light barrier array formation, the four Giant Demon and Imp martial artists were happily talking about past events of Lin Ming and the King’s Cage, making fun of the humans of Skysplit Tower as if they were nothing but worthless clowns.

They didn’t know what was happening in this array formation. This light barrier array formation was purposely arranged to isolate the senses of others so that they couldn’t see or hear what was happening inside. Naturally, a High Lord of Skysplit Tower wouldn’t want it known that he was deliberately killing the outstanding heroic youths.

Now, as these four Giant Demon and Imp martial artists saw a large chunk of the light barrier ripped apart, they thought that the King’s Cage was finally being opened for use again.

“It’s finally over! F*ck, we’ve waited such a long time!”

“What bad luck. The King’s Cage can only be entered once in a lifetime. The average person can only go in for several days, and even that abnormal freak Feng Shen only lasted 28 days before he was forced out. But that idiot Lin Ming actually died as soon as he went it. I don’t care if he died, but it actually delayed us for so long, f*ck, I’ve never seen someone so dumb before! It’s truly a work of art how stupid he was.”

An Imp martial artist cursed out loud.

Another martial artist smiled and laughed, “Haha, he was really stupid to the extreme. But hey, at least he also gave us a lot of fun…”

As he spoke here, his next words caught in his throat.

He looked, numb, at the torn light barrier in front of him.

First, his face twisted like he had seen a ghost.

Then, surprise, disbelief, confusion, fear, all of these emotions flashed plain on his face. He stared blankly on as a young man with shredded blue robes and waist-long hair stepped out from the torn light barrier array formation, taking one calm step at a time.

The ruined light barrier was pushed aside by him as easily as if it were a spider’s web.

The Imp martial artist’s expression instantly twisted!

“Lin Ming!!”

In an instant, all four martial artists stood dumbfounded, scared stiff on the spot as if they were all statues!

“This… how is this possible!?!?”

Almost four months. 108 days.

And Lin Ming… was still alive!!!!

Heavens! The Eightfall War Emperor had stayed in the King’s Cage for 60 days, and that was already the record for the last several thousand years! How could anyone actually stay inside for more than 100 days!?

As Lin Ming glanced at these four martial artists, he casually put out a hand. Atop his palm, Blood Drinking Seals wildly danced in the air!

Tides of killing intent recklessly gushed out!

“You… what do you want to do!?” The Imp martial artist who spoke was unnerved.

“Don’t be afraid! This is a fighting restricted area! He wouldn’t dare to do anything to us here!” The  Giant Demon who seemed to be the leader of the group said. According to the rules of Skysplit Tower, fighting was prohibited within the special practice area. Violation of this rule would lead to the enforcement team coming to kill you!

Lin Ming didn’t speak. As he neared one step at a time, his Asura martial intent unconsciously spread out!

Heavenly Demon martial intent, Asura form. Its most powerful aspect lay in the pressure of its force field.

The four martial artists felt as if a mountain range had come crashing down on them. All of the true essence in their bodies was suddenly stifled!

“You… what are you doing!? If you do anything to us then the High Lords will sentence you to death!” The Giant Demon martial artist’s words were brave, but he was actually close to fainting in his heart.

“High Lord?” Lin Ming’s lips curved up. In this smile, there was a somewhat fierce and wicked flavor to it.

“Are you… are you defying the High Lords, you…” The martial artist spoke to here when a sudden zooming sound filled the air. A bloody light flashed, Blood Drinking Seals shooting out!

“Uhkk!”

The Giant Demon’s stunned cry stopped in his throat. He felt dizzy, and then saw the ground getting nearer and nearer even as his body went further away. His head was like a rubber ball as it rolled onto the ground!

Previous Chapter

Chapter 595 – Sacrifice To My Saber

A fountain of blood erupted 20 feet into the air. The Giant Demon’s eyes were as large as brass bells. He stared at Lin Ming, his eyes and mouth twisted, his last expression pained and unable to die in peace.

“Lin Ming!”

All the other martial artists were scared silly. Lin Ming had killed someone, and in an area that prohibited fighting!

“Everyone split up and run! Wait for the enforcement team to come!”

A martial artist suddenly shouted. After all, he was someone who had experienced countless slaughters on the edge of life and death. Although he was afraid, he could still stay calm.

An Imp martial artist ran away quickly as he pulled out a sound transmitting talisman, readying to send a sound transmission to the High Lord responsible for the enforcement team.

However, as he was preparing to light his sound transmitting talisman, he suddenly felt his speed slow down, everyone lagging around him. No matter how fast he ran he couldn’t run quickly. This sort of feeling made him go crazy.

As he pinched the sound transmitting talisman with one hand, he didn’t even have time to use it before he felt something ice cold behind him. He watched helplessly as something shot out from his chest, right over the position of his heart, causing a spray of blood to follow behind it. This terrifying speed formed a sharp contrast to the slow movements he was mired in.

His body softly plopped to the floor… a pool of blood quickly formed around him…

The three escaping martial artists were instantly killed by Lin Ming. Even from the time that he had killed the Giant Demon martial artist, killing these four had only taken several breaths.

“Lin Ming… you killed me… you will die too!” The Imp martial artist hadn’t died yet, still on his last breath. His heart was completely broken, and blood welled up from his body.

He clenched his teeth as he spat out this final threat, but he didn’t find any trace of panic on Lin Ming’s face, only finding a cruel sneer and ridicule there.

Peng!

A foot crushed his throat and the Imp martial artist stopped breathing!

Of these five people that had died, four of them were challengers, and all of them were strong seniors. After they died, the infernal energy on their bodies began to dissipate, forming fierce Heavenly Demon phantoms that rushed towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming coldly humphed. The Heavenly Demon force field erupted!

Four Heavenly Demon phantoms were directly crushed to smithereens by the force field, turning into pure infernal energy that flowed into Lin Ming’s body.

Lin Ming was a peak six-winged Heavenly Demon. Since these four challengers were all characters that could enter this special practice area, the amount of infernal energy they had was no less than Lin Ming’s.

Four forces fused into one and instantly rushed into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea! It rushed forwards with a menacing aura, vowing to swallow Lin Ming’s mind!

Lin Ming coldly snorted. The Samsara martial intent revolved, twisting this tempestuous energy into shreds!

The infernal energy finally scattered completely and began to slowly be absorbed by Lin Ming. The Heavenly Demon Tattoo on his arm rapidly formed a fourth pair of wings. The blurred outline of the wings became increasingly distinct. Finally, it reached the early eight wings before ceasing to grow.

An early eight wings was almost at the standard of the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars.

Taking a long breath, Lin Ming shook his head, his heart brimming with an irrepressible killing intent that was impossible to satiate.

Although Lin Ming had the Samsara martial intent and was able to defend his heart and mindset, after all these long years of killing and death battles, it had formed an incorrigible bloodlust that was hard to alleviate.

Not just that, but he had also been stuck within the King’s Cage for an entire 108 days, constantly having to withstand the massive pressure of the Heavenly Demon force field. His spiritual and mental concentration had been highly tensed the entire time, and all of this was thanks to the plotting of the 12 High Lords!

If he didn’t just happen to have the Nameless Divine Pill and the Demon God Bone, both with energies that were polar opposites of each other, and having the lucky coincidence that they would battle each other and open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, then Lin Ming would have likely died in the King’s Cage.

This grudge, hostility, and killing intent had all been suppressed for a long time.

Now it had instantly erupted, affecting Lin Ming’s mindset for a brief period.

Lin Ming took the spatial rings from the four dead martial artists, and also used their blood essence to form new Blood Drinking Seals. Then he tossed a ball of fire at them, burning their corpses to ashes.

Stepping out of this room, Lin Ming opened the heavy stone doors and came into the great hall of the special practice area.

The hall was very broad, shaped like a square that was 1000 feet wide and long. The one-armed Deacon Bai was busily attending to a few people.

In that brief battle just now, because it had been too short and there hadn’t been any loud earth-shattering sounds, these factors coupled with the spells that covered the stone door made it so that the martial artists outside hadn’t noticed anything.

As the stone door rumbled open, Deacon Bai looked in surprise towards the direction of the stone gate. He saw a single young man with tattered blue robes, waist-long hair, and an expressionless face stepping out.

Then, Deacon Bai turned completely stunned.

With him, the few other martial artists in the room also fell into a stupefied daze.

Lin… Lin Ming!

After fusing with the Heavenly Demon martial intent, Lin Ming’s body was constantly releasing a pressuring aura, whether he was doing it intentionally or not. This made it so that when someone looked at him they felt their hearts gripped and found it difficult to breathe.

At this point, this pressure had unknowingly enveloped the entire hall. The few people in there suddenly fell silent.

Lin Ming hadn’t died yet?

He had stayed in the King’s Cage for almost four whole months!

He was still alive!?!?!?

……………………….

News of Lin Ming’s return spread through the entire Skysplit Tower like a twister. Everyone, whether they were human, Giant Demon, Fey, or any other race were all completely shocked.

This was beyond all results in history, beyond all results that would be in the future!

This was completely unprecedented from ancient times until now!

The Eightfall War Emperor had only been able to stay in the King’s Cage for two months.

The Netherworld Asura, a month and a half!

Of these two people, the Netherworld Asura went missing afterwards and his achievements became unknown. But, the Eightfall War Emperor had become an Emperor level Supreme Elder, even as he had the qualifications to look down on all other Emperor level powerhouses at his level!

It had to be known that each and every person that reached the boundary of an Emperor was a peerless heroic youth of their era, each of them undefeatable Emperor level talents. Not just that, but there were even great disparities among those at Emperor level, wanting to jump ranks to fight was difficult, far too difficult!

Even in this case, the Eightfall War Emperor could instantly kill an Emperor on the same level as him!

And compared to someone that was a small realm or two small realms above him, he could still fight on equal footing with them!

Such capability made one tremble with fear!

Without exaggeration, in the distant future, the Eightfall War Emperor had hope of becoming the Holy Demon Continent’s number one powerhouse!

And now, the time that Lin Ming had stayed within the King’s Cage was actually double that of the Eightfall War Emperor!

In particular, the King’s Cage was more difficult the further one went. This meant that Lin Ming’s talent was far higher than two times the Eightfall War Emperor’s!

This had already surpassed the scope of imaginations for these martial artists…

“I can’t believe this…”

Muk Gu, who was already planning on leaving Skysplit Tower, began to mutter to himself. He thought that he had fallen into a dream. One month ago, he had still hoped every day that Lin Ming would come out, but he had always been disappointed every day.

But now, Lin Ming had finally come out. This had left him bewildered.

That Lin Ming had actually stayed within the King’s Cage for 108 days in a single go.

Was he even human?

…………………………………….

Skysplit Tower, fourth floor, Road of Emperor!

Ka ka ka!

A stone door opened and a black-robed Imp stepped forwards from the Road of Emperor. His entire body was shrouded in a layer of black fog, his eyes were bright, and his face had a restrained ferocity and look of rapture to it.

“Yan Chi, how was it, did you make a breakthrough?”

Yan Chi laughed, “Yes! I’ve already discerned the profound and esoteric principles of the Road of Emperor! I can’t wait to fight Feng Shen now, I want to see whether or not he’s still my match! Hahaha!”

Yan Chi cackled with confidence, his wild laughter filling the entire room like thunderclaps!

Several months ago he had obtained approval to enter the Road of Emperor. Although it was said that the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars who had pledged their allegiance to Skysplit Tower would be able to enjoy massive amounts of practice resources, as for the true core Road of Emperor, one couldn’t enter it as they wished. They needed to complete tasks for the High Lords in order to be rewarded with small amounts of time to enter.

Even Feng Shen, who had a deep background, couldn’t obtain the qualifications to enter the Road of Emperor.

Entering the Road of Emperor was not minor in helping a martial artist grow stronger. The 12 High Lords feared that their servants’ strength would be too great and they would then be unable to control them, thus they placed all sorts of limits on entry.

But this time, because of the events with Lin Ming, Skysplit Tower’s High Lords believed that it was necessary to enhance the strength of their subordinates, in order to cultivate a powerful enough Heavenly Demon Seven Star that could solve their problems.

Maha, who was standing near Yan Chi, smiled and said, “Hehe, it’s rare for us to enter the Road of Emperor. It’s true that you made a breakthrough, but my harvest might not be any worse than yours.”

“Oh really? No need to hurry. Wait for me to defeat Feng Shen and then I’ll spar with you again. This time, I have 60 to 70% assurance that I can defeat Feng Shen!”

“Haha, since you say that then this little brother is also extremely looking forwards to it.” The Heavenly Demon Seven Stars’ Kai Yang laughed as he spoke.

Yan Chi and Maha were originally two of the top ranked three within the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars. But, Kai Yang was one of the weaker ones. Although he too had gained enormous harvests within the Road of Emperor, he didn’t show off his abilities, instead wisely choosing to flatter the two.

However, this didn’t mean that he wasn’t confident in himself. What he was doing was patiently waiting until that one moment when he could amaze the world with a glorious moment so that he could obtain more respect from the High Lords as well as more resources.

‘Hehe, perhaps I am weaker than you two are now, but not by much. If I can obtain another Demon God Bone, then I’m confident I can surpass you! When that time comes, then this father will also be ranked in Skysplit Tower’s top three!’

Kai Yang was happily creating his own plans. But at this moment, a sound transmitting talisman lit up in the great hall, a beautiful flame flashing for a brief moment.

This sound transmitting talisman was for the three of them at the same time. As they heard this voice, all of them froze in place.

“What!? Lin Ming is still alive!?”

The three of them had all entered the King’s Cage before, and the one in there the longest was Yan Chi with 20 some days. They naturally knew what it meant to stay in the King’s Cage for nearly four months!

“How is that possible…” Kai Yang mumbled to himself. This was completely unbelievable. Was the King’s Cage that Lin Ming entered different from the one they had entered? Was the difficulty much lower?

He couldn’t help but think this. The Eightfall War Emperor had stayed in for only two months! Lin Ming, no matter how much of a monstrous genius he was, it was simply impossible for him to persist inside for four whole months!

Perhaps… after two months in the King’s Cage, the difficulty would begin to level out? Otherwise, Kai Yang found it hard to imagine to just what difficulty the King’s Cage would be at after four months.

The only one who could explain this was Lin Ming. Nobody in history had ever stayed longer inside longer than two months.

Maha thought for a moment and then suddenly laughed, his laughs growing louder and more manic. “No matter what he experienced in the King’s Cage, what I learned within the Road of Emperor was far better! This is great! Since I’ve made a breakthrough in my strength, I’ve been looking for a good match to see just what boundary my strength has risen to. This Lin Ming has just about the right qualifications to do so. I will take him as a sacrifice to my saber!”

Chapter 596 – To Use Fingers As a Spear

After Maha’s words, Kai Yang also recovered from his shock. Although Lin Ming’s talent was high, it wasn’t enough for him to dread.

For a martial artist’s improvement, the King’s Cage fell far short of the Road of Emperor.

Lin Ming had undoubtedly grown stronger within the King’s Cage. But, they hadn’t been lazing around either; they had entered the Road of Emperor during these past months!

They were completely different levels of practice areas. How could their gains be any worse than Lin Ming’s!

‘Good! Then before my fight with Feng Shen, I will fight Lin Ming as a warmup, hehe!’ Yan Chi licked his lips, his eyes shining with voracity. He too was thinking of fighting with Lin Ming.

Yan Chi had absolute belief in the increase of his strength. Much less, they had originally been stronger than Lin Ming to begin with. Whether it was him or Maha, both of them were ranked in the top three of the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars.

When Lin Ming had easily killed Hong Zhong, then killed Yan Hu, and proceeded to force Ming Sun to admit defeat, the evaluation of Lin Ming’s strength had steadily risen into the top 10 of the third floor.

This evaluation had also included, to a degree, Lin Ming’s hidden strengths.

Easily killing Hong Zhong and Yan Hu was something that even Kai Yang could achieve without revealing his true strength.

Within Skysplit Tower, the difference in strength between the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars and other martial artists was enormous.

Conscious of these things, Kai Yang’s mind also moved. Now that Lin Ming returned, he would be at the height of his fame and power. If he could defeat Lin Ming at this time then he would be able to greatly enhance his own reputation. He could obtain more attention and respect from the 12 High Lords, and even obtain more resources!

Speaking of which, Lin Ming had been in the King’s Cage for four months. That meant that he owed two matches!

Kai Yang grew increasingly excited. Lin Ming had just come out of the King’s Cage and broke every record for the last 10,000 years. He would absolutely be brimming with confidence at this moment. But, Lin Ming wouldn’t know that he had entered the Road of Emperor and his own strength had risen so dramatically. If he could fight Lin Ming and mercilessly beat him up, stepping on this once in 10,000 year top talent so that he would never be able to stand up again, then this would make his thoughts incomparably happy and smooth.

…………..

Skysplit Tower’s third floor, Dark Day Restaurant.

Lin Ming sat in an airy, open hall. He had ordered a dish of high-grade vicious beast meat, steamed fish, and a pot of millennium-aged wine.

A piece of meat, a cup of wine, he was eating it all at a brisk pace.

During his 108 days within the King’s Cage, Lin Ming had eaten nothing but dried meats and fasting pills. Although it was able to fill his stomach, it was bland, the same as chewing wax.

Outside of this Dark Day Restaurant, the streets were already packed full with people. A great deal of people hadn’t believed that Lin Ming had come out alive and wanted to see him with their own eyes.

As they saw Lin Ming calmly sitting in the restaurant, he had already changed into a new set of light blue clothes. He unexpectedly looked somewhat like a refined and elegant scholar.

However, there was a strange energy field emitting from his entire body, reminding everyone here just how fearful this youth in front of them was.

“This aura is…” A top 50 ranked martial artist of the third floor looked at Lin Ming, his eyelids jumping. Lin Ming had obviously restrained all the true essence in his body, but he was still sending out a vast aura. Whether intentional or not, it was still shocking! As Lin Ming sat there, he was like a peerless divine spear, impossibly sharp!

“Where is this aura coming from?”

A martial artist’s aura sounded as if it were an illusion, but it did in fact exist. In truth, this so-called aura was an energy field.

Heaven and earth origin energy was a kind of energy itself. When it was gathered together it would naturally produce an energy field.

When a normal martial artist fought, their entire body would erupt with true essence and their aura would do the same. But Lin Ming had obviously curbed his true essence, yet his aura was actually powerful to this degree.

Just what was this?

All the martial artists on the third floor had outstanding eyesight. They also discovered this phenomenon occurring on Lin Ming’s body, causing them to be startled.

“Lin Ming, he must have grown much stronger these past four months!”

“He is truly worthy of being called someone with talent greater than the Eightfall War Emperor’s…”

“How terrifying! I’m afraid that even the lower ranked Heavenly Demon Seven Stars might not be his match anymore!”

The surrounding martial artists were all talking. Those that had formerly flaunted Lin Ming’s death and cracked jokes about him had all shut up.

Originally, they had all firmly promised everyone that Lin Ming had most assuredly died after 80 days. But now, 108 days after entering, Lin Ming had calmly and safely come out. This was a slap in the face to all of these martial artists.

At this moment, a Giant Demon martial artist grimaced as he said, “Lin Ming is truly fierce, but it’s too much to say that he can defeat one of the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars. The Heavenly Demon Seven Stars’ strength is much higher than that of all other martial artists on the third floor, and I heard that Yan Chi and them also entered the Road of Emperor. After they came out, their strength would inevitably have risen by a large degree! I think that not even Feng Shen could be Yan Chi’s match!

When one reached the very end of the Road of Emperor, they would become an Emperor level powerhouse.

This was not an exaggeration.

Of course, there hadn’t been anyone that had actually reached the end. Even so, the King’s Cage was far from comparable with the Road of Emperor.

As Yan Chi’s name was brought up, the martial artists present were somewhat scared. Yan Chi’s infamy was too heavy now; he was only inferior to Feng Shen. Also, Yan Chi had pledged his utter loyalty to Skysplit Tower, so he definitely obtained more resources than Feng Shen.

At this moment, there was suddenly the brusque sound of rushing footsteps. A group of armored martial artists rushed towards the front of the restaurant, pushing away the crowd. These martial artists all had the same unified armor set, and they all had a small tower embroidered over their right chest.

“The enforcement team?”

Seeing the enforcement team suddenly appear, the martial artists were confused as to what was going on.

The members of Skysplit Tower’s enforcement team weren’t any great talents when compared to the challengers of the third floor, but even though their talent was ordinary, all of them were on the older side. Thus, their members’ true strength was equal to the upper levels of the third floor.

Lin Ming quietly continued drinking, not even bothering to toss them a glance.

“You are Lin Ming!”

The captain of the enforcement team stared at Lin Ming, a cold light flashing in his eyes. “At the entrance to the King’s Cage at the special practice area, after you left, Wan Shu, Lin Feng, and two other martial artists went missing. In addition to this, Master Suo Ge was found with a hole pierced between his eyebrows. Were these five people killed by you?”

Lin Ming put down his cup of wine and stood up. He impassively said, “That’s right.”

He didn’t plan to hide this matter to begin with, nor could he have.

“Good! You openly fought in a prohibited zone, and you openly killed in a prohibited zone. It seems you have no idea of death or danger! Brothers, take him and cripple his martial arts! Ready him for judgement by the High Lords!”

The captain of the enforcement team shouted out and soon several martial artists began to move forwards!

Lin Ming used his fingers as a spear and swept them out.

In the next moment, a brilliant spear light flooded the entire hall.

Peng!

The wooden doors and windows of the restaurant flew away and every piece of furniture in front of Lin Ming exploded into pieces. Terrifying waves of air pressure forced every martial artist present to take a step back. As for the enforcement team martial artists who were swept up by that spear light, they gave stuffy coughs and vomited out mouthfuls of blood, their bodies sent flying backwards.

Suddenly, the entire area fell silent.

Lin Ming was crazy! He actually dared to attack the enforcement team!?!?

Chapter 597 – No Backing Down

Skysplit Tower’s enforcement team represented the 12 High Lords! Who would have the courage to so brazenly attack them?!

To attack the enforcement team meant opposing the 12 High Lords. In Skysplit Tower, the 12 High Lords were the emperors, they controlled life and death in their hands!

Now, Lin Ming had just blatantly slapped the High Lords’ faces.

Moreover, although the enforcement team members’ talents weren’t too high, their ages were. They were not weak. Otherwise, why would they have the ability to enforce the law on the third floor?

But just now, five or six of them had been casually struck by Lin Ming and sent flying back!

“To use fingers as his spear and sweep away the entire enforcement team!”

“What a terrifying spear light. Although it wasn’t even aimed at me, I still felt my heart shake!”

The surrounding martial artists were not weaklings. But they faintly imagined what would happen if they were to take that one strike a moment ago, and every conclusion they came to made them depressed. The majority of them had to admit that they simply didn’t have the strength to resist in the face of that attack. Even if some of them thought they could resist it, they feared that they would probably suffer minor injuries.

This was just Lin Ming’s casual attack; he hadn’t even used his spear!

“Lin Ming! You… you… do you have a death wish?!” The enforcement team captain burned with anger, but he was actually quaking in his heart, crying about why this was happening. He had taken his team here but they had been instantly swept away with a single strike. Now he could only watch, he didn’t dare to do anything to Lin Ming.

Lin Ming hadn’t been ruthless in that strike just now. Otherwise, these people wouldn’t have been severely wounded and vomited blood, but rather directly perished where they stood!

If Lin Ming dared to kill people in a prohibited area, then he would dare to kill the enforcement team!

The enforcement team captain had ridden the tiger and now there was no more backing down. He simply didn’t know what to do. With so many pairs of eyes looking at him, under their gaze he had been smacking around. If he walked away then he would be shamed so much that even his grandmother wouldn’t recognize him. How could he still continue to enforce the law on the third floor?

He couldn’t run but he couldn’t stay either. As the enforcement team captain was agonizing over what to do, the sound of noisy footsteps suddenly stirred.

Turning around, he saw a troop of over a dozen warriors rush over. They all wore the same battle armor, and their individual strength and cultivation were far beyond the enforcement team of the third floor!

“The fourth floor guards.”

The martial artists were stunned. The guards for the fourth floor were the same as the personal guard for the High Lords! Their status was also much higher than the enforcement team’s.

A High Lord had come?

In Skysplit Tower, it had been too many years since a High Lord had been aroused!

“Make way! Everyone make way!”

The captain of the fourth floor guards snapped at everyone before him. Although his attitude was crude and barbaric, nobody dared to say half a word back to him. All of they gave way, lest they were slow and blocked his path.

In the center of these fourth floor guards, a black-robed Imp slowly stepped out. He had a cruel smile on his face as he coldly looked at Lin Ming.

This was High Lord Heian!

High Lord!!!

All of the martial artists present felt their pupils shrink. In fact, there weren’t too many martial artists that had seen High Lords up close, but they could feel a faint imposing aura emitting from him, and could correctly guess that this Imp man in front of them was one of the 12 High Lords.

One of the 12 High Lords, the highest existences within Skysplit Tower!

“Lin Ming, this is the first time that we’ve met!” As High Lord Heian spoke, his eyes filled with a sparkling killing intent.

At this time, Lin Ming had sat back down in the restaurant, slowly eating his meal again. He looked up at High Lord Heian and laid down his chopsticks, standing up once more.

Facing High Lord Heian, his actions were sincere.

“You are Heian?”

All of the martial artists felt their hearts tighten. Lin Ming had directly called a High Lord by his name!

What arrogance! What pride!

High Lord Heian’s eyes narrowed as he looking at Lin Ming, his vision as sharp as his knife. It seemed as if he were trying to completely understand him, penetrating through his entire being.

This boy was truly formidable!

“Addressing me by my name, disrespecting me, killing in the prohibited zone, even attacking the enforcement team. You… your unbridled actions are far too audacious!”

“Me? Audacious?” Lin Ming smiled. “Heian, wasn’t it you who hired that old Imp to lay down a great space locking array around the King’s Cage? You wanted to lock me in the King’s Cage and kill me in there? Hehe… if I hadn’t made a miraculous breakthrough inside, then I fear I would already be dead in the King’s Cage!”

His words were relentless. Combined with the Asura force field that seemed to burst out from his body, this caused his words to loudly ring in everyone’s ears, causing them to tremble.

“What?”

Lin Ming’s words shocked everyone present!

It wasn’t a secret that Suo Ge had been busily working inside the King’s Cage these past days.

Skysplit Tower’s practice areas could be considered relics from the ancient times; it was impossible for Suo Ge to repair any of the array formations because he simply lacked this ability. If so, then what was he doing for so many days inside of the special practice area?

Also, after Lin Ming emerged from the King’s Cage ater 108, although it was truly shocking, everyone was filled with their own suspicions. Just what had Lin Ming experience inside the King’s Cage? Why had he stayed inside for so long?

Thirdly, if Skysplit Tower recognized Lin Ming as dead, then why wasn’t the King’s Cage opened again?

All of these doubts were actually laid bare by Lin Ming and all of the martial artists present realized what had happened. None of them were fools. They connected all the possibilities and were able to instantly judge that what Lin Ming said was most likely true!

The 12 High Lords wanted Lin Ming to die in peril within the King’s Cage. But, by whatever means, Lin Ming had emerged from the King’s Cage!

With the great space locking array laid down by Suo Ge, in addition to the inhumane environment inside the King’s Cage that only grew worse every day, Lin Ming actually stayed within for 108 days and broke out himself!

Was he even human?

Now that this plot was revealed by Lin Ming, High Lord Heian’s complexion turned ugly. His plan to kill Lin Ming had been perfect. But he never imagined that even in this situation, Lin Ming would still be able to come out alive!

“Lin Ming, the reason that I asked Suo Ge to come is because I wanted him to set down a new transmission array for an improved escape talisman. This is so that martial artists that enter the King’s Cage can have greater chances of escaping alive! Who do you think you are, that you think you are so worthy that I would personally concoct schemes to deal with you?” High Lord Heian spoke with contempt.

However, no matter how disdainful High Lord Heian’s expression was, there was basically no martial artist present that believed his excuse. They weren’t silly children that would be fooled so easily. But although everyone understood how things were, no one dared to reveal anything otherwise.

“Hahaha! Is that so?” Lin Ming sneered, the derision in his eyes and voice obvious.

High Lord Heian subconsciously clenched his fists. This matter was becoming increasingly troublesome.

If he personally dealt with Lin Ming today, then he would undoubtedly be able to capture or kill Lin Ming.

But he himself would be seen as in the wrong, and would have been shown to be vagrantly breaking all decorum and rules. When that happened, he would be known as the High Lord of Polar Skysplit Tower that schemed and used every means possible to strangle rising talents!

Polar Skysplit Tower’s reputation could not withstand such damage!

‘This damn boy!’ Heian cursed in his mind. But, he couldn’t back down at this moment. Killing Lin Ming now was no good, but letting Lin Ming leave like this was even worse.

He had no idea what to do!

At this moment, there were more noisy footsteps approaching. High Lord Heian turned and saw that not too far away, Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang were all soaring over here.

As Heian saw these three people he was instantly overjoyed. With these three, he thought of a safe solution to all his problems!

Chapter 598 – Three Continuous Matches

“Yan Chi, Maha, Kai Yang!”

As these three people appeared, the martial artists present were all shocked. Three of the Heavenly demon Seven Stars had simultaneously arrived!

Compared to Lin Ming, none of these three auras were in any way inferior. As these three auras faintly overlapped with each other’s, it even overshadowed Lin Ming’s!

“Sir High Lord!”

Yan Chi slightly bowed. Whether it was because of the soul contract or resources, the always proud Yan Chi was respectful towards the 12 High Lords.

High Lord Heian nodded with satisfaction. He was happy as he noticed that Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yan’s strengths had increased by a great deal. Fortunately, he had let the three of them into the Road of Emperor a few months ago. Now he had soldiers at the time he needed them the most.

“Good, you have not disappointed me.” High Lord Heian slowly said as he turned back to look at Lin Ming. “Lin Ming, I remember than you were in the King’s cage for 108 days. With some of the time from before, you should owe two or three matches now?”

Lin Ming heard High Lord Heian speak and the corners of his lips curved up, “What are you trying to say?”

“You have doubted me, offended me, and falsely accused me. If I kill you now, then others will inevitably spread rumors about if, treating me in a completely unfair manner! Since this is the case then I have a chance for you. You’ve just come out of the King’s Cage so your strength should have risen. So, you will now finish all the matches that you owe!”

As High Lord Heian spoke, the martial artists present began to understand. What High Lord Heian wanted was for Lin Ming to enter the arena stage and fight the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars!

Not just that, but in accordance to the rules of Skysplit tower, if one owed matches because they were in practice then they would have to fight in continuous matches! There would be no rest time between them!

When Lin Ming had continuously fought Yan Hu and Ming Sun, this was also a similar situation. Lin Ming had killed Yan Hu with absolute superiority, forcing Ming Sun to peacefully raise the white flag so there wasn’t even a real second match.

But this time was different. His matches would be against the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars! Who would still dare to continuously fight them!?!?

“Time? Opponents?”

Lin Ming calmly said without a hint of fear.

High Lord Heian was surprised for a moment. This kid was far too confident!

Even facing continuous matches with the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars he didn’t care at all, even letting High Lord Heian arrange the matches for him. To what degree did his confidence extend to!?

The surrounding martial artists were all secretly shocked. As they looked at Lin Ming leisurely standing, this definitely wasn’t an act!

High Lord Heian glowered. He coldly said, “Since you are so bold then I won’t disappoint you. 10 days from now at the martial arena, you will fight Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang!”

Three continuous matches?

All of the martial artists present were confused. They knew that High Lord Heian wished for Lin Ming to die, but didn’t think that he would directly put out three continuous matches. Arguably, Lin Ming only owed two now. The third would still have to wait for some time.

They turned towards Lin Ming, seeing if he would refuse.

Lin Ming faintly smiled. “Three continuous matches? Sure!”

Lin Ming easily agreed, startling all the martial artists.

To continuously fight three Heavenly Demon Stars, especially Yan Chi and Maha who were ranked in the top three, was simply madness! Utter madness!

“Lin Ming is too reckless. It’s true that he’s strong, but according to some reliable sources, Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang have all entered the Road of Emperor, gaining experience inside for the last few months. What they gained in there is most likely no less than what Lin Ming gained in the King’s Cage! And what is even worse is that if Lin Ming battled just Kai Yang alone I’m still afraid he would be in a perilous situation, and now he wants to fight three of them continuously!”

“For sure. Lin Ming just doesn’t understand how strong these three are. Agreeing to this is just too rash.”

Continuous matches was an enormous test on a martial artist’s true essence and physical strength; one could only win if they had an overwhelming advantage. Otherwise, the longer these battles dragged on the more exhausted they would be, and the more tired their spirit and mind would be, causing their true essence usage to accelerate, and finally, they would be defeated.

Even Feng Shen didn’t dare to boast he could do this. There were even some that suspected that after Yan Chi entered the Road of Emperor, his strength might be no worse than Feng Shen’s!

“Hehe, this boy is too stupid!” Yan Chi sneered.

“Humph! He doesn’t want to walk the road to heaven but would rather storm through the gates of hell! If you want to die then I’ll give you a hand!” Maha said with ice cold killing intent. How could he allow their Heavenly Demon Seven Stars to be looked down on so much by a human? This fellow even thought that he could continuously fight three of them!

“Haha, allow this little brother to take the first match. Otherwise, the little brother fears that he won’t have the chance to do anything.” Kai Yang said, grinning. His strength had grown by leaps and bounds within the Road of Emperor, and he had finally absorbed a piece of Demon God Bone. His strength was incomparable to how he used to be. He certainly didn’t want to miss this chance to show off his newfound strength.

The only way for him to get the High Lords to pay more attention to him was this match.

Not only did he need to win, he needed to do so in glorious style!

Now, even fools could see that High Lord Heian wanted Lin Ming to die.

Perhaps if one of them killing Lin Ming, they would even be able to obtain a bit of Demon God Bone as a reward!

“Good. Kai Yang, you will go first. Then Maha will take the second match.” High Lord Heian said. From the weakest to the strongest was the best way to arrange a squad.

“Haha, maybe Maha won’t even need to do anything.” Kai Yang cunningly smiled.

Kai Yang was extremely confident in himself.

Lin Ming’s lips curled up. Towards these three continuous matches, he didn’t feel much. It was true that he knew nothing about Yan Chi, Maha, or Kai Yang’s strength, but all he knew was that he was absolutely confident he could defeat them.

After opening the Gate of Healing, Lin Ming’s regenerative abilities had reached a terrifying degree. Three continuous matches? He wouldn’t even care if they all came together!

“Let’s go.”

With the gauntlet thrown down, High Lord Heian turned and left. His retinue of guards also drew back like a tide.

As Kai Yang turned to leave, he said to Lin Ming with a true essence sound transmission, “Boy, wash your neck and wait for death. When I kill you, I’ll likely be granted a Demon God Bone! To me, you are nothing but a Demon Gone Bone!”

Lin Ming didn’t bother to speak again. He sat back down at his table, picked up his chopsticks, and began to eat a piece of meat.

Eating meat, drinking wine, all of this done calmly!

As if nothing had happened just now.

Seeing Lin Ming eating a meal so languidly, all of the martial artists present were taken aback. He had to continuously battle Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang in 10 days.

How could he be so calm?

This calm was not an act. This was a death match. Who could be so calm before so many death matches? If he couldn’t even live, then what was the point of putting out a front?

It could only be said that Lin Ming was truly calm. In a situation where he didn’t even understand Chi Yan, Maha, or Kai Yang’s strength, how could he be so calm?

Just how confident was Lin Ming in his own strength!?!?

…………………….

News of Lin Ming’s continuous three battles with Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang soon spread out like a tidal wave. It wasn’t just the third floor, but all the martial artists on the second floor quickly learned this!

This was truly explosive news!

This would be Lin Ming’s first battle since returning from the King’s Cage! With the reputation of the number one talent since ancient times on the line, the impact of this match could be imagined!

Even if Lin Ming battled an ordinary top 10 challenger on the third floor, it would still arouse a great amount of interest.

But now, Lin Ming’s matches were completely comprised of the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars. Not just that but… it was three continuous matches!

Yan Chi, Maha, Kai Yang! Especially the first two. Their reputation sounded out like a thunderclap in everyone’s ears!

When Lin Ming first arrived at Sun Flood City, he had already heard of Yan Chi and Maha’s names. In Skysplit Tower, there were even many mortals that knew of them.

And from reliable sources, it was learned that they had stepped into the Road of Emperor months ago. Their current strength was incomparably to how it was in the past!

It was rumored that Yan Chi was now in no way inferior to Feng Shen. Even Maha had the qualifications to fight with Feng Shen on even footing.

At that same time, Lin Ming would be fighting three people. This was simply crazy!

Even if Lin Ming wasn’t crazy, all the other martial artists on the third floor were going crazy.

Every martial artist that had gone into closed-door seclusion had left their practice area, and every martial artist that had gone out for adventuring was also running back as fast as they could to watch this unparalleled battle!

The prices for admission tickets had already risen to astronomical levels.

…………………….

Skysplit Tower, martial artist service center.

Wearing blue clothes, a beautiful and delicate-looking young girl was blankly staring out a window, deep in a trance as she was lost in her thoughts.

This girl was only 15 or 16 years old. Her face still had a faint hint of blossoming youth. Although her hair and face were cleaned up neatly and her clothes were also ordered, it couldn’t conceal her tired and pale complexion, a constantly ill appearance that aroused the pity of those who saw her.

This girl was the maid servant that had helped Lin Ming during his stay at the martial artist service center – Wan’er.

The proprietress of the martial artist service center had originally allowed to Wan’er to be Lin Ming’s concubine. But for the entire two weeks of time, Lin Ming hadn’t even touched Wan’er once. Afterwards, when Lin Ming had gone to the second floor, a black-caped Imp martial artist had used her life as a threat in order to force Lin Ming into a match.

At that time, Wan’er had known nothing about this. After Lin Ming defeated that black-caped Imp martial artist, Xu Yan had informed her of this matter. Her feelings had become incomparably complicated after learning of this.

She never imagined that a challenger of Skysplit Tower would take such dangerous risks for a mere mortal.

When it was learned that Lin Ming had perished in the King’s Cage, if there was anyone that truly felt sadness from the heart for Lin Ming, then it wasn’t Muk Gu, nor was it Da Gu or Xun Ji.

No, the only one who felt such deep heartbreak was Wan’er.

Wan’er knew her limits. She was well aware that her path and Lin Ming’s would never cross again. She knew it was impossible for her to ever serve him again, nor did she have the qualifications to stand vigil for him. Even seeing him just once more was a wild and unattainable hope.

What she could only do was to worry about him from the bottom of her heart and pray for him.

After it was said that Lin Ming had died, Wan’er found it hard to eat or drink, making her entire body thin and frail.

However, no matter what, she still believed that he would come out.

Now, Lin Ming had finally emerged from the King’s Cage, and not even one day later, news was spreading that he would fight Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang in a continuous death match.

Wan’er didn’t understand anything about martial artists nor anything about the levels of their strength. Because she was worried, she asked Xu Yan.

Although Xu Yan told her that Lin Ming could win, his answer had been very reluctant. Occasionally he would sigh and shake his head. This proved that… in truth, he didn’t think Lin Ming’s chances were good.

“Wan’er.” A voice suddenly called out.

Wan’er looked around, and saw that the one speaking was Xu Yan. This year, Xu Yan had also entered the second floor. But he would often come back for a visit.

“Big Brother Xu Yan, is there any news about Big Brother Lin Ming’s fight?” Wan’er’s face filled with hope.

“Mm… the match will be tomorrow. But, even if I sell everything I have, I still wouldn’t be able to afford a ticket. Also… I don’t have the authority to enter the third floor.” Xu Yan shook his head. There wasn’t anything he could do besides wait for the final result.

“Oh…” Wan’er lightly replied.

Xu Yan sighed. He wanted to say some comforting words, but he eventually didn’t say anything.

Continuously fighting Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang…

How could Lin Ming ever hope to win?

Previous Chapter

Chapter 600 – Instant Death

Lin Ming stood motionless on the arena stage, the Purple Comet Spear still grasped in his hand as if he were some stone sculpture.

But in front of Lin Ming, with his entire face covered with blood, Kai Yang was laughing, “Haha! How is it? Does my Emperor Will taste good!?”

This scene caused the audience to be stunned. Kai Yang had spent a great deal of time gathering potential for his attack, but after his strike collided with Lin Ming’s, he was the one that had been sent flying back. They thought that Kai Yang was done for, but never expected such a strange turn of events. It looked as if someone had cast a dark spell over Lin Ming. Without a doubt, this was the mystery that had been added to Kai Yang’s strike just now.

“Emperor Will… what is that? It sounds dangerous!”

“Lin Ming… he… it looks like he can’t move!”

“That Emperor Will is definitely some sort of soul attack. Kai Yang is truly worthy of being called one of the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars. As a genius of the Imp race who is skilled in soul attacks, even though Lin Ming’s soul defense abilities are strong, they actually couldn’t fend off this move from Kai Yang! It’s too terrifying!”

Lin Ming was like a statue, and his bodily protective true essence was also disappearing. As long as Kai Yang cut him with his Soul Extinguisher Saber, then Lin Ming’s head would fall!

Did the fight end just like this?

Kai Yang’s eyes flashed with a fierce excitement. The time to prove himself had arrived! The number one talent of the last 10,000 years had actually died under his hand. From this point on, he had taken Lin Ming’s destiny as his own!

He had borne so much pain and suffering with the Road of Emperor all in order to obtain this Emperor Will. This Emperor Will came from a true Emperor level powerhouse. It wasn’t something that an ordinary martial artist could withstand. Even just a single wisp would have a massive impact on one’s spiritual sea!

“It’s a pity that you can’t hear what I’m saying. Who cares how strong you are? You will still die by my hands!” Kai Yang roared. He took a step forwards and then began rushing towards Lin Ming!

As the surrounding martial artists saw this, none of them blinked. Muk Gu’s hands were sweaty, Feng Shen was silent, and High Lord Heian’s lips had curved up in a devilish grin. As a High Lord, he certainly knew how terrifying the Emperor Will was. He didn’t think that Kai Yang would have been able to capture a wisp of Emperor Will to use for himself. For this fellow, there was no better cultivation method!

“Die! With the blood of the number one talent for the last 10,000 years, I will lay down my road to becoming a Demon Emperor!”

Kai Yang flashed a manic smile. He flourished his saber, cutting straight towards Lin Ming’s throat!

But at this time, an indifferent voice sounded out in Kai Yang’s ear…

“What a pity… I almost realized what this will was. If you could have waited just a moment more…”

This was just a gentle and light voice, but Kai Yang’s soul instantly froze over, a biting cold penetrating into his farthest depths.

“What?” Kai Yang asked, dazed.

The next second!

Blinding purple thunder filled everyone’s vision. An incomparably keen spear light spread through the entire martial arena, so sharp that people couldn’t open their eyes, as if their own souls were pierced by this spear light!

Bang!!

A thick ray of spear light thrust straight through Kai Yang’s chest. Blood and flesh flew out in all directions. Kai Yang’s eyes widened as he spat out a mouthful of blood, his body thrown backwards like a rag doll.

Puff!

Kai Yang smashed into the floor like a dead dog, breaking all the tiles beneath him as he landed. The area on his chest where the heart was had a shockingly large hole pierced through it. His heart was smashed apart, and blood erupted from it like a crimson fountain!

“…What?”

This change had occurred so suddenly that none of the martial artists present could react in time!

Just the moment before, they had all thought that Lin Ming would die under Kai Yang’s hand. But in a split-second, the tides had turned!

The frozen Lin Ming had suddenly thrust out his spear, piercing Kai Yang’s heart!

A simple spear strike had killed him! Although there was a factor of surprise, this was enough to prove just how great the difference was between Lin Ming and Kai Yang’s strength!

“He ignored Kai Yang’s attack and killed him instead…”

Muk Gu mumbled to himself. Lin Ming’s strength had far exceeded his wildest imaginations.

Even Feng Shen had somewhat lost his former calm. He let out a long breath and slowly shook his head. It was unknown just what thoughts were racing through his heart.

Dozens of feet away, even though Kai Yang’s heart had been crushed, he still hadn’t died yet. He grabbed at the floor underneath his body, his black nails digging into the floor, covered with blood.

“Why… why, could… why like this…”

Kai Yang’s face was twisted. His two beady eyes were filled with disbelief.

He was unwilling! He had patiently endured soul-shattering pain within the Road of Emperor for an entire month. It had simply been inhumane torture. But finally, he had obtained a wisp of Emperor Will that he could use for himself.

He thought that this had laid the path for him to become a Demon Emperor in the future. He thought that, with this, he would be able to soar into the skies and inter everlasting glory! But in just this first battle, he would die like this!

The Emperor Will had clearly stabbed into Lin Ming’s body, so how did this happen?

“You…”

Kai Yang propped himself up to glare at Lin Ming. As he spoke, more blood dribbled out of his mouth. The blood left pumping from his heart slowly stopped, the rest draining off. He had wanted to say something, but before he could say his last words, his eyes had glazed over.

Pa!

Kai Yang fell to the ground, dead and alone with his regrets.

For a time, silence fell over all the martial artists in the arena. Lin Ming’s victory was within expectations, but with the battle having reached this degree and so many twists and turns and reversals, they didn’t have time to respond.

However, what no one doubted was that Lin Ming’s strength far surpassed Kai Yang’s.

At the special guest area, High Lord Heian’s face had darkened. The Emperor Will was actually useless against Lin Ming?

Maha was also looking solemn. It was his turn to face Lin Ming. Although he didn’t place Kai Yang in his eyes, for him to defeat Kai Yang without revealing the majority of his hidden strength was not necessarily possible!

“This boy!” Maha traced the hilt of his treasure saber, his eyes filling with a brilliant killing intent!

Huuu—!

On the arena stage, the infernal energy leaking from Kai Yang’s body formed into a Heavenly Demon avatar that plunged at Lin Ming. Kai Yang’s Heavenly Demon Tattoo had been at the late eight-winged Heavenly Demon stage!

Lin Ming pointed out his fingers, and with his fingers as a spear, a bright spear light flashed out. The infernal avatar was crushed by this spear light, turning into pure infernal energy that poured into Lin Ming’s body. On his arm, the fourth pair of wings was slowly forming…

Peak of a middle eight-winged Heavenly Demon!

After Lin Ming absorbed half of Kai Yang’s infernal energy, he was getting close and closer to becoming a ten-winged Heavenly Demon!

Lin Ming took a deep breath, slowly pushing down restlessness in his heart. A moment ago, when he was struck by the Emperor Will, he had truly come under a great impact!

Even though he had the Samsara martial intent, his mind had nearly fallen into illusions.

Thus, Lin Ming had let the Heavenly Demon martial intent erupted within his body. The Heavenly Demon martial intent could not only suppress the body, but it could also suppress soul force. With the Heavenly Demon martial intent combined with the Samsara martial intent, the two martial intents ganged up on the Emperor Will, forcibly suppressing it!

Lin Ming had originally wanted to take this opportunity to gain some insights on this Emperor Will, but just as he had a small look, Kai Yang was already attacking. So, Lin Ming had no choice but to interrupt himself and open 50% of the Heretical God Force, instantly killing Kai Yang!

Lin Ming took Kai Yang’s spatial ring and then shot the Blood Extinguishing Demon Thunder at him, sucking up his blood essence.

Now, the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’s’ techniques weren’t Lin Ming’s strongest killing moves anymore. But that didn’t mean that Lin Ming had given up on cultivating the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’. This was because this cultivation method primarily used the path of slaughter in its attacks, so it gave him a great deal of inspirations.

Chasing Thunder, Chasing Sun, Penetrating Rainbow, these three moves were all born from the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’.

Unconsciously, Lin Ming had stepped onto the path of fusing martial arts together, reaching the boundary of a martial arts grandmaster that created their own martial arts legacy.

Using his right hand to hold the Purple Comet Spear, he pointed it towards the floor and drew a crescent moon.

Then, he looked towards where Yan Chi and Maha were sitting, and calmly asked, “So, who’s next?”

Chapter 601 – Saber Light Domain

For a time, every martial artist’s eyes turned onto Maha!

Maha coldly snorted, “It’s like you believe you’re invincible!”

He moved. Crossing hundreds of feet with a single step, Maha arrived directly atop the arena stage.

“You killed Kai Yang, now you think you’ve already won against me?” Maha’s mouth twisted. He couldn’t help but acknowledge Lin Ming’s soul defense abilities. He had actually even resisted the Emperor Will!

However, none of this mattered to him. Maha was a Giant Demon martial artist. His main form of combat had always been and would always be related to violent and close-combat fighting. Soul attacks were primarily the domain of the Imps.

He extracted the long saber from his back. Maha’s saber blade was seven feet long, and in addition to the hilt, this weapon was as long as an adult male. The saber ridge was three feet thick, and the weapon itself weighed no less than several tens of thousands of jins. Giant Demon martial artists generally loved using heavy weaponry like this.

“Words are useless, let’s fight!”

Lin Ming snapped the Purple Comet Spear in his hand. On the spearpoint, electricity sparkled.

Maha gripped his saber with both hands. Clouds of demon essence began to gather around him. With a cut of his saber, saber energy swept out, and wherever it went, tiles would turn into ash before vanishing to nothing!

Concept of Annihilation!

Compared to Xing Tian, Maha’s Concept of Annihilation was several times stronger. With just the saber wind, tiles were destroyed, and even large areas were carved out of the hardened metal ground of the stage that was supported with array formations!

The saber wind blew through the arena. Luckily, all of the surrounding martial artists were masters in their own right. They quickly summoned their bodily demon essence protection to resist this saber wind attack. But as soon as this demon essence touched Maha’s saber energy, it would rapidly melt away!

“Terrifying!”

“Even the aftermath shockwaves are like this. A direct hit must be horrifying!”

Lin Ming also felt the pressure of the Concept of Annihilation. He wasn’t a stranger to the Concept of Annihilation. Without a doubt, Skysplit Tower had areas where one could perceive the Concept of Annihilation. Xing Tian and Maha must have comprehended their Concept of Annihilation at this area.

Heretical God Force – open!

Blood Seal Twisting Murder!

A spear thrust out and Blood Drinking Seals twisted in circles as they flew, smashing against the Concept of Annihilation in a furious confrontation as it released screeching, bone-aching sounds.

Kacha!

The saber light and spear light simultaneously exploded. Lin Ming gently floated upwards from the force.

Easily breaking apart the Concept of Annihilation, Lin Ming didn’t even break a sweat. His expression was calm and his breath was even. Although everyone had expected that Maha’s saber strike wouldn’t be able to do much to Lin Ming, it was still startling to see him block it so smoothly.

The Concept of Annihilation was not an ordinary Concept, but one of the highest order.

“No need to test the waters. Come at me with everything you have!”

Lin Ming lightly landed, his spear pointed straight at Maha.

“Insolence!” Maha’s eyes flashed with a cold light. “Since that’s what you want, let me help you!”

Maha held his saber against his chest as his demon essence erupted to the limit. In this light, all of the muscles on his body bulged, his veins sticking up like blue worms. A black light enveloped Maha and then instantly expanded to 100 feet. Wherever this light covered, countless saber lights shimmered. Every saber light contained the Concept of Annihilation.

“This is the Saber Light Domain!”

“Maha’s signature move!”

The Saber Light Domain was a style that emerged from the Holy Demon Continent’s western regions. This was a move that used an extremely thick true essence to create countless saber energies. Normally, when a martial artist sent out saber energies, they would need to use them to attack. Regardless of what situation it was, the saber energies needed to be set free, where they would then transform into destructive power.

But the Saber Light Domain that Maha used just now was actually able to gather these saber energies and ensure that they didn’t disperse, instead endlessly enveloping their body. This was a technique that was both offensive and defensive. If a martial artist were to step into this Saber Light Domain, then they would be directly cut into pieces!

The most powerful point of the Saber Light Domain was that every time Maha used a saber strike, that strike would then fuse into the Saber Light Domain. This meant that the Saber Light Domain would continue to grow stronger!

Seeing Maha go all out with his maximum strength, all of the martial artists present rubbed their eyes.

This was the true battle!

A great number of Giant Demon martial artists began cheering for Maha. This Maha who could use the Saber Light Domain was simply a massive living meat grinder; just who would be able to defend against this?

Not just that, but in comparison to the Saber Light Domain’s amazing attack power, its defensive power was even more terrifying. Within the countless and endless Saber Light Domain, any attack that entered would be completely minced to pieces!

“Ho-!”

Maha slashed out with his saber. Near him, countless saber lights were affected by the force of this saber strike. As his saber cut out, saber energies crazily flew out!

This Saber Light Domain had fused in the Concept of Annihilation. The Saber Light Domain’s essence was that it could cut anything within it to pieces. Now with the Concept of Annihilation added on, its destructive power could be imagined!

Lin Ming’s expression was finally sincere. All of those that held the famous title of Heavenly Demon Seven Star had true ability. Even the weaker Kai Yang was no exception. If he hadn’t ran out of luck and bumped into someone with such an abnormal soul defense, then things would have been different.

But now, the Maha in front of him was even more powerful than Kai Yang!

Lin Ming opened the Heretical God Force to 90%. Lin Ming held the Purple Comet Spear, the sharp point flashing with sparkling thunder and thick arcs of electricity waving around it like dancing pythons.

Chasing Thunder!

Pouring all of his will and potential into the Purple Comet Spear, this was a killing strike created from the fusion of the Concept of Thunder and the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’!

Lin Ming became one with his spear, turning into a bolt of lightning that howled forth, impacting straight into the Saber Light Domain!

Frontal collision!

It wasn’t just the people watching the battle, but even Maha was greatly shocked. The Saber Light Domain could crush and cut everything! When the average person faced this ability, they would retreat and use long distance attacks, slowly consuming the strength of the Saber Light Domain bit by bit.

How could anyone think of directly rushing in!

Chi-la!

Radiant thunder light filled the entire arena. Even the impregnable Saber Light Domain was directly pierced through by this impossibly keen spear light!

Then, the countless saber lights within the domain twined together with the spear light, sending out a series of crackling sounds. Saber light was constantly being broken by the power of thunder! But, the power of thunder was also weakening at the same time!

In this split-second, before the audience even had time to respond, Lin Ming had turned into a bolt of lightning and arrived right in front of Maha!

“Humph! Anyone that rushes in has a death wish!”

Maha roared. Both hands gripped his saber as he slashed down at Lin Ming!

“Mountain Shattering Strike!”

Maha’s Mountain Shattering Strike truly had the ability to split apart a mountain peak. Now, this saber energy transformed into a several dozen foot wide saber light that cut towards Lin Ming!

Such a magnificent and overpowering saber strike caused everyone to be inexplicably frightened.

Kacha!

Countless saber lights broke apart. The bolt of purple lightning that Lin Ming had turned into passed straight through Maha’s Saber Light Domain, breaking straight through the other side!

At the same time, Maha’s saber heavily struck the arena.

Before the tiles came into contact with the blade, all of them were already shattered into fine dust by the saber energy before disappearing without a trace.

The saber light smashed into the metal ground, cutting out a massive 300 foot long fissure in the arena. The entire arena had actually been split in half by Maha’s single saber strike!

The audience felt their blood freezing in their veins. This saber strike was too terrifying!

In the arena, a 100 foot wide and 300 foot long region had been destroyed. The floor tiles there had completely disappeared under the impact of the Concept of Annihilation, and in places further away, they had even turned into sand. Even the hard metal ground that was supported by array formations was cut open, leaving behind shockingly deep cracks.

Everyone’s eyes almost turned onto Lin Ming’s body at the same time. After Lin Ming penetrated the Saber Light Domain, he only calmly turned around, not a single hair on his head harmed.

As for Maha, his complexion was pale and a trace of blood slowly dripped down his shoulder.

“Maha was injured!”

“Heavens! Even though I was so far from that terrifying saber light I still thought I had been cut apart. But… the one that was injured was actually Maha!”

“That just now should be Lin Ming’s ultimate attack. If this continues then he really might be able to win two continuous battles and then challenge Yan Chi! Lin Ming is truly worthy of being called the number one talent of the last 10,000 years!”

“It’s not wrong that Lin Ming is strong, but what I don’t understand is why although Lin Ming’s spear light is extraordinarily fast, it doesn’t seem all too terrifying. But on the other hand, Maha’s saber light contains the Concept of Annihilation. You just have to look at the sad state of the arena to see how scary it is. How could it be this result if this two collide?”

The audience wasn’t able to understand what had happened. The Concept of Annihilation was known as one of the highest level Concepts, and this reputation was not unearned. Maha had elevated his Concept of Annihilation to this degree, yet when he faced Lin Ming, it was like his Concept of Annihilation was useless.

As Maha looked at Lin Ming, his complexion was ugly. The audience couldn’t understand, but he did. In truth, his saber strike just now hadn’t even touched Lin Ming!

When his saber cut down, he suddenly had a very strange and weird feeling surrounding him. Then, Lin Ming, in a completely impossible situation, actually managed to escape the path of this saber energy. Lin Ming had only been scratched by some of the aftershocks, but these saber energy aftershocks had been far from being able to break through his protective true essence.

His Mountain Shattering Strike had struck nothing!

“Lin Ming, if you really have the ability then come and break my Saber Light Domain!” Maha tore apart a piece of his clothes that had been ripped by his own spear light, his eyes flashing dangerously at Lin Ming.

“Break your Saber Light Domain?” Lin Ming faintly smiled. Maha’s demon essence was condensed to an incomparably thick state, and the Saber Light Domain could grow endlessly as it contained a terrifying power. Wanting to break it wouldn’t be easy.

Lin Ming’s cultivation was far inferior to Maha’s. Also, Maha was defending while Lin Ming was attacking. The saber light in Maha’s domain didn’t scatter. After Lin Ming’s spear light pierced in, it would be constantly attacked. In this situation it would be an extreme advantage. In this case, if he wanted to crush this saber light with absolute strength then he would most likely need to use the power of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates.

Lin Ming didn’t want to do this. The Eight Inner Hidden Gates was his greatest trump card.

After that exchange of moves, Maha seemed to dread that strange movement of Lin Ming that had dodged his saber attack and proceeded to throw out more saber lights around him, surrounding him even more. This way, his defense would reach the pinnacle.

The Saber Light Domain had always been a marvelous defensive ability. Now that its defensive strength had reached the limit, it was like being protected in an unbreakable golden bell.

Maha had already made his decision. At worst, he would drag this into a battle of attrition. He had full confidence in the amount of demon essence he had as well as his ability to regenerate it.

Lin Ming had already seen through Maha’s plans. Battle of attrition? He wasn’t afraid of this, but he didn’t want to. Skysplit Tower’s third floor was full of enemies everywhere. Lin Ming was inclined to maintain his peak condition as long as possible.

He didn’t want to open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates nor did he want to start a battle of attrition. His feet began moving, and Lin Ming slowly walked towards Maha, approaching the Saber Light Domain step by step.

What was Lin Ming trying to do?

The audience had no idea.

There wasn’t too much protective true essence condensed on Lin Ming’s body. But he was walking towards the Saber Light Domain as if he were going to walk directly into it…

Chapter 602 – Another Killing

Use his flesh and blood body to step into the Saber Light Domain?

What a joke!

Such terrifying saber light was also coupled together with the Concept of Annihilation; everything would be crushed upon entry. Generally speaking, a martial artist’s bodily true essence protection was the same as scrap paper when faced with these saber lights. Even though Lin Ming’s true essence was thick, there was a limit to what it could do. It was impossible for him to depend on his bodily true essence alone to block this storm-like attack.

“What he is doing?”

“He’s taking another step forwards… he wants to enter the Saber Light Domain!”

In the special guest section, Feng Shen’s eyes were glued onto Lin Ming. He himself had fought with Maha once. When he faced Maha’s Saber Light Domain, he didn’t have any better method than to delay the battle and slowly whittle the domain away through a battle of attrition.

Now, Maha’s strength had obviously risen by another level and his Saber Light Domain became correspondingly more terrifying. To walk into the Saber Light Domain with just their body, even a High Lord would die like this!

Maha also wasn’t sure just what Lin Ming was trying to do. He glared at Lin Ming, his true essence revolving to the limit as he said, “If you’re trying some trick, then you’re looking to die!”

Ca!!

With a step forwards, Maha’s saber lights began to stir up strong gusts of wind that covered Lin Ming. “I don’t believe that you can block these hundreds and thousands of saber lights!”

In the second that the saber lights were about to pierce Lin Ming’s body, Lin Ming lightly caressed his Purple Comet Spear and took a sudden step forwards. The Purple Comet Spear thrust out!

Although this one spear seemed ordinary, an impossible scene suddenly occurred. Lin Ming carried his spear and seemed to pass through space itself, instantly arriving in front of Maha. He had completely ignored the saber lights as if they hadn’t even existed!

“What!?!?”

Maha was tremendously shocked!

When Lin Ming had been in the King’s Cage, the space storms that he had faced were many times more terrifying and deadly than this Saber Light Domain! By using the power of space within  the Saber Light Domain, he had instantly crossed the void

Chasing Sun!

Lin opened up 100% of the Heretical God Force, thrusting his spear forwards!

A brilliantly shining flame combusted in the void like a miniature sun had been birthed within the arena. Between Lin Ming’s eyebrows, the flame mark there began to issue a radiant light.

By burning the blood of the Ancient Phoenix, the power of Lin Ming’s Chasing Sun had risen to the limit!

“Ahhhhh!”

Maha didn’t have time to think about how Lin Ming had passed his spear lights and appeared in front of him. He howled and summoned all the strength within his body, his saber cutting down at Lin Ming.

However… as this saber came cutting down, he suddenly felt everything around him slow down. Those saber lights that were dancing in the air slowed, and even Lin Ming’s spear seemed slow.

But this spear, although it was slow, it was actually impossible for him to block or dodge. This was because the speed of his saber had become even slower!

“No!!”

Maha raved like a madman. Demon essence erupted like a volcano within his body, and blood vessels on his arm began to burst open. But, no matter how much of his bodily potential he released, he was unable to break through these shackles of time! He could only stare helplessly as Lin Ming’s Purple Comet Spear ran right through his throat.

Blood gushed out!

Woosh!

In the next moment, Lin Ming had already left the Saber Light Domain. Behind him, Maha was blankly standing there, his eyes glazed over and fresh blood spraying out from him.

After Killing Kai Yang, Lin Ming had now killed Maha!

Bang!

The thick seven foot long saber fell into the metal floor foundation, breaking it even further. Maha’s tall and burly body lost all support, and he plopped onto the floor.

The entire audience was in utter shock.

It could be said that Lin Ming had been able to kill Kai Yang because his specialty was suppressed by Lin Ming. But when he killed Maha, it had been a true battle under fair circumstances!

Maha was originally ranked third within the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars. Not just that, but after entering the Road of Emperor, his strength had increased astronomically. How could he possibly have died in such a miserable manner?

Lin Ming had only entered the King’s Cage, and yet the gains he had made within the King’s Cage had far surpassed Maha’s gains from the Road of Emperor. Just what sort of abnormally monstrous talent was this!

Also, many martial artists present didn’t understand. Just how had Maha died?

What had happened just now?

Maha’s Saber Light Domain was a technique that was both offensive and defensive. Its defensive capabilities were especially strong. With the ability to grow endlessly, it could simply be called a perfect defense. But Lin Ming had walked into that Saber Light Domain with just his flesh and blood body, and had somehow instantly passed through space, completely treating the Saber Light Domain as if it were nothing but air.

Then, that spear thrust seemed very ordinary and its speed seemed slow, but for some reason, Maha didn’t even have enough time to withdraw his saber and was then killed by Lin Ming!

If this were a normal fight, then people might have even thought that Maha had faked it and lost on purpose. But this was a life and death battle, there was naturally no way he had allowed that to happen.

“Those were the Concepts of Space and Time just now…” In the audience, a martial artist had recognized Lin Ming’s technique.

“That is too terrifying. After reaching the pinnacle in comprehending the Concepts of Space and Time, can Lin Ming actually teleport?”

“It isn’t teleportation. It was only stepping forwards using the Law of Space. We don’t understand this Law, thus it looks like teleportation to us.”

A Fey martial artist explained. As a Fey, he had a somewhat limited understanding into the Concepts of Space in Time. In the ancient legends, it was said that those existences that had reached the utter limits of the Concept of Space, once they touched upon the origin of Space Laws, could actually teleport across vast distances. But, that sort of boundary only existed in the ancient texts. These days, it was unachievable. Not even the Eightfall War Emperor had the ability to do so.

“Aiya! The difference in talent is too great! Each of them had entered into practice areas, but Maha had entered the Road of Emperor and Lin Ming had only entered the King’s Cage. If Lin Ming enters the Road of Emperor in the future, just how strong would he be then?”

Thinking of this, the martial artists present couldn’t help but shudder. Killing Kai Yang and then executing Maha, Lin Ming had simply swept away his opposition with absolute force without allowing any of them to resist. Kai Yang’s Emperor Will and Maha’s Saber Light Domain were completely useless against Lin Ming.

At this moment, a martial artist with a deep voice said, “Don’t be an idiot, it’s impossible for Lin Ming to have the chance of entering the Road of Emperor. How could the 12 High Lords ever allow that to happen? Isn’t that just taking a rock and smashing it against their own feet? The only way would be for Lin Ming to wholeheartedly pledge his loyalty to Skysplit Tower.

None of the martial artists present were fools. They could all see that High Lord Heian had wanted to place Lin Ming in a deathtrap.

“This damn boy, letting him live will only mean disaster for the Blood Slaughter Steppes; it might even mean catastrophe for the Giant Demon and Imp races within the Holy Demon Continent!” In the seat of honor, High Lord Heian traced his ring, his eyes flashing with killing intent.

Lin Ming and the Eightfall War Emperor were too alike. In the King’s Cage, everyone’s experience was different. Whether it was difficult or the type of cage, it was completely different for each person.

But, Lin Ming and the Eightfall War Emperor had both comprehended the Concepts of Space and Time within the King’s Cage. This sort of chance coincidence caused High Lord Heian to feel fear in his heart.

The Eightfall War Emperor’s accomplishments in the Concepts of Space and Time were exceedingly high and he had also reached the eighth stage of Life Destruction. Because of these factors, no Emperor powerhouse within his same level could even think of offending him.

Now, Lin Ming was also the same. Moreover, what was most horrifying was that the time he stayed within the King’s Cage was almost twice that of the Eightfall War Emperor!

If this was allowed to continue, then dozens of years later, as long as Lin Ming didn’t die, he would become an Emperor level powerhouse.

And several hundred years from now, Lin Ming would become nearly unrivalled throughout all the lands.

And several thousand years from now, Lin Ming would have a high chance of becoming the number one powerhouse of the entire Holy Demon Continent!

When that time came, the interests of the Giant Demon and Imp races would inevitably be severely damaged.

On the arena stage, Lin Ming was calm as he took Maha’s spatial ring. At the same time, Maha’s infernal energy also rushed into Lin Ming’s body.

As someone that been ranked in the top three of the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars, the richness of Maha’s infernal energy could be imagined. As half of that infernal energy rushed into Lin Ming’s body, Lin Ming’s Heavenly Demon Tattoo instantly promoted to the peak of eight wings!

From a ten-winged Heavenly Demon Tattoo, the difference wasn’t all that far.

To reach 10 wings was possible, but to go from 10 wings to 12 wings was an extremely long and arduous process. When arriving at that level, the greatest problem would be finding a match. In order to further form the tattoo, one would have to fight with High Lords. But what High Lord would dare to fight?

Not just that, but a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon was a great taboo within the Blood Slaughter Steppes. This was because once this character became an Emperor level powerhouse they wouldn’t be affected by that mystical curse within the Blood Slaughter Steppes that killed all entering powerhouses. A twelve-winged Heavenly Demon could return to the Blood Slaughter Steppes as they wished. This was simply a massive factor of instability!

After killing Kai Yang and Maha, Lin Ming had in fact obtained a Hundred Winning Streak Emblem and earned nearly a 100 slaughter points. But after reaching this level, emblems, slaughter points – none of these mattered much anymore.

Next… this third match was also the last match.

Lin Ming against Yan Chi!

Everyone’s eyes turned onto Yan Chi. Yan Chi appeared surprisingly calm, without even the slightest trace of fair.

When Yan Chi had entered the King’s Cage, he obtained the title of earth-step Asura.

Of course, when compared with Lin Ming he was completely overshadowed. But when placed within any fifth-grade sect within the Holy Demon Continent, this was actually a first class result!

Without a doubt, Yan Chi was also an Emperor level talent. As long as he could maintain this pace of progress, then it was very likely he would become an Emperor level powerhouse in the future.

His footsteps light, Yan Chi slowly floated onto the arena stage like a fading autumn leaf. Without a sound he extracted his weapon from his spatial ring. This was a black high-grade earth-step treasure sword.

With sword in hand, Yan Chi’s aura suddenly changed. It had immediately become sharp, violent, and swift!

It was true that Imp martial artists were skilled in soul attacks, but if anyone were to presume that they were only skilled in soul attacks, they would be making a fatal mistake.

Yan Chi was an excellent example of this.

He was proficient in soul attacks and also in physical attacks.

“Truly worthy of Yan Chi. Facing Lin Ming, he doesn’t have the least bit of panic!”

“This is the bearing of a true master!”

“Don’t underestimate Yan Chi. Lin Ming is strong, but Yan Chi’s strength is also unfathomable. No one knows just how much Yan Chi’s strength has risen within the Road of Emperor. Moreover, Lin Ming has already fought in two matches. Although it looked like he easily won them, in truth his consumption of energy probably isn’t minor.”

Martial artists had limited reserves of true essence. When martial artists fought, they would normally start with probing moves before using their true ultimate techniques. It wasn’t strange for a powerful martial skill to use 10% of one’s true essence. As for a final killing move, it was normal for those to use up 20 to 30% of one’s true essence.

Thus, even if one easily ended their fights, they would still usually consume 10 to 20% of their true essence. If they fought in two straight matches then they would only have 70 to 80% of their original true essence from when they had been in their peak form. When fighting continuous matches, unless there was an overwhelming difference in strength, it would be difficult to continue.